Hey, how are you doing today?
How many eggs did you lay?
Whoa.
Hey...
They really lay eggs every day?
If it feels comfortable, then yeah, every day.
So that means
maybe we shouldn’t get too close to it.
If it gets stressed, it might stop laying eggs.
I doubt it’d get stressed around someone like you.
Why’s that?
Because it probably thinks you’re one of them.
Always staying inside your own cage.
So this is what you meant when you said
you’re gentle with all your guests?
I am gentle.
It’s just that some people
love challenging my feelings.
Did this chicken hate me in a past life or something?
Well, you
walked in without permission.
Hey...
They are chickens, not people.
And what about you?
Have you ever asked permission before writing about people’s feelings like that?
Or is that the only way
to escape from your own feelings?
Maybe you should start by not trying to explain everything
like the way you are doing.
And...
what if I can’t stop?
Because...
if I don't have a reason.
I’ll just get even more scared.
Then maybe you should let yourself be scared for once.
So you’ll know what real feelings are like.
Even with a view this beautiful right in front of you
you’re still staring at your keyboard?
Well...
it isn't going anywhere...
but the ideas in my head is.
Then...
when you write,
what voice do you hear in your head?
Probably...
my own thoughts, I guess.
The voice that...
keeps trying to make sense of everything.
And...
does that voice ever go quiet?
Hardly ever.
Except...
when someone’s voice
is the one I want to hear instead.
Staring at me like that...
is there something you want me to prove?
No.
When you’re focused on something
you feel different from
when we’re arguing.
Then...
maybe I should stop talking for a while.
Then I’ll hear my heart more clearly.
Silence between two people doesn’t always mean there’s nothing to say.
Sometimes...
it’s the moment when your heart finally hears itself again.
I had no idea
what she was thinking.
But in that silence...
I could hear my own heart more clearly than ever.
This kind of atmosphere...
is perfect for writing.
Looks like...
it's raining.
Hey, wait!
Ow!
You can’t just run past people like that. What if you hit someone?
It’s because my papers are...
Hey!
What are you doing?
You really didn’t have to go that far.
It’s just paper.
But sometimes the things that you look past
might be the reason someone still wants to stay.
Thank you.
I just didn’t want the next book to end
before it even began.
Sometimes your heart doesn’t race because of sweet words.
It races because
of the sincerity.
And honestly...
I don’t even know when
my heart started reacting to little things like this.
She’s usually sitting here typing every morning.
She always do the same things...
When she disappeared like this,
it made me worry.
Without her...
I should be able to write more, right?
So why does everything feel so quiet?
That’s weird.
It’s only been one morning.
This isn’t my equation at all.
Hey...
reading someone else’s journal is against the rules, you know.
I wasn’t trying to read it.
I was just afraid it’d blow away again.
That’s good.
Because in there
there are more secrets than you think.
A writer’s secrets?
Are you hiding your feelings there?
You always know exactly what to say.
I tried keeping my distance to prove it was nothing.
But
it became too quiet.
Quiet enough to hear my heartbeat louder than the keyboard.
I don’t know where she went
but the thing that disappeared
made everything around me louder.
Including the feelings I kept trying
not to admit.