If you add too much water,
the dough loses its elasticity.
Ugh.
How am I supposed to know when it’s just right?
Why isn’t there a formula for this like in math?
Ugh.
Nice.
Another failed method.
You always manage to surprise me.
What?
What did I do this time?
The fact that you’re sitting here.
Yesterday, you said
you didn’t like doing anything emotional.
I’m just joining one of the resort activities included in the package.
That’s all.
Wow.
But with that expression, it looks like someone forced you to come.
If anyone walks by,
they’ll misunderstand
and think I forced guests to make Bualoy.
Hey.
Haven’t you heard?
Writers need to keep learning new things all the time.
Everything can become useful for writing.
Wow.
Hey.
So your next book will be called
“Ten Theories on How to Shape Dough Without It Sticking to Your Hands”?
You’ve probably seen people make this a lot, right?
Yeah.
Hundreds, maybe thousands of times.
Good then.
Come help me.
Then we can find out
where this theory went wrong.
Why should I help?
Well,
if you don’t help me,
I’ll sit here complaining
until other guests misunderstand
and think you forced me to do this.
So, what do I do?
Do you actually know how to do this?
I do.
And then?
Check if the texture feels right.
If it does, stop. If not, add more.
Is this enough?
Not yet.
Then add more flour.
Hey, are you messing with me?
No.
Your hands just need more flour on them.
See?
You said you’d seen this hundreds of times.
Then why do you look so pitiful doing it?
When did I ever say I was good at it?
Huh?
You said you’d seen it hundreds of times.
I said I’d seen it hundreds of times.
That doesn’t mean I can do it.
Then let me ask scientifically.
What’s wrong with this equation?
The problem is that it’s not an equation. It’s art.
And it seems like you’re not very good at this kind of thing.
Some things require feelings, not just logic.
Why is it that every time I’m close to you,
my brain isn't braining?
Then stop using your brain.
Try using your heart instead.
Please, go ahead.
Wait... what is all this?
Seriously, why does everything seem so formal today?
The chef wanted to thank both of you
for helping cook the other day.
Please, have a seat first.
Today’s special menu is called
“Omakase: Ten Flavors of Emotions.”
Honestly, it sounds more elegant than my book's title.
The chef wanted to create a new menu
especially for first-time guests staying here.
Don’t tell me this is the chef’s first experiment.
Or are we secretly being used as test subjects?
Why are you two getting along so well today?
Chef, please serve the dishes.
Please enjoy your meal. Excuse me for now.
I keep trying to understand this feeling, but every time our eyes meet,
she becomes the exception to every theory I’ve ever known.
Because some feelings aren’t from reasons.
They come from someone you never expected to feel this way about.
So, how was the meal?
It was delicious. Some things may seem bland on the outside,
but once you taste them, there’s a hidden sweetness inside.
Yes, it was amazing.
Eating it feels like something that appears clear on the outside,
but inside is so confusing that no equation could ever explain it.
And they say Shakespeare is dead.
You even compare food to emotions.
Well, that’s because everything
is finally starting to have flavor.
If the two of us had a flavor,
what flavor do you think we’d be?
Hmm...
A little bitter.
But after swallowing it,
a sweetness lingers inside.
Hey...
How did you get in here?
Your door wasn’t locked.
And it seemed like the owner of this room
wanted someone to come in.
I’m writing a book.
Or maybe just trying to write one.
Trying to write...
or trying to run away from your feelings?
I want to prove something.
Prove what?
That feelings
don’t need a reason to exist.
And... what if it’s wrong?
Then we’ll be wrong together.
Hey...
Are you sure this feeling is real?
If it needs logic,
then it’s not really a feeling anymore.
Then...
there’s nothing left to prove.
We just need to feel it.
Am I...
dreaming?
So it was a dream...
Did you sleep well?
I did.
It felt strange too.
Strange how?
Like dreaming about something I shouldn’t remember...
but still can’t forget.
I feel the same way.
I thought she lived inside my head,
but actually, she lives in my heart.
Maybe dreams aren’t just things we think about while asleep.
Maybe they’re what our hearts wish could become real,
but we’re still too afraid to say out loud.