What’s going on?
Why is it so noisy?
Yesterday,
a customer posted a review saying our Pad Thai with fermented rice noodles
was the most delicious ever.
So today we’ve been flooded with orders.
There are so many coming in.
Hello, yes?
Another seven orders?
Of course.
Chef Tai,
the customers just ordered seven more portions.
Seven more? We haven’t even finished the last batch yet.
Should we stop accepting orders?
No, no.
This is a golden opportunity for the homestay.
Exactly.
And all the ingredients come from the villagers too.
The more we can sell,
the more we can help the community.
That’s true.
Then I’ll help out too.
Really, Lean?
Of course. I will help a lot.
Come on.
What do you want me to do?
Okay.
Chef!
The sauce is about to burn!
We’re running out of vegetables too.
Lean, could you grab more vegetables from inside?
Then who’s going to watch the sauce?
I can’t.
I have to prepare the ingredients.
The delivery guy has been waiting for a while already.
I have to go first.
Hey!
You there.
Yes, you.
How much longer are you going to sit there?
Hey...
How much longer are you staying there?
Me?
Well...
probably a while.
I haven’t gotten very far with my writing yet.
That’s not what I meant. I mean...
everyone else is busy like this,
and you still don’t plan on getting up to help?
I’m sorry.
I’m a writer, not a chef.
We don’t need a writer.
We need every kind of labor we can get.
At this point, if you’re a living being,
we need you.
If it’s manual labor,
I’m probably not much help.
Hmm.
So you can’t do anything at all?
Don’t underestimate me.
When I was little, I helped my mom cook all the time.
Oh?
What can you do?
Well...
I can wash vegetables and peel garlics.
Mm-hmm.
Then...
why don’t you show me your skills?
Are these two going to flirt forever?
Oops, I mean—
are you going to keep fighting, or help me first?
If you’re really that capable, then show me what you can do.
Hey.
Why aren’t you arranging the plates from left to right?
If you do it like this, everyone will get confused while serving.
Geez.
Things are already chaotic and you’re still giving orders.
Haven’t you heard?
Organization is the basic of every job.
Even in chaos!!
if they’re not arranged properly, how will we know which plate has shrimp and which has pork?
Wow.
Fine, whatever you say.
But first, try cutting the vegetables beautifully and symmetrically.
Hmph.
Like you’re so good at it yourself.
Even squirrels would break their teeth trying to eat these.
Oh?
Have you ever even been in a kitchen before?
Chef, are they really helping us?
I’m not so sure myself.
Hmm.
Can you really handle this?
Yay!
We finally finished everything in time.
Thank you, everyone.
Especially these two, who seemed to bicker nonstop,
but actually helped a lot.
Bickering, Fah?
I call it...
driving force.
Powered by sound waves.
Wow.
More like the kind of sound waves that make people want to cover their ears.
At least it turned out better than expected, didn’t it?
See?
When you stop overthinking,
it works better than relying on theories.
But some things need thought, don’t they?
That way you know if it’s really right.
But something...
you know the answer just by doing them.
Then...
I’ll try not to think so much.
And just follow my heart instead.
Oh?
Don’t say things like that.
You’ll make people misunderstand.
Like you’re confessing your feelings to me.
If you keep joking like that,
be careful...
it might come true.
You really want to win against me that badly, huh?
Wait.
I thinks there’s no winning or losing here.
There’s only the one who falls first.
What kind of person puts noodles on their head?
I used to think love had to be calm
to feel safe.
But actually, arguing
or even misunderstanding each other...
they make us realize
that we still want to be part of the same story.
Because when everything becomes completely silent,
that may not be peace.
It may just mean we’re no longer in each other’s hearts.
Hey.
You’re still awake?
Yeah.
I can’t write anything.
Your book?
Mm.
I feel like...
the more I try to write from real emotions,
the quieter my mind becomes.
The voice in my head
can’t explain anything anymore.
I think...
maybe you should rest for a while.
Sometimes the heart
just needs a little rest too.
Have you ever thought
that maybe we don’t have to understand every feeling?
Just knowing they’re real is enough.
That’s exactly
what I’m afraid of.
Afraid that
if I feel too much,
I won’t be able to keep writing.
Afraid you won’t be able to keep writing
or afraid...
that your feelings are actually real?
Maybe...
it’s both.
You don’t have to be strong all the time, Tymn.
You talk like you’ve never been afraid of anything.
I’m afraid of a lot of things.
But you seem like
someone who’s never afraid of anything.
Everyone has something they’re afraid of.
Actually...
I’m afraid of staying in this house alone.
Because this house...
holds memories I don’t want to remember.
Every sound in this house...
whether it’s
the faucet,
the rain,
or the doors opening and closing...
those sounds...
they keep reminding me that silence never truly comforts anyone.
Then...
right now,
are you still afraid?
Mmm....
Actually, not as much anymore.
Because now,
there’s something
that feels warmer...
right here.
You may not know it,
but
I'm really feeling warmer.
Sometimes, the thing that scares us most
isn’t being misunderstood.
It’s being understood too well...
so well that we’re afraid
there’s nowhere left to hide our feelings.
And on the day we let someone
see our vulnerable part,
that’s when we realize true relationships
don’t need explanations.
They just need someone to stay
when we’re not strong enough to smile.