- Kayano-san.
- Hmm?
These two guys we're about to
meet... which one's the bottom?
Yamada, if you dare ask
them that question to their faces,
I'll have you replaced.
Hey...
(Day 0)
One hundred days?
That's the idea.
But we won't be following you
and filming for all 100 days.
We'll film your daily life
for the first few days.
After that, the only mandatory
shoot is the final day.
For the rest of the time,
we'll be in touch with you regularly.
We're hoping to capture
your most authentic moments...
Hmph... Authentic moments, huh?
We hope we can.
Oh, right.
My only redeeming quality is that I
never drop crumbs when I eat toast.
Huh?
This project...
Isn't this a bit like false advertising?
Well, it's true we won't
be filming every day.
But we'll be in constant contact with you
during this period.
If anything comes up,
we'll be there to film.
So, to call it a 100-day documentary...
isn't technically a lie.
I see.
So as long as you don't call it "100 days
of non-stop filming," you're in the clear?
You could say that.
I can also finish an iced coffee with a
straw without making a single slurping sound.
Huh?
So...
When does filming start?
We have a deadline, so at the latest...
We can start tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yeah.
The sooner we start, the sooner we finish.
Right?
Um... Okay.
Great, it's settled then.
We became well-known after being interviewed
about the partnership oath system.
But honestly,
the very fact that we have to be
interviewed for something like this...
is strange in itself.
Yes.
I want this country
to become a place where same-sex couples
can exist as a matter of course.
Not for today,
but for the future.
That's the kind of
documentary I want to make.
Let's create something that
can change the world together.
Okay.
- Thank you for the meal.
Do you two have any
plans for the rest of the day?
We were thinking of catching
a movie before heading home.
A date. How nice.
Well, we'll get out of your hair then.
Thank you so much for today.
We look forward to working with you.
Hey, what was that all about?
Huh?
Man... I'm exhausted.
Could you at least try
to have a better attitude?
I almost burst out laughing.
All that talk about capturing
our "authentic moments."
We broke up ages ago.
"Broke up" is a strong word.
We still live together, after all.
Hey, this...
Oh, aren't you going to the movies?
I'm heading home.
Huh?
What?
So filming starts tomorrow now?
Yeah, that's right.
Are you sure about that?
It's fine. Actually, I'm
pretty fired up about it.
As long as you think it's fine.
But you know,
shouldn't you make a little more time
for your personal life?
Take a page from Naomi's book.
She...
balances everything so well,
both work and her life with her husband.
Right?
- I guess so...
- See?
Your belly's gotten so big.
Well, I could go into labor any day now.
- I'm sorry to bother you at a time like this.
- Not at all.
Kasuga-san is nice, isn't he?
Yes.
What about Hasegawa-san?
What's your impression?
Oh, well...
I do sense a bit of distance between them.
But I'm hoping they'll
warm up to us over time.
I feel that the issues
Kasuga-san and his partner face
are not entirely unrelated to us as women.
I agree.
That's why I want to make a documentary
that not only dispels prejudice
against homosexuality,
but all prejudice related
to gender and sexuality.
That was my thinking
when I proposed this project.
I can certainly feel your passion.
Don't worry, you can count on
me to take over for Naomi-san.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Croquettes?
Yeah.
It's rare to see you frying things.
Do you want some?
I can fry them up if you do.
Hey, about dinner...
Let's try to eat together.
Why?
For the shoot.
We need to get that happy couple
vibe back as soon as possible.
Can't we just act the part?
It's not that simple.
The atmosphere today was
pretty awkward, wasn't it?
Okay, okay, I get it.
Should I just chop this?
Oh, no, no.
I'll do it.
It's fine.
It's fine, I've got it.
It's fi...
Ow!
See?
Is this the only kind we have?
Stop complaining.
No, I'm not complaining...
That was a total disaster.
Ow.
Hmm?
That pop-up shop... the line was insane.
And in the end, this was all we could get.
But you seemed so happy then.
That's because you looked happy.
Your mood was contagious.
Hey.
The Honey Gourami died.
One of the five we got last week.
What?
Are they all dead?
No.
It looks like... just one died.
Eh, maybe it couldn't handle the heat.
What?
I'm just saying, maybe
the tank was too hot.
Maybe there really are tropical
fish that can't take the heat.
Don't joke about that.
We're talking about a life here.
Where are you going?
For a walk.
"The Boy and I Who Will Breka Up in 100 Days"
(Episode 2)
Are you two the type to have a big appetite
and eat a hearty breakfast in the morning?
(Day 1)
No, not really.
Oh, I see.
- Time to eat.
- Let's eat.
What is it?
Your mouth. You've got some sauce.
No, not there.
Mm.
That's a cute bandage.
Huh?
Oh, no.
It was just the only one we had.
We've been together for
about a year and a half.
We started living together
around the same time.
Oh, I'll get it.
I'll just put this here then.
Okay.
Back then, I got kicked
out of my old place.
I was broke.
And I was forced to quit my job.
Once you come out as gay,
you really run into all
sorts of situations at work.
I wasn't clear enough just now.
Firing someone just for being gay
is illegal, at least.
The reason I quit
was simply because it
was the easier way out.
But it's been great living together.
He has delicious meals
waiting for me when I get home.
He completely won over my stomach.
Oh.
Um... Is this a BL novel?
- Yes, it is.
- I actually bought this book myself.
So gay people actually read this stuff?
We do.
In this day and age,
it's harder to avoid it.
Besides, when I was a teenager,
knowing that stories like this existed
was a kind of salvation for me.
- Oh, I see.
- Yeah.
Do you read them too, Hasegawa-san?
Oh, I'm not much of a reader.
I see...
Huh?
Aren't we doing an interview?
Oh.
Sorry about that.
And in order for same-sex
marriage to be legally recognized,
it's necessary for society to
see that same-sex couples exist.
That's also why
we utilized this system.
We want to prove that
if this system exists,
people who need it will use it.
Um...
What he just said isn't entirely true.
Can I make a correction?
What?
Not entirely true?
Yes.
This guy said
that you can't obtain those rights
without same-sex marriage.
But that's not exactly the case.
Things like notarization, adoption,
or voluntary guardianship contracts...
There are actually a
lot of things you can do.
It's true that the process
is a hassle and expensive,
and some protections
aren't comprehensive enough.
So same-sex marriage is definitely
the most straightforward way.
But to say it's the only way...
that's a lie.
Besides, marriage isn't
just about legal rights.
Not that I'm saying they're not needed.
- I see.
- Yes.
Oh, can you please not cut this part out?
I'll do my best.
Something about those two...
they don't really seem like a couple.
You should stop judging people based on
stereotypes of what a couple "should" look like.
Okay, fine.
By the way, Kayano-san, you're into BL?
Is there a problem with that?
Nope.
It's just that you don't seem
interested in romance stories.
I'm just not interested in romance
stories between men and women.
What's the difference?
Gay and straight romance are
completely different, obviously.
Oh.
It's freezing!
Itsuki.
Let's have a debrief.
A debrief?
Point out what we did wrong today.
And use it to improve the next shoot.
Was there something wrong
with our performance today?
I'm saying we could have done better.
Ah...
I get it... You want
us to be more like that.
More couple-like?
Wiping sauce off each other's mouths.
That's what makes us a couple, right?
Emphasizing that we share
chores like washing dishes.
That's what makes us a couple, right?
Got it. Next time, let's just hold
hands through the whole interview.
Maybe that'll be more effective, huh?
No, why did you lie
about not reading books?
That book was clearly yours.
What if our stories don't line up later?
We're literally filming
based on a fake premise.
And now you're telling me not to lie?
Don't you see how ridiculous that is?
And what about you? What was
that during the interview today?
I had to say it that way.
If I said, "There are other ways
besides same-sex marriage,"
or "You can't easily be
fired just for being gay,"
wouldn't the audience just think,
"the current situation is fine as it is"?
It's just a strategy.
That's called lying, isn't it?
And you have the
nerve to tell me not to lie.
From the very beginning, you've
been asking me to lie with you.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
(Day 2)
Good morning.
About him being gay...
He mentioned it during his self-introduction
when he joined the company.
When you first heard that,
were you taken aback at all?
No, not at all.
Our company aims to be
an LGBT-friendly enterprise.
We've implemented a
variety of supportive measures.
For example, same-sex partners
can live together in company housing.
- I see.
- Yes.
So if Kasuga-san wanted to apply,
he could move into the
dorms with Hasegawa-san?
Yes. Since they've
registered their partnership,
they are eligible.
By the way, I'd like to ask, how
well do you know Hasegawa-san?
Oh...
We've met.
Once, I was looking for a place
for a reunion with some college friends,
and Kasuga recommended the bar
where his partner works.
- That's when we met.
- Oh, I see.
What was your impression of him then?
Um...
We didn't really talk much then,
so I can't really say.
But I think he's a very handsome guy.
Okay, thank you.
Yes!
He's such a nice guy.
Treating poor young people like us
to pasta.
- Kayano-san.
- Yes?
After today's shoot,
what's your impression of our company?
Um... I think your company
is very progressive.
It's a wonderful company.
Not just in terms of its LGBT initiatives,
but there's also a high
ratio of female employees.
It seems like a great work environment.
Unlike our company, which is all guys.
Oh?
Besides me, there's only one other
female employee at my company.
And the president sometimes
says some pretty outdated things.
Like sexual harassment?
I don't think he means any harm by it,
so I've never really paid it much mind.
You don't have to forgive him.
Huh?
I don't know what exactly you've heard,
Kayano-san,
but if you feel in your
heart that you can't forgive it,
then there's no need to.
I believe that's an undeniable fact.
Okay.
If you feel you can't forgive
it, then you don't have to.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I just thought
that was really well said.
Because all this time, I've forgiven a lot
of things that were actually unforgivable.
But from now on,
I want to take what
you said to heart.
And try not to be so quick to forgive.
Whatever.
Oh, right.
Kasuga, does your partner ever mention me?
- You mean Itsuki?
- Yeah.
Because Kayano-san
asked me today if I knew him.
So I was wondering if he'd
said something on his end.
No, I don't think so.
He's not really interested
in other people...
It's more like he just drifts through life.
Oh...
It's Batch-kun.
They put you on a pedestal for a while,
and when they lose interest,
they just toss you aside.
Everyone's so selfish, right?
Yeah.
Everyone's selfish.
Right?
What are you doing?
What?
Huh?
Were you just talking to that figurine?
No, I wasn't.
No, no, no, you were
definitely talking to it.
I was wrong yesterday.
Hm?
I apologize.
Oh.
Telling you not to lie
was strange, I admit.
After all, I'm the one
who asked you to lie.
But...
with that said,
I want to ask you again.
For the sake of this documentary,
I need you to lie more convincingly.
- This documentary is for people like us...
- That's why I agreed to do it.
Huh?
For people like us,
so that when it counts, we
don't have to just suffer in silence.
We have to clearly lay out the rights
we can fight for now, don't we?
But still...
But still what?
I'll play along a little longer.
This little game of house you're playing.
Are you serious?
Serious about what?
Is this how you pour it?
You've been a terrible
pourer your whole life.
Shut up.
Actually... I've been
keeping a secret from you.
What is it?
I can't really hold my liquor.
What?
Huh?
Why?
Didn't you used to go
on and on about whiskey?
Nah.
I was just trying to
act cool in front of you.
Because you like to drink.
That's so lame.
But you fell for me
because of it, didn't you?
I was totally fooled.
Back then, it was so
obvious you were into me.
Don't be ridiculous.
You were the one who liked me first.
Hey.
Tomorrow...
let's eat together.
Yeah.
We should practice to
make our story convincing.
That's not it.
I just... I genuinely want to eat with you.
Tomorrow, and the day after.
And every day from now on.
Can we...
start over?
(Next Episode)
I don't want to let those kids down.
(Our Unseen Lies and Truths)
Have you always...
planned on living your
life for other people?
Why don't you just get a job?
You're taking this way too lightly.
I'm not talking about a right.
I'm talking about commitment.
Then just commit to it.