[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 7]
Zha, vanquish demons!
What a realistic illusion.
No.
That wasn't your voice just now.
Did you
save us just now?
You two lack skills.
Why did you rush in here
so recklessly?
Who are you saying lacks skill?
I just picked the wrong spiritual paper.
You two are no match for the demons here.
Hurry up and follow me.
Rickshaw.
Excuse me.
Come look.
Our nation is in crisis,
we must take action.
That's right.
Today,
we must join the protest.
That's right.
We need to gather our friends.
Brothers, together!
Did we travel through time?
It's an illusion.
Is this an illusion?
Come take a look.
Of course it is.
Therefore,
don't talk to them
or make eye contact.
If they bewitch you,
you'll be in trouble.
Such a lifelike illusion.
This demon is really powerful,
creating such a huge illusion
out of thin air.
Can we eat this?
Of course you can.
It's just an illusion,
not poison.
In this illusion,
you can also get full.
But once you leave,
you'll feel hungry again.
May I ask who you are?
My surname is Bai.
Call me Bai Xiaonian.
Don't ask anything more than that.
We are not
on the same path, anyway.
I'm here waiting for someone.
Waiting for a friend?
Do you guys know about
the big demon in this town?
I have a friend who was
young and arrogant.
He came to eliminate the demon,
but was caught by it.
I have been looking for him
in this town for 3 years.
Three years?
Wouldn't he have been
digested by the demon
and excreted as fertilizer long ago?
It has nothing to do with you.
Speaking of which,
what kind of demon is it exactly?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
Since you are also looking for the demon,
the two of us can help.
How can you two help?
You're here to catch the demon
for money, right?
I've seen many people like you.
You're just causing trouble.
You won't be making any money.
If you want to live,
stay close to me.
I'll get you out of here right now.
Okay.
I'll leave the money here.
Look.
Isn't that Ms. Huang?
What Ms. Huang?
The person who hired us.
That's not her.
All of this is an illusion.
Let's go take a look.
Where did he go?
Dongqing.
Dongqing!
Stop shouting.
Come here.
Where did you run off to?
She disappeared.
Let's go check out that well.
This well is very strange.
There is a special energy on the rope.
Look.
But the rope snapped,
so the energy has weakened.
This rope doesn't look like it snapped.
Rather, it was untied by that woman
who looks exactly like
Huang Shang.
There is a demon
imprisoned in this well.
That woman who looks
exactly like Huang Shang
is Huang Shang's ancestor.
She was the town witch of her generation.
Generally speaking,
witches protect the town.
You mean...
I mean,
why did she untie the rope
and release the demon?
Stay away from that well!
Bai Xiaonian?
Why did you run off on your own?
There is a demon in this well.
I will take you two
out of here immediately.
There's no time. Hurry!
-Zhao Hengzhi, run!
-Stop!
Bai Xiaonian.
I think that demon
is you.
How could he be a demon?
He saved us just now.
What are you talking about?
He did that to gain our trust
and trick us into leaving the town.
Bai Xiaonian.
You say this is a demon's lair.
I guess
it's yours.
Zhao-
What are you doing?
I'll say it one more time.
Let go of him!
Don't push your luck.
I gave you a way out,
but you insist on seeking death.
You've forced me to play the BGM.
The Eighth Spiritual Paper
is the Demon Subduing Formation
of the Zhao family.
When the formation is activated,
the spiritual paper will produce
the Samadhi Fire.
Since you're a demon, it'll vanquish you.
Samadhi Fire.
Demon Subduing!
Zhao Hengzhi!
Dongqing!
He's missing?
Ms. Huang.
Let's call the police.
How can we tell the police about this?
And if the word gets out,
who would dare to come to town
and buy houses in the future?
You...
You're so fierce.
Are you
obsessed with money?
Here.
What for?
Isn't this my money?
Yes.
Now it's yours again.
Hurry up and come with me
to save my buddy.
This is your reward.
I won't let you work for nothing.
I really don't know any magic.
Are you scared?
Nonsense.
Why would I be scared?
This entire town
belongs to my family.
That demon has a deep connection
with your family.
Maybe this demon
was released by
your ancestors.
The one who started the trouble
must end it.
Hurry up and find the magic book.
Right now.
Come to town with me tonight.
Sorry,
the number you dialed
is out of service,
and cannot be reached temporarily.
You're getting bolder.
Not coming home at night
without telling me.
Look!
So handsome. Look!
So handsome.
What are you looking at?
Director, look.
That's Wang Fang's boyfriend.
He's so handsome.
Right? Right?
So handsome and tall.
They are kissing.
Yuanji?
Director,
do you play that game too?
What game?
The game Wang Fang plays.
Once she reaches
a million intimacy points,
the character she chose in the game
will come into her life
and date her.
He really came.
Hello?
Ya, you're up early.
I have something to ask you.
Yuanji
is a character from the game.
He relies on the adoration
of those women to gain power.
When this power
is strong enough,
he can appear in real life,
just like me.
You still remember
that I used to be a painting, right?
Doesn't that make him a demon?
Is he absorbing
Wang Fang's vital energy?
What are you laughing at?
I really thought
you had turned over a new leaf.
There's a huge difference.
That girl
knows
what price she has to pay.
She knows?
Yeah, go ask her yourself.
Wang Fang.
You need to leave
your boyfriend now.
Why?
He's not human.
I know that.
Aren't you scared?
He treats me very well.
Why would I be scared?
Don't you think this relationship
is super eerie?
Director.
Look at me.
I'm so ordinary.
I'm no stunning beauty,
nor do I have a wealthy background.
Normally,
why would Yuanji ever fall for me?
Look.
The diamond ring he bought me.
Do you know
what price you have to pay?
It doesn't matter
as long as I can afford it.
Director,
why do you look so haggard?
Did you not sleep well?
Go back to your seat and rest a bit.
I'll make you a cup of coffee.
Director.
Have some coffee.
Okay, thanks.
Get back to work.
Dongqing's car lights are on.
I'll go check.
Dongqing!
Open the door!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Do you remember anything?
I only remember
heavy rain
pouring down.
Then I couldn't see anything.
I only heard the sound of flowing water.
It sounded like
a beast roaring.
What beast?
I've never heard it before.
It sounded like a cow,
but deeper
and more shocking.
A bit like thunder.
This demon really doesn't
mean any harm.
It left you here
in one piece.
You guys
saw the demon?
He's a handsome young man.
That's just an avatar.
His name is Bai Xiaonian.
It's a fake name.
But it doesn't matter.
Let's go back.
Go back?
What else?
You've been missing all night.
Isn't your wife worried?
Right.
I need to hurry up
and call my wife.
What do you mean?
You quit?
That demon
just wants to protect this town
from invasion.
It means no harm.
I don't think it's necessary
to eliminate it.
Then what about my development plan?
You accepted my money.
Ms. Huang, your memory isn't very good.
I already returned the money to you.
Besides,
why must you develop this place?
It's such a beautiful small town
with hundreds of years of history.
You insist on tearing it down
to build villas.
But will they even sell?
I'm done reporting.
My wife was worried sick.
What's the plan now?
Let's go home.
Huang Shang!
Huang Shang, where are you going?
None of your business.
I do whatever I want.
I'm going to slay the demon.
Are you crazy?
Are we still leaving?
Didn't you hear?
She does whatever she wants.
What a stubborn woman.