[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 8]
Leave me alone.
Useless men.
Who are you calling useless?
Us, obviously.
Whatever I, Huang Shang, want to do,
I will get it done.
Our family of witches
has been guarding the town
for generations.
I don't believe that
I can't handle
a small demon myself.
Demon!
Don't yell.
Show yourself!
Demon!
Don't yell.
Where is the demon?
Demon!
Show yourself!
Demon...
Why is there a butterfly
flying around at night?
Such a big one, too.
There's nothing.
So it's... A demon?
Bai Xiaonian!
In... In the East,
the green demon of pestilence,
spirit of rotten wood.
In the South,
the red demon of pestilence,
spirit of flame.
In the West...
Biyun, you're back.
You're back.
Let go of me!
You jerk!
Biyun.
Don't you remember me?
Who is Biyun?
Bi- Biyun?
Huang Biyun?
You're not Biyun.
Then where is Biyun now?
Huang Biyun?
She is my great-grandmother.
Your great-grandmother?
Then she must be
from almost a hundred years ago.
She
was a mortal.
It's been almost a hundred years.
She's long gone.
Biyun...
Is gone?
[Many years ago]
Are you there?
I know you are there.
Hiding is useless.
I am a witch.
I can feel your demonic aura.
Look, this is plum blossom.
Have you seen it?
It's very pretty.
Unlike your mountain,
which is so barren.
I'll leave if you don't come out.
I will leave
this plum blossom branch for you.
I'll come find you when I have time.
Remember, my name is Huang Biyun.
I'm leaving.
Don't come looking for me again.
You spoke to me!
It's my first time hearing your voice.
Let me see your face,
okay?
So afraid of seeing people.
Are you very ugly?
You're the ugly one.
Everyone in town says I'm pretty.
You run fast.
You ugly girl.
The people in your town
are all liars.
Ugly girl.
Don't come looking for me again.
Are you there?
The red plum branch I gave you
has almost grown into a forest,
but I've yet to see your face.
Grandma said that
in a few days,
a great disaster will come.
I need a spirit beast
to protect my town with me.
It's been so many years.
I come to beg you every year.
Why won't you ever agree?
Because you are not pretty.
Ugly girl.
There's a custom in our town.
When the red plum blossoms bloom,
girls will tie red strings
on the branches.
Soon, they will get to marry
a good man.
Are you going to get married?
You're so ugly,
who would want to marry you?
Nonsense.
I'm not ugly at all.
I figure that
the red plum blossoms here
have absorbed your spiritual energy,
so they should be more effective
than the ones in our town.
You have to bless me, too.
Ha! You fell for it!
This demon-binding rope
was made specifically for you
by my own hands.
Now you can't escape.
Calling me ugly?
Let me see
if you look any better.
You call me ugly every day,
but you're not that good-looking either.
You tricked me.
You humans are so shameless!
So stubborn.
Since I caught you,
you are my spirit beast.
If you don't listen,
I will beat you.
I can even kill you right now.
From now on,
I am your master.
In the future,
you will be our town's
guardian spirit beast.
If you refuse,
I'll extract your inner core
and destroy your cultivation.
As for your true form,
I could send it to
an acrobatics troupe
to be a sideshow.
I'll kill you!
You can't even move.
What's your name?
Speak.
Bai Lin!
So, you're called Bai Lin.
So Huang Biyun
brought you back
and sealed you in that well.
You're also stupid.
For so many years,
she went looking for you every year.
She was a witch;
she was bound to find a way
to capture you one day.
Yet you stayed there every year.
Weren't you just waiting to be captured?
Living here all by yourself
must have been very lonely.
Actually,
I hoped she would visit every year.
I lied.
She was not ugly at all.
She was beautiful since childhood.
I was so happy she captured me.
She said
she wanted me to join her
in guarding this town.
I was very happy too.
She said the land of China
was facing a great disaster.
I wanted to watch over the town
together with her.
Your great-grandmother...
Didn't she go to Nanyang?
Nanyang?
Wasn't it a town over the mountain?
Why did you break the barrier?
Aren't you afraid I'd run away?
I'm leaving.
Father is taking our whole family
to Nanyang.
This way,
when I'm not around,
you can still come out.
You are my spirit beast.
When I'm gone,
you must protect this town for me.
Where is Nanyang?
Is it another town?
Yes.
It's
on the other side of the mountain.
Just another town.
Then how many days will you be gone?
Bai Lin.
When I'm not around,
can you
watch over this town for me?
Are you going to get married?
What are you talking about?
Who'd get married
at a time like this?
Okay, I promise you.
Before you return,
I will guard this town for you.
Bai Lin.
I...
Wait for my return.
You must wait for my return.
I waited for her for a long time.
So long that this town became deserted,
yet she still hadn't returned.
Actually,
by untying that rope,
she set you free.
You could have left at any time.
I promised her
to protect this town.
A promise is a promise.
Let me tell you.
My
great-grandmother's father,
who is my...
Never mind.
Her whole family
moved to Nanyang for business
and never returned to China.
As for my great-grandmother...
After 3 years in Nanyang,
her father found her a Chinese man
to marry into the family
as a live-in son-in-law.
Then,
she gave birth to my grandmother.
Many years later,
I was born.
Bai Lin,
thank you
for protecting this town
for our family
for so many years.
My great-grandmother
has been gone from this world
for a long time.
You are free.
I have decided
to give up developing this town.
After all, you have protected it
for so many years.
From now on,
I will protect it for you.
I can go?
But where can I go?
Right.
This
was passed down from my great-grandmother
to me.
I'll give it to you.
You can
keep it as a memento.
This is
what I gave to Biyun
when we parted.
Wait.
I have something for you.
Keep it with you.
I have never been to
the other side of the mountain.
I don't know if there are any
powerful demons there.
If you are in danger,
it can protect you.
You must come back quickly,
Biyun.
What is that?
It's Bai Lin's inner core.
Biyun!
Is that
my great-grandmother?
It's Huang Biyun's soul,
attached to Bai Lin's inner core.
She came back.
I knew you would come back.
Bai Lin.
This place doesn't need
our protection anymore.
This time,
I'll go with you
to your world.
I will never leave you again.
Are you kidding me?
She made him a spirit beast?
He's...
A dragon?
A deep yearning hidden
in 10 years of encounter.
A century of waiting
reflects deep affection.
She entrusted her freedom.
He answered with time.
A promise is an unspoken contract.
Waiting is gentleness
etched into the soul.
So romantic.
The witch
and her demon's love is so touching.
Ms. Huang,
I didn't expect a strong woman like you
would shed tears.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Well, generally speaking,
dragons are not considered demons,
and they wouldn't be
a human's spirit beast.
It's because they fell in love.
So,
Bai Lin has left?
This town
can actually still be developed.
How can you go back on your word?
I was just considering
the dragon's feelings just now.
You already promised him.
This isn't very good, is it?
No, wait.
Forget about those.
Ms. Huang, do you remember?
At that time, you gave us
a 100,000 yuan reward.
We gave it back to you.
You should give it back to us now.
What role
did you two play?
You men are useless.
Why don't you two
get me a spirit beast, too?
I also want a dragon.
A dragon?
From where?
Do I look like a dragon to you?
Get one for me.
Waiting for a hero.
I am that dragon.
No.
We worked so hard.
You have to give us what we deserve.
You were completely useless.
Ms. Huang!