[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 10]
Are you ready to face
your destiny?
To be an ordinary person?
It's still not too late.
If you are willing to
get rid of this child,
your body might still recover.
Get rid of it?
I'm just making a suggestion.
It's your body and your destiny.
You can do whatever you want.
But being a mother
is quite nice too.
You'll be a good mom.
We're here.
Thanks for walking me back.
Aren't you going to
invite me in for a drink?
Sure.
I just got some new red wine.
I'll mull some for you.
About my pregnancy,
don't tell Dongqing yet.
Zhao,
have a drink.
Yan,
I'm not really into mulled wine.
Drinking mulled wine makes me too hot.
You drink it.
Why is it
so hot in here today?
Don't you feel it?
It's like a chimney in here.
Dongqing,
cheers.
you only prepared
these few snacks?
That's so boring.
I ordered some good food.
It'll be here soon.
Come in.
Mr. Zhao,
your food is here.
Chen?
Why are you delivering food?
It's mealtime,
and deliveries are slow.
Boss Tian was afraid you'd be starving,
so she sent me to deliver it.
Let me introduce you.
Okay.
He's just temping as a delivery guy.
He's a boss himself
and runs a plain noodle shop.
Those noodles taste amazing.
Your homemade soy sauce is delicious too.
It's a small business.
Just a small business.
Mr. Zhao.
Here.
Boss Tian has a message
for you.
What message?
Can we hear it?
I guess
you can.
Boss Tian said,
"Mr. Zhao hasn't come to my place
to eat for a while.
I kind of miss him.
Is he tired of my food
and going to
other places to eat?"
Isn't that vilifying me?
Can't I make something
to eat at home?
That's what I said too.
But Boss Tian said,
"Mr. Zhao is a bachelor
and doesn't like cooking.
Once he starts cooking for himself,
he must be attached
or interested in someone."
Then, to prove my innocence,
should I go to the snail stall
in person tomorrow?
Absolutely.
All right, I won't disturb you anymore.
Okay, I'm off.
Thanks, Mr. Chen.
Okay, bye.
Enjoy your meal.
Come on.
Try it.
It smells so good.
Is it chicken soup?
Snail soup.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Although this shop is small,
it's a century-old shop.
It smells so fishy.
It doesn't.
Right. It doesn't taste fishy at all.
Only you think so.
Is there something wrong with your taste?
Then maybe there is
something wrong with my taste.
Zhao Hengzhi.
Is this Boss Tian
very pretty?
Not really pretty, just average.
But...
But what?
Hard to say.
Just drink the soup.
[Snail]
[Chapter 7: Snail Killing]
Boss Tian.
Mr. Zhao.
Long time no see.
Have a seat.
We're having steamed buns today.
Snail fillings.
With snail meat?
I've had radish,
zucchini, broccoli,
seaweed, and seafood buns,
but never snail meat ones.
All right,
give me 2 bowls of soup later.
Two bowls?
You brought a friend?
A girl?
A guy.
I asked you to buy milk tea.
Why did you get this?
I suddenly really wanted to eat it.
Here.
It's fine if you want to eat it,
but you can't bring it
to someone else's shop.
-It’s fine.
-What's wrong with that?
This is from the barbecue shop
ahead, right?
I like it too.
Mr. Zhao, your friend
is really handsome.
Have a seat.
Director.
Hello, Director.
Where is Wang Fang?
She didn't come to work today.
She didn't ask me for leave either.
She didn't ask for leave
and didn't reply to messages.
I even called her,
but she didn't answer either.
Could something have happened to her?
Drink less milk tea.
It's unhealthy.
Okay, go back to work.
Ya.
I miss you so much.
Why would you?
We just saw each other yesterday.
Snail meat buns.
Th-This is a full snail feast.
I'm starting to get hungry again.
When can we start?
It's still too hot right now.
So in the meantime,
please wait for me a little longer.
I've been busy at the stove all day.
Look, I'm covered in sweat.
I'll go up and change clothes.
I'll be right back.
Wait for me.
Okay.
People used to talk about the Tofu Beauty.
Look at her,
she can be the Snail Beauty.
I didn't notice that.
What do you think
a legendary beauty looks like?
Gentle,
capable,
and very charming.
Anyway,
she's the kind of woman men really want
to marry and take home.
Dongqing,
you're a big pervert, aren't you?
Don't forget you have a wife.
Of course.
I'm strictly disciplined.
I forgot to report to my wife.
Okay,
I got it.
Come back early after dinner.
Bye-bye.
If you have nothing to do,
have dinner with me.
Drink some.
I'm not good at drinking liquor.
This is Boss Tian's hospitality.
Drink some.
Okay.
No going home
until we're drunk.
Steak from Florence.
Dry-aged for 30 days.
The best steak,
better than Wagyu.
Wagyu has too much fat.
It's too greasy.
Come on, cheers.
Yuanji?
Isn't he with Wang Fang?
Yuanji!
Who is she?
Who are you?
You...
Yuanji is my boyfriend.
You shameless
woman!
You...
Miss,
who are you?
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Are you okay?
Let go of me!
-Let go of me!
-Wait!
Let go of her!
Director.
Take her to my room.
-Yes.
Your dating time
is over.
Over?
Although he exists
in this world,
he's only a 2D character.
His memory of you
has been cleared by the system.
But my Affection Level...
I spent so much money on it.
You have already been rewarded.
I can renew the Affection Level.
Wang Fang,
this is just a game.
Game over.
I don't want that.
I only want Yuanji.
Lady Yuzhen,
please think of a way.
I only want Yuanji.
I don't want anyone else.
Lady Yuzhen.
Lady Yuzhen, Lady Yuzhen!
Please, please,
make Yuanji remember me.
He clearly loved me so much.
Wang Fang.
Lady Yuzhen!
Lady Yuzhen...
Cheers!
Boss Tian.
This all-snail feast
is quite delicious.
You were drinking happily.
Why did you suddenly start crying?
Here, a tissue.
I'm sorry, you two.
I made a fool of myself.
Living in this world
itself
is tied to suffering.
Why did I say that?
Just to fit the occasion, I guess.
Zhao Li?
How many times have I told you?
I am not Zhao Li.
Did this Zhao Li
owe you a lot of money
or hurt you deeply?
I am Zhao Hengzhi.
Zhao Hengzhi!
The men here are handsome,
but the women are plain-looking,
just like Wang Fang.
Why did you do this?
I'm saving these women.
I let them gain it first,
then lose it,
then gain it again.
After a few repetitions,
they will know
that love
is no big deal.
No wonder Wang Fang is like this.
Handsome, rich, and devoted.
Where in the world is there such a lover?
Party time.
Only women who pass my test
can become my friends.
Xia Dongqing.
Xia Dongqing!
I'm not drunk.
Let's go home.
Why don't you go home?
What do you want to stay for?
I'm telling you,
you're already drunk.
Your wife is waiting for you at home.
Go home!
Boss Tian.
I...
I heard some noise.
Have a seat.