[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 11]
Why are you sitting on the floor?
There are no chairs here.
Sit here.
Take off your coat.
Mr. Zhao,
please don't think
I'm an easy woman.
Actually,
I'm a very decent woman.
I just want
a man who understands me.
I can wash his clothes, cook for him,
and have children with him.
Then how many of those men
have you had?
I've met a few.
Tall or short, fat or thin,
light skin or dark, handsome or ugly—
they were all different.
But in the end,
they were all the same.
Mr. Zhao,
what about you?
Are you the same as them?
I'm not like them.
How are you different?
I'm completely different.
I am a night watchman,
possessing a pure yang body
that burns like Samadhi Fire,
specializing in eliminating all evil.
Aren't you a university teacher?
Tian Guixiang,
you are not human.
What are you?
What is this?
So disgusting!
I possess a pure yang...
I misjudged this time.
How unlucky!
Tian Guixiang!
Where am I?
A cellar.
The shop is right above us.
You're lying in the pool
where I keep my river snails.
You demon!
What's wrong with being a demon?
I am a demon,
but I'm a kind, hardworking,
and self-reliant good demon.
There are many people worse than demons.
Right.
There are good demons.
Like you.
And there are bad people.
Like...
Well, definitely not me.
I'm a good person.
I really am a good person.
You're a good demon.
We have no grievances against each other.
Just let me go.
Do you think I'm stupid?
You're a demon hunter.
If I let you go,
won't I just be waiting for you
to eliminate me?
I want to share
a secret with you.
I'm actually quite pent-up.
I don't want to keep
my pure yang body anymore.
I want to get married.
W-With someone just like you,
curvy, beautiful,
hardworking, and capable.
Think about it. If we get married,
we'll be running
that river snail shop together.
You work outside,
and I take care of the house.
You fetch the water...
No. I fetch the water
and water the garden.
I mean, I'll do all the chores.
I'm really good at doing chores.
I'm a hardworking man.
And you sing quite well too.
I-If you like it,
I'll sing for you every day
after we marry.
What a pity.
You know everything now.
How could I let you go?
If my river snails eat you,
the soup I make
will definitely be more delicious.
You're going to feed me
to the river snails?
You're not just a big demon.
You're also a huge...
pervert!
I'm just trying to scare you.
The river snails won't eat you.
So cute.
When I have time,
I'll use you to pass the time—
and eat you myself.
You big per—
vert!
This jerk.
What time is it?
Why isn't he answering the phone?
Dongqing, coffee, the usual.
Dark roast Americano,
one spoon of brown sugar,
a splash of milk, two ice cubes.
Next time,
I want to try a
more beautiful makeup look.
Sure. And I think
with your vibe,
you can also go for
a really cool style.
That way,
it'll suit you better.
Excuse me.
Wait a minute.
Zhao Hengzhi
still hasn't answered his phone.
I'm a little worried about him.
He's a grown man.
Why are you worried about him?
Stop hanging out with him that often.
What's wrong?
As a grown man,
he just met a girl,
and he stayed over at her place.
Isn't he a scumbag?
Well, it's normal
for men to be attracted by appearance.
Whose place did he stay at?
The river snail soup restaurant girl
from the day before yesterday.
They specifically went to eat
river snail meat buns
and even drank with the owner.
Now I get it.
Drinking...
They're all adults.
It's consensual.
Something's off.
It's already noon.
Why isn't he answering his phone?
His phone isn't dead,
and he's not out of service area.
What does that mean?
It means he
doesn't want to talk to you.
You two look pretty free today.
Ma'am.
Where is Zhao Hengzhi?
He left.
I don't remember
when he left.
I drank a bit too much yesterday.
I remember...
Mr. Zhao helped me upstairs.
As for how I fell asleep...
I don't remember.
When I woke up, it was already dawn,
and he had long gone.
But up till now,
he hasn't answered my calls.
He isn't answering mine either.
You looked for him too?
Well, he's a man.
Disappearing at a time like this—
isn't it quite common?
Ma'am.
Where's my river snail soup?
Coming.
Excuse me.
Careful. It's hot.
Okay.
Ma'am.
What is upstairs?
It's where I live.
Do you want to go up and take a look?
Why?
I don't even know you.
I'm an honest merchant.
I pay taxes legally every year.
If you want to enter my private property,
at least get a search warrant!
We weren't born yesterday,
so stop playing this trick with me.
I felt it.
Your pulse is full of demon energy.
You demon.
Honey!
You're so disgusting!
What are you doing?
I didn't do anything.
Do I know you?
Why are you here
to interrupt my business?
Can't you let people eat in peace?
That's right!
Are you guys
going to eat or not?
If not, get the hell out of here!
Yeah, leave if you're not eating!
Don't bother us!
Why bother her?
Exactly.
There are too many people here.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Honey, are you okay?
Is this her saliva?
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt or itch.
It's just disgusting.
It stinks.
Why didn't you lick her?
This probably isn't saliva.
If it were, it would have dried by now.
We can't get in there now anyway.
Dongqing,
why don't you go back to the café first?
Why should I go back?
Aren't you going to run the business?
Just go back as I told you.
But...
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and go.
Yuzhen,
can you go to the hospital with me?
Are you feeling unwell?
You're taking the saliva to the hospital?
Hurry. Come on.
Honey! Honey!
Where...
Where did you go?
Say something.
You didn't answer my calls
or reply to my messages.
I was worried sick.
I went to the hospital.
How was it?
I'm terminally ill.
It's incurable.
That serious?
Honey.
Honey!
We're just kidding.
It's not saliva at all.
The hospital wouldn't test this.
Luckily,
the doctor we met
is a fan of mine.
So we found out its composition.
What is it?
Mucus.
Animal mucus.
What animal?
A snake demon?
A snail?
You forgot what you ate?
A river snail.
A river snail?
Ms. River Snail?
Bingo.
Help! Help!
Help!
Come in.
Why are you acting so sneaky?
I'm looking for my friend.
Just you?
Yes,
just me.
Come and sit.
Thanks.
Have some soup.
Is Zhao Hengzhi...
really not here?
He's not here.
After I left last night,
nothing happened between you two, right?
What do you think?
Of course nothing happened.
If something had happened,
you would have said bad things about him.
I know Zhao Hengzhi
very well.
He's not interested in women.
Did he reject you?
If you're angry about this,
there's no need.
What about you?
Me?
Are you interested in women?
I'm married.
My wife is
one of the two women
who came to your shop
this after—
One of those two women
is also a demon.
As for the other one,
I couldn't tell.
You look like a normal human.
Why are you hanging out with demons?
Are you scared?
I got it!
You're Ms. River Snail,
right?
You are a hardworking
and kind good demon.
Every Chinese knows you.
You helped the poor farmer,
and even washed his clothes
and cooked for him,
right?
Then why am I here now?
Aren't...
Aren't you immortal?
But your husband...
He was a mortal after all.
I assume
he's been dead for many years.
You must be very lonely.
Actually,
it's okay to find another man.
But Zhao Hengzhi...
He's not suitable.
Who is he to you?
Who are you to meddle here?
What if he is willing?
The wife you married
isn't a mortal either.
Why is it okay for you but not for him?
What's the logic in that?
He didn't say it was okay.
From last night until now,
he hasn't answered his phone.
You must have hidden him away,
right?
How about this?
Just take me to see him.
If he tells me
he wants to be with you,
as his friend,
I won't say another word.
On your wedding day,
I'll give you a big red envelope.
But right now,
I can't find him anywhere.
There's no trace of him,
dead or alive.
I really have to call the police.
Follow me.
He's over there.