[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 14]
Ms. He Feng,
this is your room, right?
Yes.
Why does this mansion
have a room for you?
This is my home.
I am the mistress here.
How is it?
Do you like it?
Yes, I like it.
From now on,
this will be your home.
Darling.
I personally picked out
all these pieces of furniture for you.
They are the latest French designs
shipped across the ocean,
and I just got the full set.
We are just missing your dolls now.
But the thing is,
when are you moving in?
Anytime.
As Tang Yu's fiancée,
I moved into the Tangs' mansion.
And that was the beginning
of my misfortune.
What happened later?
This family
had a hideous secret.
I found out about it
soon after I moved in.
That brother and sister
were disgusting!
You mean
the brother and sister...
Thinking back now,
I still feel disgusted.
How did you end up
trapped in the dog skin?
It was Tang Huan.
She is a witch.
Who knows where she learned
that demonic magic?
I just wanted to leave here,
leave this disgusting home.
Sister-in-law...
Feng.
Hands off me!
Sister-in-law!
Don't call me that.
You are just like your brother—
you both make me sick!
Feng!
My brother and I only had each other.
Our parents died early.
We didn't know anything...
We only knew that
we were the closest people to each other.
But it's different now.
Now we have you.
My brother really likes you.
Do you even
hear yourself?
You are insane.
You and your brother
are both insane!
I am leaving this house right now.
You two,
stop pestering me!
Brother.
Get out of the way.
How could you push my sister?
I told you to get out of the way!
How dare you?
Open the door.
Let me out.
How much longer
are you going to lock me up?
What you are doing is
illegal.
I'm going to the police station right now
to turn you in.
Feng,
let the three of us
live a happy life together,
okay?
Disgusting.
You left me no choice.
So,
you've been trapped
in that strange body?
It's been almost 100 years.
I can neither die
nor escape.
I can only be trapped there.
How does the saying go?
You can run, but you can't hide.
Their ancestral home is here,
so
you can always find this family.
And they
happened to have twins again
in this generation.
And the twins just
look exactly like the siblings
you knew in the past.
Exactly.
I was consumed by hatred.
The moment I saw those siblings,
my hatred only grew stronger!
Tang De and Tang Lin are
not Tang Yu and Tang Huan.
They didn't do anything to you.
The son pays for the father's sins!
Their ancestors committed the crime.
What's wrong with me
making them pay for it?
Not to mention that
these siblings are
also disgusting,
just as disgusting as the ones back then!
You mean...
What you're saying is none of my concern.
They didn't hurt anyone.
But I was paid to solve
their problem.
I need to eliminate evil things.
You attempted to kill Tang De.
There's solid evidence.
Fire, come!
Master,
I-I was wrong.
I was wrong. I did it wrong.
I'm also a victim of evil magic!
I-I used to be a perfectly normal person.
I didn't want to be a demon!
Master,
I was wrong. I was wrong.
Demon, no more excuses.
Fire, come!
Wait!
She didn't become a demon voluntarily.
Is there any way
to free her
from that dog skin?
She has already turned
into a pile of dry bones.
After 100 years,
she is now
an utterly great demon.
There's no cure for her,
and her hatred is extremely deep.
Didn't she already admit
that she was wrong?
Wait, you trust a demon
over me?
She deserves to be destroyed.
As a cultivator,
you should have compassion!
Please
spare me your phony
compassion.
I only have drastic measures.
She's consumed by a strong obsession.
Her inner demons are way harder
to get rid of than herself.
Just give her one last chance!
I have a plan.
What is it?
To be honest with each other.
Really?
Can you do it?
Letting the dog live on the second floor
is a bit weird,
but that room is
empty anyway.
Y-Yes, we can do it.
Actually,
you just need to act as usual.
Don't be afraid.
Just treat her as a dog
with a human mind.
Your ancestors
once hurt her a bit.
You only need to make it up
to her every day
and treat her
a little better.
You call this
being honest with each other?
Sort of.
Sort of? You...
You completely made up
a whole different story.
It's not bad, right?
The brother of the siblings
from a century ago
had an affair with the maid,
who was accidentally killed by the sister.
The maid had her resentment
attached to a dog
and became a demon.
The truth is a bit complicated
and scary.
I was afraid they couldn't accept it
right away.
If the brother and sister
treat He Feng well
and save her from wandering,
any hatred
should fade away.
I think this is the only way
to avoid
any more accidents, right?
This is also a last resort.
She's already such a poor thing.
Are you really
going to burn her
to ashes?
Wait...
Sirs.
I still can't rest assured.
Now that we know
this guy is a demon,
and she almost killed my brother,
why should we still keep her in our house?
Let me observe for a few more days.
If you observe for a few days,
that demon will naturally behave.
But can you stay here
and observe for a lifetime?
Treat her well, and she will be grateful.
If you can't do it,
I'll turn to someone else.
Don't worry, Ms. Tang.
I am a pro at this.
I promise I'll settle this matter
to your satisfaction,
okay?
Let's drop it for now.
Fang Yuan!
Lin!
These two gentlemen
look unfamiliar to me.
They're our business partners.
They came to discuss something.
Sirs,
this is my boyfriend,
Fang Yuan.
Boyfriend?
Why so distant from me today?
I am
your fiancé.
You are right.
Morning.
Your coffee.
You came so early.
What were you doing yesterday?
Looking up information.
What information?
The information from a century ago.
It was paid,
and quite expensive.
[Republic of China Daily]
Tang Huan was engaged?
Tang Lin is also engaged.
Could this be
some sort of fate repeating itself?
You know, Xia Dongqing,
you are quite stupid sometimes.
That dog woman asserted
that Tang Lin and Tang De were
in a secret relationship,
right?
These siblings are
also disgusting,
just as disgusting as the ones back then!
If they were really
in a secret relationship,
why would Tang Lin
have a fiancé?
These siblings
have a large ancestral mansion.
They have family property
and plenty of money
and don't need to assimilate
into society at all.
All they need to do is live
their happy lives in their own place.
Wait a minute.
By the same token,
things were exactly the same
for the siblings back then.
Therefore,
these two pairs of siblings
never had any kind
of improper relationship.
He Feng was lying?
She deceived us!
That's why I told you
never to trust a demon.
But...
No buts.
There are lots of loopholes in her story.
If Tang Huan
had turned her into a dog,
the person she hates the most
should have been
Tang Lin,
who looks identical to Tang Huan.
Why did she try to kill Tang De?
Maybe that was
because Tang De got in the car first.
Open it and take a look.
Is there anything wrong about this photo?
This is He Feng's necklace.
Yes, it is He Feng's necklace.
Tang Yu was her fiancé.
But it was the photo
of Tang Huan inside the necklace
she wore.
Why?
Did your brain stop working
after hearing this?
Mine stopped working after I said it, too.
We need to go back and take a look.
You mean, Fenghua Photo Studio?
What are we doing here?
Looking for something.
Looking for what?
Evidence.
Dongqing.
Found it.