[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 13]
Brother, I'm back.
Where did you go without telling me?
Brother,
I have guests with me.
Are these two
your new friends?
Hello,
I'm Tang De.
I'm Zhao Hengzhi.
Hello,
I'm Xia Dongqing.
You two can take a rest here first.
Brother,
please entertain them for me.
I'll go get some food.
Go ahead.
These pieces of furniture
look pretty old.
They were bought by my ancestors.
My parents passed away early,
so my sister and I have only each other.
Thankfully,
we still have some properties left.
This photo looks really good.
Is it a photo of you and your sister?
It's so retro.
It matches the style
of this mansion perfectly.
This is an old photo.
It had already been here
even before I was born.
So the people in the photo
are not you and Tang Lin?
No.
He is my ancestor
from three generations ago.
I look exactly
like him, right?
He's my great-great-grandfather.
This mansion is
the property he left behind.
So this girl who looks exactly
like your younger sister is...
She is my great-great-grandfather's
younger sister.
That's too much of a coincidence.
You and Tang Lin are twins?
Yes.
Family genes.
Your family
should have identical twins
appearing
every few generations.
You should have a family tree, I guess?
It's a pity
that we don't have one.
My great-great-grandfather was called
Tang Yu,
and his younger sister was called
Tang Huan.
When Lin and I were young,
we really wanted to see them.
But before we were born,
they had long been gone.
Tang Yu passed away earlier.
He died soon after taking
this picture.
Was it an accident?
He shot himself in the mouth.
Brother,
stop talking nonsense.
Come on, sirs,
please sit down and have some dessert.
Please.
Okay.
Come on.
Make yourselves at home.
Brother,
where's your dog?
I haven't seen it for quite a while.
It was still around before you came back.
Why is the door open?
Sirs, please try some.
Did it run to the garden?
Doggy!
Doggy?
Not sure where it went.
It's fine. Just leave it.
Why do you call it "doggy"?
Haven't you given it a name?
I haven't got the time to do it.
I think
it should have a name.
But it can't speak,
so I can't ask it.
It's a stray dog.
It followed
my brother home the other day.
It's about time.
I have an appointment.
Are you going to play ball again?
If you two are
free tonight,
please stay,
and let's have dinner together.
Okay.
Mr. Tang.
This is our first meeting.
I have a little gift for you.
It's an amulet.
Keep it with you or in your car.
It will keep you safe.
Thank you.
Then let's have dinner tonight.
Brother,
come back early.
Okay.
I knew it.
There's something off about this dog.
Seeing you here,
it didn't even dare to show up.
That's good, actually.
With Zhao Hengzhi here,
even if there is a demon,
it will be scared away.
Please come upstairs with me.
I will...
show you something else.
I didn't even dare to tell my brother.
I was afraid it'd scare him.
Sirs,
this is the room
Tang Huan used to live in.
After all these years,
it still remains the same?
So many dolls.
This doll
looks a bit like you.
I think it looks like Tang Huan.
She is quite narcissistic.
Having so many dolls
that look exactly like her
in the room,
wasn't she afraid?
This set of furniture
is all made of peach wood.
Sirs,
please check this out.
Is this Tang Huan?
This dog in it looks identical
to that stray dog.
It's been about 100 years.
It must've become a demon
and found our family.
I think there's something
malicious in its eyes.
It gives me bad feelings
just looking at it.
Can we borrow
this necklace for a while?
[Chapter 8: Malice]
Doggy?
Doggy,
why are you here?
Don't tell me you ran all the way here.
That's so dangerous.
What if you get lost?
Let's go home.
Hello, Lin.
I'm done.
I'm heading back now.
Do you need me to bring anything?
Okay,
I got it.
I'm hanging up.
You're awake?
[Convenience Store 444]
Fenghua Photo Studio.
[Fenghua Photo Studio]
The photo of the siblings on the wall
also has this small line of text.
Yes, I've recalled it now.
I just feel that there's something weird
about those two siblings.
To me,
it's way more obvious
than some dog demon.
What do you think is weird?
I can't put my finger on it.
I just feel that there's
a certain vibe in their family.
An old mansion,
the siblings in white,
and the identical twins
appearing every few generations,
with beautiful faces.
Whether there's a problem
with the dog or not, I've used
protection magic on Tang De.
Since we're idle anyway,
do you want to go take a look
at what exactly happened
to the Tang family?
Where to?
Fenghua Photo Studio.
With this,
we can
enter a fragment of time,
although
we can only stay for a couple of minutes.
Lean on me.
What are you doing?
I told you to lean on me,
not hug me.
Are you deaf?
Turn around.
Fenghua Photo Studio.
In the Republic of China?
This is a crevice in time.
We are just bystanders.
People here
can neither hear us
nor see us.
There are no photos
of the Tang siblings here.
Where is the boss
of your photo studio?
I made a call earlier.
I want her
to take a picture of me herself.
Just a moment, please.
Ms. Tang.
This is...
Tang Huan.
Welcome.
I am He Feng.
Hi, Ms. He.
Ms. He?
Sorry.
It smells so good.
I can't smell it.
I've heard
that this photo studio's owner
is a lady.
But I didn't expect
you to be so stylish and modern.
This necklace...
It belonged to He Feng.
That Pekingese!
Ms. He,
I came all the way here
just to ask you
to take a nice photo
of my dog and me.
Don't worry about this.
Leave it to me, and I'll
make sure you get what you want.
Time is up.
We are back.
This is that outfit, right?
This photo was
taken on the day
we just saw.
Tang Huan brought the dog.
That dog really belonged to Tang Huan!
The dog is not important.
What do you mean?
Hello?
Mr. Zhao,
my brother just had an accident.
I saw
black hands
grab the steering wheel.
Something
tried to kill me.
And then...
Then the fire came.
The amulet I gave you
contains
the seed of Samadhi Fire.
Once there's a flicker of demonic magic,
it will automatically backfire.
It's
the one I put
in your chest pocket.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving my life.
So,
your Samadhi Fire
has killed
this dog demon?
It escaped.
Then...
It will come back again.
It's not some dog demon,
but something
attached under the dog's skin.
But leaving the dog's skin,
it won't last long.
As long as we have the dog's skin,
we can sit and wait
to catch this demon.
What on earth
is this demon up to?
It wants to kill my brother!
Maybe
it wants to kill both of us.
Why?
No more random guessing.
When the owner of the dog skin comes back,
we will ask it directly.
I'm going to set up
a barrier here.
Right... Right here?
Mr. Tang, Ms. Tang,
you may go and rest first.
Dongqing and I
need to borrow a place from you.
Dongqing,
what time is it?
It's 11:40 PM.
Dongqing,
the demon wearing the dog skin
can't survive past midnight without it.
It will come back.
We'll wait for it.
Since we have some time left,
let's go back and see
if we've missed anything.
Use this?
Lean over.
Alright,
the photo shoot is done.
So beautiful, Ms. Tang.
That's only because
you excel at taking photos, Ms. He.
The dolls on the table.
You have
so many dolls here.
They are produced
by a German company.
I'm so into them.
These dolls
were all He Feng's?
There were more.
More?
Don't you think these dolls
look so much like you?
Really?
It is a bit like me.
Sister.
Brother.
Brother,
let me introduce you
to my new friend.
This is Ms. He,
the owner of Fenghua Photo Studio.
Ms. He,
nice to meet you.
Hello, Mr. Tang.
I am He Feng.
So
these dolls
belonged to He Feng.
You just said there were more.
This closet smells
like He Feng.
These qipaos...
These qipaos
don't seem like Ms. Tang's style.
You mean
this room...
It's very likely
that it didn't belong to Tang Huan.