[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 12]
He's over there.
Zhao Hengzhi?
Zhao Hengzhi.
Dongqing!
Honey!
You river snail demon.
Dongqing!
Dongqing, Dongqing!
Did you get hurt just now?
I'm out of energy.
I've turned into an ordinary woman.
What should we do?
That hole seemed
to be sealed by magic.
There must be
a magic vein underneath
leading to her lair.
Do you have a way to open it?
Yes, I do. But...
But what?
It's a bit embarrassing,
since I'll have to dance.
Do you need music?
Zhao Hengzhi!
Shut up.
Get in there.
No, no!
The pool's already full.
It's completely full!
Why come down here at all?
Come here.
Squat down.
Hold that river snail in your arms.
Do as I say,
or I'll kill you right now.
Let me ask you.
What exactly is your honey?
She's a Heavenly Maiden.
What about that temptress?
What were you saying?
I said Yan Yuzhen
is a formidable demon,
having lived this long!
She's superior to you.
This is all your fault,
for bringing
these troublesome people here.
How is it my fault?
Isn't this happening
because of your evil intentions toward me?
What's there to do now?
Now...
Just quickly
release us.
Listen,
if you behave well,
they might show you some leniency.
Heck no!
Stay down!
You said your honey is a Heavenly Maiden.
But I escaped under her nose.
It seems she's not that good.
It was because she didn't have
her feather cloak on.
Feather cloak?
You know what?
As long as she put it on,
thunder will roar
and lightning will strike you.
Just you wait.
She must've gone home for the cloak.
I'm sure she'll be back soon to save me.
That's right!
Y-You'd better let us go
right now.
Otherwise,
you'll regret it
when his honey arrives.
Don't you dare try to scare me.
I've lived for a thousand years.
What have I not seen?
I fear nothing!
You...
I won't touch you.
As for you...
You're a two-faced hypocrite
who hunts demons.
Keeping you alive
will invite endless trouble.
I doubt it.
You do have a pure Yang body.
Eating you
will bring great benefits
to my cultivation and magic.
Even if your fellows come after me
one day,
I won't be afraid.
How much longer will this take?
Be patient.
Dance with me.
My miasma
is gradually
neutralizing her magic.
The magic vein will be opened soon.
Y-You're going to eat me?
Won't you make a soup?
Zhao Hengzhi!
Samadhi Fire?
Fire, come forth!
Subdue the demon!
Honey!
Dongqing,
are you alright?
I'm fine.
But I'm not.
Can the two of you get off
my back?
River Snail Demon,
I will execute you on the spot
so you can't harm the human world!
I object to it!
Why execute me?
Just because I'm a demon?
Humans have human rights.
Demons should have their rights too!
Demons have no rights!
You attempted to kill a night watchman.
I'm wronged!
I have something to say!
What's there to say?
I'm a night watchman. Samadhi Fire...
Hold on!
For what?
She should get to say her defense.
What defense?
She tried to kill me just now.
I'm telling you, her tongue was...
Ms. River Snail,
how are you wronged?
Please tell us.
Thank you, Dongqing.
You really are a nice person.
Tell your story already.
Most legends
are not consistent with the facts.
I am rather interested in it.
Ms. River Snail, tell us now.
Do you truly work hard
without asking for anything
in return as the legend says,
or have you been doing so
for an ulterior motive?
I'm a river snail after all.
What ill intentions could I possibly have?
Demons also stick to certain principles.
That farmer saved my life.
I should
repay his kindness.
It's how things work, right?
I married into his family
and became his wife
without asking for a dime.
His household had
more than a dozen people.
Seeing that I had magic
and the strength to labor,
they started lying about all day in bed,
leaving
all the farm work to me.
Though I was protected by magic powers,
I still felt exhausted every day.
Their entire family became lazy
exactly because
you worked too hard.
It wasn't just that.
Noticing
that I was a diligent wife
with magic powers,
the villagers got jealous
and often stirred up trouble with words.
The family were envious of Dong Yong
marrying the Seventh Fairy
and thus benefiting the entire household.
They were also envious of the man
marrying a crane fairy,
who could weave magnificent brocade
with her feathers
and finally made the whole family
wealthy landlords.
To add to that, they despised me
for my humble looks.
All those female demons and fairies
were enchanting
and gorgeous beauties.
Your looks are truly humble.
Why didn't they mind it
when I married the farmer?
Were they blind at that time?
They were too poor
to get their son a wife,
and I was just the last resort.
When I finally managed to improve
their financial situation,
they started to resent me.
Her family said
she can't
have children.
What good is all her capability then?
With that ugly face of hers,
she'll still be despised in the end.
Exactly.
You can't satisfy an insatiable appetite.
Given what happened,
why didn't you leave that family?
By then, I had just taken human form
and was really silly.
Since I married my husband,
I thought
I should treat
his family as my own
and dedicate
my whole life to them as his wife.
Although he resented me,
he never really let me go.
He and his family
racked their brains day and night,
considering how to get more money
out of me.
They had me
sell river snail soup
at the village entrance.
It was a small business,
but I managed to make some money
after a few years.
My husband's family
then built a new house
with the money I earned.
Well,
they treated you better
after that, right?
People have bigger desires
when they become better off.
All of a sudden, one day,
my parents-in-law told me
they would take a concubine
for my husband.
All was settled. They chose
a girl from a neighboring village.
"Settled"? No way.
My husband was clearly
having an affair with that woman.
I complained to him about my troubles,
yet he said
I couldn't help him carry on
the family line since I'm a demon.
Opposing to their plan
would make me a shrewish jealous wife,
for which he could divorce me
and make me go back to the river!
I never expected my husband
to be so heartless.
On that very night,
he divorced me.
I had no home to go to,
and I couldn't go back
to the river either.
Later,
I met some other men.
They were all the same.
Seeing me, a woman by her lonesome,
running a business,
they all wanted to take advantage of me.
They took me to bed
and went after my money then.
None of them were any good!
River Snail Demon,
are you done talking?
This moment will mark your end.
Samadhi Fire!
This lady seems
quite pitiful.
How could you
be so hard-hearted?
She nearly killed me!
But she failed, didn't she?
I don't have time
for your nonsense.
You're all pleading for mercy for her.
But is she really excusable?
She's truly in a pitiful state.
I...
Ms. River Snail,
you have my support.
Actually, you just met some terrible guys.
Exactly.
There's not a single good man out there.
Samadhi Fire!
Zhao Hengzhi!
You played dirty.
I don't care
if you're overflowing with sympathy
or grieving for your own kind.
For attempting to harm humans,
she deserved to be executed on the spot.
This is the duty of a night watchman.
She's still alive.
Cultivation is no easy task.
Let's set her free
in a river.
Maybe in a few hundred years,
we'll meet her again.
Go ahead if you want.
What a huge snail this is.
Are you going to hire
a truck to transport it?
Dongqing, come here.
M-My mind is a bit of a mess right now.
I'd like to confirm something with you.
Have I been eating more
take-out snail soup than anyone else?
There's an exit here, right?
Where is it?
I finally bought it.
The coffee in Coffee 444
tastes really good.
I must make a post about it.
Hello.
Welcome.
Are you Xia Dongqing?
You can eliminate demons, right?
Where is your partner?
You mean Zhao Hengzhi?
Zhao Hengzhi asked me
to meet him here at 3:00.
How can he be late?
Ms. Tang.
Mr. Zhao,
you are late.
I can't be late.
Your watch must be running fast.
I am Tang Lin.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Tang.
Ms. Tang,
you are so pretty.
In fact, I was even prettier in childhood.
Everyone said
I looked like a doll
when I was little.
You still look like one now.
Let's get down to business.
Last month,
my brother took in a stray dog.
A dog?
It is a white pug.
But I think
this dog is a demon,
as it has a pair of human eyes.