[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 9]
Kitty.
Kitty?
[Chapter 6: God of Fortune]
Zhao Hengzhi, what are you doing?
Why did you scare the cat away?
Why so anxious?
I was just playing around.
If you want to keep a cat, fine.
But why a crippled one?
What crippled cat?
That's...
I get it now.
Come on, have some soup.
I see you're still wearing it.
Glad you have a conscience.
Who would say no to a freebie?
It looks pretty cool.
What kind of soup is this?
Snail soup.
It's delicious.
It's so good.
I can tell you didn't make it.
In your dreams.
As if I'd make snail soup for you.
I bought it from a street stall.
Mostly because
the lady who runs it
is still quite attractive.
Are you still in touch with Ms. Huang?
We sometimes message each other.
Why ask so many questions?
Just drink your soup.
L-O-V-E.
Use Water of Love.
Become more beautiful with me.
Good. Highlight the product a bit more.
Let's do one more take.
Got it.
Good.
The reflector, please.
Check if she needs a touch-up.
Okay.
Director.
Water of Love has been online for 2 hours.
We've already sold over 100,000 orders.
Not bad.
Bath essence.
Use while taking a bath.
What's the point of this?
Yan Yuzhen's fans believe
that if they use this,
they will become
as beautiful as her.
Idiocy tax.
Fashion
is just about selling beauty and dreams.
What's that smell?
Is it the stench of smoke?
Doesn't seem like it.
I can't put my finger on it.
It smells like rotting meat.
Director.
Have you been too tired lately?
You need to wash your hair.
Are you...
Stop it.
I just didn't rest well.
Do you need me to help you relax?
Stop pestering me.
I'll be fine after sleeping.
Ya.
What's wrong?
Ya. Ya!
Wake up!
Your coffee.
Okay.
Come again next time.
I will, bye.
Xia Dongqing.
Come here.
What's a married person looking at?
Get me a cup of that
Convenience Store 444
paper cup coffee.
Iced.
I'll make it for you right away.
Young man.
What are you looking for?
Nothing. I just came back to take a look.
Four to five years ago,
it didn't look like this here.
what did it look like here?
It used to be a fried chicken shop
and a grocery store here.
Is this a cafe?
Yes,
Cafe 444.
I'll have a cup of coffee.
Come in.
I'll sit outside.
Okay, feel free.
Young man.
It's empty here.
You alone? Sit here.
They are short-handed here.
You're so young. Why are you sighing?
This street didn't use to look like this.
Now, everything is gone.
If you start
reminiscing now,
in a few years,
how sentimental will you become?
At my age,
you must think I'm
just feigning sorrow.
Actually...
I lost something here.
Something very important.
Lost something...
Is it your childhood?
No.
I lost a friend here.
She and I
met right here.
But,
you can find your friend again.
With social media
and online posting,
finding someone after 4 to 5 years
is pretty easy.
I'm afraid
she can't be found.
Thank you.
If you want,
you can tell us your story.
Talking about it
might make you feel better.
Five years ago,
she and I made a promise.
We were going to leave here together.
How old were you?
Were you running away from home?
Back then,
I already had no home.
If my mom kept me with her,
she wouldn't be able to get married.
She wanted to send me
to a relative's house.
She said
she would come back to see me.
I know
she'll have a new family
and new children.
One day,
she won't come to see me again.
Since you don't have a home either,
let's leave together, okay?
I've saved up all my past
New Year's allowance.
I won't let you starve.
Even if it's just the two of us,
we can still be a family.
It's a girl.
She must be very pretty.
Very pretty.
What's her name?
Her name is Lingling.
Speaking of this name,
I was the one who gave it to her.
Lingling.
I once gave her a bell.
She really liked it.
But
on the day we agreed to meet,
I stood her up.
Why?
That day,
I got into a car accident.
That car hit me
and ran over my leg.
But surprisingly, I wasn't hurt.
I just had a mild concussion
and stayed in the hospital
for observation for a few days.
Your leg was run over,
but it wasn't hurt?
Yes, it was like a miracle.
My leg was completely fine.
What happened after that
was also like a miracle.
Child!
Child, are you alright?
The person who hit me
is now my mother.
She was infertile
and never had children.
After knowing my situation,
she discussed it with my mother
and became my guardian.
She gave me a good education
and has always been very good to me.
You are really lucky then.
Yes, it's like
all the bad luck I've had since childhood
was swept away.
When I got out of the hospital,
I came back to find my friend.
But I never saw her again.
Not long after,
my current mother and I
moved out of this city.
So you came back this time
to find Lingling.
I probably won't be able to find her.
This street has changed so much.
That day,
she must have waited for me
for a long time.
She must think I lied to her.
After I finish this cup of coffee,
I'm leaving.
I'm going abroad tomorrow.
I might
never come back again.
Wait a moment.
What's wrong?
It's her.
Lingling.
Lingling?
Then,
the Lingling that young man mentioned
is you?
Since you don't have a home either,
let's go together, okay?
Lingling.
She is this street's...
God of Fortune.
I am no longer the God of Fortune.
Because
you gave all your luck to him.
It happened during that car accident.
Child!
Child, are you alright?
Hello.
I am at the intersection.
I hit a kid.
I need an ambulance right now.
Why are you okay?
You took his injury
and blessed him.
That young man originally
had extremely bad luck.
From then on, his life
went smoothly.
A hundred years ago,
my temple was right here.
Back then, I had great power.
Later, the temple was demolished,
and my magic got weaker and weaker.
This is all I can do.
I gave him my last blessing.
I wanted him to have a smooth
and peaceful life.
After that, I could no longer
give blessings
to anyone else.
Now, I am just
an ordinary little demon.
No wonder my business
hasn't improved despite you
constantly freeloading here.
I am sorry.
You were hurt.
That's why he couldn't find you
when he came back for you.
I hid myself at that time.
Didn't you and that boy
make a promise?
Who would want
a crippled cat?
He came back for you.
Throughout his smooth life,
he never forgot you.
You stayed here all this time,
waiting for him,
right?
Meet him.
Since you have an agreement,
give him a chance
and meet him.
Because if he leaves this time,
he may
never return in the future.
Boss.
I'm done with my coffee. Check, please.
No need.
This cup is on me.
This...
You're lucky. It's free today.
Thank you, boss.
I've always had good luck.
I'll be leaving then.
Lingling.
Is that you?
You must have suffered a lot.
It shares its good luck
with the human world.
We should give our tenderness back
to our silent companions.
After all,
who can be certain
if we are taming them
or being saved
by them?
Lingling.
I'm back.
I finally found you.
I'll take you home right now.
I'll never let you wander again,
okay?
A reunion after a long time.
In the future,
this boy will definitely give his blessing
to the God of Fortune.
He will protect it for a lifetime
and bring it happiness and health.
I'm a little touched.
Ya, why are you up?
You need to rest. Come here.
Where am I?
My home.
Your home?
How are you feeling right now?
Not so good.
Maybe I should go to the hospital.
There is no need.
When you were unconscious,
I already had a doctor check on you.
Ya,
you're pregnant.
I'm pregnant?