[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 15]
I had planned to take my time
toying with you two siblings.
But I didn't expect
you'd find a Taoist priest
to subdue me.
I waited nearly 100 years
before you finally came.
Tang Lin,
you look exactly like Tang Huan.
So beautiful,
just like a doll.
Darling,
give me a smile.
Brother!
Are you alright?
How dare you!
Ms. He, you lied to us!
And you have the nerve to question us?
You lied to me,
and I kicked your camera.
I just kicked it.
These past few days, I've been trying to
figure out how you got trapped there.
And finally, it hit me.
By using that lousy Western camera,
right?
What you'd always wanted
was Tang Huan.
This necklace
is yours, right?
You always wore it close to your heart.
Inside it
is a photo of Tang Huan.
You're right.
From the very first time I saw her,
when she walked into my photo studio...
She was so beautiful.
I never imagined
a living person
could look exactly
like a doll.
Oh, please, save it.
You just wanted to
take over Tang Huan's body.
You schemed
your way into
Tang Huan and Tang Yu's lives
and successfully moved into
their residence.
Then you wanted to use that Western camera
to transfer your soul
into Tang Huan's body
and possess her.
You carried her photograph with you
because she embodied
the version of yourself
you always dreamed of becoming.
Those dolls—
the dolls you loved so much—
are the evidence.
Now I just want to know
how you ended up
trapping yourself in there.
Something went wrong.
I was so close to succeeding.
I was so close.
I used every scheme imaginable
to win Tang Yu's love.
Then I moved into their residence
as his fiancée.
Every day, I watched Tang Huan,
and my desire
to possess her body
grew stronger and stronger.
When I was studying in England,
I learned of a witch
who could infuse magic
into a camera—
magic that could swap souls.
I immediately wrote
to a friend of mine in England,
wording the letter as subtly as I could.
He understood what I meant.
In his reply, he told me
the witch had been found.
He also sent me
a brand-new camera.
But to infuse it with magic,
it had to remain under the open sky
for three full moons.
He asked me to wait patiently.
Sister-in-law,
what are you doing?
Is this a new doll?
It's so adorable.
I'd soon have
a perfect body.
But while I was waiting for the camera,
I ran into a problem.
Tang Huan had a fiancé.
She would get married after the New Year.
But my camera hadn't arrived yet.
Her fiancé
would definitely get in my way.
I wished they would
break up immediately,
but their feelings for each other
only grew stronger.
I had to think of something.
I came up with a plan.
I drugged
Tang Huan's drink.
The drug would render her unconscious,
completely unaware
of everything around her.
Ms. He,
I love you.
Don't go.
Ms. He,
I love you.
Don't go.
I'm right here.
Tonight,
I won't leave you.
After such a scandal,
Tang Huan shut herself
in her room every day.
Not long afterward,
she called off her engagement.
And Tang Yu
shot himself.
Finally,
the camera infused with magic arrived.
Just like last time,
I drugged
Tang Huan's wine.
I was ecstatic.
I was so ready.
I thought
I was only moments away
from becoming Tang Huan.
The process itself was very simple.
All I had to do was press the shutter.
But that dog...
That Pekingese...
was just unbearable.
Hasn't Auntie treated you well?
Why are you always barking?
She had known all along.
She poured out the drink I gave her.
That wretched dog—
it was that wretched dog
that led her to my letters.
She found out everything—
my intentions toward her,
what I had done
to her siblings,
and my plan.
You deserve exactly this fate,
you wretch.
The scheme I carefully prepared
ultimately became
my harshest punishment.
You truly got what you deserved.
No.
We have to make her turn to ashes.
Zhao Hengzhi,
use your fire.
Demons and monsters, evil and wicked.
Fire, come!
When jealousy fuels the flames of desire
and a person's humanity is consumed,
his soul has already begun its countdown—
dissolving into smoke and ash.
Today is the first time
I've wanted a demon
to be utterly annihilated.
I don't even know
if I did the right thing.
I'm not a heavenly enforcer.
I have no right to pass judgment.
Ordinary people
should stay away from these things.
Dongqing...
♪ Listen to the rhythm of her heartbeat ♪
I'm no longer a Heavenly Maiden.
♪ Once more, I catch sight of
that familiar figure ♪
♪ After a lifetime of joys and sorrows ♪
I've turned into an ordinary woman.
♪ Still here, waiting for you as always ♪
Will you still love me?
We'll grow old side by side
♪ In this world,
some farewells go unanswered ♪
and rest together in the end.
♪ Some linger, while others move on ♪
I'm very happy.
♪ Across vast mountains and seas ♪
♪ One day ♪
Dongqing,
♪ We'll meet again ♪
I'm pregnant.
Yan Yuzhen?
Hello, my lovelies.
It's your Yuzhen.
Today
will be my last livestream.
Even though it's hard
to say goodbye,
that's life—
every reunion
is eventually followed by a parting.
I believe
that someday,
we'll
meet again.
Thank you all so much for your company
and support during this time.
Meeting you all...
has been the greatest fortune of my life.
Thank you.
And of course,
I've prepared
a special surprise gift for you:
one hundred thousand bottles
of Love Potion.
Order now,
free shipping.