[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 16]
Congratulations on reaching
Affection Level 1,000,000!
You have unlocked a new husband:
Yuhuang.
He's the first Stellar Awakener
of the Gate of Illusion,
[Limited Character: Yuhuang,
First Stellar Awakener]
the newest limited-edition character
to descend into the game world.
Those emerald-green eyes
resemble spectral green flames
burning deep within a glacier—
cold and aloof,
yet concealing a blazing, searing force.
So slow.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Are you ordering takeout again?
No.
My daughter,
you should cook for yourself
when you have time.
Takeout food isn't hygienic.
Haven't you seen
those whistleblower posts?
The places that prepare takeout food
are absolutely filthy—
rats running everywhere in the kitchen,
and they don't even wash the vegetables!
Mom, I really didn't order takeout.
I gotta go.
I have to reply to a WeChat message.
The filth is the least of your worries.
Did you see the news?
A delivery driver broke into the home
of a young woman living alone and robbed
and murdered her!
Mom,
what are you talking about?
Don't try to scare me like that.
I'm not trying to scare you!
It's a real case.
You keep ordering food late at night.
When they see a girl like you
living alone,
what if they get bad ideas?
I don't open the door.
I have them leave it at the door.
And you think that makes it safe?
Don't you have to open the door to get it?
I really need to reply
to a WeChat message.
Our director is messaging me.
All this talk... It's terrifying.
Who is it?
Delivery.
Leave it at the door.
I said leave it at the door!
Help!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Help! Help!
Let go! Let go!
Let me go!
I've had my eye on you for a long time.
I couldn't forget you
after seeing you once.
Tonight,
I must have you.
Let go of me, Yuhuang.
I can get up on my own.
What's wrong, my princess?
[Chapter 9: Love Game]
Was my acting not convincing enough?
This is boring.
I don't know
how to satisfy you,
my princess.
Stop calling me "princess."
It's so cringe!
I'm not a princess; I'm just a work slave!
You want me to call you
"work slave"?
You can fulfill any wish of mine?
Come on, lick my feet.
Gross!
My dear princess,
your Affection Level
has reached one million.
I must come to your side
and satisfy your every wish.
Your service period
is only two weeks as well?
Yes.
You know that very well.
After two weeks,
I will go serve another user
who reaches one million
in Affection Level.
Can't you stay by my side forever?
The program is set up that way.
There's nothing I can do.
You'll forget me by then?
My memories
will be wiped.
This is also to serve
the next princess.
Leave.
Are you dissatisfied with me?
Don't ask so many questions.
Aren't you supposed to satisfy
any wish of mine?
Fulfilling our princess's wishes
is our sacred duty.
Then my wish is that you leave my home
and never let me see you again!
Enjoy.
My flight is at two tomorrow.
Come see me off, will you?
I only want Yuanji.
I can't live without him.
It's already been half a year.
Why are you still...
Relationships take two people.
No matter how heartbroken you are,
it's meaningless.
Besides,
Yuanji is not even a real person.
This all began on a whim of Yan Yuzhen's.
She started all of this.
She just had to bring
those 2D fantasy husbands
into the real world.
Director,
can you help me
find Yan Yuzhen
and talk to her for me?
Since she can bring Yuanji
into the human world,
she can make Yuanji
fall in love with me again!
She's quit social media.
I haven't seen her
for a very long time.
Have you visited where she used to live?
The entire building was emptied out.
She just disappeared.
Forget it.
You can't spend your whole life
obsessing over
a fictional character, right?
He may be fictional,
but my love for him is real!
Besides, I spent a lot of money
on Yuanji.
A lot.
How much is "a lot"?
You didn't spend
all your salary, did you?
Oh, you!
You look smart,
but how can you be so naive?
Who even
pays to be in a relationship
these days?
You know what?
A lot of relationships nowadays
are built on spending money.
Stay out of this.
You've never even been in a relationship.
The reason I don't date
is for the other person's sake.
I need to preserve
my Pure Yang Sacred Body.
Besides,
love is just a false concept.
Living things reproduce.
Once they reach sexual maturity
and encounter a suitable mate,
their brains start producing
all kinds of chemicals—
like phenylethylamine,
the stimulant of love;
dopamine, making you lose your head;
and oxytocin,
triggering intense sexual urges.
If you ask what love is,
the answer is:
love is just a collection
of hormones designed to
ensure reproduction—
a farce.
Dongqing.
Let me give you a hand.
Just rest easy.
Don't tire yourself out.
I'm fine.
How is it?
Did the baby kick you today?
So many people are watching.
In short,
there is no such thing as love.
It's just a chemical reaction
in your brain.
Once serotonin levels stabilize,
even the most passionate feelings
fade into ordinary routine
and eventually disappear.
Understood?
Aren't you
a Taoist priest?
Or maybe a shaman?
Do you have some kind of magic
to get the one you love back?
Talismans or something?
What a waste of breath.
Welcome to the AI time-space
folding hub.
We'll locate the scattered fragments
of your interests across the timeline
and bring dimensional news
within your reach.
Where is Wang Fang?
She left
looking as if she'd lost her parents.
Can you not be so mean?
I'm simply stating facts.
What are you watching?
The first batch of characters
entering the real world
includes Gate of Illusion's
most popular hero,
Yuanji, Stellar Swordsman,
along with Karl, Void Prophet,
and the villain, Shadow King.
Yuanji?
The game Wang Fang is playing?
Wasn't he
by Yan Yuzhen's side at first?
These characters have not only integrated
into the real world
but have also retained their skills
and personalities.
They have even found
new career paths.
As Morris jokingly remarked,
"Don't worry—
I won't unleash a Shadow Storm
in the real world."
How did they do this?
Blue Blood Technology has launched
the Character Companionship Program.
Players can build connections
with characters
through a dedicated app
and invite them to participate in
everyday activities.
Blue Blood Technology?
Blue Blood Technology CEO
Situ Fei stated
that the dimensional fusion system
is not just a...
Dimensional fusion...
But also a...
What does that mean?
I don't quite understand.
I think our world
has lost its boundaries.
The advancement of technology
can be frightening sometimes.
Is technological advancement
the only scary thing?
Yuanji is so handsome!
He's so handsome!
I've been saving this one for ages!
Amazing!
This one's a limited edition!
He looks amazing!
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty; Su Wuming]
-Yuanji!
Yuanji!
Don't push! Don't push!
Excuse us, please!
Please let us through!
Hello, hello!
Excuse us, please!
Stop pushing. Stop pushing.
Excuse us.
Step back a little.
Yuanji is over there!
-Over there!
-He's there!
Yuanji! Yuanji!
Who is Yuanji?
He's more popular than me—
"No Name" Su Wuming?
Yuanji! Yuanji!
I'm Wang Fang!
Do you still remember me?
Stop pushing! Make way!
Stop pushing! Stop pushing!
I'm Wang Fang!
Come on, look here!
This is Love Potion from Yuanji
to everyone!
The Love Potion from Yuanji!
Why are you dressed like this?
I'm filming a drama.
You look pretty good
in this costume.
You're cold?
Hot milk tea.
Thank you for the milk tea.
Why are you filming a drama here too?
I also have to sing, dance,
perform on stage,
and be an idol.
Those are my new commands.
With those green eyes of yours,
you obviously
don't look like a real human.
And you're playing an ancient character?
I'm playing a demon.
That's quite fitting.
Do you have many fans now?
I'm just getting started,
so I don't have many fans.
This week,
I've only given out
10 bottles of Love Potion.
Love Potion?
You guys
have KPIs for that?
The commands I received
are:
gain more fans
and distribute Love Potion
as rewards.
Your costume is so thick.
Aren't you hot?
What is "hot"?
You're really not human.
You don't even know
what being hot feels like.
Yuanji isn't a real human either.
So?
Why do you like him
but not me?
I don't like you—
not because you're not real,
but because you're not Yuanji!
Does hearing that...
make you feel sad?
I don't know what sad is.
I wonder which of us
is crueler.
However...
I don't like Yuanji anymore.
I hate him.
"Hate"?
What is "hate"?
It's been over a week
since we last met.
You told me not to appear
in front of you,
so I didn't.
I know.
Two more days.
Two more days until what?
Until I forget you.
All the Affection Level you've grinded
will be in vain.
Would you like to renew your subscription?
I have no money left!
You spent an entire month
topping up for him until he became
the best-selling character.
I've spent all my money.
I used
Yuanji's last gold coins to summon you.
Why aren't you answering it?
What's wrong?
What kind of bird is this?
I've never seen one like it.
I wish I could be like this little bird,
completely free.
No one would know me anymore,
and no one would remember me.