The person that we are suspecting
to be dangerous and a deadly assasin,
which is La Fornarina, look!
She is with Mikoy!
It's an honor meeting
the infamous La Fornarina.
That's exactly what's so frustrating, Bok.
Shouldn't we just stay focused
on our mission?
But everyone has an opinion,
everyone has to be heard.
Valid.
Everything you said,
all your sentiments, are valid.
But, Bok,
just a piece of advice.
Don't think about everything at once.
Focus on the task at hand first, okay?
Otherwise, nothing gets done.
You'll get overwhelmed.
You won't be able to breathe.
You really won't be able to move, okay?
So let's just deal with what's manageable.
Like Mikoy.
The task at hand is we need to talk to him
as soon as possible. That's the priority.
I have an idea.
The minute that I find out
that you're gossiping to my father
or you tell anyone about my business,
mark my words,
You won't hear anything from me anymore.
I'm actually easy to deal with.
I want you here because I need a clone.
All calls and messages
from the original SIM
will transfer to the cloned device.
I can monitor everything remotely.
Whoever sends a text or call,
we'll know exactly who they are.
That phone will not be private anymore.
Sofie!
Hi, Luisa!
Hi!
I know you said before
he was kind of a loser.
But actually, he's kind of sweet.
I'm talking about Angelito.
Like, surprisingly.
- I know. Surprisingly.
- Yes.
Actually, you know what?
He invited me to go somewhere.
Like a concert or something.
Do you wanna come?
- Me?
- Yes.
Oh, wait, sorry.
I don't mean to put you on the spot
or make you feel like a third wheel.
Nothing like that.
No, no, no.
It's fine.
- Really?
- I'll bring my boyfriend.
Mikoy?
He's not answering.
What's taking him so long?
Chiara!
- Hello!
- Hi!
Hi!
You're alone? Where's Sianong?
I came so long. He's on his way.
We noticed Mikoy's been busy lately.
He hasn't been responding to our invites.
So we figured the drinks
should come to him instead.
Wow, that's so nice of you.
I don't know what got into him.
He suddenly missed work,
now he's buried in it.
Do you want to…
start without him for now?
Sure! Game!
- Come in.
- Okay!
He should be here soon too, right?
Yes.
Holy crap!
My God!
Hey, hey, hey!
Where are you going, brother?
What's going on?
I'm meeting Alex.
We're going to talk to Mikoy.
There it is.
Why do you look like that?
Is something wrong?
Not yet, but there's a complication.
- What is it?
- Wanna know?
What?
You!
You're one huge complication!
You're such a hassle. Move!
Will report to Chief
that the agents have no manners.
So how are things between you and Mikoy?
We're good. Great even!
Oh, that's good then!
How about you and Mikoy?
Oh, we're good. Same as always, buddies!
Alex.
Why do you ask?
Nothing. Like…
Oh, definitely.
That guy's practically an open book!
Sometimes it's even TMI.
Really?
So he's that open to you!
Oh, absolutely, everything.
Everything? Even his sex life?
Sex life?
I think he talks to Sianong
about stuff like that.
That's more guy talk.
But look,
I don't think Mikoy kisses and tells.
He's super protective.
Protective of you.
Wait.
Is there a problem?
Senator, it's getting harder
to run this agency.
Because the expenses keep growing.
Well, sometimes…
Change doesn't make you rich.
Because most of the time,
change is just loose coins.
Maybe the Greek philosopher Parmenides
didn't believe in change because
he had no spare change!
But Heraclitus had plenty of coins.
Because he believes
that change is constant.
Excuse me, Sen.
Excuse me, General Ruiz.
I'll step out for a bit.
I don't think I digested the "corn" I ate.
Because of all the corn"-y jokes.
Good thing that idiot caught on
and left too.
I was almost running out
of punchlines myself.
But actually, bro,
I really wanted to talk to you.
Just the two of us.
Because we've known each other
for a long time,
and our friendship runs deep.
You sound so serious.
I don't have a problem with him.
It's with his father.
Mario Pinagpala.
Honestly, my friend,
I felt so betrayed
that you kept this information from me.
I didn't want to add more charges
against the Moravianos.
But you're playing with fire, my friend.
You and I both know
what Mario is capable of.
Or should we call him by his real name?
Isidro Catacutan.
ISIDRO A. CATACUTAN
YOU WILL ALWAYS BE REMEMBERED
Did you and Mikoy have a problem?
Not that I'm fishing, but…
Woman to woman.
You can confide in me, Chiara.
Anything!
Thank you!
But no!
Nothing. We're okay.
Actually…
there is one thing
that I would say kind of bothers me.
But it's not a big deal.
You know Mikoy, right?
He's so kind, right?
Yes.
So…
He's too nice?
You get me?
Like he's too much of a gentleman.
What I'm trying to say is,
of course, we all want that at first,
- you know.
- Of course.
But that's the thing.
We're together now, and I'm here.
I've been waiting for so long.
Waiting? Hold on.
- What do you mean?
- The waiting part.
I get it though, because…
- He grew up in a conservative country.
- Yes.
And I'm liberated because, of course,
I'm European. I'm from Europe.
- Yes?
- But…
But still, it's 2026.
We're both of legal age.
I think it's about time
that our relationship
leveled up a little more.
More exciting!
More passion!
What do you mean?
You know what?
Let me just ask you something else, Alex.
Have you ever met
any of his ex-girlfriends?
I just wanna know because…
If they've ever mentioned
that he's really like that.
Like he's really that much of a gentleman.
So unbelievably nice.
What if he's actually waiting
until marriage, right?
Oh, girl, you know what?
None of his exes ever mentioned
anything like that.
- Okay.
- But sure, for you, I'll try to find out.
Really?
Yes!
- My gosh!
- I'll handle it.
Thank you, Alex!
Thank you. Oh my gosh! Whoa.
Oh, you know what?
If I wasn't straight,
I would've fallen for you already.
- I'm not kidding.
- Really?
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Finally, I'm so happy.
- Yes.
Sweetheart!
Good thing you're home already.
Because…
we have a surprise visitor.
Does he know his son is an asset?
‪Does Mario know?
No.
He doesn't know anything.
When he finds out, he'll get angry
because you used his son.
And second, you're putting
his family's lives at risk.
You won't be able to hide that from him.
Eventually, he'll find out
what happened to his son.
The past between you and Mario
runs deep and complicated.
And I know you want
to bury it in the past,
but you need to tell him the truth
about his son.
Because if not,
it might blow up in both our faces.
Because of his skill set,
I'm sure he can help you
with your Moraviano problem.
Mikoy's father has a specific skill set
that is actually very dangerous.
It's deadly.
If we bring him in,
he is a variable that we cannot control.
We can't even be sure
if he'll side with us.
I can see that!
Sweetheart, I missed you.
Well, Alex is here,
and she brought food
and drinks to surprise you.
Surprise indeed!
What are you doing here?
Did we have plans
that I didn't know about?
Oh, no, nothing!
Sianong and I just thought
we'd surprise you.
Because it's been a while
since our last night out, right?
Turns out I'm the one surprised
because Chiara's here and not you.
You didn't even mention
that she moved in with you.
And you know, the timing
of our surprise is perfect too
because we can celebrate
this milestone in your relationship!
- Yes!
- Right?
Wait a second.
Didn't you say you and Sianong
were surprising me?
Where is he?
He's on the way. You know him.
That guy's always running late.
You know what? Alex is right.
This really is a milestone
in our relationship.
You know, it's a good thing
you and Sianong are here
because I wouldn't have realized it. Yes!
That's a big milestone for us, sweetheart.
Oh my gosh!
I'm just happy for both of you!
Oh, wow!
Yes.
Well, eat now, sweetheart.
Okay.
Let me take this off first,
so you'll be more comfortable.
Yes.
Have you eaten yet?
You guys go ahead first.
I'll just put this in your room.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Hurry up, sweetheart.
- This is so fun!
I can monitor everything remotely.
Whoever sends a text or makes a call,
we'll know exactly who they are.
That phone will not be private anymore.
TRANSFERRING DATA
What are you doing, Chiara?
Why are you doing this
to the person you love?
TRANSFER COMPLETE
Is it done now?
I look stupid, you know.
My jaw already hurts.
Okay, safe.
But let's keep our voices down low.
Okay.
Not like that!
Then how?
- Low.
- Oh, okay.
Is this okay now?
Yes, you're doing well.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Is there an emergency?
That personal assistant
of yours is La Fornarina.
What?
Keep it down!
Chiara might hear you.
But what do you mean?
Carlota is La Fornarina?
Yes, it's really her.
She's been spotted the night
Vicek disappeared.
And we have reason to believe
that she's the one who killed him.
But why is she pretending
to be my secretary
if she's an assassin?
Do you think…
She is not here to be your assistant.
They sent Carlota to monitor you.
So starting now, that phone we gave you,
don't use it anymore.
How am I supposed to contact you?
We'll handle it. We will contact you.
We'll figure something out.
What?
I can't understand you anymore.
We'll figure something out.
Wait, that tickles. Do it again.
Come on now.
- Sweetheart!
- Oh my God!
We're, um…
We're thinking of playing a game!
Right?
- A game?
- Right?
Well, I'm in. What game is it?
Money or Whisper!
Oh, that must be Sianong!
There he is.
‪Yo, yo, yo!
No, just in time.
They're playing a game.
Money or Whisper?
He's too interested in logistics concerns
and the company's manpower.
But he wants all managers
to report directly to him.
Including very specific reports
about our drivers
and low-level manpower.
Like he's sensing something is off.
It's not just that, sir.
Look at this.
This car arrived at the same time
when I got to the café with Mikoy.
And when we left,
that same car also left.
Whoever was in that car,
they're Mikoy's handlers.
An asset.
They can't use a government vehicle.
They use a safer way, like what
the civilians and criminals always do.
Chiara must focus on her last mission.
If only you could see your daughter,
you will realize how much in love she is!
It's time for Mikoy to know the truth.
And you will realize
how dangerous this world is.
Spin the bottle?
That's truth or dare!
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Game.
- Ready.
I'll choose truth.
Do you like someone now?