That personal assistant of yours
is La Fornarina.
What?!
Hey!
What's going on?
They're playing a game!
Money or whisper?
Bro, that's so Y2K! Okay?
We need to play something new!
- Go on!
- Go!
What game do you suggest? Come on!
Oh?
Is that new?
Spin the bottle?
No, no, no, no, no!
That's truth or dare!
That's such a Jurassic-era game, Mikoy.
It still has the same mechanics!
You still spin the bottle!
Fine then, if you want something new.
Let's slap each other with pizza.
Whoever cries loses.
Enough. It's bad to play with food!
- Mikoy is such a killjoy.
- Come on!
You know, whenever you guys are together,
you always end up arguing.
Anyway, enough of that.
Let's play.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Game!
Game.
See?
Gotcha!
You talk too much.
All right, choose. Truth or dare?
Op, op, op! Real men always choose dare.
Fine, dare.
Nice, okay.
Spell your name using your butt.
Mikoy is so naughty!
- Seriously.
- Hey!
The one who's naughty is naked.
The one who's special--
Enough already.
Just do it, so we can move on.
You're wearing pants anyway.
Nothing scandalous about that.
- Come on.
- Exactly.
- Come on, Sianong.
- Ooh!
There.
What font?
Wow!
That's it!
Why is my name long?
It could've been Ced. Right?
This is my Mom's fault!
You even drag your Mom's name.
Fine, I want my revenge.
Game, game, game, game.
- Game, game.
- Okay, game.
There!
Wait, I'll be the one
giving the dare. Okay?
Because you boys might end up
asking for something crazy.
Aww!
Thank you, Chiara!
But I'm not choosing dare.
I'll choose truth.
Oh, really? Okay.
Well…
What's a good question?
Do you like someone right now?
Yes!
Yes?
Well…
Of course, yes!
I'm just a girl who can stand in the MRT
when it's packed.
No need for a knight in shining armor
to offer her a seat.
It's just that…
I hope someday…
someone will…
also love me…
unconditionally.
Police operations in this country
aren't really that sophisticated.
When they're in the middle of a mission,
whether it be surveillance or covert ops,
they can't use government vehicles.
The red plates would give them away.
That was beautiful.
Is that original?
So you're a romantic, Alex.
Yes, who do you like anyway?
You're suddenly quoting
all these romantic lines.
You suddenly became poetic, right?
Who is it? Come on. Tell us.
Come on. Spill it already.
Sy…
John.
John Sy.
John Sy?
Well… A chinito?
Don't you like a Korean?
All right, then.
Let's check him out on Fishbook.
John Sy…
Wait, is that Sy with an "I" or a "Y"?
Y!
Y, okay.
Oh, wow!
His profile isn't locked!
Confident because
he's got nothing to hide.
Doing it for the clout, yo!
Look.
- He even plays pickleball.
- Wow!
Very sporty!
I love it!
Okay.
John Sy.
Bok!
What are you doing?
What was that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's just go home. I'm already sleepy.
Bok, come on!
Seriously? John Sy?
Really?
Bok, I know you too well.
You're too lazy to even go online,
let alone play pickleball.
I know this John Sy guy
doesn't exist in your world.
Look, earlier,
Chiara asked you,
"Do you like someone, Alex?"
What was your answer?
I saw it clearly.
I saw it in your eyes,
your body language, everything!
You can deny it all you want,
but your eyes, Bok.
They're saying otherwise.
We've known each other for a long time.
We've worked together
in this agency for a long time.
I know when you're
telling the truth or not.
So if you're starting to fall for Mikoy…
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm just trying to be nice.
I care about Mikoy
the same way I care about you.
Like I said, right? I know you.
I know when you're lying or not.
Don't use me Bok, okay?
Do you think I'm blind?
That I wouldn't know
what you really feel for Mikoy?
You and I both know that Mikoy
is not just an asset to you anymore.
Okay?
Wake up, Bok.
Listen to me.
Don't allow yourself
to have anything with Mikoy.
To have any feelings for Mikoy.
Because it's not just your life
that's on the line here, Bok.
My life too.
Everyone sacrificing, everyone working
just for this mission.
Alex is something else, huh?
Can you believe that?
Turns out she likes chinito guys.
I thought she was into foreigners.
Well, maybe Filipinos too.
But Filipino guys with abs.
Probably someone like Piolo.
That would totally be her type.
Sweetheart? Are you okay?
You've been so quiet.
Feels like you don't love me anymore.
What are you talking about?
Why does it feel like
your mind is somewhere else?
It's not like that.
I've known Alex since…
I applied here in Manila,
before going to Prague.
Didn't I tell you about that at the bar?
Remember that?
So it's still pretty recent, huh?
I guess…
But it doesn't feel new like that.
You know, when I first
met her and Sianong,
it felt like we've known
each other forever.
You know like…
What's that called?
Twin flames?
Something like that.
Of course!
She's the best friend ever!
She's seriously so cool.
What? More than friends?
Of course not! No way!
We're not like that.
No.
What do you mean she likes me?
Chiara, wait. Where is this coming from?
Did I do something?
Come on. Tell me what it is.
- No, sweetheart.
- What?
Sweetheart.
Listen to me.
Okay, but you're scaring me.
I'm not mad.
Really?
I'm not jealous either.
I'm saying this
because I'm a woman too.
And as a woman,
I know how painful it is
when the man I like
doesn't feel the same way about me.
So I just want you to be very careful.
It gets wounded easily,
and it breaks easily, too.
Okay?
Okay.
You're just too cute!
I thought you were sick.
You were so quiet.
Help us build a case
against the Moravianos.
Because you're the only one
who can help us reveal the truth.
I kept my end of the bargain.
Now it's your turn, Mikoy.
Help me this time.
We need to train you, too.
Well, I know you missed me so much.
You're ridiculous.
A.k.a. Alex, so it's cooler.
He's so sweet and so fun to be with.
Really?
You're just messing with me.
Do you like someone right now?
Yes?
Sir, we already informed
our asset about La Fornarina.
You take initiative.
I like that.
Where's Alex?
Weren't the two of you
supposed to report together?
She's just not feeling well.
She already went home, sir.
She said she has a headache.
Maybe it's from using her phone too much?
Maybe she needs to manage her screen time.
Maybe she needs
to get checked at a hospital.
No need for that, sir.
She just needs some sleep.
Don't lie, Sianong.
Since our breakup,
Alex has never really been the same.
It's safe to say she still
hasn't moved on.
And I think it's called delayed grief.
I think it's called "delulu", sir.
Did you say something, Agent Sianong?
He said nothing, Officer.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
CURRENT ROLE: SENIOR SPECIAL AGENT
Is this your girl? This is your girl!
Or your ex?
She's just a police agent
hovering around Mikoy.
What?
Circling around him!
Oh, no. That's not allowed.
I'm telling Chiara.
Don't.
I'll take care of it myself.
Chiara must focus on her last mission
regarding the agency director.
You know, if you saw your daughter,
you would realize how much in love she is!
She's practically acting
like Mikoy's housewife already.
La Morte Bianca was right all along.
If Chiara doesn't want
to tell him the truth,
then I will personally tell him the truth.
It's time for Mikoy to know the truth.
Nothing but the whole truth about us.
What happened?
VERTEX
GLOBAL
I wonder what happened.
Why would they have to go to my house?
Kian.
Where's Alex?
Haven't seen her yet.
She only has ten minutes left
before I mark her late.
Know that I will include this in my report
because tardiness is next to evilness.
You know what?
Go ahead and list everything.
Noisy, standing, community service,
cleaners, list everything.
I don't care about you!
What I'm concerned about
is Alex, not you, okay?
So if you don't want to become a panda,
just stay quiet over there.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
What's happening?
Why are you yelling?
Sir, I'm sorry.
Alex still hasn't arrived
for our morning briefing.
But she's never late
for the morning briefing.
I know.
Sianong, check her apartment.
- Okay.
- Dara! Kian!
- Roger, sir.
- Go now.
- Roger.
- Copy, sir.
Bok?
Bok!
Is Carlota here because you want
somebody to watch over me?
Your Papa found out
that someone's following Mikoy.
We need to keep an eye on Mikoy.
Better yet, dear,
maybe this is the right time
to tell him the truth.