Is your friend really like that?
He acts like an Indian.
Think about it.
I prepared for this movie date,
then he will just ghost me.
Only his eyes will be left
without bruises!
You are ruining your relationship
with your daugther!
And you know what she's capable of doing!
La Morte Bianca wants Mikoy dead!
I'm indeed a lucky man.
I already have a stylist
and even a personal chef.
I'll go ahead.
Take care!
Bok, we've been sitting here
for a while now.
Are you sure about this?
-There she is.
-Let's go.
Are you scared of falling for her
or something?
I'm scared of dying, Bok.
Come on. A little flirting won't kill you.
It's not just
some harmless flirting, okay?
We both know her background, okay?
The moment I saw her earlier,
she already gave off
a suicide mission vibe.
What a waste.
You two seemed to have chemistry.
There she is, Bok.
Bok, someone got ahead of you.
She's meeting someone else.
Mikoy?
So, that's why he stood me up.
-Come on.
-Hey, bro, this suits you!
-What's that?
-Hey.
You're such an idiot.
Wait, why are we meeting here?
People might think
I'm dating my executive assistant.
A date? Really, sir?
Wow, that actually makes me blush.
Sir, come on. You're being so extra.
You act like you're some famous celebrity.
There are no paparazzi here, anyway.
And besides, you know what?
It's inspiring to work
in an aesthetic place.
Especially when the food is good!
Bok. Bok, do you see that?
Look at La Fornarina.
She's with Mikoy.
And look, they seem to know each other.
They are even dating!
The one Viktor assigned to him.
So you're telling me Mikoy's
new assistant is an assassin?
A killer?
What does that mean?
What we need to do is talk to Mikoy
as soon as possible.
Because this is the only thing
I'm sure of.
Black, of course.
Because my love is pure.
Please. Just admit it.
You like black coffee
because your taste is boring.
Wow, boring?
Wait, are you really my EA?
You sure talk a lot.
Sir, I'm just joking!
I'm just bantering with you, you know.
To build rapport.
Since I've been away
from the office for weeks,
I want to schedule
an alignment meeting with the team.
I want to know their progress
and status reports.
What they've accomplished
and what challenges they have.
And, of course,
what top-line concerns we need to address.
And make sure everyone
from each department is present.
I want to be updated on everything.
Even the smallest details.
Like manpower,
who's been coming in late,
and of course, our drivers.
The ones detouring our shipments.
Do you want to try it?
I don't drink anything
I can't afford to order.
Please, it's still coffee.
Just with a little matcha and milk.
Come on. Try it.
This is good.
Because once in a while,
you should be trying new things.
You know,
that actually makes sense.
Of course, that's my personal mantra.
Just keep trying.
You have nothing to lose anyway.
Come on. Let's go.
So does that mean Mikoy's
acting performance isn't working anymore?
He's starting to suspect Mikoy too.
Looks like his innocent
lover-boy era is over.
For me, we can't really blame Viktor.
His head of security in Prague.
Imagine, after all those years
they spent together,
I think, in Viktor's eyes,
all newcomers are possible threats.
Like Mikoy, for example.
He's still new to their family.
Maybe Vicek already betrayed Mikoy.
He already revealed
that he's one of our assets.
Do they also have three true loves?
Right?
That's so cool.
Cool. Seriously, octopuses are so cool.
-Wow!
-Right?
Which brings me to my point.
If Vicek really betrayed Mikoy,
then why is he still alive?
What does that octopus
have to do with your point?
There are only two reasons
why Mikoy is still alive.
First…
he's in love with Chiara.
Second, Mikoy is still alive because…
he's already a Moraviano.
I went shopping for you
because I missed you so much.
Chiara Valtrovi!
You clap, girl.
You clap too, girl.
You're really winning at life.
To think,
we raised you without knowing
how to do household chores.
Turns out it's actually really easy.
Because I am an empowered modern woman.
For now.
Because you and Mikoy
are still in the honeymoon phase.
You're still all sweet with each other.
But wait until weeks or months pass.
Especially if Mikoy snores.
Will you still be able to handle that?
Oh my gosh, best actress!
Girl, go o. Clap as well. There you go.
Clap louder for her.
You're really something else!
So fun!
So he can use her.
The easiest person to convince
is someone who is in love.
You know, Ma, I'm really loving it.
That I would actually enjoy
this domestic side of life.
And yet, nothing makes
me feel more at home than this.
No joke, I'm really proud.
That you're strong enough to fight
for what you want in life.
Wait a second.
Something suddenly came to me.
Memories of your father.
I suddenly remembered
our first night together.
Even though you didn't ask.
Here comes the flashback.
Oh my God.
Mama Mary, Saint Mary,
whoever's on duty right now.
Ma, you, really!
Every time there was a new movie,
he would even drag me out of my class
just to watch it.
I don't care about Star Wars.
That wasn't a thing in our province.
All I knew was FPJ's The Blacksmith.
Even after going to Europe and whatever.
Maybe Mikoy has something like that, too.
Come on. Tell me.
Does Mikoy have any secrets?
He doesn't have quirks.
He doesn't have obsessions or whatsoever.
Nothing.
Well, then there's no problem.
Mikoy…
I'm sure he has an opinion
about this situation.
What we need to do
is clearer than daylight.
I think he can shed some light on this.
And let's stop wasting time.
But Senator, we can't just do that.
If we are assuming
that he is already being watched,
we'll only compromise ourselves more.
Why don't we just call him there?
Sir, I think your suggestion is dangerous.
Because it might further expose
our operations against the Moravianos.
And that phone issued to Mikoy,
I think it's already compromised.
So all we do is think?
What are we supposed to do?
Just stare at each other and wait?
CHIARA
Sofie.
I'm sorry.
Here's what happened.
I even took a shortcut
so I wouldn't be late.
Then she had this paint stain
somewhere around, you know?
Her stress level was at 100.
And I couldn't just ignore it anymore.
So I went to her.
I became a wardrobe
emergency service that day.
Then she stopped me.
Of course, I said, "Yes, sure."
Sofie.
I don't know what you told her.
But thank you so much!
But…
I promise, Sofie, I'll make it up to you.
Aside from the fact
that I really owe you one,
I just want to say thank you!
Thank you so much, really!
Of course.
It's nothing.
Hello?
Ma'am, I checked your main box.
Your cable seems fine.
Here's what we'll do, ma'am.
If your internet is still weak
after a few hours,
just give me a call.
And I'll personally follow it up
with the office.
You don't have to pretend.
It's just me here.
I've heard a lot of stories about you.
You're a legend.
No one else is listening to us here?
Are you sure…
that you're the only eyes
and ears in this house?
Brusko.
Boom Labrusko.
That's why I called you.
Bok.
I feel like it's already compromised.
Mikoy is careful.
Looks like his instincts were right.
Because if Viktor ships now,
then he already knows
we've been monitoring him.
I just want to point out.
The Senator is right.
We need to talk to Mikoy
as soon as possible.
Are you okay?
It's just frustrating, Bok.
It feels like random people
keep becoming part of our mission.
They just keep bringing people
into the Agency.
First, there was Ben.
Now Senator Quintin
keeps showing up here, too.
Isn't his job supposed to be making laws?
Yup, you're right about that.
But to be fair,
they say the senator has never missed
any of their sessions.
Missing even one day a month
would already be rare for him.
And I don't think he has a personal life.
That's why he often comes here
to the office.
Has the love of your life
been compromised?
Cheating on you?
I wish he was just cheating.
What if he's already
reporting to the police?
It's not your job to give me
suggestions about what I should do.
Does he know that his son is an asset?
He has no idea.
When he finds out,
he will be angry because you use his son.
Good thing you're home!
What are you doing here?
Is there an emergency?
What?!
I am easy to talk with.