You know what this is?
That's right. Cash.
Wondering where it came from?
It fell right out of that wall.
A full thirty million.
I can't believe something this lucky
actually happened to me.
This has to be heaven's way
of rewarding me.
I never knew thirty million yuan
could be this much,
and this heavy.
But I was still hauling it around
with the biggest grin on my face.
From that moment on,
I finally got to live
the life I'd always dreamed of,
a life of pure luxury.
Feels great, doesn't it?
But just three days earlier,
I was nothing more than
a miserable rat
everyone wanted to crush.
=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 1=
Liar!
You scumbag!
You heartless piece of trash!
You're selling fakes!
You trash!
You punk!
Fraud! You're a fraud!
You think you can hide?
Not a chance!
I didn't spend years dancing
in the square for nothing!
Cut the crap!
Look at my face!
Just wait!
I'll smear thisall over your face!
Is this you?
Is this you or not?
Three strokes on the left,
three strokes on the right.
Remember, three each time.
one, two, three,
three strokes are all you need.
Listen...
Only 120 yuan
a bag.
One bag isn't enough.
Two bags.
No, make that four bags.
And I'll even throw in a free jar
of genuine hand-ground pearl powder.
It'll give you flawless skin
and turn you into
a real-life Snow White.
Look at this Snow White face of mine!
Do I still look like Snow White?
How should I face my husband?
This pearl powder
is like a lump of mud!
You brat!
Idiot!
Short-lived troublemaker!
If you don't compensate us,
we're calling the police!
The police will stand up for us!
Always first in line for meals,
always hiding when it's time to act.
No money,
but plenty of tricks.
It's you!
Is this you?
Is it you?
Is it you or not?
How could it make us flawless?
Look at my face! It's red as a tomato!
Let me handle this. Talk to me.
Yitong, go inside and check out.
She'll be responsible?
Alright. Listen to me.
Tenfold refund.
1,200 per person.
12,000 for ten people.
Any objections?
- Yes!
What about our faces?
That's right, we need medical exams too!
Facial allergies.
Why do you need medical exams?
I really don't get it.
Can you stop talking for a second?
Medical. Exams.
Medical exams.
That's 1,360 per person.
For ten people, that's 13,600.
Any objections?
- Yes!
We want medical checkups.
Or we'll call the police.
The police decides
who is responsible
for this.
You've trashed my shop,
you've beaten him up,
and you've messed these up.
When the police arrive,
we'll sort it all out.
Otherwise,
nobody leaves this place.
But we can pay you with
tenfold refund.
We mean it.
Okay?
Well...
Well then, let's not bother the police.
Just pay us already.
Then I want compensation too.
That backdrop wall of mine
cost 3,200 yuan!
Can you just shut up?
They said livestreaming was the future.
Someday,
it would be huge.
So I wanted to give it a try.
I thought Wenwen
would need tuition money too.
I just wanted
to help out.
I never expected...
Let me ask you.
How many people were in your channel?
Five?
Four.
Did anyone
buy your pearl powder?
I made one sale
to those people just now.
If your crappy pearl powder
can get me
even a power strip
I'll be impressed.
Look at the mess you've caused.
How much is it?
Yu Ming, how much?
25,672 yuan.
Do you think we have
that money lying around,
Yu Ming?
I'd rather kick you to death.
Stop following me!
What am I, a workhorse?
Am I your family's workhorse?
I've been busting my back
dragging this family
forward step by step.
You think it's easy?
Have I ever spent a dime on myself?
Look down.
Look at my shoes.
They cost only 58 yuan.
Look how worn out they are.
Look at them.
How can you not feel guilty?
Come on, don't be mad.
Get lost!
Just get lost!
(Luzhou city, Minnan)
Jia.
Yu Ming is driving me crazy.
I'm sick over it.
Slow down.
Hello, Ms. Pang.
Seriously,
Take it easy.
I'm falling apart.
Right now, on the ferry,
I'm honestly thinking
about throwing myself overboard.
No one can make me better.
Who could possibly make me better?
If I go to therapy,
doesn't that cost money too?
Right now, I don't even
have the money to see a therapist.
I'm depressed, Jia.
I don't think I'm ever getting better.
And today, Yu Ming cost me
another 26,000 yuan.
Where am I supposed to get that money?
I understand.
I know you're feeling
awful right now.
But all this
running around Yu Ming does,
deep down, he's
just trying to shoulder
his share of the responsibility.
He wants you to have a better life.
He wants to ease your burden.
His intentions are good.
How is he easing my burden?
I have to leave him.
Then I won't have any burden at all.
I can't take this for another minute.
I just want to leave him.
I can't live like this anymore.
As long as I'm not with him,
my life will be better no matter what.
Business has always
been outside his comfort zone.
Failure is normal.
You need to give him a little more room.
Give him a chance to make mistakes.
Right?
People who lack confidence
often struggle to
build a good life for themselves.
His brother's death
left him with deep emotional scars.
Since then, he's been distracted
and absent-minded.
Really, he just wants
to do more for this family.
Ever since college,
I've been pushing myself nonstop.
I kept telling myself,
as long as I do my job well,
put in more effort,
and work hard,
at least I wouldn't
end up worse off than everyone else.
But look at me now. What am I doing?
Sometimes I look down
at myself,
and I feel like
a beast walking in circles,
turning a millstone.
I'm 40 years old.
I have no money.
No career.
I can't even have
a child.
What am I doing with my life?
What do you mean "free time"?
You let this whole group
of seniors wander off,
and didn't round them up?
What if something happened?
But nothing did.
You photography club folks
really are something.
Impressive.
Besides,
if it's all free time,
why do they need a tour guide?
You're not guiding
and still want to get paid?
Fine.
Maybe you can brush off
one complaint,
but a whole tour group?
If they file a complaint
with the tourism bureau,
who's taking responsibility?
Mr. Song.
if I remember correctly,
last year there was a time
when you personally led a tour.
It was that
Ludao Island sightseeing tour.
As I recall,
you lost the whole group, didn't you?
If I hadn't stepped in
and helped you out,
how would you have handled that, huh?
(VIP Ms. Wang)
Ms. Wang.
My VIP client.
Sis!
Yitong!
Sis, what made you
call me today?
(VIP Ms. Wang)
This month,
I made over two million this month.
That's amazing!
Why do you always rub it in?
I almost
forgot my problems.
I'd forgotten I was broke.
Then you called,
and now I remember.
You're so annoying.
Making money is easy.
But I can't even spend it all.
Every day I'm out
with my girlfriends,
for good food and drinks.
If you can't spend it all,
give me a call, okay?
I'm happy to help.
Trust me, I'm great at that.
Bring your girlfriends
on a trip with me.
Deal.
We'll join your tour
early next month.
We'll keep you
at the top of the sales rankings.
I'd be lost without you, Sis.
Don't keep me waiting.
Thank you, thank you.
Where are you going?
Well, there's a customer complaint.
I need to go handle it.
Get back here.
It's none of your business.
Only two people left.
Don't distract Xinlu.
As for me,
I don't even have a boyfriend yet.
But once I learn
your photography skills,
maybe I can use these photos
to land a rich, handsome guy.
Can I see it again?
Come on.
Take a look.
See how good these are?
That's awesome.
Right?
It's smelly here.
I'm heading out.
Alright. Take care. Bye-bye.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Master.
Master, everything's done.
They even said
they’ll refer clients to us.
Well...
Don’t thank me.
You trained me.
You’re the best,
I’m just a junior.
We're on the same team, right?
(Old Witch)
Actually, I meant the Greentown project.
Add two more sections.
Include the ship rituals.
Make it clear to them
this is intangible cultural heritage.
It's worth seeing.
And add Minnan Opera as well.
Got it. Got it.
No problem.
(Old Witch)
I’m also planning to add
a traditional tea workshop.
From picking leaves to roasting.
Sure, go ahead.
I'll put it all together
and send it tonight.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye, Master.
Hello?
Did you just hang up on me?
How dare you?
Listen.
Today is Wenwen's birthday.
No matter what,
get back home right now.
And get things ready early.
What kind of stepmother are you?
What does she call you?
She always calls you "Amu."
"Amu" means mom,
you know that?
Hurry up.
You don't cook, you don't clean,
just out fooling around all day.
You really are...
Hello?
You hung up on me?
That country bumpkin.
No manners whatsoever.
You are driving me crazy.
Seriously.
There's still one person
moving around in the kitchen.
If you stopped moving,
I'd think you were already dead.
Every day at home,
you sit there like a sealed gourd,
without saying a single word.
But the second
you go out and dance
with those old women,
you're happy as can be.
Especially when there are
pretty ones around.
You can't wait to get close to them.
Wrapping your arms
around those tiny waists.
That's when you start smiling.
That's when you're happy, huh?
As for me,
I lost my job
because you were
fooling around outside.
Where are you going?
Scallions.
I already pulled them.
You stubborn old man.
(Wen)
(Mr. Wang, Zhenyue Jewelry)
Mr. Wang?
Um...
It's me, Yu Ming.
The distributor.
A few days ago,
I got a shipment from you.
Then the customers
used the products,
and all of them
ended up with faces so swollen
they looked like red lanterns.
Something's clearly wrong.
Could you see
if headquarters can
send me a replacement batch?
Thank you.
(Message recalled)
Mr. Wang,
are you messing with me?
It's Yu Ming.
Your distributor.
That shipment you sent me
left all my customers
looking like swollen pigs.
You and your headquarters
owe me an explanation.
(Mom)
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
♪A villa by the sea♪
♪Seafood every day♪
(Mom)
♪Fancy cars, pick what I want.♪
♪I want to get rich♪
♪Living like a dream♪
♪Everything will be mine♪
Who raises chickens like this?
The cages are hanging outside,
(No. 1 Compound)
and the place reeks of chicken waste.
And the flies!
I step outside and get hit by the smell.
Does it bother you when playing chess?
Of course!
If it weren't for that,
it'd be so nice
sitting here in the fresh air.
I know Wenwen
has her birthday today.
So I waited here for you.
Why?
Look.
Come here. Take a look.
Look at your chickens.
Your mother's chickens.
Whose mother?
Your mother-in-law.
Your mother-in-law, okay?
Your mother-in-law is raising chickens
right here.
The smell is unbearable.
Just look at all that chicken poop.
Take a look.
Also,
those chickens
crow all morning,
crow all evening,
and even in the middle of the night.
The noise has my heart
pounding nonstop.
It's driving me crazy.
And let’s be clear,
this isn't
Sun Lanying's private compound.
Why should she
get to do whatever she wants?
Exactly. This is outrageous.
Yitong,
your mother-in-law is unreasonable.
You need to talk to her.
You're educated.
Try to persuade her.
That's right.
People who went to college
have manners.
You should teach your mother-in-law.
If people don't have manners,
they're no better than animals.
What did you just say?
My Doudou
is way better than
rude people.
Exactly.
Okay, got it.
Doudou is a good boy.
Doudou is the best.
Hurry up.
Don't leave. Don't leave.
Look at this.
All this trash on the floor.
You need to clean it up.
You need to fix it.
My dog!
My baby, my baby!
My baby!
Get that chicken!
My baby! My baby!
My baby's so scared!
(Luzhou Yingsi School)
Hello.
The number you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please try again later.
Sorry...
Your dad isn't picking up.
It doesn't matter.
The choir teacher told you
to stand in the front today.
Why didn't you?
Why so many whys?
Big smile,
but all fake.
Like zombies.
What's the point?
(Luzhou Yingsi School)
Kid!
Let's go!
Your dad's got things to do.
Hold on.
I'm not ruining your date.
Look at you,
choosing girls over your own dad.
You should go. See you tomorrow.
Your dad's waiting.
Let him wait.
My mom told me
his business dinners are shady.
I'm helping him
get back on the right track.
Sorry. Sorry.
Dad's here.
Sorry I'm late.
Hello, Mr. Yu.
Thank you.
Bye, Mr. Yu.
Bye.
Wenwen, see you tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll treat you
to fried chicken sometime.
Mr. Yu, then don't forget.
I promise.
Fried chicken
isn't great for kids.
It's greasy junk food.
How much can a kid eat anyway?
Why not just eat a proper meal?
Buckle up.
Seatbelt.
It's a good day for our family!
Don't come here
and stir up trouble!
I'm not that easy to push around.
They're all awful people.
Alright, alright.
Sis,
we still need to celebrate
Wenwen's birthday.
Stop arguing.
You're always so tough
on Yu Ming,
but look at you now.
Getting pushed around like this.
Even the cake got ruined.
I think you did it on purpose.
How about this,
find her another stepmother.
I don't care.
Alright, alright, enough.
Yitong,
why aren't Yu Ming and Wenwen
back yet?
Call them
and rush the cake.
It's not a birthday if there is no
cake and birthday wishes.
I called. It's downstairs.
I make a wish every year.
It never comes true anyway.
That's exactly what I like
about Wenwen.
She doesn't sweat the small stuff.
A kid raised by Yu Ming and Yitong
is bound to
be unique.
That's right. Exactly.
Wenwen,
next year
we're planning to move
into a bigger place.
When your birthday comes around,
come celebrate at our house, okay?
No, thanks.
Wenwen has celebrated
every birthday here
since she was born.
Yu Ming,
warm up some wine for me.
At my age, I can't
drink it cold anymore.
Yitong,
does your travel agency
have any family route
for the New Year?
Where would you go?
Europe, probably.
Zihan's growing up.
Weijie said
he wants to take him around
to see more of the world.
Take our boy to Iceland
see the Blue Lagoon,
the Golden Circle,
the black sand beaches,
and maybe see whales.
Okay?
We don't really have that route.
But if you're going to Northern Europe,
you might as well do all five countries.
And if you like it,
you could settle there.
Right?
Sounds great.
Then forget
travel agencies.
We'll do it ourselves.
Sure.
Yitong.
Let's go together then.
We'll see.
It depends on the timing.
Wenwen will probably
be in her tutoring classes.
Maybe next time.
It's hot!
Careful!
And when exactly is "next time"?
Yu Ming,
Wenwen's grown up now.
She remembers
everything you say.
If you can't keep your promise,
she'll be heartbroken.
Right, Wenwen?
That Kui guy... what's his name?
Hong Jinkui.
Right. That fat man.
He owes you a fortune.
Over 200,000 yuan, isn't it?
If you could collect
that money back,
you could take Wenwen
on a nice trip too.
I-I'm trying to find him.
Yu Ming.
You're not a kid anymore.
Act like a responsible adult.
Stop jumping from one thing to another
all over the place.
You're almost forty.
And your pockets
are emptier than your face is.
How is that okay?
What about your parents?
What about Wenwen's education?
I heard you two are even thinking
about having another child.
Honey,
your wine is warmed up.
Drink it.
Stop talking. Stop talking.
Ming,
Listen to me.
You’ve got to be steady
in your life.
Nobody becomes fat from a single bite.
You have to take it step by step.
Move forward steadily.
Look at our young couple.
They both work at the bank,
holding solid jobs.
They've got a decent standing
in society now.
And you're satisfied with that?
That's not enough.
You've got to move up.
Higher and higher.
You motherless fool.
Your mother is my mother.
And my mother is your mother.
I'm done eating.
All this food
can't keep you quiet?
Hello, delivery.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks.
Mom, I'll get it.
I've got it.
Wenwen,
the cake is here.
Come on. Be a good girl and come out.
Everyone's going to sing
Happy Birthday to you.
Then we'll cut the cake,
blow out the candles, and make a wish.
Come on, sweetheart.
Wenwen?
The older the kids,
the worse their temper.
This whole family...
The elders don't act like elders,
and the kids don't act like kids.
We came here
to celebrate her birthday,
and now what?
They're giving us attitude
for no reason.
Who raised them like this?
Exactly.
If Zihan ever acted like that,
Weijie would've...
That's enough!
Of course your son is amazing.
Your son is amazing.
Collecting subsidies,
collecting benefits,
and knowing how to butter people up.
Let me tell you.
If Yu Feng were still alive,
none of you would matter.
Lanying,
that's not fair.
That's just not right.
Yu Feng, Yu Feng, Yu Feng.
You know where he is.
He's in the photo frame now.
You know that, right?
What are you even talking about?
I'll say whatever I want.
I’ll say it anyway.
Enough!
That's enough.
Every single family gathering
ends the same way.
Don't get too discouraged.
When can we have a baby?
Today,
I was late because
I went to buy you a pair of shoes.
Try them on.
I'm asking you, Yu Ming.
When can we have a baby?
Any time.
We're in charge of our own lives.
Fine.
But preferably next year.
No later than the year after.
You need to make up for your brother.
I didn't say anything.
And I've been doing this
with you, right?
Wenwen is your brother's daughter.
When we took
Wenwen in,
we gave her the best food,
the best clothes, everything.
I never complained, did I?
About her private school,
I told you
it wasn't necessary.
But you insisted.
120,000 a year.
I gritted my teeth and paid for it.
I never said a word.
Right?
Your mother calls me a stepmother.
Says I'm evil.
She even wrote names
on eggs so I couldn't eat them.
(Wen)
Who’s evil here?
How can they treat me like this?
I'm really at my limit, Yu Ming.
You can understand that, can't you?
Your mother made you kneel and swear
not to have a child
before Wenwen started kindergarten.
And I agreed.
Then she said after elementary school.
I said fine.
After elementary school,
she said middle school.
Three more years.
Then high school.
Then college.
How old am I, Yu Ming?
Do I really need to remind you?
I'm 36.
If I wait any longer,
I may never have a child.
I just want to ask you.
When will this be an end
for your family?
When will you
finally get past
your brother's death?
When will I get to live
a normal life?
Just give me a date.
I'm sorry.
I really want
a child of our own.
For years now,
you ask me
the same question almost every week.
and it always turns into a fight.
I understand.
I’ve been avoiding it.
But today, I want to say...
I really don't know. I...
You're tired.
Mom's tired.
Dad's tired.
It's all my fault.
Maybe I really am a jinx.
If you're really tired…
maybe we should separate.
Let me try the shoes on.
Finally, you bought shoes that fit.
Comfortable?
Tomorrow morning at ten.
What for?
Civil Affairs Bureau, divorce papers.
Why?
What's wrong with you, Yu Ming?
Have you lost your mind?
Bring your ID.
I just want to ask you something.
When will you
finally get past
your brother's death?
When will I get to live
a normal life?
Just give me a date.
Watch out!
Brother.
Wake up.
Sister-in-law.
I'm sorry, mom.
It's all because of me.
I killed my brother
and sister-in-law.
I'll raise Wenwen
as if she were
my own daughter.
Are you looking for mom?
Is that it?
Do you want mom?
Here, hold it.
Come here.
It's okay.
She just keeps crying.
Mommy's here.
It's okay. Don't be scared.
It's okay, it's okay.
Stop crying now.
Give me that.
Try to cheer her up.
Okay.
Come on.
Look.
Take a sip.
Come on. Drink some.
Go on, make her laugh.
Look at dad.
Look at daddy.
Whose milk is daddy drinking?
Look.
Who is this?
♪I♪
♪Once went up to the heavens♪
♪I battled 100,000 heavenly soldiers♪
♪The Queen Mother washed my feet♪
♪The Jade Emperor carried my tray♪
♪Buddha tricked me into a wager♪
♪Pinned me beneath Five Fingers Mountain♪
♪I suffered for 500 years♪
(Wenming Souvenir Shop)
♪You said, don't rush♪
♪Take life one day at a time♪
♪That cup of tea on the table♪
♪Has sat there cold for two days♪
♪Nothing much has happened♪
♪Nothing earth-shattering at all♪
♪Half the words we meant to say♪
♪Were lost beneath a sigh♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Then we'll be on our way♪
♪If the umbrella's downstairs♪
♪We'll just get a little wet♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Instead of worrying so much♪
♪Maybe this time♪
♪We might finally learn to let go♪
Didn't I pay for the car and house?
You bought them? You spineless loser.
You make 3,000 a month,
how can you afford that?
You've got to be kidding.
That 3,000 yuan
was money I earned honestly.
Don't go.
Number 5014,
please proceed to Window 19.
Have some breakfast
and milk.
Number 5017,
please proceed to Window 12.
(Civil Affairs Bureau Service Hall Window 12
Now No. 5017)
I'm already calm enough.
Why do I need a cooling-off period?
How am I not calm?
Tell me.
I came here calmly.
And later,
I'll leave calmly too.
He's calm too.
We're both calm.
Just hurry it up.
According to Article 1077
of the Civil Code,
once we receive
your divorce application,
we will issue
an acceptance receipt.
Starting today, there will be
a 30-day cooling-off period.
During this time,
either of you may
withdraw the application.
After 30 days,
if both of you still wish to proceed,
you must both come here in person.
If you're not here by then,
it will also be deemed withdrawn.
I need to calm down?
Thirty days will kill me.
It'll drive me crazy.
I'll suffocate myself.
I'll just suffocate.
I'm sorry.
But this is
the legal procedure.
I can't help.
What if there's
domestic violence during the 30 days?
What would happen
in a month?
She didn't abuse me.
Each case is handled individually.
According to regulations,
a cooling-off period is required.
You can file a lawsuit.
Lawsuits don't require that.
Then I’ll sue you.
I didn't commit any crime.
So it can't be done today, right?
It can't.
This process
is really quite merciful.
I like it.
♪Unfulfilled vows♪
♪Unfinished love♪
♪One wrong move♪
♪And all is lost♪
Which one do you want?
♪No road ahead♪
Are you waiting for a fish to die?
♪Flames rise in the courtyard♪
♪Longing remains♪
♪Yet we're torn apart by fate♪
♪When fortune fades♪
♪The world shows its true face♪
♪Some will always♪
♪Put you down♪
♪Wealth may be lost♪
♪Yet troubles remain♪
♪The roof leaks in rain♪
♪The storm still comes♪
What's wrong with that car?
Yeah.
Seems someone's inside.
Hold on. I'm recording this.
The engine's off.
I'm not moving.
Back up.
Move back.
Nice!
Come on. Give me your hand.
Don't be scared.
Come on. Take it slow.
We're getting out now.
Don't be scared.
The kid's out! The kid's out!
Take care of the kid!
Where are your parents?
Who parked this car?
Man.
Are you self-driving?
Little Rice Cake!
Daddy's here! Daddy's here!
Is this your child?
Daddy's here. It's okay now.
It's okay.
You've got some nerve.
Is this really your daughter?
You left a little girl
alone in a car?
I was there...
Whose car is it?
Are you okay?
Daddy's here. It's okay now.
You did a good thing saving the child.
But you should've pulled the handbrake.
I was in a hurry to save her.
There was smoke everywhere.
So...
I know you were helping,
but rules are rules.
You're fully liable for the accident.
Aren't you the parent
of my son's classmate?
Am I?
Yes.
You picked up your daughter late
and promised my son fried chicken.
That greasy junk food.
Officer!
Someone's hitting me!
What are you doing?
Come here!
Come on!
Thank you, officer.
Hong Jinkui?
(Twenty minutes earlier)
Yes, of course.
Developing AI
is the global trend today.
Hello, Susie.
Right now,
the global situation is unstable,
the economy is slowing down,
populations are aging, and so on.
These are all problems.
That's why
smart elderly care
is the next
big thing.
In the U.S.,
it's already no secret.
Exactly.
Everyone who is alive
and breathing
is a potential customer.
I've even got the slogan ready.
Smart Elderly Care:
arrive easily,
leave happily.
Old Ba and Little Ma.
Yes, those two guys.
The rocket guy.
He doesn't do rockets anymore.
He's already shifted his focus
to smart elderly care with me.
So I'm telling you,
this is a big opportunity.
This is the future.
You get it?
Hong Jinkui.
This is a prohibited weapon.
Put it away.
Bro,
investing itself
carries risks.
Actually, the information I got
was from other people.
Mostly from my relative in Hong Kong, China.
Speaking of my relative,
you guys probably know him.
What relative?
What's my surname?
Hong.
Think about the entertainment industry.
My surname Hong.
Look at my build. Think about it.
Hong...
Keep it down.
Don't tell anyone.
Wait,
aren't you from the northeast?
Well,
my ancestral roots are in Hong Kong, China.
My grandfather migrated to the north.
If it wasn't him,
I'd still be
a Hong Kong, China resident.
Let's forget who's right or wrong.
And remember the old days.
Those hard times
were full of good memories.
We never gave up hope.
We never felt worn down.
Let's drink together.
When did Hong Kong, China people move north?
See you then.
Get him!
Come on!
How dare you?
Stop right there!
Stand still!
Stop!
You did a good thing saving the child.
But you should've pulled the handbrake.
Officer!
Someone's hitting me!
What are you doing?
Come here!
Thank you, officer.
Hong Jinkui!
Where are you going?
We're not done yet.
Is he running away or playing hero again?
Officer,
is it a hit-and-run?
What a good day!
A creditors' convention?
Hello, Susie.
Where's my bike?
Hurry and lock it,
or they'll dock my pay.
Give me back
my 200,000.
I'm telling you,
I've been waiting
for this day.
Today,
there's no way you're getting away.
I'm out of breath.
I don't care.
Even if your liver falls out,
Sir,
one iced sugarcane juice.
Make that two.
I want mine with no ice.
Give me my money.
Listen to me, Ming.
Let me get up first.
There are people all around.
Things get exaggerated so easily online.
If someone films this
and posts it online,
it won't be good for you.
I've done nothing wrong.
Let them film it. Let them post it.
Let me try this.
This one's no ice.
Get up.
Come with me to the bank
and give me my 200,000,
or...
I'm taking you to the police station.
No.
Why go to the police station?
Why trouble the officers
with things like this?
How about this, Ming?
Will you trust me just one more time?
No.
I...
I'll take you somewhere special.
I'm not going.
Yu Ming, why are you
so stubborn?
Fine.
Twelve years ago,
you wanted to be a singer.
You asked me to help you
put out an album.
And yes,
I gave your 200,000 yuan
to someone else.
They failed,
so you can't
come after me alone.
No.
Well...
Yu Ming.
Seriously.
Just trust me one last time.
One last time.
I'll show you something worth 6 million.
Come take a look.
After that, you can decide.
If it doesn't work
take me to the police then.
Deal?
(Next Episode)
(Guo Jingfei)
Hi, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
(Guo Jingfei)
This is the best villa community
around here.
One million.
Give me a chance
to make it up to you.
Congratulations, Xinlu!
The Greentown project.
You know how much work
I put into that project.
She can just snatch it so casually,
and feel fine?
Hello?
I need a loan.
What's your collateral?
My apartment.
You pledge the property deed. I transfer the money.
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪