=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 2=
Ming.
This is the best villa community
around here.
Two stories above ground,
plus a basement.
The basement is 5.6-meter high.
you could split it into another floor.
See that?
That huge garden.
Over 100 square meters.
Grow some flowers, veggies,
chickens, ducks,
or even a dinosaur.
Nobody would care.
Let's go inside.
Take it slow.
The previous owner
moved out quite a while ago.
It's left unattended.
But just take a look at the layout.
The high ceilings.
Ming, I don't have to tell you.
You've got a phone.
Look it up online.
The houses for sale in this community
are listed online.
Take a look.
6.2 million.
Bigger units go for 6.8.
I'm not making this up, right?
Once you get it, make it your own.
Clear out the clutter.
It's perfect for your family.
Let me show you the layout.
Here are two kitchens,
Chinese and Western.
plus a huge island.
That door leads to the maid's room
and laundry room.
This door is the guest bathroom.
Come on, I'll show you the second floor.
See this? Right in front of the door
is the garage.
Private parking.
This door is to the outside.
In the summer, you,
your wife, and your kid,
plus a few friends, can have a barbecue.
Second floor has three bedrooms.
One for you and your wife,
one for your kid,
and one for your mom,
Ming,
back then,
I did let you down.
But I haven't forgotten.
I keep it all in my heart.
I've always thought
that one day, when I can,
if fate brought us
back together,
I'll make it right.
I'll return that 200K to you
to make up for
our broken friendship.
♪Our flag flies high in the wind♪
♪Our songs of victory ring loud and clear♪
♪We sing for our beloved homeland♪
♪Marching toward prosperity and glory♪
That's all
for this morning.
Feel free to take some photos.
You have two hours of free time.
Explore on your own.
Straight down this road,
at the second intersection,
there's a store called Wenming.
Check in there, take some photos,
post them online,
and get 20% off everything.
Off you go.
We'll meet back here in two hours.
Stay safe, guys.
Take care.
And don't buy the pearl powder
from this shop.
It's not very good.
Hello?
We paid it already.
We paid it two months ago.
Yes, my husband handled it.
Only liability coverage?
No way.
It should be full coverage.
How much?
This is an S-Class Maybach.
The "S" stands for special class.
The car itself costs
millions.
A routine service runs around 10K.
This headlight alone
costs about 150K.
And over here,
there's the paint damage
the door,
the bumper.
All together,
it's going to be over 300K.
Replacement parts
have to be imported.
We're verifying
the final amount.
We also checked with
your insurance company.
Take a look.
Your policy only
offers mandatory liability coverage.
So in this case,
vehicle damage
won't be covered.
Okay... I understand.
So today,
for a house this good,
it needs only this much.
How much?
One million.
Ming,
give me a chance
to make it up to you.
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
You hit someone's car?
Yeah.
Today,
there was a kid
trapped in a car.
The car was smoking,
so I ran over to help,
but I forgot to set the parking brake.
The car rolled,
and hit a car's headlight.
Do you know what car it was?
No idea.
Some random brand, I guess.
Ever heard of a Maybach?
A what?
A Maybach.
Maybach. Not a McFlurry.
An S-Class Maybach.
Worth several million.
A single service costs 10K.
One headlight is 150K.
You scraped up the door,
the paint, the bumper.
Altogether, you're paying over 300K.
Over 300K, Yu Ming!
One headlight costs 300K?
That's a scam!
Call the police!
You hit the car, man.
If you call the cops, they'll arrest you.
You know that?
Didn't I give you 3,000?
You did.
I gave you 3,000 yuan
to pay the insurance.
What did you do with it?
Insurance costs a little over 2K.
You could've kept the rest.
So why?
I'm asking you.
I... I bought inventory.
What inventory?
Fridge magnets or pearl powder?
Pearl powder.
Go to hell, Yu Ming!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thought it over, Ming?
I'm not forcing you.
If you've decided,
one phone call
and the deed and contract will be here.
Just sign and
fingerprint it,
then this house will be yours.
This house's worth six million,
but you charge me one million
That means
there's a five-million difference.
In that five million,
there are a lot of 200Ks.
Jinkui,
I owe you an apology.
All these years,
I thought you were a con man.
I'm sorry.
Jinkui.
I was wrong.
I'd love to pay you 6 million.
I don't want to take advantage of you.
But I just don't have it.
I can't even scrape together 1 million.
Ming,
that's because you're my friend.
How about this.
if you can't come up with a million,
make it 800K.
That's my final offer.
Jinkui,
I'll do whatever it takes
to get that 800K.
You're my friend for life.
Hong Jinkui,
even if it turns out to be a scam,
I'm taking the chance.
(Jiari International Travel Agency)
(Outstanding Employees)
Come on, where's the crown?
Here.
Give it to me.
Try this one on.
No, not this one.
This one looks good.
Yeah, this is better.
Let's take a photo with the top sales.
I'll do it.
Three, two, one.
Say cheese!
(Song Youcheng)
Hello?
Why aren't you at the office?
I was out handling some things.
You always have so much going on.
Are you done yet?
Almost done.
Hurry back to the office.
Celebration party.
Celebrating what?
The Greentown project.
Xinlu closed the deal.
You know
how much work
I put into that project.
These past few months,
I was there every single day.
I treated clients to meals,
I chased them down,
attended countless
pointless meetings.
I revised the proposal
how many times, fifty?
Fifty times, didn't I?
Employees' and bosses' feedback.
I revised a million times.
I didn't say a word.
From start to finish,
I only took two days off.
Just two days.
And I did all that work,
so why...
she can just snatch it so casually,
and feel fine?
Is that right?
This is our biggest contract this year.
Shouldn't it be finalized quickly?
It wasn't easy for them to choose us.
The contract's signed.
Isn't that all that matters?
Who signs it...is that important?
It's not important who signs it, right?
So all my hard work was for nothing?
Song,
I've worked my tail off for you
all these years.
You could've given me
a heads-up.
You could've told me.
What am I supposed to make of this?
Look, the contract is already signed.
Who can change that?
What can I do?
You're a senior employee.
You should show some magnanimity.
Didn't you say before?
If you want a good life,
you have to be shameless.
You have to speak up and take action.
I'll slap myself, okay?
I was wrong.
Let me take that back, okay?
Congratulations, Xinlu!
Thank you.
Congratulations!
Three, two, one!
(Top Sales. May Liu Xinlu
win deals every day)
I want that piece!
That one!
Plate!
Don't rush.
Quick!
Thank you!
First piece!
This is amazing!
Come on.
Looks good.
Come on, let's...
Master.
Please let me explain.
You don't have to.
Young and talented,
I'm happy for you.
I know you're angry,
You think I stole your deal.
But the company was
in a hurry, and so was I.
I just wanted to help the company
secure the contract quickly.
Master,
please don't be mad.
I know I was wrong.
How about I kneel for you?
Go ahead.
You won't, right?
The performance isn't convincing.
Well then...
If you don't want the cake,
I'll take it in to Mr. Song.
You're blocking my way.
Don't worry.
I can't block your way.
How come...
Mr. Song,
I'm coming in.
Stop staring.
(Top Sales)
You never focus on work this much.
Eat the cake.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
Come upstairs, come on.
I'm not going up.
I just came to see you.
Here, take this.
Dad, don't.
Just take it.
No.
Come on, you have to take it.
Take it.
Yitong,
Yu Ming's had
a rough few years.
He's been trying
every way he can to prove
he can be as capable as his brother.
But mistakes just keep piling up.
Still, deep down,
he's a good person.
he was trying to
prove something to us,
But now, from what I can see,
he's doing everything he can
to prove himself to you.
I know you two are planning to separate.
From your perspective,
I shouldn't say anything.
But Yu Ming
ended up like this today
because I wasn't there for him enough.
It's okay, dad.
Come on, let's go upstairs.
I'm not going.
I'll head home.
Come upstairs and sit for a while.
No, no.
I'll go.
Alright.
(No. 1 Compound)
Listen,
you have no idea
how huge that fire was.
He rushed straight in
to save that kid.
Honestly,
I think the city government
should give our family an award.
He saved a life.
Right?
So who should be paying for the damages?
Surely not
the person who got rescued,
nor the one
who did the rescuing.
Otherwise,
doing a good deed
would only bring trouble.
It's like a fool washing mud.
The more you wash it,
the dirtier it gets.
So anyway,
I think
we...
Where are you going?
Home.
What?
This is your home.
Where are you going?
My study materials are at home.
I need them tomorrow.
I'll take you home.
No need.
Call me when you get there.
I know.
My granddaughter
loves studying more than anything.
Her teachers say
she's a exceptionally hardworking
model student.
Honestly,
it makes me so proud.
♪You said, don't rush♪
♪Take life one day at a time♪
♪That cup of tea on the table♪
♪Has sat there cold for two days♪
♪Nothing much has happened♪
♪Nothing earth-shattering at all♪
♪Half the words we meant to say♪
♪Were lost beneath a sigh♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Then we'll be on our way♪
♪If the umbrella's downstairs♪
♪We'll just get a little wet♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Instead of worrying so much♪
♪Maybe this time♪
Hello, welcome.
♪We might finally learn to let go♪
Why are you back?
Grandma's scolding again.
Calling dad a fool washing mud.
Stop picking up your grandma's habits.
Don't use it like a knife
all the time.
♪The clock has stopped ticking♪
♪The light has started to fade♪
♪The dripping pipes♪
You two aren't splitting up.
♪Keep the beat of a sleepless night♪
♪I pull out an old shirt♪
♪Its creases make me smile♪
♪Even if I stay inside today♪
♪The world will keep turning just fine♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Then we'll be on our way♪
♪If the umbrella's downstairs♪
♪We'll just get a little wet♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
Put it on top of this.
♪Instead of worrying so much♪
♪Maybe this time♪
♪We might finally learn to let go♪
♪When the rain stops♪
Any water? I need a drink.
♪We'll set off again♪
It's yesterday's water.
♪If the umbrella's downstairs♪
So what? Water doesn't go bad overnight.
♪We'll just get a little wet♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Instead of worrying so much♪
♪Maybe this time♪
♪We might finally learn to let go♪
Alright.
- Sir.
- Hello.
Same as always?
Yeah. Same numbers, ten draws.
Got it.
Some eight-plus-two set?
Just over a hundred.
What if that's the one that hits?
Just don't let your wife find out.
Problem solved, right?
Imagine hitting tens of millions,
then you wouldn't have to work everyday.
Right?
I'm not that lucky.
(Mortgage Loan)
You never know.
Have a try?
I'd rather buy some booze.
Get drunk, and in my dreams
I can buy anything I want.
(Mortgage Loan
Bridgeway Financial)
Thanks. How do I pay?
Over here.
(Bridgeway Financial)
Hello.
Hello?
I need a loan.
Mr. Du.
we've got an inquiry.
Do you keep fish?
Yeah, I do.
What kind of fish?
Small ones.
You know, the kind in that cup.
Those little red fish.
What do you feed them?
Those tiny fish pellets.
What's your collateral?
My apartment.
How big is it?
I'm... still young.
I can pay the money back.
Don't worry.
How big is your apartment?
Where is it?
It's 119 square meters.
on the deed.
The actual living area
is 99 square meters.
It's on Xinchen Road.
How long for it?
One month.
I need to stay in the apartment.
I'm short on cash right now.
You give me the money,
and I'll pay you back
in full within a month.
One month?
Borrow sixty, pay back sixty-five.
A hundred-plus-square-meter place
on Xinchen Road?
Sixty thousand?
That's not enough.
Then how much do you want?
Eighty.
Eighty thousand?
Borrow eighty, pay back ninety.
You pledge the property deed.
I transfer the money.
Pay it back in one month.
(Certificate of Real Estate Ownership)
Why don't you
turn on the light in the bathroom?
I can see just fine.
Why are you back?
Didn't mom tell you not to come home?
I came to get some clothes to change.
Where are they?
They haven't been washed yet.
Never mind, I'll go.
Wake your mom up later
and tell her to sleep in the bed.
Sleeping like that is bad for her neck.
Mom!
Dad says you should sleep in the bed.
It's not good for your neck.
You know,
the contract can be signed anywhere.
You don't have do that in here.
Ming,
but thank you for this.
Put some effort in.
We're good friends.
You've been good to me.
I should be good to you, too.
This contract between us
(Property information)
is just a formality.
Just some procedures.
The important parts are on page two.
The villa address.
(Property price and payment terms)
And the amount on page seven.
Everything matches, right?
800K.
Tomorrow morning, you make payment.
In the afternoon, I'll go handle
the transfer.
Then the house will be yours.
Sign it then.
(Seller: Hong Jinkui) (Buyer: Yu Ming)
Bro.
Do you think this time
we can get our money back?
My great-grandma said
no problem.
We'll definitely get it back.
Forget it, man.
If your great-grandma weren't sick,
you wouldn't
have told us today
that Hu Deshuai
hid the money inside the villa wall.
You don't know what kind
of person Hu Deshuai is?
Back then, he said he knew us.
Said we built walls for him,
He even knew where we lived.
He told me
if I told anyone about it,
he'd kill my whole family.
Bullshit.
Kill our whole family?
How dare he?
That's just like you.
Alright, alright.
Stop rambling.
Let's go take a look first.
This way.
What are you doing?
You can't just come in here.
Leave.
Well...
I built this place.
I just wanted to have a look.
Leave. Stop wasting my time.
What's with that attitude?
Let's go.
Bad attitude.
(Certificate of Real Estate Ownership)
Hello.
Are you the new owner?
Yes, yes.
You've already moved in?
No, not yet.
The place isn't ready.
I'm the security team leader
here at Ziyu Garden.
My name is Zhan Chun.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
I just came by
to see if you needed
anything.
Actually,
I've got a lot of construction debris.
Could you help me clear it out?
Construction debris? We...
don't offer that service.
But no problem.
I can check around for you.
Great! Thank you.
It's okay.
I'll come find you
once I've arranged it.
Great!
Alright, then.
Goodbye.
Congrats on moving in.
(Chongqing Noodles)
Unit 505 has a new owner.
He moved in this morning.
What should we do?
Figure out what we can do. What else?
Those three guys
knew Hu Deshuai.
Who?
Hu Deshuai.
Bro, I'm still hungry.
I want another bowl.
Why don't you eat the bowl, too?
We haven't got the money back,
and you are eating me into poverty.
Listen.
Tomorrow,
grab your tools
and go find a job.
Every debt has its debtor.
Why don't we go see
if Hu Deshuai's company
is still around?
Hu Deshuai's been dead for years.
No one is there.
How did Hu Deshuai
die, anyway?
No idea.
I heard someone killed him
and dumped him in the sea.
Alright, alright. That's enough.
Stop talking.
Get some of this.
Ma'am,
can I get another serving?
Sure.
No problem.
Chun?
You don't remember me?
Tiechui!
Look... who he is.
What a small world!
Me.
Tiezhu.
The foreman.
Yeah.
I remember.
Right?
It's been years.
You're doing pretty well now.
Civil servant?
No, don't talk nonsense.
I'm a security guard now.
Guard?
Not a driver any more?
No.
I changed careers.
This restaurant is mine.
My wife and I run it.
This is my wife.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
What brings
you guys here?
Collecting money.
Hu Deshuai owes
the wages of 133 workers.
He never paid us.
He owed me money, too.
How much does he owe you?
Two million.
You know he's dead, right?
Yeah.
What're you going to do?
Sometimes we have to accept bad luck.
That's what I did.
Listen to me, go home.
No way.
If I can't get the money,
I'm not going home.
What else
can you do then?
Who can you ask for it?
When we were building
Ziyu Garden,
I went to the bathroom
and I saw Hu Deshuai...
San.
Hey, um...
Weren't you still hungry?
Then eat my portion.
I... I'll eat first.
Okay.
Take your time.
I'm working
as a security guard
at Ziyu Garden.
Are you looking for a job?
Sure.
Really?
Yeah.
What job?
New house cleanup.
How about that?
Can you do it?
Yes.
Mr. Yu,
I've found the workers.
They can help clear away
the construction debris.
And they're affordable
and reliable.
Awesome! Thank you!
You're welcome.
(Bridgeway Financial.
Need Cash Fast? Call Us.)
Sorry.
Yitong.
You're back.
You must be his wife?
Who are you?
Yu Ming.
You're his wife, right?
What's going on?
We're from Bridgeway Financial.
Um...
Funds transferred.
Our boss
asked us to come over
to do a property appraisal.
What?
A property appraisal.
You just moved in, right?
I'm your neighbor.
This house is cursed.
The first owner drowned in the sea.
The second hanged himself from the beam.
This house
has been empty for years.
One after another just comes and goes.
They all got scared off by that thing
hanging from the chandelier.
Can you feel it?
That chill
crawling up your spine?
No.
Didn't you hear it?
Someone's blowing in your ear.
Put me down!
Put me down?
Wait. Didn't he kill himself?
Kill himself?
Even suicide can come with regret.
Go ask around.
Within ten miles,
everyone knows this house is cursed.
They wouldn't take the money for it.
How come you bought it?
Back then, I went home.
My mother-in-law was here.
She saw it.
Saw what?
He hung for days before anyone noticed.
The window
was wide open.
The wind was strong.
He looked like a big red sausage,
swaying in the wind.
By the time the coroner arrived,
his skin was all swollen.
As they walked in,
his head and body were separate.
Each one in a different place.
You'd think
his body
was on the floor, right?
No.
It was sitting on the couch.
And his head
was still hanging on the chandelier.
Scary, isn't it?
Mr. Yu.
Hello.
I'm Jiang Xiaoling
from property management.
You can just call me Jiang.
Hello.
This is also our staff.
Are you planning
to start renovations?
Just doing some cleanup first.
Here's the thing, Mr. Yu.
The villa you bought,
Unit 505,
has unpaid property management fees
and utility bills.
So we can't issue
a transport pass for trucks.
Which means
you can't remove renovation debris yet.
Once you settle all fees,
and get the pass,
then renovations can begin.
Here's our notice.
Please sign it.
Wait. I don't quite understand.
To be clear,
without the pass,
we won't open the gate
for trucks.
So all this debris they're moving
won't get out of
the community.
I haven't even moved in yet.
I just got the keys.
How could I possibly have those fees?
Those were left behind
by the owner before last.
Altogether, it's about
120,000.
How much?
Do you need my contact info?
No, no, no.
If the owner before last
owes the money,
then go collect it from him.
Why are you asking me?
How?
If you can't find him,
then go ask the previous owner.
Hong Jinkui.
Mr. Hong told us
he sold this house
to you.
He said
it's clearly stated
in your contract
that all debts and claims
related to this property
now belong to you.
Where?
Where does it say?
Right here.
Look.
Property management fees.
Utility bills.
How could I have missed that?
Ms. Jiang.
You're taking this too seriously.
Mr. Yu is not the type
to skimp on money.
He has bought the house.
those fees are nothing for him.
Yu Ming!
Are you insane?
I'm asking you, are you insane?
Could you give us a moment?
For what?
Answer me.
Whose name
is on the house deed?
Both our names.
Then how could you mortgage it?
Why?
Where is Wenwen and I supposed to live?
Where are we supposed to live?
Listen.
Are you even a man?
Why would you do this?
Why?
Hong Jinkui owed me money.
He didn't have the money,
so he mortgaged it
to me at a very low price.
We'll be moving
into this big house soon.
Our tenth anniversary is coming up.
What do I have to celebrate with you?
I just want to leave you.
I want to separate from you.
I can't live with you anymore.
Even if we separate,
this house
will belong to you and Wenwen.
It's yours.
I don't want anything.
I just want you to go. Get lost!
Mr. Yu.
Please sign
this notice.
Well...
One fine ticket for each truckload.
Two truckloads, two tickets.
Listen,
that chandelier must come down.
You need to smash it.
You've seen it for yourself.
It affects your feng shui.
You'll be arguing every day.
Smash the chandelier.
Pay us for the work.
Enough.
Come on, Ms. Jiang. Let's go.
We'll leave you alone now.
Peace brings prosperity.
The table's full.
Ask your wife come join us.
Ma'am, stop cooking already.
Don't bother.
It's fine.
Enjoy yourself.
Don't wait for me.
Come on, let's start.
Look at all these dishes.
Bro.
Chun and his wife
have been so good to us.
They seem to know
even more than we do.
Yeah.
We've been hiding all these years,
and now these three fools
have delivered the clue right to us.
The money is ours.
Didn't Hu Deshuai
owe them money too?
He's a security guard.
He has access.
Bro.
Should we bring him into the plan?
Here, one last dish.
That's too much.
We can't finish it all.
Is this okay?
Sure.
Come on.
Take a drink.
Chun's booze must be top-notch.
Good stuff.
Alright, alright.
That's enough.
Not enough.
Chun.
That's enough.
I... I want to ask you something.
Can I?
Go ahead.
Are you still hiring
security guards?
You want to be a guard?
Why would I lie to you?
For now,
um...
we are not hiring.
Bro,
I want to be a security guard too.
That's no big deal.
If you really want a job,
I can pay a bit and
get it done.
You can do that with money?
Then I want to do it too.
You can't. How could you?
You've got to be built like Chun and me.
Come on, come on.
Quit talking
and take a drink.
Let's do this.
Cheers, to Chun.
To Chun!
Take a sip.
It's strong!
By the way...
How much did
Hu Deshuai owe you?
Not that much.
Just some wages.
Tens of thousands.
Hu Deshuai was really shameless.
He owed money to everyone.
Exactly.
That money
can't go to waste.
We have to get it.
We sure do.
You guys...
Do you
have some way
to get the money back?
Chun.
We're all
down on our luck now.
So I'll be honest with you.
There's something valuable
hidden inside the wall of Unit 505.
♪The fridge keeps♪
♪Coughing in a low♪
♪Steady hum♪
♪That expired♪
♪Discount flyer♪
If you keep being together with him,
you're headed for a dead end.
There's no hope.
♪Still hangs on the door♪
He's useless.
Every year he's worse than the last.
How many more years
can you keep scraping by?
♪I'm afraid to face♪
Tell me.
How many more years
can you keep living like this?
♪This room of polished decay♪
Am I your family's workhorse?
I've been busting my back
dragging this family
forward step by step.
♪Neon seeps♪
You think it's easy?
Look down.
♪Through the curtains♪
Look at my shoes.
They cost only 58 yuan.
♪Through the curtains♪
Look how worn out they are.
♪With the last of the hard liquor♪
What do I have to celebrate with you?
I just want to leave you.
I want to separate from you.
I just want you to go. Get lost!
♪The darkness is so thick♪
♪Like freshly poured asphalt♪
♪Just enough to seal me♪
♪In the middle of the road♪
♪Like an insect in amber♪
♪Frozen in despair♪
♪Still reaching out for help♪
♪Yet no sound can escape♪
Feng.
Open your eyes.
How could leave us behind?
♪Don't let anyone break in♪
Wenwen isn't even one year old yet.
♪And ruin fate's design♪
Mom.
I swear
from now on,
I'll never sing again.
This is all your fault.
If you hadn't insisted on releasing
that ridiculous album,
your brother and his wife
wouldn't have that accident.
They wouldn't have died.
Brother.
Brother...
(Next Episode)
(Actress Ren Suxi)
I'm Ren Suxi.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
You have no idea what you missed out on.
From this moment on,
we're done.
Have you lost your mind?
Why would you borrow this much money?
It walked to me
on its own.
Keep this up and I'm calling the cops.
Relax...
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪