=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 3=
(Year 2012)
Feng!
(Yu Ming)
(Yuming)
Hello?
May I speak to Wen Yitong?
She's out leading a tour.
Try her cell.
Okay.
Thank you.
(Jinbaolong Hardware)
Excuse me.
Which bags are sturdier?
The ones on top
or the ones below?
The ones on top.
What's the difference?
They cost more.
Got it.
Five bags. 80 yuan.
So that's 160.
♪Rolling in cash♪
Great.
(Yu Ming)
(Block this user)
Sorry.
The number you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please dial again later.
Manager Zhan.
Mr. Yu.
I found a locksmith
for you.
Hello.
Come on in.
Come.
I got this.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Sure, sure.
Just tagging along.
Bye.
Hey, I know you.
I've collected trash from you.
That's no reason to kneel.
Force of habit.
Which lock?
Over here.
Okay.
Sir, all set.
Enter code.
You forgot to pay me.
Everything okay?
That means...?
Two updates.
One is bad.
The other...
Start with the good news.
is even worse.
Quit stalling. Just say it.
The wall is busted.
What?
Busted?
Wasn't it fine yesterday?
What's worse?
The money's gone.
Gone?
Where'd it go?
Buddy,
you have no idea.
Someone died
in this house.
Gum?
You also owe
120,000 yuan in property fees.
But listen,
in this house,
- Yu Ming.
- I found...
Here's the thing.
Someone died there.
Did the house shrink?
Did the layout change?
So you knew
someone died there?
Of course I knew.
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought we were friends!
Since when are we friends?
Yu Ming, this is business.
Business is business.
Buddy.
You must be kidding me
You played me!
And those
120,000 in property fees
Pay them yourself.
Why should I pay them?
How are those
my property fees?
If you want that
120,000 yuan,
go after the previous owner.
They owed it, not me.
The man hanged himself!
Who do I ask?
His wife...
Well, she's in jail.
They have a daughter.
Her name is Chen Zinuo.
I give you her number.
(Chen Zinuo)
Go collect it from her.
Hong Jinkui,
you've no idea what you just missed.
You deserve it.
From now on,
we're done.
We're done.
You're so gross.
So this house
has nothing to do with you now?
That's right.
So everything
inside this house—
none of it is yours?
- Right?
- Not a thing.
Put it in writing.
You dare?
Sure.
Fine.
You asked for it.
You just won't leave me alone,
will you?
How many times?
Don't wait for me here!
You're completely insane.
Have you lost your mind?
Why'd you borrow so much?
Didn't I tell you
to avoid loan sharks?
Didn't I tell you?
I didn't borrow this money.
It came to me
on its own.
How are you going to pay it back?
I told you, I didn't borrow it.
Buying that house was the best decision.
That villa...
it was waiting for me.
It was meant to be mine.
- I was meant to own it.
- Listen to me.
The loan sharks...
Do you know that villa...
You can't mess with them.
You'll lose everything.
So much...
That villa is a goose
that lays golden eggs.
One after another.
Hello? Can you connect me
to Psychiatry?
Hang up.
I'm not making this up.
This money is heaven-sent.
Luck is finally on our side.
It's finally
our turn.
We should be thrilled.
We should be excited.
We should celebrate.
Kiss me!
You're insane.
Yu Ming, you're out of your mind.
Keep this up, and I'm calling the cops.
Relax...
I...
Name?
Yu Ming.
Y-E-U?
No, not that Yeu.
Y-U, Yu.
We're legally married.
A real married couple.
We've had
some issues lately.
So I brought...
When did you bring him in?
This afternoon.
Where?
At an internet café.
Bigfoot?
Guo Li!
What are you two doing here?
(Wanbei Police Station)
Don't let this happen again,
okay?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Thanks. Have a good one.
I can't believe you.
Give me the keys.
Do you know why
Guo Li gave you a hat?
Even your old friend
think you're embarrassing.
She gave it to you
so you could hide your face.
That...
Small world.
Yeah.
Why are you still here?
I...
I just remembered
something about a friend.
I wanted to ask you.
He's a screenwriter.
He's writing a script.
Since when
you know screenwriters?
Why have I never heard of him?
A new friend.
A guy or a girl?
A guy.
Good-looking?
Looks like Guo Jingfei.
Never mind, then.
Back to the point.
In his script,
someone finds an antique
inside a house.
Legally speaking,
does it belong to him?
Can he prove
it's a family heirloom?
No.
What if he's renting the house?
Ask the landlord.
Right.
What if he owns the house?
He bought it himself,
and found an antique.
Could it belong to him?
That depends on
when
and what kind of antique
your writer friend invented.
He hasn't figured that out yet.
What are you asking?
No,
it's...
He's a little confused too.
Let's say it's not an antique.
Let's say it's gold.
Right.
You can spend it right away.
Nobody knew
it was there.
Nobody was looking for it.
Then he finds it.
Can he keep the gold?
That's such a cliché.
Tell your friend to rewrite it.
He's stubborn. He won't listen.
No wonder
nobody watches TV anymore.
Tell your friend to find out first
whether the property has any heirs.
He can look it up online.
If I remember correctly,
collective property stays collective.
No heirs? It goes to the state.
Got it.
Why are you carrying
so much cash today?
To buy stock.
Pearl powder again?
Fridge magnets.
200,000 worth of fridge magnets?
This money...
Captain Guo.
The paperwork's done.
Keep an eye on that money.
Don't get scammed again.
Do you sell flashlights?
Bottom shelf.
How much?
35 yuan.
I'll pay cash.
One bill.
Authentic.
What?
I'll pay with my phone.
Do you sell money counters?
Sure.
I'll take one.
Actually, two.
100 bills.
Authentic.
Hello, Ming.
Ouyang.
I've got some huge news.
I bought a house.
And...
I don't even know how to explain it.
Come see me tomorrow.
Meet someone with me.
I'll send you
the address.
Okay. I'll come by tomorrow.
Thirty million!
Come on, let's move.
Did you hear something?
No.
Ming!
Ouyang.
You're here early.
Dressed like a biker and all,
you gave me a scare.
What do you think of the place?
Not bad, Ming.
Great protection, great energy flow.
Have you studied feng shui?
This place is like a treasure bowl,
right?
You know feng shui, huh?
A treasure bowl means
I'm about to get rich.
Better start sucking up to me now.
Why did you knock down this wall?
The layout was better with it.
It makes the place feel bigger.
Come on.
I need you to come with me.
Who are we going to see?
(Lindao Nursing Home)
Easy now. Easy.
Mr. Wang's improved a lot this week.
Watch your step.
Careful here.
Be careful.
Really impressive.
Great job.
That's right.
Good.
Excuse me.
We're looking for Chen Zinuo.
And you are?
Friends of hers.
Okay, this way.
See?
The seniors here
are all very happy.
They're living well.
She's over there.
Have a seat here.
Thank you.
Sure.
I got one too!
I'm on a roll!
Your turn.
What's with you today?
What's taking you so long?
Hurry up!
No, no, no.
Discard that one.
You'll have three winning tiles.
Right.
Seven Dots.
Mahjong!
Self-draw!
You must've seen my tiles!
No, no.
No way.
This hand doesn't count!
Mr. Yu.
I'm short on time.
Just tell me what this is about.
Ms. Chen, here's the thing.
I'm living in your old house now.
The villa you used to own.
The property manager said
there are unpaid fees.
I know.
After what happened
to my family
the court seized the house
and auctioned it off.
So all outstanding debts of the house
are assumed by the buyer.
So those debts
have nothing to do with me
or my family.
That's an actual rule?
Sir,
how long has that cello girl
been volunteering here?
What cello girl?
Show some respect.
Her name is Nuo.
Nuo.
How long has Nuo
been volunteering here?
Seven or eight years.
Seven Dots.
Nuo
comes from a good family
Everyone here adores her.
The line of admirers she's got
stretches all the way
to Italy.
Looking at yourself.
What chance do you think you have?
Mr. Yu.
Is there anything else?
Just one thing.
I get the feeling
your family moved out in a hurry.
So...
did you happen to leave
anything behind?
Or maybe...
while you were living there,
did you ever come across
anything unusual?
Nuo.
Aunt You is looking for you.
She wants to hear Hungarian Rhapsody.
Like this.
The paint goes on more evenly.
Give it a try.
Wenwen, who did you draw?
My grandma.
What's grandma doing?
She's trying to bite my dad to death.
Everyone, back to your seats.
Work on your own drawings.
Wenwen.
Look at my markers.
There are 120 colors.
I've got several blues
for drawing the sky.
And several yellows
for the ground.
Next time,
we can share them.
So what if you have 120 colors?
You still failed art.
Your drawings are as ugly as you are.
What's ugly about them?
They're okay.
But I think
yours looks better.
All those big sharp teeth.
It's different.
I heard Ms. Cai
calling your mom.
She said you're really talented.
Can you teach me?
Please teach me.
Would you stop bugging me?
She's bleeding!
What do we do?
Wenwen!
Your head!
She's bleeding!
It doesn't hurt.
What's going on?
What are you all looking at?
Let me see.
Wenwen, what happened?
Are you hurt?
What happened, Wu Xiaoxuan?
It's okay.
Don't be scared.
Hello, 120?
This is Yingsi School.
One of our students is injured.
It's serious.
♪I'm gonna work hard and make money♪
Ms. Zhang.
Where is she?
Taxi!
Does it hurt?
Does it still hurt?
I'm okay.
Feeling better?
Good. You're okay.
Where to?
39 Xinchen Road.
Okay.
People's Hospital?
What happened?
She got hurt?
Where?
Her head? Her head!
Okay, okay.
People's Hospital.
I got it.
She's fine.
Kids heal quickly.
Even if it scars,
it'll be very faint.
There are laser treatments now.
So don't worry.
She'll be as beautiful as ever.
Thank you, Dr. Li.
What on earth were you doing?
Look what happened.
I take care of her
so well.
And you?
You?
What's it got to do with you?
Can you watch her
twenty-four hours a day?
What do you mean
it has nothing to do with you?
Look at all those stitches.
Nothing to do with you?
So this is my fault?
It wasn't his fault!
I can't tell you what to do,
but he's my son.
I can still talk to my own son!
Say something!
Someone's arguing over there.
Come on.
This is a hospital, a public place.
How embarrassing!
This embarrasses the family. Let's go.
What are you doing?
Let go.
Go ahead.
Beat him to death.
Go on.
One is dead already. Just kill another.
I'm sorry.
Yu Ming, why are you apologizing?
Who hasn't been hurt?
Haven't you?
And didn't it hurt?
Your son was hurt.
Do you even know where?
Do you?
His brother gave him that.
Every time you scolded him,
he cut himself.
Didn't that hurt?
You're his mother.
You think he wasn't hurt?
Answer me!
Kill him!
Don't give me that.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Listen.
Let go.
Get out!
That's enough.
He's my son.
I can discipline him.
Mind your own child.
What did your son do?
Get over here.
You can't afford 100 yuan
for a set of markers.
Yet one mistake outside,
you're out 300,000 yuan.
Loser.
That's 300,000!
You can't do anything right.
Can't you ever amount to anything?
Are you trying to kill me?
Please stop.
Ma'am,
please calm down.
Wenwen's parents,
um...
Wu Xiaoxuan's parents
have arrived at school.
Could one of you
come with me to handle it?
I'll go.
Let's go.
The injury is on her face.
Wenwen is a girl.
What if she feels insecure
and other kids
pick on her?
Let me be clear,
kids her age
care most about their appearance.
What if she breaks down
and needs therapy?
And even needs medication?
And if that scar doesn't heal properly,
this won't be over in a few days.
That scar could stay with her
for the rest of her life.
Ma'am.
The kids fell down together.
We don't even know who started it.
Just 'cause she's hurt worse,
doesn't make her right.
Let's be reasonable.
My son was hurt too.
Oh, really?
Did he need stitches?
Was the wound deep?
Was he bleeding?
Was there blood everywhere?
Stop right there.
Let me tell you,
Wenwen is my precious granddaughter.
If anything happens to her,
I couldn't go on living.
And if I die,
none of you will have any peace.
I've seen plenty of people
like you.
The facts aren't even clear yet,
and you're already taking
the moral high ground.
Yes, I admit
Wenwen bled more,
so everyone will naturally
take your side.
Then we'll
get torn apart online.
People will expose us,
where we work,
and even our home address,
and put us on public trial.
Isn't that what you want?
Get off your high horse.
Why are you insulting me?
Who said I was talking about you?
Did I insult you?
Stop that.
We're not here to fight.
The most important thing
is to find out
how serious
Wenwen's injury is.
Right?
No need for more tests.
It's obviously serious.
Let me handle it.
I'll take care of this,
okay?
No matter who got hurt
or who was hurt worse,
lots of people were there.
Someone must have seen
what happened.
Isn't the school responsible?
It is.
What we need now
is to get the facts straight.
Whoever's responsible is responsible.
Right?
We can work out a solution together.
Arguing here
won't solve anything.
Wenwen and Xiaoxuan
were playing around here,
and accidentally fell downstairs.
I noticed when I walked by.
Sir, please let us handle that.
All right, stop staring.
Go back to class.
Everyone, back to class.
How many times do I have to say it?
Get back to class.
Nothing to see here.
Back to class.
Yu Ming.
Director.
Stop cleaning.
Stop, don't do this.
Blood.
It's gone.
It's all Wenwen's blood.
Stop.
Please.
Put it down.
Stop.
Don't do this, Yu Ming.
Please stop.
There's still some in the crack.
I see it.
I'll get it.
Sit down and rest.
Give me that.
The doctor said she's young,
so she'll heal quickly.
She'll be okay.
Don't do this.
What are you talking about?
Home field, away field...
If I didn't tell you,
could you tell which was which?
Fine, I have to go.
Can't you figure it out yourself?
Your daughter?
Your son?
Well, isn't that something.
The one guy who hit our car.
That headlight...
How about this?
That headlight costs 300,000.
Let's call it even.
Your daughter's forehead
for my headlight.
What did you say?
Calm down.
What?
How about this?
I'll give you three million.
For what?
For five stitches on your head.
Just five stitches.
Deal?
No.
(Emergency)
Do I look ridiculous
with this net?
You look good in anything.
You're gorgeous.
Don't believe me? Ask Grandma.
You look lovely.
Come on, sit still.
Careful with that arm.
Your left one.
Did it hurt
when they stitched you up?
Why would it hurt?
They gave me anaesthetic.
Did you cry?
Why would I cry? I had anaesthetic.
Where's dad?
♪Once king of Flower-Fruit Mountain♪
♪Now lost upon the endless road♪
♪I fought demons for my master♪
♪Yet he failed to understand♪
♪He mistook loyalty for ill intent♪
♪A master's word is law♪
♪What did I do wrong♪
That Monkey King
always shows up when I'm lost.
He walks past me singing.
And as I watch him,
my mind gradually settles.
I don't want porridge.
Then what do you want?
Fried chicken.
No fried chicken.
The doctor said no spicy food,
no seafood, beef, or lamb.
But fried chicken is chicken.
Absolutely not.
It's too greasy.
Get better,
and Grandma will buy you some.
I know what she means.
She knows what I mean.
Here...
Mom, stop fussing.
You should head home.
I've made up the bed for you.
Everything's ready.
Go home.
All right, I'm off.
Bye, grandma.
Bye.
What?
Stop playing and finish your food.
What's wrong?
Has she ever hit you?
Who?
Who else? That old witch.
Has she laid a hand on you?
I'll report her if she has.
Report her for what?
She wouldn't dare.
Now I need a new pair of glasses.
You were so protective of him today.
What changed?
Thought you were leaving him.
Divorce is one thing.
Stopping a fight is another.
I couldn't just stand there
and watch Sun Lanying beat him.
Don't worry about it. Go home.
Go get some rest.
You've had a long day.
Go home and get some sleep.
All right, I'm going.
Be careful. Watch for traffic.
I'll buy you a new pair of glasses.
Have you finished?
Such a fuss over porridge.
Tell me,
this afternoon,
who pushed whom?
Who started it?
Nobody did.
Blame me for being skinny.
I never get enough fried chicken.
I'm as skinny as a monkey.
No wonder I'm the one who got hurt.
Listen to you.
But nice try.
None of this is dad's fault.
So you heard everything?
You were so loud.
How could I not?
That's why you can't get hurt.
You know?
Whatever comes your way,
you need to get through it.
Keep going.
Stay strong.
If you're strong, Dad will be too.
If you're okay,
Dad will be okay too.
Got it?
After your Dad and I get...
Dad!
Thank you.
Even now,
you're still standing up for me.
That's a another matter.
Wenwen is a good kid.
So well-behaved.
Why...
does she have to go through this?
Why her?
Why not someone else?
You seem distracted with Wenwen lately.
Do you know why?
I do.
She's taking after your brother.
When you look at her,
it's like seeing him.
You feel you owe your brother.
You owe Wenwen.
It's eating you up.
I just want to ask,
living like this...
when will it end?
Yitong.
Listen.
Come back to the house with me.
I must show you something.
Don't mention that house.
I know.
My whole family has held you back.
You've carried us for too long.
But this time, trust me.
Better days are ahead.
Don't leave me.
Please.
I've got a hammer!
I'm not afraid of you!
I'm not afraid!
(Next Episode）
(Guo Jingfei)
Hi, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
I just want to
check yesterday's footage.
Those two knew this place
really well.
If they're familiar with this place,
could they be someone you know?
Perhaps you should go back
to check
if you left anything behind?
That house has nothing
to do with me anymore.
Ms. Li,
Unit 505
has been sold.
The buyer went to see Zinuo.
He mentioned
the property management fees
and asked
if there was anything
she left behind in the villa.
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪