(Previously)
Oh!
Hey!
Mr. Boiling Tofu.
Stray-Dog Scammer.
Come on!
No f*cking way.
This must belong to that
tofu-faced flight attendant.
This must belong to that punk.
How dare you guys wear my clothes?
Someone like you needs
to learn who runs this area.
My stuff!
You guys are going to work off your debt
until it's fully paid off.
I need you to investigate
my boyfriend's cheating.
If I help you with this,
can we consider my debt paid?
I might consider forgiving your debt.
Beer, what's this case about?
Walk me through it again.
It's a 30-year-old woman
with a heart condition.
She needs to be moved immediately.
Ak, you've practiced this, right?
Yes.
I've got it nailed.
We can't mess this up.
It's very important to me.
Where's the patient?
This way.
Please follow me right away.
My friend can barely hang on anymore.
This way, please.
Right here.
Here they are!
Hello.
The rescue team is ready
to rescue your heart.
"A Dog and A Plane"
(Episode 2)
♪ I don't trust a word you say ♪
♪ You and your cruel heart can go away ♪
♪ I should've run when warned ♪
♪ But I chose to stay ♪
♪ I don't trust a word you say ♪
♪ Not a single word you say ♪
♪ I don't ♪
♪ I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't ♪
I thought you'd disappeared.
Instead of spending time
coming up with a plan to help me,
you're busy taking escort jobs.
I'm desperate for money.
My creditor happens to be greedy.
I have to do whatever I can.
Hey.
Don't tell me this is the rescue guy
who said your face looked like
tofu boiling in a sukiyaki pot.
You didn't have to remember
every word I said.
Oh.
This is great.
Tonight, please take
care of her down there.
Oops!
I mean, take care of my friend.
Be extra sweet.
Okay?
You got it.
And what's your name?
Akki.
Akki?
Come with me, baby.
Come on.
You got it, sis.
Come on!
I gotta go, bro.
Hey, Pailin!
Bye now!
Hey.
Tonight has nothing to do with the debt.
If you want me to entertain you,
you'll have to pay.
I need money for my sister's tuition.
Sure, Mr. Wonderful Big Brother.
I don't need you to entertain me.
Go entertain someone else.
Make it extra strong.
Yes, sir, Mr. Flight Attendant.
I'll make it strong as hell.
You're never going to sink a shot
if you hold it like that.
Look, it doesn't matter how you hold it.
You just have to hit it and make it go in.
You really don't care, huh?
There's technique, form,
and art in everything.
Come on.
Let me teach you how to shoot.
Hey, stop it.
Why are you touching me?
Who even wants to touch you?
I'm just going to teach you.
Come on.
Place your hand like this.
Put your thumb up.
Place the cue between
your thumb and index finger.
Relax.
Breathe slowly.
Aim. Don't shoot yet.
Aim carefully.
We met again.
Oh.
You're the guy from the bag shop.
I didn't know
you knew Mandy, the bride.
I'm sorry about that day.
I'm terrible.
When I want something, I get it.
Me too.
Whatever I think is mine,
I don't let anyone else take it easily.
It's crazy, right?
It's just a bag. Why so serious?
It's not like we're
fighting over a partner.
Who knows?
I mean, you never know.
One day, we might be
fighting over a bag again.
Your taste and mine are similar anyway.
But I won't be fighting
over this rescue guy.
He's not my taste.
Ouch.
That was intense.
Did you piss him off before?
Look, everyone's jealous of my life.
Right.
No wonder he finds you annoying.
You're so good at spoiling me.
I'm going to end up broke tonight.
Come on. Cheers!
Cheers.
Cheers!
Excuse me, Pailin.
You can't keep him all to yourself.
It's my party.
I'm just doing a test run for you.
Stop it.
I brought one of my juniors to say hi.
His name is Veha.
He works for the same airline as me.
We've met before.
Oh!
How did you two meet?
Veha, have you taken him home before?
Don't be ridiculous, sis.
But it's my hen night,
so go for it.
Excuse me, could you take off your shirt
so my friend can run his hand over you?
I'm giving you 1,000 baht.
Wow.
Of course.
I'm not doing it.
Yes, you are.
You're already here. Go on.
I'll give you 2,000.
Don't reach too deep.
If you touch it,
you pay more.
You look familiar.
Have we met before?
We met at the airport.
No.
We've met somewhere else.
But I can't remember where.
Oh.
I remember now.
We met in a dream, didn't we?
Wow!
You're so bold.
I love it.
Come here!
Come on, let's drink!
♪ Wanna change Monday into Sunday ♪
♪ Wanna make my life easier ♪
♪ Wanna turn day into night ♪
Eat it!
♪ Wanna give those standing a seat ♪
♪ Wanna turn war into love ♪
♪ Wanna make grumpy faces smile ♪
♪ Wanna turn flames into ice cream ♪
♪ Let the poor have a taste of caviar ♪
She seems to enjoy it.
Is it good?
I'm throwing up.
You guys enjoy the food.
What?
Whoa.
Kanit.
What?
Eat it.
You're close with him, right?
Are you crazy? I'm not doing it.
Oh!
Come on. I'm not going to tell Lion.
I paid ten thousand for this.
Make it worth it.
Go!
No.
Wimp.
Fine.
I'm going to eat you up.
Kanit!
Oh my god!
Ugh!
Who's screaming now?
Hey! Mandy can't breathe!
She's allergic to shrimp.
There's shrimp in the sushi!
What?
Mandy!
Hey!
Whoa!
Shit! Look at her lips!
Guys, please give her some space.
Please lie down.
Excuse me.
It's so swollen!
How are you feeling?
I'm itchy all over.
I can't breathe.
Ak, can you check her blood pressure?
Breathe slowly.
Low blood pressure.
Difficulty breathing.
Let's get her to the hospital.
Go.
Calm down, Mandy.
Hang in there, girl.
You're not married yet.
Hang in there!
Make way, please.
Excuse me.
Hey.
The doctor said
your friend's doing better now.
Her blood pressure is back to normal
and she can breathe better now.
Still, she needs to stay overnight in the
hospital so they can monitor her condition.
Mm.
Luckily, you got her here quickly.
My friend almost lost the chance
to get married.
I have to thank your friend.
She paid me a lot.
Now I don't have to worry
about my sister's tuition.
By the way,
what about catching my boyfriend cheating?
What are you going to do?
So, you're not worried about your friend.
You're worried about your man.
Hey, I understand your life,
but my love life is important too.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
On one condition, though.
What is it?
Every time I investigate,
you're coming with me.
Alright.
What?
Why do I have to go with you?
I hired you, so go on your own.
I want you to see how evil he really is
with your own eyes.
Come on. We still don't know if it's true.
Don't call him evil yet.
You're protecting him, huh?
Let's talk about the investigation later.
But now,
I need to get to know
you on a deeper level.
How deep do you want to go?
What's your plan?
PROJECT: CATCH THE CHEATER
SIDE PEACE? AND LION
Before we talk about the plan,
I have a little question
about you and your boyfriend.
What is it?
When was the last time you slept together?
What kind of question is that?
Listen, I've caught a lot of cheaters.
Most of the time, people break up
because they don't sleep together enough.
Sex…
is important in a relationship, you know?
I last did it… two weeks ago.
How often?
Hey, what are you talking about?
The thrusting rhythm, maybe?
I mean, how often do you sleep together?
In the beginning, every day.
Later on, once a week.
Lately, once a month.
These days I fly a lot,
so once every 3 months.
Listen, just working is already exhausting.
Just sleeping in each
other's arms is enough.
Naive.
Very naive.
So while you're cuddling
in your little bubble,
do you look at his phone?
How does he put it? Face down or face up?
Face down.
It's clear then.
He's keeping secrets from you.
Please. It could be because
the light is glaring in his eyes.
You still won't stop being foolish.
I'm telling you, in this case,
the chances of him cheating on you are
70%.
70%?
That might even be too low.
He rarely sleeps with you.
He has secrets on his phone.
Plus, he lied to you.
If you don't believe me,
we'll prove it together.
Brace yourself.
We're getting the job done today.
Hey.
I feel bad doing this.
It's like I don't trust him.
I knew it.
Just like what Toon said.
Toon who?
Toon Bodyslam's song.
Love makes you so blind
that you can't see the truth.
Your boyfriend's bullshitting you.
Why are you still siding with him?
Well, I don't know.
People can feel many things
at the same time.
Like both love and suspicion.
The brain has many layers.
Unlike yours, which only has one.
So?
Do you want to call this off?
What's with your mood swing?
Let's wait a little longer.
But I don't think he's going anywhere.
Usually, he stays home all day
on his days off.
Right, he stays home all day.
He's sleeping and driving off now.
I'll open your eyes
to your boyfriend's true colors.
He's a lying piece of shit.
Look, he's driving so fast.
He must be on his way
to see his side piece.
What kind of theory is that?
It doesn't even make sense.
Listen.
When someone's cheating on you,
they manage time efficiently.
One hour they're with one person.
The next hour, they're with someone else.
That's why he has to move this fast.
Really?
Yeah.
But he always drives fast.
He loves watching Fast &amp; Furious.
Amateur.
He's got nothing on me.
If I shaved my head and bulked up,
I'd be pretty much Vin Diesel.
Lion, just you wait.
Toto Benzine 97 Premium.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Slow down!
Hey!
Drive carefully!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Drive carefully!
Hey.
That driving almost turned us into
corpses in the back.
Come on.
It's the F1 spirit.
Gotta go a little fast, bro.
People usually sneak off to clubs.
He sneaks off to a temple.
It'd be hilarious if he's cheating with
someone from the monastic community.
Hey.
Keep saying things like that
and hell's going to swallow you whole.
I'm not afraid.
I'm a descendant of the Grim Reaper.
I'm going in alone.
If he spots you, our plan will fall apart.
What? You're going in like this?
Lottery tickets!
Wanna try your luck?
Let me go undercover.
Yathā vārivahā pūrā
Paripūrenti sāgaraṃ
Evam-eva ito dinnaṁ
Petānaṁ…
What?
Shit.
Maybe it's not someone
from the monastic community,
but the betel nut-chewing generation.
Oh, shit!
Shit!
What are you doing here?
I thought you were a ghost.
That's harsh.
Why do you have to insult me like that?
You scared me.
I thought you were some wandering ghost.
What are you doing here?
I told you to wait in the car.
He could catch you.
I've been waiting for a while.
I want to see what's happening too.
Honestly…
Hmm?
Your boyfriend is cheating on you.
Huh?
With an old woman.
She's over 60.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Where is she?
Careful.
That one in the purple shirt.
Hey, that could be Lion's mother.
What? You've never met his mother?
No.
Seriously, what kind of boyfriend are you?
What can I do?
He said he's not ready.
A liar always has a hundred excuses.
Ever heard of that?
He's coming!
Hide!
Where?
There!
Go!
Lottery tickets, young man.
Want some lottery tickets?
Buy some today, get rich in your next life.
Excuse me.
Have we met somewhere before, Uncle?
I don't think so.
Are you mixing me up with Nadech?
Nadech?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
Tell you what,
I'll buy some of your lottery tickets.
What number should I get?
What did you see in your dream?
I'll just get this number.
Okay.
And this one.
It's my partner's room number.
He's been upset with me lately.
Maybe I could bring him some luck.
That's great.
How much are these?
Two pairs, 400 baht.
400?
Whoa.
Alright. Here you go.
Thanks, young man.
Do you have any change?
Yes. Give me a second.
It's alright.
Just keep it.
Oh, thank you so much.
Good luck.
Sadhu.
Thanks, young man.
He's gone.
(He's gone?)
Hey.
We've been following him all day.
Nothing suspicious is going on.
He just went to a temple to make merit
with his mother.
How about
we lower the chance to 50%?
Why are you so obsessed with numbers?
Well, you told me there's a 70% chance
he's cheating.
Hearing that is pretty discouraging.
Hey.
Look.
Now, it's 80%.
Damn.
They definitely planned
to hook up at his house.
Looks like he's into the wild,
rough-around-the-edges biker type.
The fair and bright type like you
just isn't exciting for him.
Hey, who says someone fair and bright
like me isn't spicy?
You haven't even tasted me.
You have no idea
how spicy I am.
Can I taste you then?
In your next life.
Look!
It's just a delivery guy.
The chance is only 60% now.
Fine. Let's cut it to 40%.
In the end, it's just all in my head.
I shouldn't have trusted the devil
who whispered into my left ear
to be suspicious of him.
I should've trusted the
angel in my right ear
who said he has only me.
Delusional!
That's the voice from hell.
I think I should just ask him directly
so we can clear this up once and for all.
Up to you.
I wish you good luck.
Don't listen to him too much.
Learn to use your D-I-C-K.
Rude.
Why are you giving out private parts?
What?
Digest. Investigate. Critique. Know.
What did you think I meant?
Bye.
Lion.
Kanit.
What brings you here?
I have something important
to talk to you about.
What is it?
It's about us.
Sure.
Let's have some fried chicken.
I just need to use the bathroom real quick.
Is something wrong?
You've been acting off.
Look, I'm not trying
to find fault with you,
but I want to know.
You said you were at home sick.
That day, you…
So, you found out?
Yes.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Lion!
Yeah.
Well…
My friend was heartbroken that night,
so he called me over
to have some beer with him at his house.
I got so drunk I blacked out.
Oh, why didn't you just tell me honestly?
Well, I was afraid you'd scold me.
When I drink a lot,
you're not really okay with it.
But…
I know you're worried about me,
so I've been trying to drink less.
I'm doing it for you.
Here.
Let me show you.
See?
I really blacked out.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Is there anything else you haven't told me?
Yes.
What is it?
I bought some lottery tickets for you.
I went to make merit this morning,
and I met an old man selling them,
so I supported him.
Look, it's your room number.
♪ A secret love isn't
a big deal, it's true ♪
♪ I've never said how much I love you ♪
♪ Keep it inside, you never knew ♪
Bravo, Ja-O. My dear bro!
Wow.
You're good.
Better than singers.
You're so good at singing,
you shouldn't be a rescuer.
You should be a singer.
So what do you want?
You made up with your boyfriend.
Why did you want to see me?
I need a little favor.
Alright.
Food is served.
Je, are you confused?
I didn't order grilled pork neck.
Then don't f*cking eat it.
Hey, I can f*cking eat it.
I gave you this for free.
I know you've been working your ass off,
so eat up for the energy.
Good evening.
Is this your boyfriend?
What boyfriend? No.
He's not my type at all.
He'll never get to see my insides.
We're just mission partners.
Hey.
This is Je Zo.
The beautiful, sexy, muscular
owner of this place.
Je, this is Kanit.
He's a flight attendant, a creditor,
and a drama queen.
Save the modifiers.
Hi.
Listen to that voice.
He might not be your type,
but he's totally mine.
He's so cute and fair
like a polar bear. Look!
If he's still available, can I hit on him?
No!
Polar bears are protected animals.
You can't just keep one.
I'm an officer. I'll take care of him.
He's not your type,
but you're keeping him for yourself?
Your logic is weird.
So what is it you want me to help with?
Our anniversary is coming up.
I want to decorate my room to surprise him.
So I want you to help me do the shopping.
You need my help for something so simple?
Look, I can do it myself,
but I don't want to carry stuff on my own.
I want an outsider's opinion too.
Besides,
I need to find you something to do
to pay off your debt.
Yeah, I know I have to work it off.
That's why I brought this.
Here.
Parking tickets.
We'll use these as order tickets.
One ticket equals one order.
Once we've used up this whole book,
my debt is cleared. Okay?
Okay..
In that case,
let's start.
Hey.
Hmm?
You're planning a dinner, not moving house.
Come on.
Why are you buying so much?
Well, I can't choose.
So many things look good.
Why don't you put everything
you've picked out on the table first?
Are you crazy?
The staff is going to scold us.
Up to you then.
If you think you're so rich
and want to buy everything, go ahead.
Just don't cry later.
Then set it up and show me.
Go on.
You're giving me an order?
It's your job, isn't it?
Hurry up!
Fine.
Hmm… that smells nice.
Damn. The smell is perfect.
It's got that seductive vibe.
It's so good.
If I were your boyfriend,
I'd probably say something like this:
I don't want to eat the food anymore.
I'd rather eat you.
Ew.
Lion would never say anything that cheesy.
Really?
What would he say then?
Kanit,
let's f*ck.
Ugh! You're so gross.
Then the aroma kicks in,
and the mood starts to feel just right.
He'd stand up
and slowly walk
closer and closer to you.
And finally, he'd…
Sir!
You can't light the candles.
I'm sorry.
Ahh!
Wow.
The bed is so comfy. I'm going to
sleep so hard that I forget to wake up.
I asked you to come help me shop
for dinner,
not lie around.
Hey, this bed is really soft.
I'm just giving you inspiration.
You might want to buy it
to shake your hips with your boyfriend.
Is your brain only filled
with dirty thoughts?
Come on.
Come and try it.
It's really bouncy.
Come.
Hey.
Kanit, will you be mine tonight?
Lion,
if you look so much like a dog like this,
I'm afraid it's a no.
Let's go.
Bring the cart and follow me.
You can leave the stuff on the table.
Wow.
Your room is huge.
Did your husband buy it for you?
Please. I can afford it myself.
I bought it with money from working as
a flight attendant and trading some stocks.
And stop calling him my husband.
He's just my boyfriend.
Are you a sugar baby?
Hey. Take off your shoes. They're dirty.
Why did you step on the carpet?
Gosh!
This place is so big.
I bet you've done it in every corner.
Hey.
Have you ever thrust on the balcony?
Whoa.
But be careful. It's glass.
If you fall off and die,
your body won't look good.
Risky,
but thrilling.
Gross. Who would do that?
If you've never done it, try it.
It's exciting.
I have to go.
You made me work so hard,
so you better knock some off my debt.
Wait.
Your work is not done.
What now?
Go at it.
Are you sure?
How fast do you want me to go?
Up to you. Do it however you like.
I'm going in.
Oh.
Oh!
Hey. Oh!
Hey, don't be fast. It's too intense.
Stay still.
It's too intense.
Here.
Whoa.
Why does it look so easy when you do it?
I cut my fingers every time.
Why do you make it hard?
How is it even hard?
Grab the knife with your right hand.
Mm.
Grab the onion with your left hand.
Grab it like a cat's paw.
Tuck your nails in.
Then use the knife to slice it.
Whap! Whap! Whap!
Whap! Whap!
How is it even hard?
Yeah.
It really is easy.
So fake.
You want to cook for your man,
but you can't even hold a knife.
I registered my birth
at the district office,
not on MasterChef.
Hey!
It's not like you're that good.
I'm so good
I could be Chef Pom's grandson.
I've been thinking about
joining a cooking contest.
I cook for my sister all the time.
But I've never cooked for a partner.
Oof.
Nobody wants you.
With that sharp tongue of yours,
I can only think of one who'd take you.
Who?
The city office that picks up stray dogs.
Excuse me?
I'm so hot, I get hit on all the time.
My DMs blow up.
Please.
I'm on the Hot Rescue Guys Spotted page.
Do I have options? Yes, I do.
I'm not like that song by ZAZA.
I just don't want anyone.
Staying single is more thrilling for me.
Got it?
And if I had to date someone fake like you?
No, thanks.
Excuse me?
Which part of me is fake?
Everything on my body is real.
The audacity.
When you're done cooking,
set the table and do the lighting
the way I told you to.
Seriously?
You're not going to do any of it yourself?
Since you're so fabulous and amazing
at everything,
you can do it yourself.
I'm going to dress up
and wait for my boyfriend.
Hey!
Where's the power strip?
Ugh.
Why did you come in here?
Hmm?
I asked where the power strip was,
but you wouldn't answer.
What are you staring at? Gross.
Creep.
What?
What am I staring at?
I have one too. Why would I stare?
I don't want to look at you.
So…
Your power stick…
I mean, where's your power strip?
It's in the TV stand drawer.
Now go.
This is so romantic.
Do you think Lion will like it?
He probably will.
Hmm…
Hey, thank you.
I'll knock enough off your debt
to make all your hard work worth it.
Sure.
May you find ecstasy
and end up in seventh heaven.
Knock yourselves out.
Just be careful around the glass balcony.
Or I'll have to come back
and collect your body.
I don't even want to imagine
what that'll look like.
Ah!
Oh!
What position are you even doing?
The looking-back deer, of course.
Keep your dirty thoughts to yourself.
Off you go.
Don't let me catch you doing it.
I'll be watching.
Go.
Bye now.
Safe sex, okay?
I know. You don't need to lecture me.
Yathā vārivahā pūrā
Paripūrenti sāgaraṃ
Evam-eva…
It's my boyfriend's room number.
I got you some lottery tickets.
It's your room number.
I hope I get lucky for a change.
I just need to use the bathroom real quick.
Veha.
I'm sorry, but…
We might not get to
use this anymore tonight.
And I have to ask you to leave.
What?
Why?
If you want me to trust you,
don't forget to come to my room
like you said you would.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
I thought you said you'd be celebrating
with your boyfriend.
I changed my mind.
I'd rather be with you.
Oh.
It's you.
What's up?
I forgot my wallet.
Damn, I was already halfway down the road
when I realized it.
Where is it?
You're lucky Lion isn't here yet.
Hurry up and find it, then get going.
Where could it be?
Hurry up.
Here it is!
Whoa.
Did you hide it?
You found it. Now go.
Let me check first.
What if my money is gone?
Come on.
I CAN'T MAKE IT ANYMORE.
What's wrong?
Did he bail on you?
Mm.
He said work came up.
I'm glad you're here.
Can you please put that away?
Why should we?
If he doesn't show up, we eat it ourselves.
It's all good stuff.
Come on.
Wow. I plated these so beautifully.
Hey.
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
Come on!
The wine is expensive.
Let's try it.
You haven't even opened it. Come on.
Well…
At least this won't turn into food waste.
Don't worry about food waste.
I'm going to eat it all.
Do you want some wine first?
How much should I pour?
Is this enough?
Is this too much?
This is okay, right?
Wanna try it?
Since you're so proper, just have a little.
This is enough.
Come on.
Cheers.
Mmm…
Wow!
This could be served in a restaurant.
Come on, try it.
Come on.
Cheers.
You know what?
I used to dream that one day,
he'd propose to me on a plane.
Dream on.
Just don't drop dead when reality hits.
Listen.
Lion and I are perfect for each other.
Whether it's our careers
or our social status,
we elevate each other.
You get what I mean?
Sounds like it's all in your head,
if you ask me.
Hey, shut up!
Don't say that again.
Watch your mouth.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Careful, or you'll fall off and die.
I'm fine.
Put the glass down.
What are you doing? I'm fine.
How many fingers do you see?
One.
Two.
Ugh.
Three.
Hey, you're good.
90.
90, my ass!
Go to sleep. You're drunk.
Hey.
I mean, there's a 90% chance
Lion is cheating on me.
Why do you think that?
Remember that day when he bought
four lottery tickets from you?
He only gave me two.
I thought that was suspicious,
but I tried not to overthink it.
I've been fighting with the voice
in my head the whole time.
I try to believe it's all in my head
and that nothing's going on.
But you know what the hardest thing is?
Pretending nothing's going on
when my heart is already in pieces.
You look tired.
If you have to doubt
your partner like this,
you'll never be happy.
That's easy for you to say.
You don't understand love.
Your mind is always in the gutter.
Hey.
Don't judge me
by what you see on the outside.
On the inside,
I'm more sensitive than you think.
Sensitive, yeah?
Really? You're sensitive?
How sensitive? Huh?
Hey.
Hmm?
Go to sleep.
I'm fine.
Sensitive, huh?
♪ Even though you don't trust ♪
Hey.
- Hey.
♪ Someone who looks like trouble, like me ♪
I'm leaving now.
Yeah, just leave!
Just leave me like everyone else!
♪ Give me a chance ♪
- Go away, Pailin!
♪ Never mind your admirers ♪
♪ No matter how much they have to offer ♪
♪ Let me in a little, into your heart ♪
♪ Because I'm into you ♪
He's just my type.
♪ From the start, but I don't dare say it ♪
♪ Afraid you're just messing
with a hick like me ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Let's say my dream comes true ♪
♪ Like you have feelings for me too ♪
♪ My heart races
just thinking of me and you ♪
I'LL PROVE THAT LAST 10% TO YOU.
♪ Baby, it's true ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
(Next Episode)
How's it going?
I asked you to look into Lion.
Whose boyfriend are you?
When will I get to be your real boyfriend?
I really hate homewreckers.
Kanit sent you, didn't he?
Please give me a chance.
I'm giving you one week.
From now on, I'll do my best
to be a good boyfriend.
Your life goal is all about him, huh?
If you were my boyfriend,
you wouldn't have to try so hard.
I'd love you for who you are.