‪SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
‪ADAPTED FROM XI XING’S NOVEL
‪QUEEN CHU‪ ON QIDIAN.COM
I haven't congratulated
you yet, Grand Mentor.
Come on, Wangyou.
‪WANGYOU
Since when did you learn to tease people?
I feel happy for you.
After all these years,
you've finally made it.
But anyway, are you not worried?
Chu Zhao…
What do you know about her
that makes you help her?
You even abandon
the alliance with Xiao Xun.
I'm not helping Chu Zhao.
I'm securing
my own bright future.
Be careful. It may backfire.
The easier a game seems,
the more hidden threats there are.
We learned this when we were young.
It won't.
Because I always have a way out.
She knew Xiao Xun
would poison the young emperor.
In that case, she still used him as bait
just to get rid of Xiao Xun.
That was a risky move.
Fight to survive, fight to win.
I don't care who the Emperor is.
As long as I retain
my high standing.
I lost.
Mr. Deng, Old Madam invited you to dine.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have used you as bait.
I swore to the late emperor
I'd keep you safe.
But I put you in danger.
I don't deserve to be your sister.
Zhao, don't say that.
That was our plan.
Look. I'm all right now.
Don't be sad, Zhao.
My mother said
a handwoven longevity thread
embodied sincerity.
Every knot would bind good luck.
You made this for me by yourself.
I'm quite happy.
What do you think
if I pair it with a jade pendant?
Or a gold lock.
It would look more regal.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Don't say sorry to me.
We came up with the plan together
to catch the villain.
Sadly, it turned out to be Uncle Xun.
But I protected you.
I'm really happy about that.
Uncle, what food have you brought?
Feed me.
What a hassle.
You're not feeding a horse.
It's how soldiers feed people.
You're getting back at me.
You're slandering me.
I won't bring you food anymore.
Aren't you on duty?
How do you have time to bring food to Yu?
My cloak. Return it.
You don't like it, do you?
Why do you want it back now?
I intended to give it to someone else.
I lent that to you.
After you use it,
you give it back.
Take it then.
Uncle, what are you snatching?
I wasn't snatching.
I got back my own cloak.
Zhao, do you remember your promise?
Pretty, huh?
Like falling petals.
Here. Blow again.
You promised him this.
Why do I have to do it?
I order you to do this for me.
Is this swing sturdy enough?
It can hold both of us, right?
I won't play on this with you.
Why?
Swinging is so much fun.
It lets us see distant views.
Oh, boy.
You can go outside and see the views.
Why must you ride a swing?
Can I really go outside?
Come over.
Falling petals!
If you tie like this,
when you finish,
you'll sit on it and fall.
I'm making a tight knot.
How could we fall?
You can fall.
But if he falls,
it would be big trouble.
Don't underestimate me.
Your Highness, you just
wouldn't believe me until you fell.
How did this happen?
I'm sure I tied a tight knot.
Zhao, do you really know
how to make a swing?
We soldiers use this knot
to tie up prisoners.
Once tied,
no one can break free, whoever he is.
- Come on.
- I dare not.
You do it, Zhao.
Zhao.
Let Uncle Xun go back to Xiaonan.
Yu, what did you say?
Stop fighting him.
He's right.
The Lord of Xiaonan still holds power.
Xiao Xun is hard to deal with.
If he remains in the Capital
and fights you,
you'll both suffer.
This time, he escaped by luck.
Next time, he won't.
I know Xiao Xun has wild ambitions.
But what on earth did he do
that made you hate him?
He went in person to Yunzhong to propose.
I thought he cared
about you.
You…
You loved each other, didn't you?
Loved each other?
That's the stupidest thing I've ever done.
Even thinking of it
makes me sick now.
What have you been through?
Jiu,
do you believe
one can live a second life?
In my past life,
I married Xiao Xun as I wished
and became the Empress.
TAIJI HALL
Yet because of this,
I got my father killed.
So was my entire clan.
I was also strangled by Xiao Xun.
You think that's funny, don't you?
Just pretend it was a dream I had.
No.
Everything
exists for a reason.
My father told me
that people must bear
the consequences of their choices.
Just no regrets.
But this time,
you laid a trap for Xiao Xun.
He suffered a quiet defeat.
Once he's on guard,
killing him won't be easy.
He escaped by luck once.
I won't give him another chance.
Then, do you have a plan?
If I do, will you help me?
- Hit him!
Hit him!
CAPITAL
If I do,
will you help me?
I will.
The temple rite incident has concluded.
The accused were executed.
The imperial city
has been thoroughly purged.
Everyone should learn from this
and never make mistakes.
Oh.
I've been thinking.
Uncle Xun has been
a hostage for seven years.
How pitiful.
Shall we let him go back to Xiaonan?
What do you think?
Absolutely not.
Your Majesty, this is inappropriate.
I'm sure all the ministers have doubts.
Mr. Xie, you claimed
that His Majesty was wise.
But now you're questioning
His Majesty's decision.
That's not right, Mr. Deng.
I've thought about it.
Keeping Mr. Xiao as a hostage
was the late emperor's last wish.
And keeping him in the Capital
can restrain his father.
If we let him go,
changes may occur.
It makes sense, Mr. Xie.
But Xiao Xun has endured a lot here.
If any of that displeases his father,
it'll threaten the court's stability.
Your Highness, what do you think?
Am I entitled to participate in this?
By the late emperor's edict,
the Grand Princess and Grand Mentor
oversee the court.
So you are entitled.
Your Majesty
and ministers,
I've received
a secret report about the Northern Desert.
I didn't mean to stir up trouble,
but since Mr. Xie asked, I will be frank.
Unusual movements have frequently
occurred on the frontier.
Enemy troops seem to be massing.
In the Capital,
suspicious incidents have also occurred.
Everywhere, unidentified figures
are roaming.
They gather in secret
and behave suspiciously.
Your Highness,
can I read this report?
No.
This is a serious matter.
I need to verify
the authenticity of this report
or innocent people may be involved.
If this report is true,
what should we do?
Then the heir to the Lord of Xiaonan
must not leave the Capital.
Xiaonan Prefecture is adjacent
to the Northern Desert.
If they collude with each other…
The Lord of Xiaonan didn't come
to His Majesty's coronation.
It's hard to say
if he's been disloyal all along.
TWO HOURS AGO
Your Highness,
the Pine Soot Ink
is exclusive to the Xie Family.
You deliberately used it in this report.
What if the Xie Family
finds out?
That's exactly what I want.
If we release Xiao Xun,
we'll be releasing an enemy.
We'll lose all control over Xiaonan.
Once trouble arises,
Gaoyang will be affected.
Xie Yanfang is the head of his clan.
He wouldn't allow this to happen.
Therefore, he'll prevent it.
With the Pine Soot Ink from his clan,
in this matter,
he's fully bound to me.
I don't quite understand.
Why is Mr. Deng so eager
to have Mr. Xiao leave?
Isn't he supposed
to speak in your favor?
Court struggles have been like this.
No permanent enemies.
No permanent allies.
That's why I must drag the Xie Family in.
Because only an accomplice
will desperately keep a secret.
Even if this secret report
turns out to be false,
it has to be true.
I haven't mastered this move.
I'll practice more.
Living inside the palace,
you got news bout the Northern Desert.
You really have
good sources of information.
You weren't in the court,
but knew what happened there.
You're actually well-informed.
You want to drag the Xie Family in.
Do you know how dangerous
it could be?
Chu Zhao,
no one can play petty tricks
under Xie Yanfang's nose.
You're no exception.
I want to be an exception.
If he exposes
that you forged the secret report
and framed the Xie Family,
what will you do?
Still wait until the young kid
saves you again?
Then I'll say
you gave me that ink.
Let's see if Xie Yanfang
will abandon his brother.
No one can read his mind.
Jiu,
you will help me,
right?
You fought on the frontier for years.
You must know
the looks and dressing habits
of Northern Desert soldiers.
Can you tell me?
So,
you've had a plan.
What a perfect bait.
She faked a secret report
to confine Xiao Xun in the Capital.
Xiao Xun is so suspicious
that he'll take this for a trap.
Then he'll speed up his escape plan.
The spies I sent out told me
Chu Zhao arranged some men
to secretly bury weapons
along the way to Xiaonan.
When Xiao Xun reaches the border area,
fake Northern Desert soldiers
will get him.
Once Xiao Xun escapes,
he'll be shot dead immediately
in the name of collusion
and armed treason.
Grand Mentor,
once Xiao Xun dies,
you'll have no way out.
I have my own plans.
If Xiao Xun escapes the Capital,
I'll have rumors spread
that the heir to the Lord of Xiaonan
led Northern Desert soldiers in.
He'll be seen as a traitor
and killed on sight.
- If no obstacles arise…
- No obstacles.
If there are,
I'll destroy them.
A forgery woven from truth
is the hardest to disprove.
As someone reborn, I know it better
than anyone else.
The Lord of Xiaonan and his heir
do collude with Northern Desert foes.
Your Highness.
Any news?
Chu Zhao did receive a report
about you and your father
raising troops and colluding with foes.
How does she know all these things?
Over the past years,
I've stayed vigilant!
There's no way she could know
about the collusion thing.
This woman is cunning.
She must blind you with a pretense
and let down your guard.
No way.
If I stay here,
they can execute me
in public with that secret report.
But if I flee,
I'll be convicted of treason
and get killed there.
Whatever choice we make,
she will
firmly hold the initiative.
After years of planning,
will we fall like this?
That day in the court,
we actually had the upper hand.
How did things turn out like this?
What exactly went wrong?
What's gone is gone.
Don't bring it up.
But now,
maybe we have
a third option.
Still haven't found her?
Forgive us. We sent three teams on it.
We found her. We did.
Old Madam is back.
The Grand Princess sent her back.
Your Highness, my mother--
She has been sent back to rest.
I met your mother at the corner
of the West Market.
As I caught sight of her,
she was picking up vegetable leaves
from the ground.
Born in the countryside,
she's been frugal.
Only those who starved
would treasure every grain.
Just like people all desire wealth.
This is human nature.
It's her personal preference.
Please don't mock her.
Why would I mock her?
You truly have talent
to rise to the Grand Mentor
from a country boy.
Your hard work
is far beyond what others can imagine.
Such diligence
should be admirable.
This is the braided longevity thread.
Each knot
can bind good luck.
You didn't come here so late
just to give me this, did you?
I wonder if I can trade so much good luck
for something from you.
What is it?
Xiao Xun's life.
Are you so confident
that you can kill him?
Yes.
So, Mr. Deng,
please stay out of this.
Once Xiao Xun dies,
his treasures and forces
he has gathered in the Capital
all these years
will be yours.
Your Highness doesn't blame me
for opposing you in court?
I do.
If you ruin my plan,
I'll use these treasures
to have you killed.
Just kidding.
Don't worry, Mr. Deng.
So, you haven't told me your answer.
It's easy to have wealth.
But it's hard to have confidants.
Deal.
I always keep my word.
So, Mr. Deng,
hope you won't go back on yours.
I won't.
‪Your Highness,
‪Mr. Xie is here on His Majesty's order.
‪He's been waiting for long.
Waiting for me?
I'm just
enjoying the moon.
You're really in the mood.
You enjoy the moon
right in front of my palace.
Were you worrying about me
during my visit to Deng Yi's place?
So, you've been waiting for me.
In front of your Qiwu Palace,
the moonlight is rather bleak.
Bleak moonlight over a lonely minister.
Perfect.
I'm only here by the order of His Majesty.
I've been informed
that Xiao Xun will leave tomorrow.
How confident are you
he'll take the official road
as you planned?
Tomorrow, I'll send naval forces
to block all merchant ships
in the name of inspecting smuggled salt.
Once the dock is cut off,
Xiao Xun will have to take
the official road.
In that case,
I've arranged crossbowmen at Woniu Ridge.
Once Xiao Xun leaves the Capital,
he'll be shot to death right there.
Nothing shall go wrong tomorrow.
Rest assured.
Tomorrow, I'll lead the ambush myself.
Nothing will go wrong.
‪WATERWAY OF THE STATE OF CHU
Oh, Zhao.
I don't know why you do this to me.
But anyway,
you've failed to trap me.
Your Highness.
Xiao Xun ran off with his men.
- By the official road?
- No.
What?
The whole dock is blocked by naval forces.
To leave the Capital,
that is his only option. How come?
No trace of them
was found on the official road.
But our spies reported
that a merchant ship sailed earlier
at the third quarter of the Yin hour.
We've been tricked.
He escaped again.
Mr. Xie already led his men
to go after them.
Xie Yanlai.
I promised Her Highness
that you wouldn't live.
Are you sure Zhao wants me dead?
She loved me so much.
That was before.
Now,
she wants you dead.
I forgot to ask you.
The boy of the Wei Village
who survived alone…
Xiang.
Did he take revenge on you?
I'm Xiang. What's your name?
Xiang,
where are you?
It was all my fault.
Mr. Xie is seriously injured.
Thankfully, he was treated in time.
I've bandaged his wound.
I'll go make a prescription
to bring down his fever.
He lost too much blood.
He must rest very well to recover.
Your Highness, we got a tip.
Xiao Xun has fled to Xiaonan.
It will be even harder
to kill him.
I thought my plan was flawless.
Yet I was one move short.
Sorry to have dragged you into this.
You used to say you owed me.
Now,
I owe you.
Zhao.
Your Highness.
Have you found the man I asked for?
It's Fang Du, a follower of Deng Yi.
Last year, he became a Naval Commander.
Xiao Xun's ship managed to leave the dock
with his pass.
What a duplicitous Deng Yi.
Your Highness, why did you break in here
so late at night?
Mr. Deng,
I'm here to give you a present.
I've heard you like rare wood.
The golden-thread nanmu
is of noble grade.
I wonder if you like it.
No merit, no reward.
I'm not worthy
of this present.
How could you not be worthy?
You asked Fang Du
to give that permission.
You "helped" me really much.
How could I not reward you?
Buried underground,
this wood will never rot.
It's a perfect fit for your great merit.
You must be kidding.
Kidding?
I'm being really serious
to give you this reward.
What?
You don't like it?
Or will you defy my order?
I like it.
In that case, keep it very well.
Put it in the yard,
so you can look at it every day.
Without my order, it mustn't be removed.
Your Highness,
thank you for your reward.
You're welcome, Mr. Deng.
After all…
we have a long way to go.
If you think
the longevity thread is too long,
I can give you a shorter one.