‪SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
‪ADAPTED FROM XI XING’S NOVEL
‪QUEEN CHU‪ ON QIDIAN.COM
Is all this really necessary?
Weren't you afraid
she'd actually kill you?
Kill me?
It would plunge the court into chaos.
Her Highness was just trying
to humiliate me
and vent her spite.
So, are you breaking the pact
and making her your enemy?
The pact?
Since when has she ever cared for that?
She handed the Imperial Guard Tally
to a nobody from the Xie Family.
Is that her idea of sincerity?
If you had held the Tally,
she would have had
even less chance of survival.
Xiao Xun cannot die.
At least not yet.
Why?
Is this the fallback you mentioned?
The late Emperor's final edict.
Xiao Xun was the designated heir.
It was due to unforeseen complications
that the crown passed to Xiao Yu.
‪ONE DAY EARLIER
Your Highness.
My gates have been so deserted
that even the sparrows
give this place a wide berth.
It is truly rare
that you would actually reach out
to Tie Ying.
Your Highness, have you ever heard
of greatness biding its time
in the depths?
Mr. Deng, are you here
to teach me fortune-reading?
It is a pity
that your judgment has failed you
because there is no greatness
to be found here.
I am naught but a lamb to the slaughter.
No.
I am here to show you
a path to Xiaonan.
Also a path to help reclaim
your former glory.
Why help me?
The imperial court has always been
a treacherous place
of shifting tides.
I don't dare to stake everything
on a single play.
That was true then as it is now.
I am aiding you because I hold
a far more compelling hand.
This is the late Emperor's final edict.
You were the one
meant to inherit the throne.
Indeed, Your Highness.
This is a forgery.
- You…
- But I have the true one, too.
His Majesty has barely
ascended the throne.
Aren't you afraid
of being branded a rebel?
Precision is required to strike,
and clarity is needed to lead.
I aligned with Chu Zhao for a promise
she later broke, prompting my shift
to Your Highness.
My goal has stayed the same throughout.
Are you aware now, Your Highness?
When I claim my destiny,
the seat of Grand Mentor shall be yours.
Mr. Deng, you have a visitor.
So you've prepared your own coffin?
How kind of you to save
the court the expense.
Such prime golden-thread nanmu.
Not really.
It was bestowed by Her Highness.
I heard when the late Emperor
crushed the old dynasty,
the fallen ruler used this very timber
to immolate himself for his state.
I spoke inappropriately.
What brings you here, exactly?
There is a matter
I'm hoping you could shed some light on.
Do you know
Her Highness has besieged
the heir to the Lord of Xiaonan?
Of course.
Do you also know
that Xiao Xun has escaped?
I do.
Do you know
who let him go?
It was me.
Your honesty is quite touching.
Such an act proves
you have turned against Her Highness.
But have you considered
the weight of this coffin?
Can you carry it alone?
You came through the midnight rain
only for this?
I was wondering
if I were the one
letting Xiao Xun walk free,
would she have brought
this coffin
through my Xie Clan's front door?
Mr. Deng,
playing with fire
without a clan's backing is folly.
Beware you don't get burned.
I've long heard your mastery
of the board is unrivaled.
Might I invite you for a round?
It would be my honor.
‪MILITARY CAMP OF YUNZHONG PREFECTURE
General, the Northern Desert forces
know our defenses inside out.
They even have the exact locations
of our hidden sentries.
We must have a traitor.
Report!
Report. Urgent news from the Capital.
Her Highness faces impeachment.
The heir to the Lord of Xiaonan
has fled by night.
Imperial Guard Commander Fu Jiu
is wounded.
Is Jiu's condition severe?
Word is the Imperial Physicians
have consulted, and he is out of danger.
Is Zhao safe and sound?
Her Highness is unharmed.
Xiao Xun fled back to Xiaonan,
and now the Northern Desert invades
with such intimate knowledge
of our defenses.
Could it be a betrayal from within?
Pass the order.
The Third Battalion
is to redeploy to Langya Valley.
The Fifth is to set an ambush
at Yingzui Cliff.
Adjust the defensive line as planned.
Position the hidden troops
and wait for them to take the bait.
- Understood!
General!
General, what is this malady?
It worsens by the day.
Even medicine offers no relief.
It's nothing.
I'll lead the charge tomorrow.
No. You can barely stand.
This is an order.
An order is an order.
Yes.
Your Highness,
Mr. Xie has been recovering here
for three days now.
Though your title leaves
few who dare to criticize you,
the boundaries of decorum remain.
I fear the idle tongues outside
are already beginning to wag.
Since I entered these imperial walls,
when have the rumors ever stopped?
The Censorate is bent on branding me
as "a hen ruling the roost".
Besides,
his injuries are deep.
I won't risk leaving him to others.
Is it because Your Highness
has feelings for him
that you refused to marry Mr. Xiao?
After all our time together,
is that truly how you see me?
No. I spoke out of turn.
Please, do not be angry.
Every string in this palace
must be mine to pull.
But he is more than just a pawn.
He is…
different.
How?
I used him,
and yet, I trust him
more than anyone else.
Regardless,
he is different.
Urgent news from the frontier!
The Northern Desert has attacked Yunzhong.
No.
My report was a forgery.
How could it possibly be real?
Since Her Highness forged the report
of collusion between the Lord of Xiaonan
and the Northern Desert
and tried to drag my family
into this using Pine Soot Ink,
she should have been prepared
for the possibility that her scheme
could spark a real war.
Playing the game,
one must always keep a backup plan.
You look refined,
yet your style of play is ruthless.
You flatter me.
I just dislike wasting time.
However,
patience is the true essence
of Weiqi games.
At the start of this match,
you were full of confidence,
weren't you?
But look at it now.
The situation has changed.
Do my skills meet with your approval?
Your skill…
- is exceptional.
- Good.
Since you enjoy watching,
I shall set several games in motion.
But a board too full
leaves no clear opening.
Beware lest you find no way out.
You're awake.
Are you in any pain?
I failed my mission.
I've dragged you down with me
and gotten you injured.
Deng Yi sent his men
to issue orders at the docks,
which gave Xiao Xun
a chance to escape by water.
I thought it was foolproof.
Yet…
The game at court is never that simple.
Such is the nature of power.
Tell me.
How do you want me to repay this debt?
I can grant you one wish.
I've never believed in divinity.
I have no wishes.
Then is there nothing you wish to achieve?
No.
Very well.
Then let the debt stand for now.
When you decide what you want,
just come to me.
With your skills,
you shouldn't be this badly hurt.
What really happened that day?
Tie Ying
used hidden weapons.
I let my guard down and got ambushed.
Just as I thought.
They only resort
to such despicable tricks.
Last night, I saw you having a nightmare.
You seemed burdened by something.
As you said,
everyone has their own secrets.
True. But I shared mine with you.
You mean that dream?
Alright.
As an exchange,
I'll tell you a secret.
Actually…
I…
CAPITAL
I once sneaked a bite of the jujube cakes
you got for your father
and paid for it with a beating.
Thank you for sharing that.
It's just…
I'll never make that again.
No matter.
I never liked those pastries anyway.
I was thinking of making you
something else to eat.
Sounds good.
Jiu, my hairpin is a bit askew.
Fix it for me, would you?
Good, right?
Six hours at the stove,
steamer after steamer,
all for a flawless batch.
It's truly the finest delicacy
in the world.
You should've mixed the filling properly.
The ratio of lard has to be exact.
Too little or too much ruins it.
I see.
My father always said
too little makes it dry
and too much makes it greasy.
It's my fault.
I have been away from Yunzhong for so long
that I have forgotten
the recipe.
In fact,
I was never very skilled
at making these pastries to begin with.
Father, see? I made it.
I finally mastered jujube cakes.
Well done.
Just try not to sneak
the filling next time.
Father, don't scare me.
I just missed my mother.
I didn't grow up by her side,
so I wanted to take a look.
To look at the sights she saw
and walk the lanes she walked.
If Mother were still alive,
she wouldn't want me
to be an obedient girl.
She wouldn't be as arrogant as you.
She would care about my feelings.
Yeah. You're the undefeated God of War.
You're the esteemed Guard General.
You're busy protecting frontier people.
You're busy forging your fame.
You're too busy
to ask your daughter
what she really wants!
Missing someone
is nothing to be ashamed of.
And neither is being homesick.
During the years I spent
by your father's side,
he seemed truly content.
He kept himself busy,
but whenever he got rare spices
from the Western Regions,
he would tuck them away
in the room at the southern courtyard.
When he went out on patrol,
if he saw a lovely sprig of blossoms,
he would bring it back
to plant in that courtyard.
He told me it was where you once lived,
and so he kept it in order
for your return.
Chu Zhao.
Your father never blamed you
for your leaving.
He only wanted to know
whether you were doing well.
He has missed you, that's all.
You don't have to respond to any of this.
These are his feelings to carry.
So please don't be too hard on yourself.
No one needs to be forgiven.
Actually,
I miss him terribly too
and everything about the desert.
He is a man of stern discipline
yet with a tender heart.
Much like you.
The first time he took me
to the desert poplar forest,
he said every withered branch there
was fighting desperately to stay alive,
which is what shaped
this timeless landscape.
Dying is easy.
Living takes true strength.
Jiu.
My apologies.
I've said too much.
Not at all.
I'm glad to hear you speak your mind.
It's late and cold.
Please get some rest, Your Highness.
Thank you
for telling me about my father
and for sharing your past with me.
You are welcome.
Consider it repayment
for that pastry.
Then please take this box
of red bean cakes.
I appreciate it.
What I said today still stands.
From now on,
whatever wish you hold,
you may ask it of me.
Come fire or high water,
I will see it fulfilled.
I honor my promises and never renege.
Alright. I understand.
Report!
Your Highness, urgent news from Yunzhong.
The Northern Desert invaded yesterday.
General Chu drove them back,
but collapsed shortly after.
He hasn't woken up.
General. The enemy has withdrawn!
Exactly as you predicted.
Your foresight secured our victory.
General.
‪LORD OF XIAONAN'S MANOR
Father.
Are you hurt?
You may not know,
but Chu Ling's daughter
seeks to finish me off for good.
Chu Ling's daughter?
The one who refused to marry you
and only ever wanted
to be the Grand Princess?
The throne changes and chaos follows.
We and Yunzhong hold each other in check.
The Xie Clan of Gaoyang
eyes us with greed.
Yet she moved first to purge
our army in the Capital,
then used your plight
to build her power in the court.
Such methods are truly masterful.
This upheaval plunges
the Capital into chaos.
- Perhaps we…
- The essence of alchemy lies
within the mastery of fire.
When the Yellow Emperor
forged his cauldron,
the Loong's roar emerged after 49 days.
When the alchemists refined mercury,
the rosy aura condensed after 81 nights.
It all comes down to the precise moment.
Opening the cauldron
before completion risks failure.
‪LORD OF XIAONAN, XIAO HONG
You must be weary from the road.
Get some rest.
Yes.
General Chu Ling
shall be held negligent
for the Northern Desert's incursion.
Yes, they breached our frontiers,
but it is also true General Chu
led them into a void.
No reward for his merit,
yet only a trial for his fault?
Since he took command,
victory has been his solemn duty.
Had Yunzhong fallen,
the consequences
would've been catastrophic.
Merit cannot offset such a grave failing.
Your Majesty,
Chu Ling has been lax
in disciplining his troops
and must be held to account.
- Seconded.
Chamberlain, your concern
for the state is commendable.
But I must ask this.
No sooner had Xiao Xun
fled back to Xiaonan,
than the invasion happened.
Is this striking coincidence
proof of collusion from within?
Your Highness reminded me of something.
As I recall,
Mr. Deng argued most fervently
for Xiao Xun's pardon,
claiming it was to appease
the Lord of Xiaonan.
Such impeccable timing
for a show of mercy.
Watch your words, Mr. Xie.
His Majesty decreed
Xiao Xun's pardon and return.
Who am I to challenge the throne?
Word has it you've set your sights
on Xiao Xun's residence.
It is a place of great vantage.
Better to use it than waste it.
His Majesty, in his infinite mercy,
bestowed it upon me.
What?
- You wish for it as well?
- Enough.
With the Northern Desert encroaching,
our priority is to steady the troops.
As for the cancer within…
I shall see for myself
who is so desperate to usher in the enemy.
I am weary.
Should you have no other matters,
you may take your leave.
- We bid farewell to Your Majesty
- and Your Highness.
Who would have thought Xie Yanfang
would show his hand so brazenly?
Since he dared tell you
he would bring
the Grand Princess a true war,
he clearly fears nothing,
knowing we lack the evidence
to move against him.
Indeed.
The very fact he said it proves
he has a contingency plan in place.
Even if we sent men to investigate now,
they would find nothing.
Xie Yanfang is guarded
like an iron fortress.
But even the tightest defense has a flaw.
Why not start by digging
into his place in Gaoyang?
When he came to the Capital,
he brought all his men with him.
The rest at the Gaoyang estate
are of no consequence.
You are right, though.
To strike at the heart of the threat,
one must first brave the lion's den.
Shao You.
Send men to Gaoyang at once.
Understood.
Mr. Xie,
better mind your moves in this game.
PRINCE XIAO XUN'S RESIDENCE
Move more to the left. Higher.
XIE RESIDENCE
That's it. Get down.
With that plaque in place,
the whole estate seems brighter.
Mr. Xie, rumors have it
Guard General Chu Ling's negligence
allowed the breach.
Do you think he'd be like Xiao Xun,
colluding with the enemy?
If Xiao could survive such dire straits,
so can he.
Having spent years at the frontier
with an undefeated record,
the prestige he holds among the people
can not be undone by a single lapse
in judgment.
We may have orchestrated the invasion,
but his swift tactical shift
lured the enemy to Xinggu Pass
and secured a total victory.
Many now laud his braveness and mind.
It seems we've only served
to further his renown.
True.
Just as you are renowned
throughout the land.
Though away from court for years,
your foundation remains unshakable.
No.
He and I…
have never been the same.
Since the estate is renovated,
send for Yanlai.
Tell him it is the Master's command
that he return at once.
He's always been at odds with your family.
Why this?
I am merely curious.
After five years, does the hound…
still know its leash?
Blessings and calamities coexist.
Great fortune is accompanied
by great danger.
‪CHU TANG, COUSIN OF CHU ZHAO
This title may not prove to be
a shield for the Chu Family.
Of course,
I am grateful for Uncle's care years ago.
It's just…
Should I fall from this height,
as family, you will
inevitably be implicated.
So, you'd better plot your own course.
Zhao, no need to test me.
From the day you attained this title,
the Chu Family rises and falls with you.
Very well.
Then,
from now on,
I shall maneuver in the light,
while you operate in the shadows.
I'll be your fortress,
and you'll be my reach.
If we win, we shall share
in glory and splendor.
If we fail…
I am yours to command.
Please keep faith with your pledge.
After this tea,
there is no turning back.
Now that I depart the Capital,
I must rally every available ally
to hold the court for me.