Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart.
Again, you're running from me.
Following you around
is making me lonely.
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby.
Told me not to love, but I already fell.
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well.
Baby, I’m crush on ya.
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart.
Hello there, my darling.
If you were a laundry,
I'd be your Rinse Charming.
Ready for love,
I have two shoulders for you to lean over,
Even though they feel heavy,
carrying my own beauty (Yep)
I know, I'm just your type, aren't I?
You're so hot like fire (Huh?!)
Because my heart burns for you (Right!)
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love.
Baby, I wanna tell you something…
I love you!
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart.
Please take care
of Kluayhom for me.
Working together
is gonna be fun.
It's totally gonna be fun.
Higher!
A little lower.
Ugh!
Pay attention when you film!
I am paying attention!
I think.
Kluayhom is definitely
planning on nailing Fu tonight.
We meet again.
How did you get here?
You're Kluayhom, aren't you?
I'm so happy you invited us today.
Wait!
I'm gonna keep going, of course.
I'm not giving up that easily.
(About you and them,
are you gonna move on or keep going?)
(I'm gonna keep going, of course.
(I'm not giving up that easily. Go, go!)
(Good morning, M.
(Any good advice for me today?)
This early in the morning?
What a diligent one.
(The weather is nice today, so send them
(a simple text to light up their morning)
(Sure, thank you, Tutor M)
What text should I send you, my Moo-Moo?
(Handsome hotel's CEO
we won't gatekeep)
Aww!
Mr. Fu's face card is so insane,
it's basically a benefit
for the female staff working here.
Including queer folks.
- Right?
- Right on!
Especially when
he's on camera. Like, wow...
His aura devours the whole place.
I'd say his handsomeness
is this year's extra bonus, girl!
True.
If there were an award for
the most handsome hotel owner of the year,
I'd nominate him.
Mm, totally agreed.
He's a total 10, 10, and 10, no buts!
This is totally serving.
Ooh, look!
- So handsome!
- Hello, everyone.
- Oh, hi!
- Hi!
Why are you here so early?
Well, Mr. Fu said
he wanted to have a word with me,
so I rushed here.
Oh!
It must be about him going on a show!
Ooh, a show!
Then, best of luck today.
- Best of luck!
Thank you.
- I'm gonna get going now.
- Alright!
Is Fu's handsomeness
really a company benefit here?
Even when he's not being delusional, that is.
But when he acts all serious...
Yuck!
My Moo-Moo!
Are you finally here?
This fan still works.
Please take it with you, Mr. Fu.
The weather is really nice today,
don't you think?
Mm.
What's this about?
Why are you calling me in so early?
You asked me first today...
Moo-Moo, you do care about
what's going on in my life!
Well, it's my job.
So...
there's really nothing much to it.
I just want to let you know
that the show that I'm gonna be on
has asked me to shoot in the upcountry.
We're finally
going to spend the night out of town.
Are you okay with that?
Mm, I... I'm fine.
We're not gonna sleep
in the same room or anything.
Right...
Also...
I want you
to handle the script for the show.
I believe you can do it.
Right?
Script...
What kind of script do you want?
Uh... what kind of image would you like to show?
Tell me, so I can figure it out.
Just...
the camera
capturing my handsome face
is all I ask for.
That's probably
gonna be good enough to perfect the show.
Though
whatever you're into,
you can stick to that.
I'll turn in blank paper, then.
I'm gonna head out now.
He's gonna turn in blank paper...
What does that mean, Mr. Fu?
It means...
He's into everything about me,
so much so that he couldn't
possibly express it in written words.
Oh!
Enough of that.
Sorry...
Hey, here come the snacks.
Here you go.
Whoa...
Tee's making that face again.
If you'd spent all this time
planning how to pick on Jeab
on studying instead, you would've become
a top student in the country by now.
Yeah, right?
There are no thoughts
in his head all day.
I guess...
he only thinks of Jeab.
Think of whom?
Watch your mouth.
Why would I think of that Little Chicken?
There's nothing about him to think of.
I meant,
all you think about is Jeab
and how you're gonna pick on him!
Are you planning on doing nothing all day
but picking on him?
Well, look at him.
He spends his lunch break doing homework.
How is that right?
Were you spawned on
the same server as us, Tee?
He's doing the right thing,
while everything you did is wrong.
Hey!
- Jeab...
- Why are you always studying?
Whatchu doing?
Hey, what are you up to here?
- Can I have this?
- Jeab, whatchu doing?
- Let me see.
- Ooh!
Hey, they are taking Jeab's notebook.
I know these guys.
They're always going around,
taking people's stuff!
I'll have this one.
- No need to work on it anymore.
- Wow, Biology.
- Damn it, don't fuss.
- Let's go, guys.
- Thanks, dude.
- Yeah, you stay right here.
Kew, Tomo,
take care of Jeab.
James, Win,
come with me.
That tofu-face wrote such nonsensical stuff.
Take a look.
What do you have here?
These snacks look fucking unappetizing.
Here, take a look.
Whoa, what the hell is this drawing?
Come on, look at this.
Hey, the fuck are you staring at?!
Something on my face?
You took his stuff and don't
bother taking good care of it?
Why?!
Is that tofu-face your little boyfriend?
- Don't you think?
- Whoa...
Is this guy his boyfriend?
He definitely is!
And what about it?
Give me back my notebook.
Give me that.
Here.
Uh-uh.
I'm not giving it to you.
He's too chickenshit to fight you, I bet.
You can tell from his look.
What?
You gonna punch me?
I will say this one last time.
Give me back my notebook.
He definitely doesn't have it in him.
Don't you think?
- He's a fucking wimp.
- Come on.
- You wanna fight?
- Punch me!
Chickenshit!
I'm sticking my face out for you.
Go ahead and fucking do it!
Ooh...
- Fuck!
- Whoa!
He really did it!
Shit, get him!
Ow!
Ow...
Want some more?
Wait. I give up, I give up.
You can have this back.
Win, that's enough.
Aren't you tired?
I am.
Let's go.
Hey, Tee.
There,
that Little Chicken.
Bro, don't ask for another punch.
Only I can call him by that name.
Go on, give that notebook back to him.
Jeab!
Whoa...
My notebook.
How did you have it?
I came across it.
It was on the corridor.
Hey,
wait.
What happened to your mouth?
I ate something spicy.
Something spicy?
Only one corner of your mouth, though?
It's a new variety of chili.
You wouldn't know it.
Hey,
so you ate something spicy?
Must have been a huge chili, huh?
Gigantic.
So freaking huge.
Guys,
take me to the nurse's office.
It really hurts.
What?
- Come on, come on.
- Alright, let's go.
Please come in.
I brought the script for you to review.
If there's anything
you want to change, just tell me.
Thank you.
Fu, do you have some time for me?
I just think there are some questions
that you need to seriously rehearse.
Hm...
If it's for you...
Mm...
I'd give you... a lifetime.
Fu, you're fooling around again.
This show is for the sake of your image.
Take it seriously.
I've always taken it seriously,
especially when it comes to you;
I'm very, very serious!
If you're still
playing around, I'm gonna leave.
In your eyes,
am I really the type to fool around?
What does it take
for you to see that I'm serious?
Be yourself.
If that's what you want to do,
then just be yourself.
But right now,
you have to focus
on the script I wrote for you
because it's gonna go
on my portfolio, too.
Understood?
Understood.
I...
trust you.
I won't give you a hard time.
Pay attention to the rehearsal, too.
Okay.
Fu,
when you're on the show,
you need to focus on the host.
When you don't,
you have to look at the cameras.
But you can't get carried away
and stare at the floor.
If you do this,
you'll come across as
someone who's not at all confident.
It's improper and dreadful.
Then, if I get unconfident,
I'll look at you.
But why would you?
I'm not on the show with you or anything.
That's because I've already
placed my confidence in you.
I'm confident that...
there is no one in this world
more into you than I am!
Cheeky.
"Mr. Fu, what do you think
is the charm of Golden Peony Hotel
that makes it stand out
from the other hotels?"
The answer is...
I believe that
the hotel's charm is the staff members.
I always tell my staff
that the customer is not king,
but a family that
we have to take really good care of
so that they feel warm at heart,
as though they're in a nice, big home
with maids to care for them.
Hm...
That's a heartwarming answer.
But I do think it's a little forced.
Besides,
people who stay at our hotel
probably don't really feel like
it's their own home.
Then...
do you mind
if I change it up a little bit?
So...
how are you gonna change it?
Do give me a suggestion.
I like how you say that the hotel's charm
lies in its staff,
because service is at
the heart of the hotel business.
But the part I'd like to change
is probably...
Last question:
As an executive at Golden Peony Hotel,
what do you think makes the hotel
so charming that people want to come back?
To me,
the charm of Golden Peony Hotel
is neither its luxury nor perfection,
but a feeling.
A feeling...
and an experience like no other.
As soon as they step in,
they find a place where they can truly relax.
I want this place
to be somewhere...
people would want to come and stay,
and feel joy just from being there.
No matter if they come as families,
couples,
friends,
or even by themselves,
our hotel
is somewhere they'd feel safe
and at ease every time they visit.
If the guests are at ease,
I believe
they will certainly come back.
But most flatulently...
Most importantly!
Me importantlost...
Eek!
Most importantly!
Most importantly...
Eek!
Man, he got it right!
I did!
Oh... you... You did...
And most importantly,
the charm of our Golden Peony Hotel
is each and every one of our staff members.
All of us
are ready to take care of you
until you are truly impressed.
That's a simple yet sincere answer.
No wonder Golden Peony Hotel
is in everyone's demand
for a good experience.
Thank you so much, Mr. Fu.
You gave such great answers.
The viewers are gonna love it.
All thanks to your staff, too.
Also, I apologize for any mistakes today.
It's all good.
That's what editing is for.
But you already
gave perfect answers as is.
They were very natural.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Also, how was
the watermelon juice you requested?
Is it good?
I suppose it's really good.
Yes.
Then, please excuse me.
Of course.
Is it good?
Fu,
since the work has been completed
ahead of schedule,
the producer team said that
we can watch the sunset around here.
Are you interested?
What's wrong with your eyes?
Nothing.
Well...
Are you in, Moo?
If you aren't tired yet...
Then, sure.
From here,
the view is so nice, isn't it?
While we're looking
at something like this,
it makes us feel like
we're just small entities, doesn't it?
Compared to the sky,
we're actually that small.
Even the vast sky
still has to shine on me.
Ouch... Ow...
Excuse me...
Could I jump in
and tell you something, Fu?
What's wrong, Ryan?
Um...
Well...
My stomach is churning a bit.
What do you mean by "a bit"?
Oh, I mean
if I don't rush now,
I might become another landmark here.
But...
you have to go down for a while
until you find a toilet.
Whoa.
You can go, Ryan.
You don't need to give me
such a detailed report.
And don't forget
to return this to the staff.
Yes, sir.
So please allow me to defend
the secretary's honor first.
Ow, it's running down my legs now.
Ugh.
Look there, Fu.
So beautiful.
Very beautiful.
Beautiful as always.
Beautiful as always?
You said as if you've always been
looking at it.
Yeah.
I've always had my eyes on you.
Only you.
Haven't you felt it?
Ryan hasn't come yet.
I don't know if he's lost.
Mmm... Yeah.
I think so.
It's thundering.
How come?
Moo, I think we should go
before it rains. Let's go.
Let's wait for the rain to ease up
before finding our way back.
You'd better wear my jacket first.
Take it.
- Oh...
- You'll be cold.
You gave me your jacket,
then what about you?
I'm fine.
Your shirt is so thin, see?
Wearing mine is better.
But you'll be cold.
You know that I'm a cozy man.
A little bad weather
won't bother me at all.
Well,
a cozy man.
Shaking this hard,
when will you get cozy, Fu?
Being this close to each other will warm us up.
Moo...
Won't you feel uncomfortable?
It's better than letting you get cold.
This can help warm us up, you know?
When will it stop raining, huh?
It's late now.
I'm so sorry, Moo.
Why did you say sorry?
Because...
I couldn't remember the way back,
and I put you through this.
That's fine.
Ryan is about to come.
Oh, Ryan.
When he's back,
I'm gonna demote him
to a security guard.
Fu!
I'd like to thank you, though,
for...
taking me to watch the sunset.
That was incredible.
Yeah, it...
It was incredible.
Jeab.
- Yes.
- Your writing is better, isn't it?
It's because...
I put my mind to it.
How to pronounce this?
This reads
"hon o yomu."
- "Hon o..."
- It means reading books.
I see.
Tutoring?
Fu.
If you're cold, just say so.
If you can't handle it, just say so.
You don't need to sacrifice this much for me.
I don't feel good at all,
seeing you suffer for me.
Good love is about both people giving,
not just one person constantly receiving.
Why are you smiling?
Did you just...
say "good love"?
Uh...
Did you see love from me
as a good love already?
You don't mind me anymore, right?
Right, Fu.
I'm curious.
So many people approach you.
Aren't you interested in any of them?
Yeah, he's right!
I was wondering the same.
Or...
do you already
have someone in your heart?
Jeez, someone in my heart, my ass.
There's no one.
I'm happy as is,
so why bother having someone?
But I do see that there's someone
following you around.
Someone... Who?
Do you mean Moo?
Yeah, that's him!
He seems so simple and mid.
It's gonna be tasteless if you date him.
True. How's that gonna be any fun?
It's gotta be someone spicy, you know?
- Yeah!
- Mm!
Right, maybe Moo is just your type?
Do you like nancy pants or something?
Like little nancy boys and stuff!
Hey!
You're going too far, don't you think?
Someone like me being into him?
He's too wimpy.
- Burn!
You bet my type is...
someone spicy.
- Right on!
- That's right.
- Though...
- Nice.
You guys don't have to talk about him anymore.
Let him be.
Yeah, you're right.
I can't even imagine Fu
being with someone so wimpy.
How would that even work?
Hey, let's get back to work.
- Yeah, work.
- So fast.
Hey, get to work.
Someone like me being into him?
He's too wimpy.
So what if I am wimpy?
Do I not have feelings if I am?
(For Fu, from Moo-Moo)
Just you wait.
From now on,
I'm not gonna be into you anymore!
Those Chinese-looking guys
with only looks to offer...
Don't even think
you'd ever win my heart again.
You know,
the reason I always run from you
isn't that I hate you.
But...
it's because you didn't like
someone wimpy like me.
Sometimes, I wonder...
why you're so persistent in chasing me
even though
you didn't even like what I was.
Moo...
you heard everything?
Yes.
In your eyes,
I'm just a wimpy boy
chasing after you.
But do you know
that word wasn't what wounded me.
What hurt me the most
was the fact that the word
came out...
from someone I was so into.
Moo,
I'm sorry.
If I'd known you were there,
I wouldn't have said it.
No, that's not it.
I shouldn't have even said it
behind your back in the first place.
Do you know
that I was never disgusted by you
or thought you weren't good enough?
And when I said the word "wimp",
it wasn't something I thought badly of,
because to me,
you...
are someone.
I want to spend the rest of my life with.
Then why did you say it?
Because...
I was a coward.
Coward?
Well...
those friends of mine were potty-mouthed.
They always speak before they think.
And I...
didn't want to hear them
always badmouthing about you,
so I thought I had to get it over with.
Though, do you know
what I was dying to tell them?
I wanted to tell them,
Yeah,
I'm so, so into him.
I want him in my sight every day.
I want him next to me.
And I never once have a second thought
about being into him.
And I want you to know...
that no matter who you are,
I will always love you.
The stars are beautiful, aren't they?
Yeah.
Are you still cold, Moo?
No.
It's cozy.
If you feel uncomfortable,
you can tell me.
I'll let go.
I'm not uncomfortable.
This is kinda nice.
At first,
I thought today
would be a bad day
since I put you through so much.
Turns out,
today was actually
another good day since...
Fu! Fu!
Fu.
I'm really sorry.
At first, I thought it wouldn't take this long.
I didn't think there would be a sequel...
Well,
you can continue then.
Do you want me to film a spin-off
and come back tomorrow?
Ah...
Why is it this dirty, huh?
Phew, that was close.
Did you kick me just now?
No, I didn't.
Hey, Fu! Fu!
Do you want me to...
I just wanted to ask
if you wanted me to leave the car with you.
My bed.
I'm so glad that a fluffy bed like this
exists in this world.
I'm on cloud nine.
It's me, Moo-Moo.
Here it is.
I brought you some hot tea
so that you can relax well.
Actually, you don't need to
bring it yourself.
You can tell the staff,
or let me get it myself.
So you can take some rest.
I want to bring it to you myself
as an excuse for seeing your face.
Thank you.
By the way,
won't you let me in to sip some tea?
Are you expecting anything?
I'm also cold, though.
I'm so cold.
Maybe not yet.
Wait, Moo!
Tutor M, today, I'm so glad
because I already confessed
my love to him.
I kinda got ahead of myself.
Also, I'm in front of his room now.
Should I knock on his door?
Of course, yes.
You've come this far.
There is no way back.
Hello, Tutor M.
Your top is here.
Fu!!
But we already agreed
that we'd never let
the people at the hotel know
that we are...
Dating?
- A mosquito! A mosquito!
- Oh, a mosquito.
Kim,
Kim, Kanklao Tangwatthanakul,
the one and only son of Uncle Chalermchai.
This Kim
is totally Fu's type.
Me? Jealous?
Who told you that?
Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart.
Again, you're running from me.
Following you around
is making me lonely.
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby.
Told me not to love, but I already fell.
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well.
Baby, I’m crush on ya.
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart