Brother Jun
Even if you beat me to death
I still can't come up with the money
Brother Jun
Run!
You two idiots
got yourselves trapped inside the resort
and can't do a damn thing
So what now?
Brother Jun
Whatever you say goes
We'll do whatever you tell us
Whatever I say goes?
Will you obey?
Yes, we'll obey
We'll obey
Then, Brother Jun
Obey, obey, we'll obey
Brother Jun
This was our oversight too
We were wrong
I had no idea something like this
could happen at the resort
Brother Jun
I apologize to you
I sincerely apologize to you
Please accept this
I...
Who the hell are you?
Hello, sir
I'm Yu Tianfang, the GM of this resort
A guest just made a complaint
that the noise from your room
might be a bit too loud
This is a VIP room
We're all distinguished VIP guests
Who's snitching on me?
Got nothing better to do?
Got too much free time?
Can't they mind their own business?
Sir
Please calm down
Let's keep it civil, shall we?
Civil, my ass!
This is my job too
And I hope you can
show some understanding
For your room
I'll give you a 20% discount
Just keep the volume down a bit
Alright?
Get lost!
You're no good
I'll beat the crap out of you
Congratulations
General Manager Yu
Keep it low-key
Low-key
You know me
I've never cared about fame or fortune
I only wish to serve the people
Cut the act
You're parading that GM title around
afraid no one knows you got promoted
Who would've thought?
You and Zhao Yan fought it out
And in the end
he ended up paving the way for you
Our resort's
performance has been sliding lately.
Boss Bai
made me the general manager
hoping our resort's revenue would
soar, soar, soar.
So Boss Bai can
earn, earn, earn.
It's lonely at the top.
Get it?
You chose this path yourself.
Whether it's fortune or disaster,
you bear it yourself.
Either way,
it's got nothing to do with me.
Siqi,
what I need right now
more than anything
is your loving support.
Get away from me.
I'll sue you for workplace harassment.
Qi-baby,
don't tell me
you don't like
the me who's now at the peak
of his career?
Only someone whose brain is waterlogged
and frozen into an idiot
would ever like you.
You're shy.
Too embarrassed
to admit you like me?
It's okay.
Take your time.
Yu Tianfang,
I'm telling you very seriously
and earnestly,
there's someone I like.
I have a boyfriend.
Give up while you can.
Mr. Yu,
I'm clocking out now.
Goodbye.
Get some rest early.
Dad,
I'm at work.
What?
A blind date?
I just became general manager
and people are setting me up already?
Am I really that in demand now?
Right now?
Right here at our resort?
Table six.
Siqi.
You heard it too.
I might need a favor from you now.
My dignity is all in your hands.
Haven't I made myself clear?
Just as colleagues.
Come on, help me out.
Not going.
My dignity all depends on you.
Hello.
Here's the thing.
My dad,
insisted I come to this blind date.
But I'll say upfront,
I already have someone else in mind.
We're just doing this for the old folks.
Just going through the motions.
So,
let's get started quickly.
Officer Qin?
What are you doing here?
That dramatic?
Am I really that scary?
No, no, no.
You're not scary at all.
You're beautiful,
have a great job,
and your detective skills are top-notch.
With your qualifications,
do you really need a blind date?
Blind dates aren't shameful.
On the contrary, I think
it's a very efficient way to find a partner.
Do background checks beforehand,
then meet up,
discuss views on marriage,
on life,
on values.
If compatible, get together.
If not,
then go our separate ways.
Right, right, right.
Here, you first.
This is much faster than waiting for fate.
After all,
time is money.
If we're not a match,
no one wastes anyone's time.
Being with you,
time really flies.
Another year, just like that.
To our anniversary,
cheers.
Thank you, hubby.
Come on.
Quite a crowd.
A lot of people showed up today.
Based on our previous case work,
and my full understanding of you,
your current qualifications
don't quite meet my standards yet.
Actually,
I think your qualifications are pretty average too.
They're far from what my family
set as the standard for a wife.
Way off.
What standard?
Let's hear it.
My dad
is pushing me to have kids soon.
You'd have to give me at least two.
Of course,
the more the better.
No upper limit.
In short, it boils down to this:
a virtuous wife and loving mother.
Officer Qin,
what do you think
of these conditions?
Sorry,
I just love being a cop.
Isn't there supposed to be a band?
We started early today.
Here, eat up.
I'm gonna
in a bit,
give everyone here
a surprise.
Look at you.
Today's a happy day, happy day.
I'm off.
Sorry.
It's fine.
My pleasure.
Pleasure.
My favorite book to read
is anatomy.
The living come in all kinds,
but the dead are all equal.
Just like this bullfrog.
This...
This isn't what I meant.
This standard
was set by my family.
As for me,
I have absolute respect for the police.
Especially female officers.
I mean...
Officer Qin, just look,
Um, Officer Qin.
Tianfang here just has a loose tongue.
Don't take it to heart.
Officer Qin,
my heart truly belongs to someone already.
Today is just...
going through the motions to please the elders.
I'm really sorry.
Today is the wedding anniversary
of me and my wife, Xu Lingling.
To celebrate,
every table here today
will receive a bottle of
Bordeaux Legend Lafite, on me.
Great, great, great!
Let's congratulate them together!
Come on,
to show our congratulations,
have a drink with me.
Come on.
Cheers, cheers!
Great, thank you, thank you.
Thanks, thanks, thanks.
Thank you all, thank you all.
Great, great, great.
Come on.
Mr. Wang.
It's good being rich.
Just buying a bottle of wine
costs half a year of my salary.
Too bad
we don't have Lafite here.
He really pulled off that flex.
Wishing you a happy marriage.
I'm so jealous!
You look
just like someone I knew
back when I was young.
Who?
Could it be your first love?
A woman I once loved.
Mr. Wang,
saying things like this,
aren't you afraid your wife will get jealous?
I'm serious about every relationship.
I treat them all the same.
I'm gonna step out for a smoke.
Mind if we have a word?
Sure.
Officer Qin,
this big shot hosting the meal
is a friend of Boss Bai.
So I
have to go offer a toast too.
Wait.
Didn't I already tell you?
The two of us really aren't suited.
Chu Feng?
What are you doing here?
I'm on a mission.
Keep quiet.
Wait,
you're tailing someone?
Who?
Don't ask what you shouldn't.
You're supposed to be undercover,
yet here you are actually going on a real date?
No, wait,
would you believe me if I said this was an accident?
I just happened to be at this table
when he came over.
Are you kidding me?
Come on,
are you making a fool of me?
Just go through the motions.
Don't cause trouble for them.
I...
Fine, for your sake,
I won't hold it against them.
Mister
Tell me
Do I look like the woman you once loved?
Call me big brother
Big brother
Can you tell me
the story between you two?
When she was young
she was just like you
Beautiful, gentle
and all alone in the world
Back then
I was just a small-time boss
I helped her out in life
and later we ended up together
And after that
my business kept getting bigger
With more money, my horizons broadened
And when I looked back
I had already lost her
What a tragically beautiful story
You know, in this life
we always think the next restaurant tastes better
But after you've tried every delicacy
you realize the best food
is still simple home cooking
That's exactly how I feel now
The woman who suits me best
is still her
Then it seems
your relationship with your current wife
has serious problems
No, no, no
My current wife is wonderful
But something just seems to be missing
Maybe it's because
she's too obedient, too indulgent with me
Right now we're out drinking
and she doesn't even care
Then do you think
the kind of woman who nags you every day
who makes a fuss with you
is the one who truly loves you?
When I was young
I hated being controlled by anyone
That's why I broke up with her
But later I realized
only when she cares
will she nag you
If she doesn't
then she only
cares about your money
and not necessarily you yourself
Your wife is here
Why is she ignoring you?
See
She doesn't care about me, does she?
But there's another possibility
She cares about me a lot
and wants to get my attention
How about this
Mister
Let's
make your wife jealous
make her get
super jealous over you, how about it?
Let's see if she really doesn't care
or whether
she actually does care about you
You're so naughty
Come, let's drink
You two are really using me as a pawn
Hey, hey, why isn't the bill being settled?
Tianfang
We've got a mission
Handsome
Come here
Ms. Xu
Yes, go ahead
You're the manager, right?
So satisfying the customer's requests
is part of your job, isn't it?
Of course
What do you need?
Well
Have a drink with me
Wait
Here's a tip
Take it
Ms. Xu, be careful
Why am I feeling a bit dizzy?