Ms. Xu
It looks like something happened to your husband.
Do you want to go out and check?
No way.
Are you sure you aren't mistaken?
What if it's true?
The police are already here.
You'd better go out and take a look.
I'm tired.
I don't want to get involved.
Go see for yourself.
Okay.
Hey, mister.
Why are you losing your cool?
She isn't even jealous yet,
and you're already jealous.
I'm not losing my cool.
Let me take you back to rest.
Thanks, thank you.
She's burning with jealousy now.
Push a little harder.
I guarantee she'll be head over heels for you.
Aren't you afraid that later
I'll start playing for real?
Bring it on.
Let me tell you,
I really want to see
tonight,
who lets loose more.
A Zhen and A Qiang
are seasoned honey trap pros.
Who knows how many people they've victimized.
I wonder if they'll succeed tonight.
Bring your body cams.
With habitual offenders like them,
we have to catch them in the act.
Ms. Xu, please slow down.
Manager Yu.
I keep feeling like in this room,
there are eyes watching me.
You don't have
any
hidden cameras here, do you?
Ms. Xu, rest assured.
Our villa would absolutely never allow
hidden cameras to exist.
Can you guarantee that?
I guarantee it.
What if there are?
If there are, I'll take responsibility.
The villa's business is my business.
But
anything else...
Ms. Xu.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wait.
Don't go.
Are you okay?
Am I pretty?
Yes, you're pretty.
You're a true beauty.
Absolutely stunning.
You men
all love beautiful women.
But beautiful women
will grow old too.
No.
Even before they get old,
you're already sick of them.
You
are like hunters.
The prey you desire
is always the next one.
I'm not like that.
I'm the type of guy
who's incredibly devoted.
Really?
Come on, mister!
I can barely run anymore.
Catch me,
and I'm all yours tonight.
Hurry!
Alright.
If a tiger doesn't show its teeth,
you'll take it for a sick cat, huh?
Hurry up!
Coming!
Come here.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
I feel terrible.
Didn't we agree to film a video
to make your wife mad?
Mister, what's wrong? Mister!
Pills... my pills.
What pills?
Are you okay?
Open it.
Open it!
Here.
Mister!
Are you okay, mister?
Help me lie down.
Mister!
Don't scare me!
Someone's dead!
Somebody help!
Help!
Someone's dead!
A Qiang! A Qiang! A Qiang!
Stop yelling! Just run!
Freeze!
What are you doing?
Take it easy!
Get down!
Hands behind your head!
Be gentle, would you?
Behave!
Ouch, that hurts!
It wasn't me!
What's going on?
What's the situation?
Holy crap.
Another dead body!
Police investigation! Step back!
It wasn't me!
Get down, now!
Watch the hair!
Don't move!
Call for backup!
Homicide at Clear Spring Villa.
Requesting backup.
Clear Spring Villa, homicide.
Brother Hui.
A Zhen and A Qiang got locked up.
But don't worry.
They'll never rat you out.
In this world,
only dead men can be trusted.
Since A Qiang's line is cut,
the business on our end,
you'd better keep a close eye on it.
A few guys still owe us money.
It's time to teach them a lesson.
Brother Hui.
Didn't we agree not to meet during the day?
Why are you here?
Well...
There's been another death at the villa.
I'd actually met the guy.
I don't know why,
but I feel terrible about it.
Qiqi.
Life is like a train ride.
Some people just get off earlier, that's all.
Just keep your mind on your destination.
Which is,
finding the documents as soon as possible,
and mortgaging the villa.
Only then can we be truly free.
A guaranteed loan went bad,
and we can't pay it off.
My place is going to get seized.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely help you.
That's my good Qiqi.
Old Wang's health
has always been pretty good.
A perfectly healthy man,
how could he just be gone?
Boss.
Don't get so worked up.
Have some coffee.
Who knows which deity up there
we managed to offend.
One case after another.
The guests have all been scared off.
How are we supposed to do business?
But don't be upset yet.
I've already asked around.
The coroner has already ruled
that Wang Kechen
died of a heart attack.
The police also ruled
his death as an accident.
It has nothing to do with our villa.
Boss Bai!
Ma'am.
A perfectly healthy man
died right here in your villa.
And you're trying to dodge responsibility?
I'm going to sue you!
Please, don't get worked up.
We can talk this through.
Whatever your demands are,
just say the word.
This is a human life we're talking about.
No amount of money
can bring my husband back.
So, what are you saying?
Do I look like I need money?
Five million.
Not a cent less.
I really am innocent.
Boss Wang...
I wasn't the one who killed him.
Stop crying!
Now you're crying after he's dead?
You still have a chance right now.
Explain to us clearly,
what exactly did you do to him?
I didn't do anything.
He wanted to test if his wife still loved him.
I just played along with the act.
Who knew...
We hadn't even entered the room.
Nothing had happened yet.
He suddenly collapsed.
Officer,
could I get a cigarette?
Even a leaf would do if you don't have one.
Since you've been tailing us, you'd know
A Zhen and I run honey traps.
We're only after money,
not lives.
If we killed our marks,
who'd pay us, right?
So you admit
that you and A Zhen
seduced Wang Kechen
to blackmail him?
Right?
Officer,
why so serious?
Isn't it trendy now
to enforce the law with a smile?
That's right.
The original plan was
A Zhen lures that horny old geezer
into the room,
I burst in to scare him,
grab the money and leave.
But who knew,
the geezer kicked the bucket before even getting to the room.
The things I did,
I'll admit to.
But murder?
I didn't do it.
I won't admit to that.
Since you started working with A Qiang,
how many honey trap victims have there been?
I don't remember clearly.
A Qiang was in charge of the whole process.
Do you have any records?
The law stipulates
that voluntarily confessing your crimes,
or exposing the crimes of others,
once verified as true,
can be grounds for a lighter sentence.
If I talk,
A Qiang will beat me to death.
That won't happen.
The police will protect your safety.
What if I get a heavier sentence?
Even if you don't talk,
we'll find out sooner or later.
In our investigations,
we look at evidence,
and at attitude.
Coming clean early
is better than having no chances left at all.
Actually,
A Qiang would always pose as a repairman,
sneak into the target's room beforehand,
and plant hidden cameras.
Mainly to get a feel for
the target's situation.
Just to get a feel for it?
After busting them at the honey trap scene,
you'd extort them once,
you'd use the video to extort them again later,
or even more.
That was all A Qiang's doing.
I'm a victim too.
He'd beat me if I didn't cooperate.
It's obvious the suspect, A Qiang,
placed the pinhole camera
in the central AC vent,
connected it to the hotel's Wi-Fi,
and set the secretly recorded videos
to automatically download onto this phone.
That's right.
The latest video
is from Wang Kechen and Xu Lingling's room.
Isn't that Yu Tianfang?
It really is him.
He's just a liar.
When we went on a blind date,
he said he already had someone he liked.
But then he turns around and gets a room with another woman.
And with such a huge age gap too.
Men...
Are all you men just...
We're on duty.
Keep it professional.
Why is being a manager so hard?
Yu Tianfang.
Officer Chu, Officer Qin.
What exactly is your relationship with Xu Lingling?
What kind of relationship could we have?
She's a guest at our villa.
I just serve the guests, that's all.
Oh, right.
You haven't paid for that meal last time.
I already paid at the front desk.
Oh, I didn't notice.
I've got work to do.
That night, you and Xu Lingling...
what exactly did you do?
Someone planted a camera in your room.
I've watched the entire video.
That was just a misunderstanding.
Yu Tianfang.
You still have a chance right now.
Spill it, what exactly did you two do?
That night, she was drunk,
so I walked her back to her room.
By accident,
she pushed me over.
Ms. Xu.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Wait.
Are... are you okay?
You're like hunters.
The prey you desire
is always the next one.
I'm not like that.
I'm the kind of guy
who's incredibly devoted.
Really?
Someone's dead!
Somebody help!
What happened?
What's going on?
Holy crap.
Another dead body.
Police investigation. Step back.
Get down, now!
I was scared out of my mind back then.
Thinking back on it,
that Xu Lingling is no ordinary woman.
She was extremely calm back then.
Tell me,
what wife hears her husband's in trouble
and isn't panicked at all?
You were with her at the time.
When she heard that her husband,
Wang Kechen, had died,
do you remember how she reacted?
She did cry,
but she didn't shed a single tear.