Dr. Xu
What are the preliminary findings?
Based on the victim's physical features,
the preliminary estimate is
the victim died about three to four days ago.
Scissors.
We found Zhao Yan's body
inside Lele's home.
But she refuses to say anything.
From what we know,
she has no real family or friends.
The person she trusts most
is you.
You want me to persuade Lele?
No way.
She can't be the criminal.
She's a kind person.
Let me tell you,
even with zero confession,
as long as the chain of evidence is complete,
we can still convict her.
Mao Lele.
Still refusing to say anything, huh?
But we hope she'll come clean voluntarily
to earn leniency.
We're giving her a chance.
Hold on.
An old friend's come to see you.
Look at you.
Haven't been eating properly again, huh?
You've gotten so thin.
There's no point in living.
How many times have I told you?
No more negative talk.
You need to pull yourself together.
Don't let people think we're easy to bully.
Brother.
Don't be so good to me.
I don't deserve it.
I'm the one who let you down.
I didn't protect you well enough.
Listen to me.
Let's tell them everything we know.
You'll feel better once you do.
Tianfang.
You always loved telling the story of the Massacre of the Bai family.
I just want to ask you,
Bai the Second killed Elder Bai's whole family.
Was it because
he couldn't have the woman he loved,
so he destroyed everything?
The human heart is complicated.
Maybe
Bai the Second was just jealous of Elder Bai.
Even if his brother
hadn't married the woman he loved,
he would've struck for some other reason.
Then I guess I did it out of jealousy too.
I envied those pretty girls
who, just because of their faces,
could get away with anything.
The body was found in my place,
but that doesn't prove I killed anyone.
I heard Captain Chu once bullied Tianfang.
I have just one request.
If you can find
evidence that I committed murder,
I'll tell you everything.
Tweezers.
Found it at last.
Mao Lele.
On the gauze that wrapped Zhao Yan,
we found an eyelash.
After DNA comparison,
it's yours.
Anything you'd like to say?
I really shouldn't have shed tears for him.
I killed him.
No one else was involved.
Then why did you kill Cindy?
I didn't kill her.
Cindy.
Look at these two.
Which one's prettier?
From the moment I was born,
I had a huge birthmark.
Everyone despised me.
Facial skin is less than 0.5 millimeters thick,
yet it dictates a person's whole life.
Some are showered with endless love,
while others...
are scorned their entire lives.
How ironic.
Lele, come here.
Paint my nails.
I won't make you do it for free.
This much money
should feed you for a month, right?
Paint my nails.
Stand right there.
We kindly offer you a job,
and you're not even grateful?
Are you going or not?
No.
Ugly freaks just love acting up.
Let me go!
If you keep this up, I'll...
I'll tell Manager Yu.
Go ahead, try telling him.
We'll deal with him too.
Tell who?
I asked, tell who?
Speak up!
Don't touch me!
Why aren't you talking now?
Let me go!
Tell who?
Get up, now!
Let me go!
Stand up!
Get up!
Then why didn't you tell Yu Tianfang?
She didn't want the person she loved
to see her at her most pathetic.
What do you mean?
When you love someone,
you only want to show them your best side.
Yu Tianfang,
how clueless can you be?
She liked me.
She cared about you too much,
that's why she didn't tell you the truth.
And in the end,
she got deceived by Zhao Yan again.
No way.
She really liked me?
Zhao Yan really is a bastard.
You're pretty much a bastard too.
What's your relationship with Zhao Yan?
I once thought
that besides Tianfang,
he was the only one who treated me best.
Pretty little thing, aren't you?
Give me a kiss.
Let go!
I've got plenty of money.
That's all you want, isn't it?
What are you doing?
Who the hell are you?
Let me tell you something.
If you dare bully this girl again,
I'll break your legs.
I won't do it again!
Get lost!
Manager Zhao,
thank you so much for today.
You offended a client to save me,
and got fined by the company.
I don't know how to repay you.
Don't mention it.
We're all colleagues here.
If you really want to thank me,
bottoms up.
I usually don't drink,
but today, to thank you, Manager Zhao,
I'll have one with you.
Alright.
Have another one.
She's got some looks, huh.
What have you done?
Lele, listen to me.
I truly love you.
I'll take responsibility for you.
There are so many beauties at the resort.
Why did you have to deceive me?
How could I be deceiving you?
You're different from them.
I love that pure quality about you.
I don't believe you.
Lele.
Listen to me. Get away from me!
Lele, Lele, listen to me.
Lele.
I think you're a gift
that heaven sent to me.
Give me time.
I'll prove it to you.
Lele.
This is my gift to you.
I tattooed your name on my body.
I'll never forget you.
Will you love me forever?
Once I've saved up enough money,
I'll propose to you.
Thank you, Manager Zhao.
Still calling me Manager Zhao?
Call me Yan.
Thank you, Yan.
That's more like it.
Order whatever you want.
Don't try to save money for me.
But we shouldn't waste either.
Order.
Then...
let's get an order of malatang.
Okay.
Waiter!
We'll have
one order
of malatang for three yuan.
Three yuan of malatang?
Three yuan.
You can mix it however you like.
Delicious.
He got a tattoo for me
and said he'd marry me.
I thought it was true love.
I truly carved him onto my body.
But it was all a lie.
I won the bet last time.
I scored Lele.
I don't believe it.
Stop trying to weasel out of paying.
Don't believe me, huh?
Take a look at this.
Squeezed her dry.
And she's even grateful for it,
got my name tattooed on her.
You're really wicked.
Just slapped on a tattoo sticker
and tricked her into giving herself to you.
She did more than give herself to me.
She handed over this month's salary too.
We agreed, right?
The kitchen kickbacks this month
all go to me.
Fine.
I'll let you off this month.
But next month,
we split it evenly.
If I really become general manager,
would I shortchange you two?
It's that suck-up Yu Tianfang.
He's always hovering around Boss Bai.
We've got to find a way to get rid of him.
Don't worry.
We've got it all planned.
We'll use a honey trap.
Take nude photos of him.
Beautiful.
Let's do it.
Going against me?
Think he'll meet a good end?
Know why I brought you here?
Based on our forensics team's analysis
and the evidence found here,
the spot where Cindy fell in
was within 100 meters of this place.
Right before Cindy died,
she was lying right here.
That day, I just wanted to ask her
why she kept targeting me.
Boss,
why is the anesthetic I ordered short?
I'm giving my friend Botox to fill in scars.
Of course I need extra for local anesthesia.
Fine, fine, I don't care.
You have to make up the amount.
Or I'll report you.
I wonder how well it works.
If only I had someone to practice on.
Cindy,
why did you team up
with Zhao Yan to deceive me?
I felt someone was watching me.
Turns out it's you, you ugly freak.
Why did you lie to me?
Me, lie to you?
Looking like you do,
what man would ever want you?
I had Zhao Yan chase you.
That's the luck of a lifetime for you.
You should thank me, your matchmaker.
I don't want it.
I know
about you, Fanny, and Zhao Yan,
how you teamed up
to take kickbacks from kitchen purchases.
I know everything.
Don't mess with me again.
Bah!
Who the hell do you think you are?
How dare you threaten me!
With that gloomy face all day,
just looking at you brings bad luck.
Let me tell you,
from now on,
every time I see you, I'll beat you.
Perfect timing.
I'll test the drug on you.
What are you doing?
Give it to me!
You ugly freak,
how dare you fight back!
You...
You forced me to do this.
Cindy.