Qi-bao
Get lost.
Get me a Water of Oblivion.
Cindy, Fanny.
Three drinks, now.
You two aren't backing up Siqi
but slacking off and drinking here, huh?
Did I go too easy on you?
He Siqi is so high and mighty,
she doesn't need backup dancers at all.
The big picture, get it?
Consider the big picture.
Just dance.
Manager Yu.
You look so handsome today.
Here,
a toast to you.
Such a smooth talker.
Right, Manager Yu.
You take such good care of us.
I really have to thank you.
Manager Yu, drink up!
What are you doing?
I'm telling you,
cross me again,
and your ugly side
will be seen by everyone.
Delete it, now!
Pervert! Pervert!
Yu Tianfang!
What are you doing?
Everyone, come look!
Manager Yu has no clothes on!
How embarrassing!
Jerk.
Qi-bao!
Cindy!
I'm telling you,
this isn't over.
You won't let it go?
Then go ahead and kill me.
In this entire resort right now,
the one who wants me dead most is Zhao Yan.
This Zhao Yan
really is a player.
He was sleeping with both Cindy and Fanny.
Anyone who falls for him must be blind.
Maybe the three of them turned on each other.
Zhao Yan killed the two women,
and then framed me.
Right now,
he must be hiding somewhere.
Whether it was Cindy or Fanny,
when they were attacked,
I was by myself.
No one can give me an alibi.
If you insist I'm the killer,
fine.
Just show me the evidence.
I promise
I'll confess on the spot.
After all your investigating,
and somehow it lands on me.
I'm swamped running my business every day.
If I were the killer,
I'd just hack my enemies to pieces.
I wouldn't bother with all these gimmicks.
Besides,
that Nuna tattoo thing,
at my age,
would I really mess with such childish stuff?
So in your opinion,
who in the entire resort is the most suspicious?
Zhao Yan.
This Zhao Yan,
no idea if he fled or is hiding.
We went to his place but couldn't find him.
Now at this resort,
both managers have vanished.
That's too much of a coincidence.
This Zhao Yan seems popular with women.
Cindy and Fanny
weren't robbed of anything.
That rules out robbery-murder.
More likely,
it's a crime of passion or revenge.
Statistically speaking in criminal cases,
the more complex the romantic ties,
the higher the odds of a crime of passion.
Captain Chu, we just got word.
Fanny's been resuscitated,
but the doctor says
she was deprived of oxygen for too long.
They don't know when she'll wake up.
According to the tests,
anesthetic components were in her system,
matching those in the victim Cindy.
Also,
neither showed signs of sexual assault.
That rules out rape-murder.
Cindy fell in the water and drowned.
Fanny was strangled into a coma.
The suspect is very likely the same person.
The attacker
used anesthetic on them
and carved a Nuna Stamp on their faces.
Why use a stamp like that?
The Nuna Stamp could very well be our breakthrough.
The anesthetic,
why would Lele have something like that?
Nuna
carries the meaning of rage.
In its place of origin, it stands for the goddess of vengeance.
The killer puts on all this theater
because she's projecting her subconscious.
She sees herself as a kind person,
a righteous goddess of vengeance.
But to me,
it actually reveals
a sign of weakness and lack of confidence.
True justice
never needs to rely on spirits or gods.
Posing as the goddess of vengeance,
could the killer be a woman?
The street cameras
showed her to be of short stature
and wearing red.
Captain Chu,
based on the clues just discussed,
I also believe
there's a high chance the suspect is female.
Compared to men,
women are physically weaker,
so violent crimes are less likely.
But when it comes to killing with poison,
women outnumber men four to one.
Fanny wasn't strangled to death,
which shows the attacker wasn't strong enough.
Both victims had anesthetic in their systems.
That fits a female killer's MO.
If this is a serial case,
then others
are still in potential danger.
He Siqi had conflicts with both Cindy and Fanny.
In other words,
she has a motive.
And there's also Bai Ruifen and Mao Lele.
Brother Tianfang,
I want to see you.
Be a good girl.
What are you doing?
One more step and I'll jump!
Put the knife down.
Qin Mo,
Call for backup, now!
Lele!
I didn't kill anyone!
This is Water Moon Pavilion.
Someone fell into the water.
Put the knife down.
I didn't kill anyone!
I'll say this one more time,
put the knife down!
Drop it!
I really didn't kill anyone.
What did you do to her?
I didn't kill anyone.
I really didn't kill anyone.
I swear to God.
I just wanted to ask Mao Lele
why she had this anesthetic.
So two murders happened in a row,
you were afraid of being a suspect,
so you hid in the resort.
Lele helped you.
And you found out she had anesthetic.
That's right.
She suddenly called me,
said she needed to see me.
And I wanted to ask her
why she had this.
But then...
I saw her...
Lele!
Mao Lele!
Le... Lele!
Don't scare me!
Lele!
Help me.
I'll call 120.
Who's there?
Don't kill me!
Get away from me!
Don't kill me! Stay back!
Stay back! Don't kill me!
Calm down.
It's me, Yu Tianfang.
Put the knife down.
Don't come any closer!
Just calm down.
Get the hell away from me!
Put the knife down.
One more step and I'll...
I'll jump!
I'm not the one who hurt you.
Don't kill me!
No, no, no!
Put it down.
Lele!
HQ. What are you doing?
I really didn't kill anyone.
Trying to save her!
I really didn't kill anyone!
I was trying to save her.
How is she now?
Still searching.
I know.
You all must think
I'm the murderer.
But I'm so good-looking,
and I have a respectable job.
I wouldn't, just because of
a couple of arguments
or a petty conflict,
resort to murder!
I'm not that twisted.
If you didn't kill anyone, why hide?
Because of you, of course!
A couple of years ago,
my dad wasn't mentally well.
He took someone's e-bike.
When you arrested him,
I feared a personal vendetta.
Just because of that?
What do you take us cops for?
Mud on your pants,
it's shit whether it is or not.
I couldn't explain myself.
If you ask me,
you just have persecution paranoia.
Treating yourself as the suspect.
No.
It wasn't me.
Then wasn't all that for nothing?
But with what happened to Mao Lele,
you still can't shake the suspicion.
Stay here for a few days.
Talk to us
about the Mao Lele you knew.
Her name is Mao Lele,
but she wasn't happy at all.
She's the most unfortunate girl
I've ever met.
Cindy, Fanny,
those two loved to bully her the most.
I wanted to beat those two up,
but never hitting women
is a principle of mine.
Let alone killing anyone.
I'm completely innocent!
Don't worry.
We cops won't wrong a good person,
nor will we let a bad one go.
Captain Chu.
Did you find anything?
We didn't find Lele.
But we found this.
Any findings?
It's a breathing tube.
If Lele was using it,
that means she was prepared all along.
Send this to Forensics.
See if there's any
residual DNA on it.
Also,
apply for an arrest warrant immediately.
Lele is a major suspect.
Yes, sir.
Why are you in such a rush to go home?
Did something happen at home?
If you need any help, just say so.
That killer,
I'm the next one they're going to kill.
I have to run.
The psycho who killed Cindy and Fanny?
Did you get a clear look at them?
Sis Siqi,
do you remember the Bai family's painting?
I had a dream.
I dreamed of a man dressed in white.
He said he was the second son of the Bai family.
He wanted to find a woman to marry.
But I was too ugly.
He didn't want me.
I never believed in monsters and demons,
but I think...
Should we just call the police first?
There are police up ahead.
I know you've always wanted to steal
what's in Boss Bai's safe.
If you don't want her to find out,
just drive through!
Stop the car!
Hurry, after them!