We agreed on eighty thousand.
Why are you raising the price?
Without three hundred thousand,
the boat won't come.
I've got a card here.
Should be close to three hundred grand.
What are you doing?
Freeze!
Don't move!
Command Center,
this is Qin Weicheng,
badge number 171326.
Suspect spotted on the west bank of Qingshui River,
Chen Dahui.
Requesting immediate backup.
Chu Feng!
Wait for backup!
Boss!
If we don't go now, he'll get away!
Chu Feng!
Freeze!
Don't move!
Boss!
Leave me, go after him!
Go!
Chen Dahui!
Freeze!
Captain Chu.
Sun Bo,
what's the situation?
According to the cleaner,
there was no body last night.
It rained this morning,
the river rose,
and something washed down from upstream.
When they fished it out,
they realized it was a body.
Have you searched upstream?
Yes, we have.
We found a cosmetics case at Shuiyue Pavilion,
along with signs of struggle and blood.
It's very likely the crime scene.
Forensic Doctor Xu,
do we have a time of death?
Based on lividity and decomposition,
initial estimate places death
ten to twelve hours ago.
That's roughly last night,
between ten and midnight.
Specifics will require
a full autopsy.
Cause of death?
Bulging eyes,
clouded retinas,
ruptured eardrums with bleeding,
silt in mouth and nose.
Consistent with drowning.
What's up, man?
What happened?
Looks like a murder.
Murder?
Here, let me take a look.
Is that a tattoo on her face?
It looks like one,
but it's actually
a pattern left by a stamp.
This kind of ink seeps into the skin.
It looks a bit like
a pork inspection stamp.
He didn't mean to steal anything.
He's been through a lot these past two years.
His mind isn't quite right.
Don't give me that.
I hear excuses like yours
eight times a month.
How many times is this for your dad this month?
You know damn well.
Of all people, this kid?
Crime of passion.
Suicide.
Revenge killing.
Please step back.
Chief Wang.
Right.
It's homicide.
Chu Feng.
From now on, Qin Mo
will be on your team.
Got it.
Captain Chu.
Long time no see.
I've already examined the scene.
My mentor's badge number.
The mission my father didn't finish,
I'll finish it for him.
Good.
Qin Mo.
Back then, your father
worked his cases the same way.
One more clue found
means the criminal
gets caught a day sooner.
Kid,
keep up the good work.
Captain Chu,
I'll leave this to you.
Yes, sir.
You sounded so sure earlier.
What's your basis?
Someone who commits suicide
wouldn't disfigure their own face like that.
It's most likely murder.
The killer destroyed the victim's face.
Psychologically speaking,
the face represents social identity.
Disfiguring it
equals destroying the victim's existence,
venting anger,
jealousy, and hatred.
Simply put,
it's a revenge killing.
And she just made an enemy.
When I got to the crime scene,
I saw the name tag on the victim's chest
and immediately went to Qingyuan Resort.
Last night, someone
publicly threatened to get back at Cindy.
That person is Yu Tianfang.
So by what you're saying,
this Yu Tianfang is a prime suspect.
What are you doing here?
Stop right there!
I have to find
the surveillance footage before Cindy died.
That's the only way to prove I'm innocent.
What a piece of junk.
Cindy's death
has been classified as a murder.
The bureau has set up a task force.
We have a deadline to solve it.
As the operators of this place,
you are obligated
to cooperate with the investigation.
Here's my police ID.
Captain Chu, don't worry.
I'll fully cooperate with the investigation.
The surveillance room is right here.
You can find all the footage there.
Thank you.
What's going on?
This...
Don't bother looking.
Could this be
Manager Yu's doing?
President Bai.
Where does this door lead to?
It's a side door leading backstage.
Take a look.
This path
is only used by our internal staff.
Through here
is the backstage area.
Captain Chu.
Traffic control sent over a video.
Take a look.
This is the back gate of Qingyuan Resort.
Around ten last night,
Cindy came out of the back gate alone.
Then someone in red appeared,
following close behind Cindy.
An hour later,
only the person in red came back.
So based on this,
Cindy disappeared around ten last night.
This matches the forensic timeline closely.
This person in red
is a major suspect.
There was a shower last night.
The footage is blurry.
We can't see the suspect's face clearly.
But we can tell
she's shorter than Cindy.
And Yu Tianfang
is obviously much taller than Cindy.
So based on this,
just from this video alone,
the suspicion on Yu Tianfang
drops significantly.
But we can't rule him out completely.
The suspect
should still be inside this resort.
Wait.
Everyone, stop what you're doing.
I need to ask you all some questions.
Come with me.
Everyone, come with me.
Please cooperate, everyone.
Before I die,
I'm not gonna die hungry.
Gotta go out right.
Yu Tianfang!
Everyone's looking everywhere for you,
and you're sneaking food?
Good lord!
Siqi,
when I'm nervous, I wanna eat.
And when I eat,
I wanna drink too.
And when I drink, I do stupid things.
First, I gotta tell you,
I didn't kill anyone.
Last night, I was with Old Li from the front desk
playing cards till midnight.
He owed me money and denied it,
so I got mad and fought with him.
I didn't sleep all night.
In the morning, they said Cindy was dead.
I'm a major suspect. I'm innocent!
You don't need to explain all this to me.
The cops are right outside.
Go tell them.
I'm scared!
Do you know,
that cop handling the case,
he and I have bad blood.
If he uses this to get back at me,
I'm done for, aren't I?
Stay back!
Think hard about
what you've done before.
Dressing like that at the resort every day.
I tell you off and you don't wanna listen?
Is this any way to act?
I've really seen it all.
What are you, from the Qing Dynasty?
Why listen to a lousy manager like you?
Bullshit!
Can't you see it yourself?
I'm the manager!
I'm telling you,
I'm laying it out here today.
If you don't follow the rules,
I'll fine you every single day.
500 today,
500 tomorrow.
If the fines don't kill you,
I'll make your life miserable.
Bring it on!
Either you finish me off,
or I finish you off.
Fine, bring it on!
If you don't want your pay, suit yourself.
Just fines, huh?
Acting like some rich princess every day.
Wearing these cheap earrings.
Pick them up!
Yu Tianfang,
you know what kind of person Cindy was.
A two-faced snake.
The people she pissed off
could fill a whole train.
I'm telling you,
anyone could have killed her.
But now everything points at you.
Either
you're cursed with bad luck,
or
someone's deliberately framing you.
If I find out who it is,
I'll string them up and beat them.
This is the kitchen.
No one would hide here, right?
We've checked the backstage.
This is the only place left.
He Siqi.
What are you doing here?
Low blood sugar.
Came to grab a bite.
President Bai.
Any other managers here?
I have just two managers.
One is Yu Tianfang,
the other is Zhao Yan.
Siqi, have you seen them?
No, I haven't.
Then have you seen Fanny?
She's closest to Cindy.
They eat and live together.
Tight as real sisters.
More like partners in crime.
He Siqi.
The police are here.
Watch your mouth.
I just speak my mind.
All the dirty things those two did,
everyone at the resort knows.
He Siqi.
So as far as you know,
who had the biggest beef with Cindy?
Cindy was in cahoots with Zhao Yan.
She helped him fight for the GM spot,
fighting Yu Tianfang tooth and nail.
But still,
Yu Tianfang only cares about sales,
is all talk,
and takes petty advantages.
He probably
doesn't have the guts to kill.
This Yu Tianfang,
he has his fair share of flaws,
but he's never crossed any major lines.
How about
you check his apartment?
Alright.
Let's go.
Come on out.
Siqi.
Like they say in wuxia novels,
we should stick together.
Siqi.
Give me a hug.
Get away from me.
I'm harboring a criminal like you,
and you still try to hit on me?
I'm not a criminal.
Didn't you have a grudge against Cindy too?
You dare suspect me?
Believe me, I'll turn you in.
Qi-baby.
I'm sorry.
I said I'm sorry, okay?
Let go.
You...
Why do you have this too?
When Cindy was killed,
on her face,
there was a stamp just like this.
But the only people
who have this stamp
are our staff members.
Could it be the killer
is one of us?
From now on,
you're on your own.
Qi-baby.
Don't leave!
Captain Chu.
Here's the resort blueprint you wanted.
Thanks.
Hello?
Where are you?
I know you did it.
If you don't pay up,
I'll turn you in.
Where's the money?