This used to be a haunted house.
A family named Bai lived here.
The elder brother seized all the property.
He forced his brother's beloved woman to marry him,
as his concubine.
On the night of the wedding,
Bai the Second killed them all.
Now,
I've finally gathered all these people.
Erlang,
no!
Please, spare me!
Please, let me go!
Erlang,
it's all the elder brother's fault.
I'm your bride.
I'll live a good life with you.
Please, spare me!
Last spring, the flowers
bloomed so brightly.
Alas, tonight,
I depart for the netherworld.
Heaven punishes those who betray love.
Those who wronged me shall not live long.
Stop the car!
Stop!
Quick, after her!
Mao Lele,
are you
hiding some kind of hardship?
Tell me.
Maybe I can help you.
Brother Tianfang said,
when a mortal is about to die,
the candles will surely go out.
It seems
my time is almost up.
Over here!
Stay here, don't move.
Come with me to the station.
I need to ask you a few questions.
Siqi,
you're very lucky.
You said you were ambushed,
and just as you were about to be killed,
Yu Tianfang appeared and scared him off.
Out of fear,
you fell into the water.
After getting out of the water,
you chose not to call the police.
Instead, you chose to flee to your hometown,
and took He Siqi hostage,
forcing her to help you escape.
That person was too terrifying.
I was too scared not to run.
What did he look like?
I was injected with anesthetic,
and I passed out instantly.
You were clearly passed out,
so how did you know he was terrifying?
He's a serial killer!
Why didn't you call the police?
Even someone as capable as Brother Tianfang
didn't dare to call the police.
How could I dare?
Speaking of Yu Tianfang,
in your bag,
he found this.
Why were you carrying anesthetic with you?
I use it for Botox and Hyaluronic acid injections.
I wanted so badly to look beautiful,
so I got some cosmetic injections,
and some anesthetic.
That night,
Yu Tianfang took the anesthetic
to confront you about it.
When he went to Moonwater Pavilion to find you,
he found only you there.
If what you said is true,
he should have at least run into the suspect.
But Yu Tianfang's statement
says he saw nothing.
Only you.
I was passed out at the time.
I don't know anything.
Maybe he ran off before that.
According to your coworkers,
Cindy and Fanny treated you badly.
They treated everyone badly.
Zhao Yan is missing.
What's your relationship with him?
He's a manager.
I'm just an errand girl.
This is a photo of Zhao Yan and his girlfriend.
Take a good look.
Do you know who his girlfriend is?
He has a girlfriend?
I never heard about that.
Based on all the leads we have,
we have reason to suspect
Zhao Yan is linked to Cindy and Fanny's case.
We'll launch a full investigation on Zhao Yan.
Tell us.
Tell us about the Zhao Yan you know.
Now that you mention it,
I suddenly remembered something.
If I don't get the money next month,
I'll go tell Boss Bai
that you're taking kickbacks on kitchen supplies.
Could you keep your voice down?
Afraid people won't hear you?
I'm a bit tight on cash this month.
Would it kill you to wait two more days?
We agreed on an equal three-way split.
If you dare keep it all,
just wait to go to prison.
I'm guessing,
maybe Cindy
and Fanny found out
about Manager Zhao's kickback scheme,
so they blackmailed him for an equal cut.
Manager Zhao couldn't handle
those two fierce girls,
so he killed them to silence them.
I happened to walk in on their fight,
and got dragged into it.
So all of that is just your speculation.
This Mao Lele is way too calm.
She just got hunted down,
went on the run,
yet she isn't panicked at all.
What's the connection between these people?
And what's her motive for murder?
Let's suppose
Mao Lele,
bullied by Fanny and Cindy,
committed the murders.
We could call it a revenge killing.
But what's her link with Zhao Yan?
This case right now
is like a jigsaw puzzle.
We're missing one piece.
Captain.
Yu Tianfang refuses to leave.
He insists on seeing you.
Chu Feng.
What is it?
Bro Sun,
grab me a cup of coffee too.
Just take this one, stop stalling.
Get to the point already.
What is it?
I just remembered something.
Lele
might have been set up by them.
Your lipstick is a bit heavy today.
Here, let me smooth it out.
Stop it.
Hold still, hold still, hold still.
You guys.
Who's been tossing cigarette butts in the bathroom?
Do you know how hard it is to unclog a toilet?
If there were no trash,
the cleaners wouldn't have jobs.
Exactly.
Those people
should be thanking us.
I've seen some thick-skinned people,
but never anyone as shameless as you.
Manager Yu.
Don't get mad.
I'll apologize for them, okay?
Lele,
I'm sorry.
It's no big deal, right?
Don't take it to heart.
Lele.
Why are you running off?
Hey,
you two managers,
aren't you just so caring.
If you ask me,
why don't you make Lele your girlfriend.
You can tell she's never dated anyone.
Yeah.
Whichever of you wins Lele over,
when it comes to picking the General Manager,
that's who we'll back.
You said it, remember.
If I win her over,
you two better back me.
Of course.
Let me tell you,
Lele is my sister.
If you lay a finger on her, just try it.
Yu Tianfang,
look at the state of you.
I'm telling you straight,
she's mine.
Zhao Yan,
I'll say it one more time,
you've got a death wish.
If you keep messing around...
At the time, I thought that bet
was just a joke to them.
I didn't realize they were serious.
So according to what you said,
Zhao Yan pursued Mao Lele
because of that bet?
Yes.
I only just figured it out now.
That's why Lele
acted so strange back then.
I was just chatting with them.
Stop overthinking, okay?
Come on,
stop crying.
Be a good girl.
You don't want those photos of yours
to get out, do you?
Zhao Yan, what are you doing?
Bullying my sister again, huh?
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Bro, bro,
tell me,
did he bully you?
Fine.
If you don't want to talk, forget it.
But remember,
if anyone dares to bully you,
you have to tell me.
I've got your back.
What photos were you just talking about?
I asked Lele,
but she refused to say.
Zhao Yan probably
used them to threaten her.
Captain,
the search warrant came through.
Good.
Yu Tianfang said
Zhao Yan used Lele's photos to threaten her.
Things like that
are usually kept at home or in the office.
Zhao Yan lives in an apartment
where there's a cleaner.
I went to check.
There was nothing there.
The album is empty.
Lele is a cleaner.
She'd never leave a single trace.
Didn't expect this guy
to be a photography buff.
This camera must be 20 years old.
Digital cameras are better these days.
Unlimited copies and backups.
Not necessarily.
Looks like our suspect's pretty young.
He only destroyed the photos
but forgot about the film.
I think
as for his motive,
we may have just found it.
Can we please not do this?
Besides me,
who else would ever love you?
While you're still young,
I want to leave you with some beautiful memories.
Isn't that nice?
But I...
But what?
These photos won't get out.
A film camera
can only be developed and printed.
There's no way to upload them online.
I'm scared.
Do you love me?
I do.
Love
is total possession without any reason.
If you love me,
you should listen to me.
That's how I'll love you even more, right?
Be a good girl.
Did he ever love me?
He never loved me at all, did he?
It's freezing in here.
The AC's on in this weather?
Nobody's lived here for so long.
This smell is way too strong.
Smelling this every day,
even a living person would get pickled in it.
This smell really stings the nose.
These are all perfume bottles.
And the caps are all open.
Isn't perfume something
you girls treat as precious?
Leaving them all open like this,
what a waste.
These
are cheap bulk-bottled knockoffs.
The smell's too strong.
Qin Mo,
open the windows.
They're all sealed shut.
This side too.
There are tons more perfume bottles here.
All this perfume,
combined with all these flowers,
it's a bit strange.
What is she trying to do?
Search over there.
Check inside the cabinet.
Tung oil.
But the smell isn't right.
Why does it stink a bit?
A wooden board.
This board is a bit strange.