I often wonder
why those pretty girls win at life
What gives them the right?
Just because of their face?
And if they lost that face,
would they still be loved?
What are you doing?
Get away!
Is this person you?
Whether you believe it or not,
I never once thought of killing anyone.
She kept hitting me.
I had no choice but to fight back.
After she passed out,
I looked at her face
and I wanted her to taste
what it's like to be ugly.
Who would've thought,
she lost her footing
and drowned in the river.
That was her karma.
And after that?
Why did you keep killing?
They wouldn't let me go.
Cindy is dead.
Did you know?
Take it easy.
Have some water first.
Say something!
Did you do it?
I had no grudge against her.
Why would I kill her?
Cut the crap.
You were the one who envied her most.
I...
Zhao Yan,
I gave you everything.
How could I ever lie to you?
I love you so much.
That face of yours...
With some makeup,
it's at least presentable.
Do you love me?
Yes.
Of course I do.
I love you too.
Where's your tattoo?
Tattoo?
I'll get one for you.
What are you thinking?
Didn't you say you loved me?
I love plenty of people.
As if you deserve it.
Liar!
You...
Fanny!
It was Lele!
Come save me!
Lele...
Take me to the hospital.
I'm begging you.
Lele...
Let me go.
It's all my fault.
Lele, don't!
Don't kill me!
Lele, I'll marry you!
Lele...
I'll marry you.
I truly love you.
The final step of making a mummy
is wrapping the body in linen,
applying spices on every layer.
Through this intricate process,
the flesh transcends time,
becoming a silent witness linking
the mortal world to eternity.
Lying to me?
No.
I'm not lying to you.
I...
Zhao Yan died right here.
You don't need to look at me like that.
I don't need pity.
Since he said he'd marry me,
he should keep his promise.
In life and death, together.
What about Fanny then?
Hey.
Where are you?
I know you did it.
If you don't pay up,
I'll report you.
Where's the money?
All my money is here.
Can you let me go?
This is only for this month.
Next month, same again.
Or I'll tell the police
that you and Yu Tianfang
conspired to kill Zhao Yan.
Why are you pushing me?
Why?
I love the Bai brothers' story.
So I used Fanny
to put together a family portrait.
Right here,
I attacked Fanny.
The hospital called. Fanny's awake.
We did a brief interview with her.
She identified the attacker.
It's Mao Lele.
My only regret
is dragging Brother Tianfang down.
He was so good to me.
What a shame.
I'll never get the chance to repay him.
Brother Tianfang.
I'm sorry.
Could you grab me a drink?
What do you want?
Coke.
Sugar-free, please.
Did you get all that down?
Take her away.
Lele. Brother Tianfang.
Why are you so foolish?
I'm sorry, brother.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
There might've been a way out.
Why did you do something so stupid?
I was afraid you'd worry about me.
I was afraid you'd hate me.
Then I'd truly have nothing left.
Say what you have to say, quickly.
Keep an eye on her.
Brother.
Your favorite Coke.
From now on,
I can't run out and get drinks for you anymore.
It's good.
From now on, every time
I drink Coke, I'll think of you.
I'll think of a girl
named Mao Lele.
I'll never forget you.
Brother.
If we could start over,
would you like me?
You
love eating really sour green apples.
Every time
you go out, you carry a little notebook to draw.
You also sneak out back
to feed the stray cats.
You don't like makeup or dressing up,
because you want to be your true self.
I like a girl just like you.
Like a little sister.
Thank you for not lying to me.
Brother.
I'm leaving now.
Take good care of yourself.
In my next life,
I'll definitely be braver.
Mao Lele.
Remember to eat your meals on time.
Captain Chu.
Let's go.
Those two people...
they looked kind of familiar.
That girl looked so pitiful.
She must've been through a lot.
What's there to pity about a killer?
She brought it on herself.
Then what about us?
You're picking a fight, aren't you?
I told you, don't stay here.
Don't stay here.
But you insisted on staying.
Now look what happened.
We ran into a murder case.
And we can't even leave.
This month's money...
we can't pay it back again.
If you hadn't gambled away even your shorts,
would I be out scamming people with you every day?
Living in fear all day long.
If I'd known,
I'd have married that rich guy chasing me.
Don't you dare.
Don't you dare!
You hit me?
Screw you!
Go on, hit me!
Beat me to death if you've got the guts!
I'll beat you to death today!
That'll teach you to keep talking!
You want another man?
I was such a fool.
Lele's been through so much,
yet I didn't notice a thing.
I sensed something was wrong,
but I couldn't help.
I'm partly to blame too.
No use overthinking it.
Just work hard from now on,
boost the performance numbers,
that's what matters most.
Money, money, money.
All you see is money.
Qibao.
Don't talk to Boss Bai like that.
We're not running a charity, are we?
What do you know?
Okay, okay, my bad.
Hello, you two.
Welcome to Qingyuan Villa.
Who made the reservation?
Under my name.
Wang Kechen.
Alright, here you go, sir.
I'll handle it.
Fanny.
I'll go check in first.
Lao Li, take care of them.
This way, please.
Hello.
Wang Kechen.
Quit rushing me.
What's the rush? What is it?
Brother Jun.
Brother Jun, what brings you here?
Boss.
Your favorite coffee.
What did you call me here for?
Tianfang.
I know you like He Siqi.
But a man
should put his career first.
Only with a career
can you truly protect
the woman you love.
Don't worry, boss.
I always separate work from personal life.
Personal romantic matters
will absolutely not affect
my professionalism or focus at work.
Do you know
what kind of man women hate most?
A wishy-washy man.
Boss.
Just say what you mean.
There've been many incidents at the resort lately.
You'd better keep a close eye on things.
Is that all?
Isn't that exactly my job?
Don't worry, boss.
From now on,
you're the general manager here.
General manager?
Can I really do it?
Am... am I the right fit?
I wouldn't have guessed.
You really know how to play coy.
Whether you can handle it or not,
right now the only person I can use
is you.
If you screw it up,
you're out immediately.
I can do it.
I can do it, I can do it.
Thank you, boss.
Don't worry.
I won't let you down.
I'll definitely run the resort well.
Sorry about that.
Boss.
You're really making that kid Yu Tianfang
the general manager?
Hey, Old Li.
Are you jealous of me or what?
A man of your age,
still eavesdropping on people?
Aren't you?
No.
Some guests are fighting
in a room again.
Go, quick!
Boss, I'll come back to sign it!