Hey
Why is the anesthetic I ordered short?
For local anesthesia, I need extra supply.
You have to make up the missing amount.
Or I'll report you.
I wonder how well it works.
If only I had someone to practice on.
You.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Let go!
Get off!
Why can't I reach Zhao Yan?
Hope nothing's happened.
Boss Bai.
Where is this?
This?
This was during our overseas team retreat.
What's this stamp printed on it?
It's a popular local thing called
a Nuna stamp.
It's made from plant-based ingredients.
It fades within a few weeks.
Look.
I have one here too.
Yu Tianfang also took everyone to buy stamps.
It's just like those pork stamps.
The people on this retreat,
especially those with the Nuna stamp,
do you have a list?
I'll make one for you.
Xiao Mao.
Come here a sec.
Go.
Make a list of everyone who went on
the last overseas retreat for me.
I happen to have the retreat list on my phone.
Let me find it.
You went on the retreat too?
Which one is you?
This one.
Do you know what happened to Cindy?
I heard
Cindy drowned.
Send me the list, then you can go.
By the way,
that list,
send it directly to me.
What's your name?
I'm... I'm Mao Lele.
No need to be nervous.
This is just routine questioning.
Don't worry.
You can go.
Captain Chu, it's so late.
Let's go grab dinner first.
Boss Bai,
dinner can wait.
Everyone on this list,
we need to question them all.
Captain Chu,
we're in a tough spot here.
If you keep investigating like this,
my resort's business will be ruined.
Besides,
you only suspect the killer's hiding here,
you don't have hard evidence, right?
Boss Bai,
we completely understand your situation.
We hope you can understand ours too.
This is our job.
Until we catch the suspect,
we're responsible for everyone's safety.
The guest rooms have been searched.
The surveillance room won't be fixed anytime soon.
Hiding here
should be safe enough.
But even the cops can't find the suspect.
Who am I supposed to investigate?
The more I think about it,
the most suspicious person is me.
Hello.
Hello,
ma'am.
Up there!
After him!
Tianfang, what's wrong?
Run!
Something's happened again.
Freeze! Don't move!
Police!
Step back! Protect the crime scene!
How is she?
She still has a pulse.
Call an ambulance!
HQ, come in, HQ.
A woman was attacked at Qingyuan Resort.
We need backup.
Isn't this Fenni?
What happened?
What's going on here?
Come take a look at this.
This footprint...
It's identical to the one we saw
outside the surveillance room.
Captain Chu.
Look at this.
Maomao,
you really saved my life back there.
Bro,
you're always the one helping me.
This is just a small favor in return.
Right now,
I'm a suspect in the cops' eyes.
You aren't afraid of getting dragged in,
and you still help me out like this.
I'm seriously touched.
Why am I so damn unlucky?
Bro,
the Cindy situation isn't even over,
and now Fenni too.
I haven't even eaten yet.
Bro,
there's bread.
Bro, slow down.
A can of beer would be perfect right now.
Bro, here's a cola.
That'll do.
Look at that thing on her face.
Anyone can come looking for work at this resort, huh.
Zhao Yan was just staring at her.
And he said,
"if there's a chance later."
A chance for what?
You know, that kind of thing.
Hey, miss.
Miss.
Are you all right?
So damn stupid.
What are you staring at?
What are you looking at?
What are you doing out here during work hours?
If you don't get back, I'm telling you,
I'll dock your pay.
You two, get back to work.
Miss.
Looking like this,
how can you go back?
Come inside with me first.
And change into some clean clothes.
From now on,
you'll work here.
Come on.
I mean, seriously, you two,
do my words mean nothing to you?
I told you to go back.
Yet you're still here mocking her.
Why don't you look in the mirror
and see what you look like?
One's a snake, the other's a crab,
and you have the nerve to laugh.
Move it.
Yu Tianfang, you...
Bro,
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have the courage to keep living.
How many times have I told you?
Stop saying such depressing things.
You've got to have more confidence.
Cindy and Fenni,
they're gorgeous, right?
They still ended up getting hurt.
Bro,
I believe you're not the killer.
If only the police believed that too.
Right now,
I just hope Fenni is okay,
and that they can save her.
That way,
she can name the real killer.
Got anything else to eat?
I'm still hungry.
What's this?
Cosmetic injections.
Bro,
I'll go find you something to eat.
Stay put.
Just wait here for me.
Captain Chu.
We've looked into everyone,
and there are no leads.
It seems like someone here
is deliberately hiding information.
Don't lose heart.
We haven't come up empty.
At least we now know
Cindy and Fenni's social connections.
We also know
neither of them got along with anyone.
But doesn't that make it harder to investigate?
You're pretty optimistic.
I learned it from my mentor.
When my dad passed away,
you were still a rookie on the force,
and I was still in grad school.
In the blink of an eye,
so much time has passed.
Whenever something like this came up,
my mentor would tell me,
"Don't always think about winning.
Focus on the path right in front of you."
Hello.
The password is still wrong.
She seems to change it regularly.
I can't find a pattern yet.
Only by getting the files inside
will we have a chance at real freedom.
I'll be waiting for good news.
Don't worry.
I won't give up.
She owes me,
and I'll make her pay it all back at once.