Zhu.
Did you hear?
Your ex-wife
and Xing Wu's mom
ended up at the police station.
What? They went to the station?
How is that possible?
Don't listen to gossip.
Ask around if you don't believe me.
Listen,
you finally found
a bright student like Qing Ye.
Don't let
family trouble drag her down.
Otherwise, she may end up
just like Xing Wu.
Why's the sign broken?
It was fine yesterday.
When bad luck hits,
it all hits at once.
Just my luck.
What's going on?
A power outage?
Probably a loose connection.
I'll fix it later.
How is Grandma now?
Grandma's in the hospital now.
Shu Han's with her now.
Don't worry.
Lanfang.
It's okay.
You're back.
What happened, exactly?
Let's talk at the mahjong parlor.
Come on, let's go.
We'll talk there.
Are you okay?
What could possibly be wrong?
Shu Han is with Grandma.
Quanya and Shu Han
will take turns tonight.
I'll bring some things tomorrow.
The surgery must be expensive.
Is there anything I can do?
Don't worry about that.
You're a student.
Just focus on studying.
Why are you back?
Grandma's more important.
I just came to check on you.
Do you need any help?
I'm fine.
I've got this.
Can you stop trying to
shoulder everything yourself?
Your mom may seem carefree,
but that's because
I'm just giving myself an out.
Grandma's treatment
may be over 10,000 yuan.
I know.
I'll figure it out.
I'll figure something out too.
Yufen.
[Lanfang.]
[Why did you leave so suddenly?]
[We know things are hard for you.]
[Don't be embarrassed.]
[Ask us if you need money.]
[When you came to the shop,]
[we could all tell.]
Well,
I...
[Cici and I talked it over.]
[Cici and I can pool]
[six thousand yuan first.]
[The neighbors will]
[help figure out the rest.]
[Don't stress about it, okay?]
You know me.
I always stay optimistic.
Hello, Dahei.
It's me. I need a favor.
Here's the thing.
Something happened to Grandma.
She's in the hospital.
I'm short on money.
Could you
lend me five thousand?
If not, three thousand.
Two thousand is fine too.
Sure, sure.
No problem.
Okay, okay.
Thanks. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
[Qing Ye.]
[Help me with English.]
[I can pay you.]
Hello, Qing Ye.
Hello?
About the English tutoring,
still 300 yuan a lesson?
Does that still stand?
Of course.
Okay. I accept.
I have conditions too.
Name them.
Pay a deposit first.
Ten lessons minimum.
Book ten, get one free.
I pick the time and place.
No problem.
Make it twenty lessons.
Okay.
Morning, Qing Ye.
Shu Han.
Get in.
Wait. Didn't we say evenings?
Why are you here now?
Shu Han said it's on her way.
She's taking us to school.
Since I'm picking you up,
I'll drop them at school
then head to the county.
Let's go.
I sent you the new contract.
I changed it
as you asked.
When you have time,
read it carefully.
Mr. Ye is
really sincere this time.
He wants to offer you
a three-year full-time contract.
Think it over.
I've read the contract.
No issues.
Print it and start the paperwork.
Okay.
Qing Ye.
I have a contract too.
I thought it over last night.
I think we should make
our relationship official.
What relationship?
A teacher-student relationship.
And the contract proves it.
Those twenty lessons,
you can't skip a single one.
Not even the two freebies.
No refunds either.
You're tutoring him?
Since when?
We agreed last night.
We start today.
Xing Wu.
Look,
You and Shu Han
both work for my dad.
I'm a VIP at Xuan Island too.
And Qing Ye is my teacher now.
Guess I'm really meant
to be part of
your Xuan Island family.
Get in already.
Coming.
Ye Yingjian, hurry up.
Almost. Wait for me.
Qing Ye, remember to sign it.
Qing Ye.
Ye Yingjian's contract.
Do you have to?
Then Shu Han's contract,
Your job here
is to study hard
and leave after the gaokao.
Tutoring is just extra.
It won't affect my studies.
I know you're trying
to help Grandma.
Exactly.
You know
I can't just stand by.
But my family's problems
can't be solved
with a few thousand yuan.
In a week,
my enrollment will be canceled.
Tell Zhu Feng
to cancel it.
You're really not going back?
I'm not.
Liu Nian.
Lanfang.
This is an IOU.
Take it.
I'll pay back every cent.
For now, ask your friends
about some odd jobs.
When we reopen,
I'll let you know.
Lanfang,
I haven't worked these days.
Can you deduct
those days?
You won't lose a cent of your pay.
Take it. Don't worry.
I have money.
Then, Lanfang,
when can we reopen?
I believe
it'll be very soon.
Who is it?
Coming.
Xiaolian.
It's me. I came to see you.
Open the door. Let me in.
Xiaolian.
Xiaolian, I really came
to apologize
and make things right.
Well,
Xiaolian, I'll go now.
I brought you some food.
I'll leave it at the door.
Remember to eat it.
Xiaolian.
Xiaolian, Xia...
This...
I paid good money for this.
Pass out the papers.
Mr. Zhu.
Can you sign this for me?
A leave slip?
Yes.
I'd like to ask
to miss evening study this week.
Grandma's in the hospital.
I need to stay with her.
But I promise
I won't fall behind.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Zhu.
Right, Qing Ye.
About what I told you last time,
how did your talk with Xing Wu go?
Grandma needs care.
Xuan Island has to fix issues.
Everything at home is a mess.
Got it.
Okay. Go ahead.
Wu.
Take a break.
Grandma can rest now.
Go to sleep.
[Your enrollment's canceled.]
[Doesn't that feel like a waste?]
Qing Ye.
Why did you leave?
Skipping evening study?
I got permission.
Leave?
Did something happen?
Not really.
You suddenly want to tutor me
because I'm already good,
so I can get even better,
so we can both
get into good colleges together?
You're still unhappy.
Are you short of money?
Is there anything
money can't solve?
You think the same as I used to.
But lately, life
has taught me
that some problems
money just can't fix.
There are things
money can't fix?
I used to be confused
why he couldn't choose
his own life and fate.
Later, I put myself
in his shoes.
If I were him,
would I do any better?
Maybe I'd make the same choice.
He?
Who's he?
Someone in my family.
Family?
I don't know how to comfort you.
And I don't know
how to help your family.
But I know
if it were me,
I'd stay by her side,
even if I could do nothing.
Thank you for telling me.
I'll go now.
Grandma.
Ye.
You're here.
Better?
Did you get wet?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
How are you feeling?
Good.
Wu
has taken care of me every day.
I'm recovering very well.
That's good.
I brought you fish soup.
Have more later.
Get some calcium.
It helps you heal.
Okay.
All right.
Good.
Here.
Okay, here.
Hot fish soup.
Here, try it.
Okay.
Taste okay?
Delicious.
Lanfang made this, right?
How did you know?
I've eaten her cooking for decades.
How could I not know?
Look.
When she makes fish soup,
there's not a single fishbone.
Grandma.
Auntie asked me to tell you
after she deals with He Xiaolian,
she'll come to you.
Okay.
Drink it while it's warm.
Here.
I'm sorry.
Xing Wu's mom, why are you here?
I...
I came to bring you soup.
Look, it's noon.
Why are you still eating instant noodles?
You do so much for your students.
Have some soup.
It smells good.
You drink it.
You need something, right?
Yes. I need your help.
I can guess
what it is.
Well...
Xiaolian keeps avoiding me,
but I really need
to see her, just once.
so I came to ask for help.
No problem.
He Xiaolian and I
lived together for years.
Her temper, her ways,
I know them best.
How about this?
I'll go with you.
You'll come with me?
It's fine.
Thank you, Mr. Zhu.
Thank you.
It's fine.
Think of it
for Xing Wu's sake.
Xiaolian is home.
Xiaolian.
Xia... Xiaolian. Xiaolian.
Let go.
Xiaolian.
We need to talk.
Li Lanfang,
my student Xing Wu's mother.
Xiaolian.
I'm sorry.
Well...
I came to bring you money.
That's all?
Not 30,000?
It isn't thirty thousand.
Your medical bill was 1,500 yuan.
The rest is yours
to spend as you like.
Go ahead.
We agreed on thirty thousand.
Xiaolian.
I scraped this money together
from everywhere.
My shop is closed.
And my mother-in-law
fell ill and is in the hospital.
She needs money too.
My family can't offer any more.
We can't pay thirty thousand.
None of this is easy.
Besides,
Your allergy looks nearly gone.
Your tattooed brows look nice too.
You'll be fine.
Mind your own business.
Li Lanfang.
If you can't pay 30,000,
we're done talking.
Leave.
Xiaolian.
I'm begging you.
Take this for now.
Don't waste your breath.
Go.
I'll do whatever you ask.
I'll kneel.
You...
I... I'm sorry, Xiaolian.
Li Lanfang.
Come on, get up.
He Xiaolian.
What are you doing?
Zhu Feng.
That's enough.
Fine.
Let's leave it at that.
Come on. It's okay now.
Come on.
That's settled.
Settled.
Here, Xing Wu's mom.
Mr. Zhu, it's so hot.
Have some milk tea.
Thank you.
My students love this.
It's good.
Mr. Zhu.
I...
I need to thank you.
You mean back there?
I could've
knelt alone.
But you got scolded too.
You really...
It's settled. That's what matters.
I don't mind.
You don't know yet.
It's not my first
kneeling before Xiaolian.
Xiaolian, you know,
isn't a bad person.
She just has a fierce temper.
And I'm too soft.
She always says, Zhu Feng,
as a grown man,
why are you always so meek?
A man should show some backbone.
Don't I know that?
Of course I do.
The thing is,
at home,
it's not about
who's right.
When life gets real,
I know when to bend.
My dreams?
No place for them.
Apologizing isn't giving in.
It's winning by yielding.
But
He Xiaolian is too tough.
I was no match for her.
Mr. Zhu.
Somehow, everything
you say
sounds reasonable.
Yes.
That's what teachers do.
Actually, Xing Wu's mom,
I really admire you.
Admire me?
Look at the mess
I've made of my life.
What's there to admire?
Ever heard of trigonometric functions?
What?
Trig functions.
They move in cycles,
with a certain rhythm.
Peaks and valleys
take turns.
Life is a little like that.
Look at you.
Right now, maybe
you're at a low point.
But I believe
as long as you
keep going with hope,
you'll come out of it
and get back
on an upward curve.
Mr. Zhu, I get it.
You mean
my luck may turn soon.
More or less.
Hope your words come true.
Well...
Sea Goddess, bless me.
Bless me, Li Lanfang.
Please turn my luck around.
Mr. Zhu.
When you come by,
I'll do your hair for free.
That wouldn't be right.
You've had it hard too.
If you really want to thank me,
then do this.
Have Xing Wu thank me at school.
The way Wu is now
is my fault
as his mother.
Don't say that.
Xing Wu is a good kid.
I just think
it's a shame if he quits school.
A child's future
can't be ruined
by adult problems.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
Since I'm helping,
let me help all the way.
Sure.
Careful.
Okay.
Xing Wu's mom.
This next song
is for you.
Great.
I'm back.
You're back.
Zhu told me
you settled the compensation.
He told you that?
Why does he tell you
all my embarrassing stories?
Embarrassing?
How did he say it?
He said
you were a rose of steel,
turning back the tide
and bracing a crumbling mansion.
I only got the first half.
Well...
the second half is right too.
By the way,
Grandma gets out
this weekend, right?
The doctor says she's doing well.
This weekend,
she can rest at home.
That's great.
I've been busy lately
getting the permit.
I'll get her room
ready in a bit.
I'll do it.
Also,
I ordered a new
roll-up banner.
We're reopening soon, right?
When you have time,
pick it up for me.
Okay.
Coming.
She's back home.
Wu.
Mom.
Careful. Careful.
Careful, Mom. Don't rush.
You're back.
Careful.
Thank you, sir.
Ye.
Okay, thanks. We're home.
Mom. Mom.
Lanfang.
Mom.
How are you?
You okay?
Good.
Listen,
everything is settled now.
The business license too.
Look.
We've even put up
the reopening sign.
That's wonderful.
No more foolish mistakes.
No, no.
Never again.
Then...
let's take a photo.
Sure. Good.
As a keepsake.
Okay, Grandma.
Okay.
Come on.
Everyone, get ready.
I'll count down. Three, two, one.
Okay, okay.
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
One more.
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
Check it. Is it straight?
Crooked.
No, it's crooked.
Wait. Is it straight?
It's crooked, son.
Is it straight?
Just right.
Good, good, good.
Good.
Grandma knows.
This photo
makes me feel at ease.
The shop
will only get better.
When family stands united, all goes well.
Exactly.
Auntie.
With that optimism,
you can make anything work.
Lanfang,
I believe in you.
You'll lead Xuan Island
bigger and stronger.
Good.
Bigger, stronger.
Yes.
Bigger and stronger.
Bigger and stronger!
Good, good.
Here.
The weather changes so fast.
It was sunny just now.
Then it just started raining.
Maybe life is like that.
One second,
the sky is clear.
the next, a storm.
So, Boss Xing,
when do you plan
to start at the county office?
Not sure yet.
Things got delayed because of Grandma.
Wait.
What?
My Mom still trying to get me back to school?
If taking the county job
is the best choice
you can make now,
I won't object.
No more school talk?
No more.
Why?
Because I believe in you.
Whichever road you take,
even through a storm,
you'll still reach
your own Rome.
And I promise,
whatever decision you make,
I'll stand by you all the way.
Got it.
What's with her?
That's wild.
Look.
Wasn't her family poor?
So she's a rich kid?
And still had the nerve to claim aid?
Her family has a criminal record.
Can she still take civil service exams?
Her dad can't explain all that money.
She can't be clean either.
Look. That's her.
It's her.
Qing Ye.
Something happened.
What happened?
Did you see the school forum?
What post?
Stop combing it.
Combing only makes it look dog-chewed.
A dog did get to it.
Who cut it?
I'll avoid it.
Want some? Dried at home.
Aren't you afraid of me?
No.
They believe every rumor.
I don't.
Shi Min.
Qing Ye.
Come.
I saved you a seat. Hurry.
Drumstick.
What are you doing?
Are you blind?
Why bump into her on purpose?
Sorry.
Are you okay?
I didn't mean it either.
It was an accident.
Are you crazy?
You did it on purpose.
We didn't mean it.
Qing Ye.
You stained
Li Wenhui's suit.
Everyone saw it.
Right?
Yes.
Bullshit.
Forget it, Fang Lei.
She's got thugs behind her.
We can't mess with her.
Got a problem? Come at me.
Don't drag others in.
Then you bullied
Fang Lei and the others.
What about that?
Me?
I bullied them?
Zhu, Zhu, Zhu...
Mr. Zhu.
What's wrong?
Qing Ye is in the cafeteria,
fighting with someone.
You cut
both their hair
and threatened them
not to tell anyone.
That's not bullying?
Fang Lei.
Am I lying?
I...
it's true.
Look at Fang Lei's hair.
Look what they did to it.
You started it.
When I'm bullied,
I can't fight back?
You scratched her hand, right?
Isn't that bullying too?
It was self-defense.
Believe what you want.
Stop right there.
Fang Lei and Li Wenhui
just want an apology.
Is that too much?
Just because you're from the city,
you twist right and wrong around.
We just want an apology.
Say sorry! Apologize!
Shut up.
Say sorry to us.
Shut your mouths.
Apologize now! Say sorry!
Say sorry! Apologize!
Shut up.
Apologize! Say sorry!
Say sorry! Apologize!
Come with me.
Apologize! Say sorry!
What happened to Qing Ye?
Xing Wu.
Where are you going?
That's too much.
Too much?
The teacher is here.
Who bullies people like that?
Bullying people?
What are you doing?
It's the cafeteria.
It's for eating.
Let me remind you.
Each of you
only gets
one shot at high school.
Don't do something
you'll still regret
years after graduation.
I'll pack it for you.
Hungry?
Try it.
What is this?
Seaweed jelly.
A local specialty.
Go on. Eat.
It's not poisoned.
It's salty.
Good, right?
Weren't you going with Shu Han
to meet Mr. Ye?
Why are you here?
What a coincidence.
Just passing by.
Wu, emergency.
Qing Ye's in trouble.
Qing Ye,
You stained
Li Wenhui's clothes.
I have to go.
Something urgent.
What about Mr. Ye?
You know this chance
is rare.
Please apologize to him for me.
I'll make it up next time.
Xing Wu.
I thought
once I got to Zhazhating,
everything would be over.
I could start over.
This is a small place.
The tiniest thing
spreads through town fast.
People don't have much to do.
They love watching drama.
They hear a story,
spice it up,
make things up,
then pass lies off as truth.
The stranger, the better.
Exactly.
They don't care about the truth.
But they forget fast.
A few days later, new gossip comes,
and the old story is gone.
Don't take it to heart.
People who spread rumors forget.
But the people they hurt?
What about their pain?
What are you doing?
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.