[Episode 18]
Slow down, Cousin.
I-It's so big here.
Excuse me.
So many people, and everyone's all covered up.
How are we supposed to find him?
I asked around.
This is the Shi family's seafood farm.
You sure Hu is here?
Shi Min said so. The location points here too.
Guess we search.
Let's split up.
Sir, have you seen a young guy?
Big ears, and he stammers.
Is there a new young man working here?
Excuse me. Have you seen a boy about my height?
He stutters a little.
Hu!
Fan Tong!
Lower your voice. You're bothering people.
I want to find him.
Hu!
- Qing Ye?
- Fan...
Wu.
- Hu?
- Hu.
Fan Tong.
Oh, my poor guy.
One day away and you already look like this?
What are you wearing?
It's nothing. J-Just doing some physical work.
You're here for Shi Min, right?
We called her before we came.
Cousin guessed it long ago.
If not for that,
why would we come straight here
when there are so many farms on Changdao?
Tell us.
What's the whole story?
I'm not going to school next week.
My dad wants me to drop out.
Don't worry.
W-We'll find a way.
Hu.
- Where'd this kid go?
- Mom.
Why are you hiding there?
Did you do your homework?
I'll go do it right now.
Hurry up. Take this medicine.
It's for your stutter.
W-What's this? It's all dark and gross.
Miracle medicine.
A-Another folk remedy?
No, it's not.
Your aunt sent it all the way from Tianjin.
She said the doctor is really good.
A few doses and it'll work.
Come on, drink it up.
Y-Y-You go do your thing.
I'll drink it in a bit.
Drink it now. It won't work if it's cold.
Don't you pour it out. Drink it.
I'm watching you.
I heard from Mr. Zhu
that your grades are stuck.
What's going on?
I don't...
Listen to me, Fan Tong.
I'm not trying to pressure you.
But the Gaokao is next year.
If you can't get your grades up,
you won't make it to college,
and you won't find a job.
Without a job, you won't get a good wife.
What will you do then?
You can't end up like your dad,
stuck here your whole life. You get me?
I'm going to do my homework.
What should I do?
My dad just doesn't agree.
Who is that girl?
What does she mean?
- Y-You heard wrong.
- Who disagrees?
- No, nothing. Mom, you…
- Nothing?
You heard it wrong.
- Are you in an online relationship?
- I...
No wonder you're not studying hard.
- That's why your grades are bad.
- It's not…
Look at you. You can't even finish a sentence.
What girl would ever like you?
If you don't study hard, you'll be done for.
I get it now.
Shi Min's dad is making her drop out.
You tried to talk her out of it.
But your mom
thought it was an online relationship.
So with all that pressure,
you ran away from home
and came here to Shi Min?
I-I'm not trying to anger my mom.
I-I just came to talk to Shi Min's dad
and ask him not to make her drop out.
She couldn't even persuade her dad herself.
What makes you think you can?
B-But Qing Ye managed to convince Xing Wu.
W-Why can't I succeed?
So did you?
Almost.
Which one of you is Shi Jian Guo?
G-Get him out here.
I've got something to say to him.
Hey Sir,
where's Shi Jia Guo?
Who's looking for me?
Who are you?
What do you want?
I...
I-I...
- I heard...
- You heard we're short on help, right?
You're a bit skinny.
Whatever, you're hired.
20 yuan an hour. Daily pay.
Take all of these.
Hurry up.
Now get to work.
Come on, you call that "almost"?
You haven't even started.
Don't get down.
At least you got to talk to him.
Yeah, right. Plus you got paid
for half a day's work.
Look, Qing Ye, you're so smart.
Just help Shi Min out.
You there, the new guy.
Are you done with your work?
That's Shi Min's dad.
Who are you guys?
Hello, uncle. I'm Shi Min's deskmate.
My name is Qing Ye.
Yes. We're all Shi Min's classmates.
We want to talk to you.
Talk to me?
About what?
If it's about school, don't even bother.
No, uncle.
We actually want to help out.
The oyster harvest is good.
We heard you're short on hands.
We're from Zhazhating.
We've got experience with seaside work.
We're at your service.
Min Min never mentioned it.
I always thought
she didn't have any friends at school.
You probably don't know.
She's really easygoing.
- We all get along with her.
- Right.
- Looks like my girl's all grown up.
- Dad.
You're here.
- They told me they're your classmates.
- Yes.
And they said they're here to help us.
Yeah.
We're here to help.
Alright. Come with me.
You too.
What's going on?
Follow him. He's going to give us work.
Let's go help first.
Play it by ear.
We should let Mr. Zhu know.
I already texted him.
- Move it, quick.
- Okay, okay.
Slow down.
- Slow down.
- Okay, okay.
- How much longer?
- 15 minutes.
Mr. Zhu?
- Mr. Zhu.
- Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
What a coincidence. You guys are also…
- Going to Changdao?
- Hurry, hurry.
Quick, quick. Hurry up.
Come on, tell me.
What do you like about her?
D-Don't talk nonsense.
What's the big deal?
I like my cousin
and I never keep it to myself.
Shi Min and I are just good friends.
Good friends?
What kind of good friends?
Like,
whatever I say, she gets it.
And whatever she says, I get it too.
Soulmates.
I guess so.
We're kind of in the same boat.
We both know no matter how hard we try,
it won't matter.
I want to help her.
It's like helping myself.
So what are you going to do?
She's into painting.
But her dad won't let her. So…
Painting?
How can you help with that?
Your family runs a restaurant.
It's not like you can paint for her.
And let's be honest,
you couldn't even talk her dad into it.
Well, I never thought I'd end up working here.
Have some more oysters.
Bulk up a bit. I bet you get all shaky
when you talk to her dad, don't you?
Forget it.
You wouldn't understand.
Why not?
Take my cousin for example.
I like her.
But I know I'll never be good enough for her
no matter how hard I try.
People like us are lucky
if we can even look after ourselves.
You can't force the shell open.
Use technique.
Push down
with your wrist and thumb,
and the knife will pop it open.
It's open.
Shi Min, is this what you do
when you're not studying?
Yes.
We used to only harvest oysters in winter.
But with better fish farming,
we do a summer harvest now too.
My family's been doing this for over ten years.
We live off the sea, you know.
So…
so you have to do this much every day?
With quick hands,
we can get through 20 jin a day.
About twice what you see here.
What's the point of shucking them?
Can't you sell them as is?
Selling them whole is only four yuan per jin.
The shucked meat goes for 20.
Four yuan a jin?
One oyster costs 20 in Beijing.
That much?
At a fancy restaurant,
it'd be even more.
Those must be really nice restaurants, I guess.
I knew our catch goes for higher prices
away from here.
But I didn't expect it to jump that high.
Shi Min,
have you ever thought about
leaving this place
and seeing the outside world?
It's not in the cards for me.
My dad said
studying is useless.
And anyway,
I try so hard
but I still rank last in exams.
Maybe I should just listen to my dad
and stay on Changdao my whole life.
Grow oysters.
Harvest oysters.
Shuck oysters.
But what about you?
What do you think yourself?
Me?
I don't want to shuck oysters anymore.
And I'm done with drying nets
and gutting fish.
So tell me,
what is it you really want to do?
I want to paint.
But it's just a dream.
Uncle,
this farm of yours is really big.
You must make decent money, right?
Are you short on help?
It pays okay.
But when harvest season comes,
we're really short-handed.
Changdao has many elderly people
but few middle-aged ones.
As for the young,
none of them like doing this work.
And this year, Min Min's sister had a baby.
Her mom went to help with the postpartum care.
That's why I had Min Min come home to help me.
Looks like
Shi Min has won quite a few certificates.
That shows she's doing really well at school.
Sure, Min Min studied well
as a kid.
But after starting high school,
she couldn't keep up at all.
But the teachers all say she works really hard.
Maybe she just hasn't found
the right method yet.
You're just a kid. You don't get it.
You know what?
If you're working toward the wrong goal,
the harder you try, the more you go off track.
Look at this big farm.
Someone's got to take it over one day.
And that'll be Min Min, no doubt.
After she starts earning,
she can do whatever she wants.
I still don't know what I can do in the future.
But I do know
this life right now isn't the one I want.
I want to spend every day drawing,
not every day stuck here.
Qing Ye,
I really want to go out there
and see the world.
You painted this?
It's really good.
It's... just a doodle.
I support you.
Look,
your family business is huge.
I mean,
money won't be a struggle for you.
Maybe you should give it a try.
Talk to your dad
and get him
to let you study art.
But my dad says being an artist is unrealistic.
Better to run this business with
all the fish and shrimp and oysters.
That's not how it is.
Studying art opens up so many jobs.
You could do architectural design,
fashion design,
or be a teacher.
You could be an art teacher.
You're right.
Qing Ye,
will you help me talk my dad around?
I promise. I'll definitely help you.
Thank you.
Put a little of this on.
- What's this?
- Clam oil.
All-natural formula.
It nourishes skin and prevents cracking.
Sort of a seaside specialty, I suppose.
The smell is kind of strange.
But it really works.
That's not enough.
Need to put it on thick.
Here.
That's how it works.
Don't leave out any spots.
Done.
It's yours now.
Xing Wu,
can I see your hand?
What for?
Shi Min said
everyone around here
gets these calluses on their hands.
It's a coastal thing.
Harvesting oysters is tough work.
Many women do this job for decades.
When they're old,
they can't even straighten their fingers.
Everyone says coastal folks are tough as nails.
The truth is, you guys have it really hard.
So I want to try my best
to help Shi Min.
Zhu should give you
a "Best Sidekick for School Returns" award.
People only come back
because they want to.
Same goes for you.
Doesn't it?
I'm not really the same
as Shi Min.
Hu!
Be careful.
You scared me to death.
Auntie.
Oh my god.
- You okay?
- All good, all good.
Auntie.
Fuzz.
Why didn't you two tell me before you left?
Look how worried they are.
- We were in a rush.
- Yeah.
- Where's Fuzz? Is he here?
- We're all here.
Fuzz!
I was wrong yesterday.
I shouldn't have scolded you.
Do whatever you want from now on.
If you're okay with your stutter,
then skip the medicine.
Just don't run away from home
and don't scare me again. Okay?
I didn't run away.
I just... I just came to help a classmate.
Okay, I believe you.
Whatever you say from now on,
I'll believe you.
It was my fault. I'm sorry.
Don't be like this. Go sit over there.
Where did Fuzz go?
So here you are. You brat!
How dare you hide from me?
Mom, Mom, Mom. Let me explain, Mom.
What's there to explain?
You took the boat out without even telling me.
What if something happened?
Listen to me, Mom. If you hit me again,
I'll run away from home just like Hu.
You dare run away? I'll...
Auntie Fang!
- Auntie, auntie, auntie.
- Enough now.
Auntie, it was my idea.
We couldn't wait for the ferry.
So we just took the boat ourselves.
Wu, this isn't on you.
I know you.
You're a good kid.
Today I'm going to teach him a lesson.
Stop right there. I said stop! Stop!
Go easy on him then.
Don't worry. I'll beat him to a pulp.
Fuzz! Stop!
You're really something now.
Your idea, was it?
It's no big deal.
Auntie, I learned how to shuck oysters.
So you're a big shot too now.
Don't ever do that again.
Oh no. We forgot about him. Quick, quick.
- Mr. Zhu. Mr. Zhu.
- He's seasick.
- I'm fine.
- He got seasick.
On a boat this big,
and he still can't handle it.
Spit it out, and you'll be fine.
Son.
On the way over here,
I thought it through.
I shouldn't push my ideas on you.
You should have your own life
and live the way you want.
Son,
I'm really sorry.
Can you forgive me?
Mom,
don't worry.
I'll definitely live for myself.
And for your sake,
I'll definitely get into a good college.
Let's go. I'm fine, really.
We want to convince her dad
to let her go back to school.
But that's a tough one.
Yeah, right.
Totally.
Mr. Zhu, why are you here too?
Here, have some water.
Auntie, you too.
Okay, thank you.
So this is your classmate?
Yes. Shi Min.
The one Hu...
Auntie, water for you.
Thank you.
Mom, this is the classmate I told you about.
Shi Min.
This girl looks pretty well-behaved.
You know,
this girl and Hu are kind of...
Don't talk nonsense.
They're good classmates.
Good friends.
Yeah, yeah, good classmates.
Anyway, we're already here,
and there's no rush to go back.
Why don't we help Shi Min with some work?
Please don't, Mr. Zhu. That wouldn't be right.
It's okay. We'll help.
We women from Zhazhating can handle this work
even with our eyes closed. Right?
And the kids can take a break.
Yeah. You kids rest. We'll take over.
- Don't worry. Let's go.
- Thank you.
See? The oysters here are really fresh.
And they're big and plump.
Oysters are great.
Yep.
A man's power-up
and a woman's spa treatment.
You should take some home
to your husband, then.
Oh my gosh.
Mr. Zhu,
are you alright?
I'm so sorry.
Just leave it here. I'll do it later.
To be honest, Mr. Zhu,
I'm grateful for your kindness.
But just drop it.
No way.
I need to do more.
If not,
my students will have to do extra.
The thing is,
you're not really helping all that much.
Having you here as a helper
is actually slowing me down.
Seriously, Shi,
are you really
going to let Shi Min drop out?
You can't get a refund
for this semester's tuition, you know.
That doesn't matter.
I don't care about that bit of money.
The point is, there's no way
she's getting into college.
Instead of wasting time on books,
she's better off helping earn money.
Makes sense.
Look, you have
this huge aquaculture farm.
You must be really short on help, right?
I'll be honest.
When I was young,
I never felt tired and worked like crazy.
But now I'm older.
Every illness has come knocking.
My body fails me more every year.
You're not even that old.
I mean, Shi Min is a girl.
Are you really okay
with putting her through all this?
Mr. Zhu,
I'm her father.
If she were
any good at school,
I'd be happy to send her.
But she just doesn't have it in her.
Who told you that?
Don't you know?
Shi Min is great at drawing. And she loves it.
Did you ever think about
letting her study art and take the art exam?
Study art?
My family's been fishermen for generations.
We've never had an artist.
Maybe Shi Min is that exception.
You know what?
There's a national policy for art students now.
If her art scores are high enough,
lower grades in academics
won't be a big deal.
Really? That good?
But if she's still at the bottom of the class,
it's just a waste of time.
How could going to school be a waste of time?
That young man who fixed your radio.
The tall one, Xing Wu.
He dropped out for two years.
And I managed to talk him
into coming back to school.
Two years off?
That boy's got
some real courage.
Look, I'm a teacher.
The most important thing
I should teach them
is the courage to face life.
Shi,
I've been a teacher for many years,
and I've taught a lot of students.
Maybe not every one of my students
will become a success.
But
I taught them
how to choose the path
they truly want.
So they can try their best
not to do things they'll regret.
I want to toast you all.
All of you here
are Min Min's classmates and good friends.
Plus Mr. Zhu
and three ladies.
You guys came all this way to help me out.
I'm really, really grateful.
You know, I'm not good with fancy words.
I just hope you eat well, drink well,
and have fun.
Bottoms up.
- Okay, thank you.
- Yeah, thank you.
Come on, cheers.
Cheers.
Mr. Zhu.
- Cheers, Mr. Zhu.
- Dig in.
Thank you.
Here, have some shrimp.
It's alright.
Thank you. Appreciate it.
It's so hard to find workers these days.
No one wants to come even if you pay them.
It's all thanks to you today.
Especially you three ladies.
You did beautiful, fast work.
Please, Shi.
Don't say that.
We're all friends here.
Actually, my husband is the same.
When fishing season starts,
he's so busy I can't even find him.
I know that. Things will be fine
after this period's over.
- Yes, that's right.
- We had no idea
the kids were this close.
Otherwise,
we'd have come to help much sooner.
- Exactly.
- Thank you.
Hu's always
been kind-hearted since he was little.
I didn't know he came to help a classmate.
I totally misunderstood.
Hu's a good boy.
- Eat.
- Yes, he is.
Every family has its struggles.
But many hands make light work.
Next time you need people, just call us.
Whoever is free will come.
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry for all the trouble
Min Min has caused you.
Actually, I know what you mean.
You didn't just come to help me out.
Right, Mr. Zhu?
Speaking of which,
Min Min, it's your turn to speak up.
Do you still want to go to school?
Shi Jian Guo, I'm going to be clear today.
I want to study.
I need to study.
I have to study.
You say my grades are bad.
But I work hard every day.
You say I can't be an artist.
Maybe that's true. But painting
doesn't mean I have to be an artist.
I could…
I could be a teacher.
I could study design.
I can do lots of jobs.
- Right.
- Well said.
- I'm not finished yet.
Go on, kid. Go on.
Dad,
I want to leave Anzi County.
I want to get into college
and study what I really love.
I want to go see the outside world.
Right. You're right.
- Well said.
- Right.
Yeah, right.
But Mr. Zhu told me.
If you have to study
both your regular classes and painting,
time will be tight
and the pressure will be even greater.
What will you do if your grades
are still at the bottom?
I'll help her, uncle. Don't worry.
I'll study with Shi Min.
There are over 200 days until the Gaokao.
We'll make progress together.
That's right.
Shi, Qing Ye is the top student in our class.
And besides, there's also me.
I'll be there to help.
Good grades
take time.
Let's take it slow. Don't rush.
Uncle, Changdao and Zhazhating are both great.
But if we stay here our whole lives,
we'll just be repeating our parents' lives.
But if
you allow Shi Min to have a try,
it'll at least open up one more door for her.
Fine, I agree.
- Your dad agreed.
- Come on.
- He agreed.
- Let's all raise our glasses to celebrate.
- You really mean it?
- Yes, I mean it. Don't cry.
Let's welcome Shi Min back to school.
- Come on.
- Come on, cheers.
Cheers, cheers.
- Welcome!
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Come on, sit down.
I never knew
Hu had such a niche talent.
Actually, Hu wanted to learn piano
when he was little.
Piano and harmonica.
They are worlds apart.
His mom said
piano and harmonica
are both instruments anyway.
In Zhazhating,
you can't make a living with this.
But now I don't think that way.
Ever since this summer,
so many things feel different.
Perhaps
to Shi Min,
there's no difference
whether Hu plays
piano or harmonica.
It's really lucky to have someone
who truly gets you.
For me,
you're that someone.
It feels so good.
- Not bad.
- Yeah, nice.
Get over here and dance. Come on.
Come on, let's dance together.
Just relax. Come on, come on.
Come on, Mr. Zhu. Join us.
- Come on.
- Come on, come on.
Let's do it together.
Come on. Here we go.
Follow me.
There's no going
back in life.
On this one-way journey,
all we can do
is think carefully and decide wisely
at every choice,
and try to leave no regrets behind.
But if regrets find you, don't lose heart.
Face them calmly and see
if there's a chance to make things right.
If everything is already beyond change,
embrace it with courage.
Let go of your regrets,
and keep sailing
toward a beautiful future.
Let's stop here.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you, my friend.
I should be thanking you all.
Here's a small gift for you.
Some fresh seafood.
The only thing we never run out of.
- You're too kind.
- Thanks for the gift.
Actually, you should stay for a few more days.
I've got my mom at home
who needs looking after.
If not, we'd love to stay.
Just let the kids stay here a bit longer.
They can lend you a hand.
And they can relax here.
It's a deal then.
Next time, bring the whole family along.
I'll cover your stay and meals.
- No problem. Thank you.
- That's great.
Mr. Zhu, and all you aunties.
Sorry for the trouble.
This is what we should do. It's okay.
Shi, Min Min really is sweet.
- Yes, she is.
- Definitely.
Hu,
do what you can to help.
Got it, Mom.
Wu,
Ye is...
Don't worry. I'll look after her.
Good boy.
Everyone, time to go.
- I still have to drive you all back.
- Coming, son.
It's okay. We'll be back the day after.
- Don't worry, Auntie.
- Take care of yourselves.
- Hurry, get in the car. Come on.
- Bye.
- Drive slowly.
- Be safe on the road.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
Drive safe.
- Let's head back.
- Okay.
What are you thinking about?
My dad.
Want to talk about it?
But if it's not a good time, forget it.
I can tell you.
My dad
didn't really
care about
me much.
But when it was a big moment,
he loved to take control.
Every time he went on a business trip,
he brought back gifts for my mom and me.
But actually, he didn't buy them himself.
He always had his secretaries do it.
I never liked those things.
Have you ever heard of
a dad giving his daughter
red‑bottomed high heels?
Maybe
he thought you were
at the age to own a pair of heels.
Not at all.
It's because he was carrying on
with those secretaries.
Those women
bought me heels
just to spite my mom.
After my mom passed away,
they all rushed to take her place.
But then,
my dad got into trouble.
They ran away faster than anyone.
Ironic, isn't it?
Any news
about your dad?
No.
Look at the bright side.
No news is good news.
You cold?
Now I get it.
Biting cold
isn't just a saying.
It's real.
Put this on.
Let's go.
Off we go.
Where are you going?
T-To have some fun.
Why didn't you wait for me?
Didn't expect you to be this fast.
There's a lot you don't know.
Go ask around.
- Come on, let's go.
- Let's hit the road.
Go, go, go.
- Here we go.
- Let's go.
- One, two. One, two.
- Halt.
Turn right.
- Right face.
To the sea!
To freedom!
- Go!
- Let's go!
Cheers!
Tastes good. So many seeds.
Working on the island is tiring.
But this is so much fun.
I almost want to live here.
You only tried it out.
It's just the novelty.
A few months here and you'll think differently.
Setting aside practical matters,
what do you guys want to do someday?
I...
I want to be a singer.
- A singer?
- Can't I even dream?
Of course you can. That sounds great.
You rapped before.
You're good. I believe in you.
I…
I want to be a painter.
But it's just a dream.
Me?
I want to...
Be a truck driver.
You still remember that?
Man, you're such a good friend.
You've been saying that since first grade.
My ears are about to fall off.
Wait, your family runs boats.
How come you want to drive a truck?
I've been on boats since I was a kid.
All I see is endless water.
I want to drive a truck because every trip
takes you somewhere new with different views.
But your parents want you to take over
the boat business and the mahjong parlor,
or at least one of them.
That's just the backup they gave me.
Actually,
all fishermen want their children
to return to the land.
Like my dad.
He's a shark.
He loves splashing around in the sea.
But I'm a dog.
I need to run wild on land.