Brother Ming,
This street is Marquis Blake's territory.
Today, we're gonna make this
ruthless, bloodsucking family
bleed big time.
Alright.
Time to test your Meridian Canon skills.
Sounds good, Brother Ming.
By the way,
this is the biggest shop
in their territory.
Don't mess around, bro.
I got it, I got it.
Quit nagging.
I'm off to handle business.
So naggy.
That's her.
Brother Ming.
I'm in love again.
When are you gonna learn?
Remember this:
You're here to cause trouble,
not to find a date.
Brother Ming,
I'm just kidding.
but you know what?
To infiltrate the enemy,
the smartest, most ruthless,
and direct method is what?
Don't tell me
you wanna divide them,
make the Princess fall for you,
and have her betray her family for you?
Brother Ming,
you really get me.
This is what they call
conquering the heart first.
Alright, alright, enough.
Cut the chatter, get to work.
Excuse me.
Where's the Scrap Area?
Out the door, turn left.
Okay, thanks.
Brother Ming,
Inside this pile of stones,
there's good material.
I can feel it has
a certain energy.
What kind of energy?
A flirty kind?
Hey, local boy,
did you use to work at a nightclub?
That technique of yours,
seems like
it's been a while since your last shift.
You've practically rubbed
the skin right off this stone.
The surface cracks are weathering patterns.
The python band is faintly honeycomb.
Look at this skin,
and the mine checks out too.
Not bad, you've come a long way.
Right?
Keep acting.
Go on, keep acting.
See that?
Two more losers hoping the scrap pile
will make them rich overnight.
Young man,
let me tell you,
last month,
I spent 800,000 cutting three stones.
And guess what?
Didn't get a damn thing out of them.
I'm telling you, even my failed stones
were 100 times better than this junk.
Young man,
out of this whole pile of scrap,
if you can pick out a single piece
with even a hint of clarity,
I'm telling you,
I'll write my name "Long" upside down.
Long Ge,
not everyone can be like you, dear Long.
You're absolutely right.
Listen, you two,
why don't you just get lost?
Don't let this scrap
get your clothes dirty.
You're biting the hand that feeds you.
You can't even tell good intentions.
I'm telling you,
with that attitude of yours,
you deserve to be poor your whole life.
Brother Ming,
I think inside this pile of stones,
there are plenty of top-grade pieces.
Excuse me!
Hey, haven't you stared long enough?
If you can't afford it, don't paw at it.
You couldn't afford to pay for damages.
Why's your attitude so awful?
Let me tell you,
this massive fortune of mine
is more than you can handle.
Look at you,
in your whole lifetime,
you'll never come close to true wealth.
Stop acting like a big shot to show off.
Let me tell you,
keep your eyes open and watch closely,
so you'll know what it means to miss out
on a fortune of a lifetime.
Cutie,
come here.
Sir, you called me?
I'm just an intern.
I don't know much.
This pile of stones,
I'll take them all.
Did I hear that right?
This is the Scrap Area,
not the Junk Area.
This isn't something
ordinary people can afford.
Young man,
keep acting.
Do you know whose turf this is?
If you can't cough up the money later,
someone'll beat the crap out of you.
You got that?
Sir, do you want to reconsider?
This much stuff costs a fortune.
Don't be impulsive.
Cutie,
you're quite kind.
Even thinking of me.
No need to worry about me.
Tally it up.
No need to calculate.
This pile is 3.2 million in total.
Will you pay by card or cash?
Forget about 3.2 million.
I doubt you two could afford
even a fraction of it.
Card.
No PIN needed.
Guys,
look at this.
The drama of the year.
Two clueless broke punks
picking junk in the Scrap Area.
3.2 million received.
So what if it went through?
Just idiots blowing 3.2 million on scrap.
That's right.
That's probably their entire savings.
Cut it open.
I'm in a hurry.
You,
cut these few pieces.
The rest,
are yours.
High-Ice Sun Green!
This is from the Mo Xi Sha mine!
A massive jackpot!
High-Ice Sun Green? No way!
Stop making such a fuss.
Hurry up and cut.
Im-Im-Im-
Imperial Blue Stone!
No.
This is top-grade ice jade,
Sea Blue Spirit!
Sea Blue Spirit...
Oh my god.
The clarity,
the fluorescence...
It's priceless!
Princess!
Princess, this is bad!
Something's happened.
Something huge!
What happened?
Someone in the Scrap Area just
cut out top-grade Imperial Green
and top-grade Imperial Blue ice jade.
The value is incalculable.
In the Scrap Area?
How is that possible?
Who cut it out?
Two very ordinary-looking men.
They bought out the entire Scrap Area,
and only cut a few pieces,
but each is the finest of the finest.
A jackpot.
An absolute jackpot!
Let's go see.
The leftover scraps,
they're all yours.
They've just been appraised.
Getting a few million is no problem.
Really?
I can't accept this.
Don't refuse.
I hope you
keep your pure heart.
Kindness and gentleness
are the keys to changing your fate.
Move aside.
How did he manage to cut those out?
The Princess is coming, step aside.
After you, Princess.
Princess.
These two guests
just cut out
top-grade jade worth around 90 million.
Gentlemen, forgive my boldness,
but may I ask a question?
Answering a beautiful lady's
questions
is my honor.
How did you
manage to find these rare treasures
from this pile of scrap?
It's quite simple.
When you use your hands
to feel the jade,
you can sense
its heartbeat,
its gentleness,
and the radiance
it longs to give off.
You're quite humorous.
You haven't told me how you found them.
Princess,
if you don't believe me,
I could also
let you touch it,
so you can feel it too.
How dare you!
Disrespecting the Princess?
You have a death wish?
A misunderstanding.
A huge misunderstanding.
What I meant was,
feeling the Princess's
jade.
Your mind is filthy.
Do you dare
bring out your shop's prized treasure,
so I can also
feel its heartbeat?
Let's see if my touch is masterful,
or if your jade is impressive.
Insolence!
Our prized treasure,
the Dragon Blood Supreme,
is priceless.
How could people like you possibly...
Enough.
I'm in charge here.
Princess,
these two are of unknown origin,
and acting suspiciously.
Besides,
It's the Marquis's Dragon Blood Supreme.
Shouldn't we ask him first?
It's just a worldly possession.
"Hear the truth in the morning,
die content at night."
Don't question my decisions.
Brother Ming,
I'll take the spotlight,
you make the money.
Everyone,
this is our shop's prized treasure,
the Dragon Blood Supreme.
From the legendary Mo Xi Sha mine.
I'm sure you've all heard of it.
From that same mine
once came a world-shaking piece of jade.
With a single cut,
it revealed
a sky-high price of two billion.
Two billion!
The color and pattern
are identical to that two-billion
Dragon Blood Supreme!
Indeed.
This is definitely top-grade!
Mr. Wu,
Now that you've had your look,
tell me your secret to identifying stones.
Dear Princess,
When I examine a stone,
I need to touch it with my hands.
From this far away,
I can't really tell.
Then open the protective case.
Yes.
Please, Mr. Wu.
What's going on?
There's a sound.
What sound?
It's your heartbeat.
That damn flirt!
Flirting with the Princess repeatedly!
He must die!
Actually, stones
have heartbeats too.
You have to use your heart
to feel them before you can hear them.
What a load of mumbo-jumbo!
Young man, if you can't back down,
what you lose isn't just face,
it's your life.
Long Ge, have you forgotten?
He just cut out a top-grade piece.
We were all there to see it.
Just a blind cat finding a dead mouse.
Pure coincidence.