Hello, Ms. Qian
The Gao family is here
Ghost Hand is with them
Alright
Got it
Clear the floor
Sorry
The number you dialed is powered off
Please try again later
His phone's off
Wu Ming's phone is off
He fears the Gao family and Ghost Hand.
What do we do?
Wu Ming isn't that kind of person
Something must have held him up
Let's go
Come with me to face
the Gao family's masters
You truly are gravely weakened
Your five senses and organs are failing.
What on earth have you been through?
Even so, you can't kill me
I'm in a hurry
Best of three
If you lose
you and your casino are mine
And if I lose?
Then me and my casino
both belong to you
First, I am not a wager
And I won't lose
Secondly
I wouldn't look at some men even for free.
Fiery and confident, aren't you?
Fine
Let's begin then
I'll give you a chance
The first round
You decide
It's actually Ghost Hand
This is bad
No matter what we play, I can't win
I'll have to stall one round first
Hopefully Wu Ming can make it in time
For the first round
let's play Thousand-Layer Tower
Wang Qianqian
Are you out of your mind?
One round of that takes over an hour
I don't have that kind of patience
Keep it simple
First round, Three-Card Poker
Trying to stall?
I have a hundred gunmen waiting outside
Wu Ming couldn't get in even with wings
Young Master Gao
who the hell do you think you are?
Do you even have a say here?
I'm still here reasoning with you.
You should be thanking your lucky stars
Wang Qianqian
Don't push your luck
Fine
Three-Card Poker it is
A flower-shuffle trick?
Showing off a cheap trick to an expert?
What?
Planning to shuffle all night?
I'll tell you the truth.
Wu Ming isn't coming
Same offer as before
Be my woman
and this casino
can still be left in your hands
Cut the deck
No need
Just deal the cards
Three Kings
Pretty lucky.
Can I ask you a question?
I'd be happy to answer
You had a chance to kill me last time
Why did you spare me?
Does it matter?
No, it doesn't
But I want to know
It's simple
Killing is easy, saving is hard
I want to save you
Are you still playing?
You cheated
Despicable!
You said that to mess with my mind
I did no such thing
Today, we're even
Next chance I get, I'll still kill you
Fine
Wait
You keep failing
Gui Chen won't let you off
Join me.
I can protect you
Brother Ming
That girl actually hurt you?
Are you alright?
This Gui Chen is truly cunning and sly
I'm this badly wounded
and he still won't act
So you were faking it
Good thing I know you well
Cut the crap.
Wang Qianqian is still waiting
Impressive
Three Kings, huh
Wang Qianqian
What a skillful play
You almost won
What a pity
I shuffled the cards myself
There's no way you have three Aces
Show your cards
I haven't looked
I don't even know what I have
This is impossible
You swapped the cards
I demand to inspect the cards
Inspect them
Go ahead
Four Aces and four Kings, all right here.
How do you think I switched the cards?
There are four Aces in total.
How did he do it?
Wang Qianqian.
You shuffled the cards.
Your man dealt the cards.
You're not going to deny it, are you?
This round...
we lost.
How refreshing.
Truly the woman I've fallen for.
Next up...
if you lose one more round,
you...
and your casino...
will all be mine.
Young master.
Wu Ming has arrived.
Gao Jin set up an ambush on all sides.
Wu Ming.
I'm placing my life in your hands.
You must not let me down.
Now then,
no one can get in anymore.
Let the second round begin.
Let's...
play something thrilling.
Fine.
Then let's bring on the thrills.
I love the thrill of a racing heart.
Six chambers, load five bullets.
Leave one empty.
The rest is up to fate.
You first, or me?
This is murder!
I wouldn't say that.
Once you're at the gambling table,
you have to keep betting.
Refusing to bet means admitting defeat.
The choice is yours.
If I lose the casino,
I, Wang Qianqian, have no reason to live.
Perhaps...
I never should have staked my very life
on Wu Ming in the first place.
Fine.
I'll bet.
Ms. Qian.
Why don't I do it instead?
No need.
This is my fate.
If I lose,
all of you should find your own way out.
Stop stalling.
How about I go first?
This shot...
has an 84 percent chance of death.
Oh, I'm so scared.
I thought I'd actually lost my touch.
Miss Wang,
it's your turn now.
This shot...
has a 100 percent chance of death.
If you admit defeat,
there's still time.
Don't even dream of it.
Your little lover can't get in here.
He's as good as dead.
Be my woman.
Come into my arms.
This casino...
I'll still let you run it.
In your dreams.
The gunshots have stopped.
You heard that, didn't you?
He's shot to pieces and sent to hell.
Gao Jin.
You'll die a horrible death.
Wu Ming.
I'm sorry.
I'll come join you.
Ms. Qian!
Wait!
Wu Ming!