Sorry to keep you waiting.
Glad you made it.
Impossible.
I had over a hundred gunmen and snipers stationed.
How did you get in?
Oh, those guys outside?
Well, you see...
It was getting late.
So I let them turn in early.
The next shot is 100% fatal.
Your words.
So you're Wu Ming.
You've got some guts.
But to throw your life away
all for a woman...
What a pitiful fool.
Today, I'll send you to your grave.
Remember the name of your killer.
Ghost Hand Shadowless.
Brother Ming!
How is this possible?
Even fate leaves one path of escape.
And as for people,
never speak in absolutes.
Your turn.
Go ahead.
Today, I, Ghost Hand,
fall at your hands, Wu Ming.
A bet's a bet.
Empty.
Quick hands, huh?
I saw it all.
That's right.
I didn't study the Pulse Classic for nothing.
Brother Ming!
I can do it too!
Wu Ming!
Never thought
you'd fall into my hands today.
Goodbye.
How did the gun misfire?
Blame your own rotten luck.
You...
You must've cheated!
Sore loser.
We never even touched the gun.
If anyone cheated, it was him.
He got himself killed.
A bet's a bet.
This round, we win.
Gao Jin.
What's the wager for round three?
I...
This was supposed to be a sure win for me.
How did it...
You've dragged it into
No,
a guaranteed loss.
You're going to lose.
This wavy-haired lady has serious presence.
It's you.
You two know each other?
She is Divine Sparrow.
Called the young gambling goddess since childhood.
Impressive, impressive.
Qianqian, long time no see.
You've got nerve showing your face.
You teamed up with the Gao family and killed my parents.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't be alive today.
What did the Gao family even offer you,
to make you turn on your own family?
The Gao family is nothing.
People like us
don't care about fame or fortune.
What draws us in is
the art of gambling.
It's the mountain peak.
It's the Way.
Don't you agree with me,
little brother?
Brother Ming,
she's looking down on us.
Take her down.
Tianyi isn't a mountain peak,
much less the Way.
A newborn calf doesn't fear tigers.
However,
even Ghost Hand was no match for you.
You truly are impressive.
Little brother,
let big sister see what you've got.
This wavy-haired lady,
she sure knows how to flirt.
What shall we bet on?
You decide.
No way.
We can't let her decide.
Don't forget,
remember what happened last time.
Qianqian,
your petty tricks won't fly here.
Gambling should be fair and square.
Mr. Tianyi taught me
the highest realm of gambling
is doing as one pleases.
She's got some skill.
This isn't swapping cards anymore.
This is transforming cards.
Can this even be called gambling?
Brother Ming,
her hands are way too fast.
I didn't even see it clearly.
So this is the Way you pursue?
Nothing special after all.
What's going on?
You can transform cards too?
I didn't transform any cards.
And I didn't swap them either.
This is just a form of mind control.
The first card she showed us
replaced every card that followed.
Mind control technique.
A crooked trick.
Yet it didn't fool you.
Little brother,
you really do impress me.
If I don't show real skill,
I can't conquer you.
Let's play Blackjack.
How about it?
Fine.
Then let's make it exciting.
You deal my cards,
and I'll deal yours.
Interesting.
Let's do it.
But
no splitting cards, okay?
Agreed.
Both players, please check the cards.
We can begin now.
Both are ten points.
Little brother.
Want another card?
If we're playing cards, just play.
Why talk so dirty?
Say one more word of nonsense
and I'll rip your mouth apart.
He's already at twenty.
You're already at twenty.
Sis only has ten.
Sis wants another.
Little brother really knows how to dote on his sis.
Are you taking another card?
If you do,
you'll bust for sure.
If you don't,
the dealer beats the player.
And then you're bound to lose.
Hit me.
Bold move.
Then sis takes one too.
If I don't hit twenty-one,
sis loses.
How about it?
Brother Ming.
She's really clever.
She left her lipstick mark on the card.
That way,
you can't swap the card.
It'd be rude not to return the favor.
Little brother,
you're so naughty.
Trying to bust me.
Right back at you.
Little brother,
you reveal your card first.
If you bust,
then sis won't even need
to flip her card.
Little brother,
swapping cards in public isn't wise.
This card
even bears sis's special mark.
When the Way is in your grasp,
you'll know what mountains and dust truly are.
Master its essence,
and you can return to the source.
And do as you please.
Twenty-one.
Impossible.
I clearly dealt you a ten.
You must have swapped the card.
This is the very card you dealt me.
This mark has my custom lipstick
and custom fragrance.
You could say it's one of a kind.
H-how is this possible?
Did you deal the wrong card?
There's no way I made a mistake.
How did you do it?
You said earlier
the highest realm of gambling is doing as you please.
But in my view,
only by not gambling
can you stand undefeated.
Remember our agreement.
Hold it!
I haven't flipped my card yet.
If I get twenty-one,
it's a tie at most.
You can't flip that card.
Aren't you a bit overconfident, kid?
Divine Sparrow, flip the card.
Fine, I will.
Fifty-four cards,
each one different from the next.
This card,
I'm absolutely certain it's the one I dealt.
How on earth did he do it?
In terms of mastery,
I've already lost.
But the hand itself,
I haven't lost.
Hitting twenty-one is easy.
This game,
I'm bound to win.