Drawing a 21 is easy.
This game...
I'm going to win for sure.
Jingque.
What's going on?
We lost.
How is this possible?
I...
Jingque.
This...
Wu Ming.
Your talent is truly extraordinary.
But that man
will never let a prodigy like you exist
to threaten his position.
The highest realm of gambling
is doing as one pleases.
How did it change back?
Master Tianyi changed the card.
It's like throwing a stone into a lake,
making ripples on the surface.
But once the ripples fade,
the lake will eventually return to calm.
That's why it changed back to the Ace of Hearts.
Wu Ming,
will you surprise me,
or will you turn out
exactly like Master Tianyi?
Brother Ming.
What card did that curly-haired woman deal you?
Does it matter?
Of course it does!
That curly-haired woman's pretty skilled.
She definitely didn't deal you a good card.
Ten of Diamonds.
I knew it!
She was definitely up to no good.
But Brother Ming,
how did you switch that Ten of Diamonds to an Ace of Spades?
And she'd already left a lipstick mark on it.
Switching the card
should've been impossible.
I didn't switch the card.
I only changed its appearance.
What do you mean?
Water has no constant shape,
no constant momentum.
It transforms endlessly,
yet its essence remains.
Study the Meridian Canon carefully.
Master one method, and all methods become clear.
Brother Ming,
I'll definitely be fine.
Don't worry.
I'll say it again:
power is a double-edged sword.
If I ever catch you abusing it,
I won't let you off.
Brother Ming,
you know I'm not that kind of person.
I want you to be the Sword of Damocles
hanging over the Noda and Wang families.
If a hidden tumor grows,
we must cut out the cancer.
Ayi,
you've disappointed me deeply.
You're unworthy of being my sword.
Everything you've given me,
I'll return it to you now.
Wu Ming's allure
is greater than I imagined.
Great enough that you'd willingly sacrifice your own foundation
to betray me.
It's not because of him.
Don't make excuses for him.
It means nothing to me.
He, the Wu Family, and I
are destined to be like fire and water.
Since
you don't wish to be my sword,
then I'll break it with my own hands.
Why haven't you left yet?
You're not welcome here.
Qianqian.
I am your aunt, after all.
How can you be so cold?
I don't have an aunt like you.
Your parents' deaths back then,
that was all a setup by the Gao family.
Master Tianyi originally chose the Wang Family.
I submitted to Master Tianyi
mostly to protect the Wang Family.
Can't you try to understand me?
I don't really care.
The outcome is what I wanted anyway.
You think I'm that easy to fool?
If you wanted to protect the Wang Family,
why help the Gao family at the gamble?
Sometimes I have no choice either.
How are things with Wu Ming?
What are you getting at?
Wu Ming is a great catch.
You'd better seize this opportunity.
My affairs
are none of your concern.
And another thing,
drop those filthy thoughts of yours.
Being so cold and stiff like this,
how will you win a man like Wu Ming?
If it were me,
with just a few little tricks,
I'd have him utterly bewitched,
bowing down at my feet.
Don't use your tricks on Wu Ming.
He's not like other men.
He seems a bit reserved,
above the mortal world,
untouched by its dust.
But deep down, he's a hot-blooded young man.
Just figure out what makes him tick,
cater to his interests,
and strike a chord.
Then you two will grow closer and closer.
Sparks fly.
All lovey-dovey.
I said my business doesn't concern you.
Want me to set something up for you two?
Get you to sleep together first?
Li Xiaoyan!
Enough!
I've never even been in a relationship,
and now I'm suddenly pregnant.
And that guy Wu Ming doesn't even seem to care.
Shamelessly going after him,
I just can't do that.
Getting him to pursue me on his own
is probably harder than reaching the sky.
What am I going to do?
I'm going crazy.
My baby,
don't you worry.
Mommy will raise you no matter what.
As for that Wu Ming,
we'll just let nature take its course.
Wan'er,
still up at this hour?
Grandfather.
I...
I'll be going to bed soon.
Grandfather, don't look! What is this?
You're pregnant?
Pregnant out of wedlock?
Do you know what this means for the Su Family?
A great disgrace!
Grandfather,
it was an accident.
Who is that bastard?
Which son of a bitch
dared lay a hand on a Su Family woman?
It's Wu Ming.
Wu Ming?
The one...
the Wu Ming from Zhongnan Mountain?
Yes.
The Wu Ming from the Chinese Daoist Medical Hall.
It really is his?
Last time, when he was treating me,
he just...
it just happened.
Wonderful!
This is great news!
Grandfather,
you change your tune so fast.
You just said
pregnancy out of wedlock dishonors the family.
Well, in all things,
one cannot generalize.
Only Wu Ming
is worthy of our Wan'er.
He doesn't know about this yet,
and I don't plan to tell him.
Matters of the heart
can't be forced.
Foolish girl!
That simply won't do.
A child has been conceived.
That is an ironclad fact.
For an ancient family like the Wu Family
with a thousand-year lineage,
what matters most?
The continuation of the bloodline.
It's greater than the heavens!
First thing tomorrow,
I'll set out for Zhongnan Mountain myself
to call upon the elders of the Wu Family.
Once the Wu Family elders
acknowledge this child,
your relationship with Wu Ming
will be set in stone.
A natural conclusion.
No one can change it.
Get some rest now.
Goodnight, Grandfather.
Older and wiser indeed.
That mood swing was truly something to behold.
Brother Ming,
why did you stop?
I suddenly feel uneasy.
What about that apartment I asked you to rent?
I got busy and forgot.
Brother Ming, just make do here for tonight.
Tomorrow, I promise I'll have it all sorted out.
Oh, by the way,
I still need to go visit Rourou at the hospital,
so I'll leave you to it for now.
Mr. Wu.
You're back.
You...
What are you all doing in my room?
Mr. Wu, you're in grave danger.
The Underworld
has issued an Astronomical Bounty on your head.
That cute little head of yours
is now worth a billion.
I'm almost tempted myself.
Don't you dare lay a finger on him,
or I'll beat you up right now.
You're a terrifyingly blunt woman.
Not a shred of femininity.
No wonder you'll never get a chance.
You're asking for it!
Bring it on!
Oh, I'm so scared.
Xiaoqi, just ignore her.
Wu Ming,
you're truly in danger now.
Why don't you come back with me to the Su Family?
The Su Family will use every resource to protect you.
What can the mere Su Family do to protect Wu Ming?
You'd be lucky not to make things worse.
Wu Ming, I know your abilities are extraordinary,
but an open attack is easy to dodge;
a hidden arrow is hard to block.
Assassins don't play by the rules.
They'll strike anywhere, anytime.
You can't stay on highest alert 24 hours a day.
Even the strongest person
will be worn down by endless attrition.
Come stay at the Noda Family.
We have the highest level of security.
Impregnable.
Enough to handle any danger.
They've put a bounty on me.
Being near me is the most dangerous place to be.
Thank you all for your concern,
but there's no need to worry about me.
If you don't want to be caught up in this,
then leave quickly.
The farther from me, the better.
The way you're talking,
that's no way to treat your friends.
Starting today,
Xiaoqi and I won't leave your side.
I'm pretty tough, you know.
With me here, you've nothing to fear.
Since you won't stay at the Noda Family,
I'll raise the security here to the highest level.
That's right.
You're our precious now.
Just rest well tonight.
We'll protect you.
That bed,
I've personally tested it for you.
It's very safe.
I need to rest now.
How about you all...
Rest? Good idea.
I happen to be sleepy too.
Wu Ming,
you know,
I don't mind a little company.
How can you be so shameless?
Second Young Miss,
that's not fair to say.
Mr. Wu belongs to all of us,
not just any one person.
Seven days a week,
the five of us,
one day each. How's that?
Fine.
I get three days.
The rest of you get one day each.
No way.
My sister wants a day too.
And the last day,
we'll let you rest properly.
Stop messing around, all of you.
Just get out, okay?
No.