Master.
You...
Wu Ming.
Why has your hair turned completely white?
Master.
Are you alright?
How is Brother Qian?
You're a good girl.
Go in and see him.
Wu Ming.
Your hair...
Master.
What happened to your hair?
I am unharmed.
Hair is the surplus of blood,
the splendor of the kidneys.
The essence of all five viscera ascends to manifest in the hair.
White hair overnight
means a drastic drop in lifespan.
You taught me all of this.
You've learned well.
All of this can be restored in time.
What on earth happened?
Your hair,
and this courtyard...
It's merely a natural phenomenon.
As for my hair,
White hair overnight is also natural.
I possess no power to defy the heavens.
See, what did I tell you?
I told you to read fewer novels.
Wu Ming.
I feel like you've changed.
You used to be like a blade unsheathed,
sharp and unrestrained.
But now you're
like an eternally silent sacred mountain,
or an unfathomable sea of stars.
I am Wu Ming,
which also means nameless.
I am whatever you say I am.
Well, you said it yourself.
Then I say you're my husband.
Husband.
I'm liking you more and more, you know.
Do not be disrespectful to Master.
Master must not be profaned.
Brother Qian.
You damn liar, you deceived me!
Didn't you say Brother Ming could save you?
Didn't you say he could save you?
How am I supposed to live on alone?
Brother Qian.
Rourou.
I want to be with you.
Brother Qian.
Brother Qian, did you just speak?
Brother Qian, wake up!
Brother Qian, wake up, Brother Qian!
This...
Brother Qian!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Xiao Rou.
Why are you here?
Didn't I die?
I remember being shot by that man,
three times.
Brother Ming saved me.
Where is Brother Ming?
He's outside.
I sense his aura has drastically weakened.
Yet I dare not make a move.
Why is that?
Why, though he's clearly so frail now,
does he still fill me with awe?
Uncle Pang.
Brother Pang.
Weren't you dead?
I...
I'm seeing a ghost in broad daylight!
You're the one who's dead.
With Brother Ming around,
how could I possibly die?
But you took three bullets.
How are you still fine?
Did he really take three bullets?
Yeah.
Of course.
We can all vouch for it.
Uncle Pang.
It was Master
who infused his own lifespan into you.
So your life now belongs to him.
Brother Ming.
Cut the nonsense.
I'll teach you a technique later.
Whatever you say.
What technique?
The Meridian Canon.
The Meridian Canon?
But your hair...
What do you think?
Pretty cool, huh?
It's wild!
It's fine.
I'll dye it back later.
I sincerely apologize.
I need to rest in seclusion now.
As for your elder's illness,
I'm truly unable to help.
You can bring people back from the dead,
so my aunt's illness should be a breeze.
Where there is no life or death,
how can one be revived?
Miss Su, mind your words.
Why won't you just admit it?
Just own it.
Either way, I definitely believe in you.
From now on, I'm sticking with you.
You actually defected?
A total turncoat!
Where's your integrity?
I...
Second Miss.
You just don't get it.
For martial artists,
the supreme realm is what we crave most.
He's the god in my heart,
the guiding light of my future.
What do you need to recover quickly?
Thousand-year ginseng?
Tianshan snow lotus?
If it exists in this world,
the Su family can find it for you.
Thanks for your kindness,
but there's no need.
I have my own ways.
Then my aunt's illness,
when can you treat it?
I'll notify you when the time is right.
Any leads on that matter?
The lead is in Jade Stone City.
Jade Stone City?
Jade Stone City is full of all sorts.
Even the Su family is a minor player there.
You must be careful.
Alright.
If you need any help,
just reach out.
The Su family will do its best to help you.
Yeah, that's right.
We're very generous.
You rascal,
don't let anyone swindle you out there.
We're your real family.
Okay.
I'll be careful.
Then rest well.
We'll be in touch.
Aren't you leaving?
Wu Ming.
Your clinic must be short-handed, right?
And I'm a top student at the TCM academy.
So I'll just reluctantly
stay here and help out.
I'm not leaving either.
It's too dangerous for the Second Miss.
That just won't do.
I must protect the Second Miss up close.
Too many pretty girls hanging around here.
With them keeping an eye on things,
it's not so bad.
You two...
Think it over before you decide.
I'm extremely well-read in medicine.
You won't get another chance like this.
Fine.
Then stay.
You'll start by grinding herbs.
You want me, the Second Miss, to grind?
Fine, fine, fine.
Whatever you say goes.
Grind, grind, grind.
Go find Huizi to get you set up.
Xiaoqi.
Do you think the two of us
hold no appeal for him at all?
Probably.
Then what kind does he like?
I have no idea.
Oh, by the way,
did you give my sister birth control?
I forgot.
You!
This is a big deal!
It'd be nice if my sister got pregnant.
Wouldn't being the sister-in-law boost my chances?
Second Miss,
that idea of yours is way too dangerous.
But still,
I find it pretty thrilling.
With so many girls fluttering around Wu Ming,
I'd better screen them carefully.
Clear your mind, see your true nature.
Cast aside all distracting thoughts.
I'll guide you.
A first glimpse into the Meridian Canon.
All things in heaven and earth
each has its own pulse.
The pulse of plants lies in their roots,
drawing in the earth's essence.
The pulse of stone lies in its veins,
condensing the earth's spirit.
The pulse of flowing water lies in its rhythm,
nourishing all things.
The pulse of the human body
is hidden within flesh and blood,
flowing through the meridians,
connecting to the inner organs,
resonating with the spirit and soul.
This is
the origin of life,
the mechanism of creation.
Calm your mind.
Feel it.
Hand over that sorcerer called Wu Ming.
He's suspected of using sorcery,
bewitching police officers,
tampering with the crime scene,
and stealing a corpse.
Officer,
this is a medical clinic.
There are no sorcerers here,
only doctors who save lives.
We have video evidence.
The proof is ironclad.
He bewitched Captain Meng
and stole that fat man's corpse.
He had three bullet holes in his chest.
Stone-cold dead.
Where's the body?
Hand it over!
And that sorcerer
must come to the station for questioning.
Or we'll charge you with obstruction.
Is the corpse you're talking about me?
Hold it!
You...
Are you human or ghost?
I'm human! Don't get worked up.
Impossible!
I examined him myself.
Pupils dilated,
heartbeat stopped,
even rigor mortis had set in.
There's no way he could be alive.
Impossible!
You're a ghost, you must be!
No, no, no.
I just came back to life.
You, you, put the gun down!
Master.
Lower your weapons immediately.
Or it's declaring war on the Noda family.
Princess Tomoko.
You don't go after the killer,
but you come to attack the victim instead.
Do you take us for pushovers?
It's a misunderstanding.
A huge misunderstanding.
We simply came
to check on the victim,
and ask about the situation.
Ask about the situation?
You question a victim at gunpoint?
Have you caught last night's killer?
The killer is
Jack, son of Marquis Black.
He has immunity.
The Black family does indeed have immunity.
A life for a life.
It's only right.
If you can't deliver justice,
then we'll do it ourselves.
We'll collect the debt ourselves.
Even the Noda family must bow
before Marquis Black.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You...
Insulting my Master
is insulting me, Noda Tomoko,
and insulting the entire Noda family.
Officer Meng,
keep your people in line.
I don't mind cleaning house for you.
I'm sorry, Princess.
I failed to discipline them.
Please calm your anger.
From this day forward,
the Nodas declare war on the Black family.
To the death.
For anyone who insults my Master,
the Noda family will use all its might
to wipe out their entire clan,
and wash away the shame in blood.
Well said.
Those three shots I took can't be for nothing.
Otherwise, my Brother Ming...
Anyway,
the Black family is hereby erased.
I'm sorry, everyone.
We'll leave right now.
Let's go.
The Black family controls
a vast underground arms and smuggling network.
Their influence is deeply entrenched.
and is one of Jade Stone City's big three.