"Double Helix"
(Episode 10: We Got
Together When We Were 18)
Lu Feng.
Whatever it is, it can
wait until after my shower.
Isn't it time you let me go?
What right do you have
to negotiate with me?
But what do you even want, keeping me here?
You should have had your revenge by now.
There are plenty of people
willing to do what you want.
But what about me?
I have nothing left now.
My brother.
My mother.
The people closest to me.
They're all gone now.
How dare you bring up your mother?
How dare you bring up your brother?
Don't you forget.
You abandoned me because of them.
You say you have no family.
What am I to you, then?
Let me tell you, Cheng Yichen.
The way you've turned out...
is the result of your own choices.
The mess I've become...
is all thanks to what you did...
back then.
It seems I've been too
good to you this time.
You still have the energy to make demands.
Is it because of Ke Lo?
Silent? I must have
hit the nail on the head.
Let me tell you something.
He's younger than you.
Better looking.
He's better than you.
A hundred times better.
You must be dreaming,
Cheng Yichen.
Where do you think you can go?
I'm telling you.
I'll never let you leave me again.
I'll make you stay by
my side forever and ever.
You're awake.
Now that you're up, go downstairs.
You have an important
guest waiting for you.
Hurry up.
Your guest...
is getting impatient.
Yichen, are you sick?
Why are your lips so pale?
And why are you covered in bruises?
I'm not.
What are you doing here?
Did something happen?
I'm here to take you away.
Take him away?
You must be joking.
Who are you to him?
He's my husband.
Husband?
Not anymore, I'd say.
Even if you're not divorced,
has he fulfilled his duties as a husband?
Have you two ever even... done it?
Disgusting.
You have nothing to do with him now.
What right do you have to
come here and demand him?
I simply invited him over...
as a guest.
To catch up on old times.
To have a chat.
Is there a problem with that?
A guest?
You took his phone.
You locked him in your house.
What kind of guest is that?
Besides,
you and Yichen are not related in any way.
What right do you have
to invite him as a guest?
Yichen, you want to leave, right?
Not related?
Do you have any idea...
what your husband and I...
Get out.
Cheng Yichen.
Tell this so-called wife of yours...
who I am to you.
Don't touch him.
What we've done together...
you have no idea.
Zhuo Lan, let me tell you.
Your husband and I...
got together when we were 18.
We were sleeping together at 18.
Stop talking.
You say he's your husband.
But what about you?
What have you two done?
What have you done?
Tell me.
Say it!
Shut up!
Go to hell!
No!
Lu Feng.
I should hate you.
So why am I lying here in front of you?
Maybe this is for the best.
In the end, going back in time...
it's as if nothing ever happened.
Cheng Yichen, what a coincidence.
Lu Feng.
I need you to promise me one thing.
As long as I don't have a girlfriend,
can you promise not
to fall for any other girls?
I just like you.
What's wrong with that?
I guess...
there's nothing wrong with it.
I want to be with you.
Forever.
Lu Feng.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Long time no see.
After the New Year,
if I still insist on being with you,
I'll no longer be a part of the Lu family.
We...
will always be together.
I,
Lu Feng,
for the rest of my life,
will never leave Cheng Yichen.
It's another year, Lu Feng.
Another year.
You have to stay with me this year.
And next year.
And the year after that.
Don't fall asleep.
Xiao Chen.
Bro.
Yi-chen.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
I just need a moment.
Drink some water.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Qin Lang.
This feeling is so familiar.
Do you think something
happened to my brother?
Of course not.
Don't overthink it.
But you've been looking for so long.
Is there really no news at all?
All I know is that your
brother is in Xincheng.
I can't find anything else.
It's like someone is deliberately
blocking the information.
Then let's go to Xincheng.
I can't wait another day.
Whatever you say.
Yichen, quick, hurry!
Yichen!
Yichen, wake up! Yichen!
Xiao Chen! Yichen!
Doctor, you have to save him!
Xiao Chen!
Family members, please stay out.
You bastard.
What the hell do you want?
Are you satisfied now?
What if Yichen dies?
Five years ago, I was the one
who forced him to get married.
In these five years, nothing
ever happened between us.
From the very beginning,
you were the one he loved.
And you?
You're just a bastard who
only ever thinks about himself.
Yichen.
I went to find you...
because I wanted to apologize.
For five years ago.
I'm sorry.
My mind was such a mess back then.
My brother...
and my mom, with what
suddenly happened to them...
I just didn't know what to do.
Lu Feng, let's talk.
Talk about what?
About how you betrayed me?
Back then, it was because
of my mom and my brother.
I had no choice.
Plenty of people would
love to do what you want.
But what about me?
I have nothing now.
My brother.
My mom.
The people closest to me.
Now they're all gone.
(Three months later)
Hold on.
Mr. Lu, you're here.
You're so punctual every day.
That's really something.
Xiao Chen.
The temperature suddenly dropped today.
I bought you a new jacket.
I think this style suits you.
I just don't know if you'll like the color.
I also went out of my way to
buy your favorite soup dumplings.
And orange juice.
Here.
If you want to eat,
then hurry up and wake up.
Where did we leave off yesterday?
Ke Lo.
Ke Lo is actually my sister's son.
He's a sophomore in college this year.
He came to intern at my
company over the summer.
He didn't want anyone to
know about our relationship.
One day, he came up and asked me...
if the company was hiring.
He said he'd found a
talented person for me.
I never thought...
I'd hear your name from him.
I only found out today
that you live in Xincheng.
It turns out it's so close to Lancheng.
The Zhuo family really
hid you well all these years.
I had to use work as an excuse...
just to find out any news about you.
I went looking for you before.
But I saw you and Zhuo Lan,
looking like a happy couple.
You looked so happy.
I really hated you back then.
I couldn't understand how
you could just leave me.
And let me suffer alone for so long.
While you got to live so well.
I really wanted to destroy you.
To make you...
suffer just like me.
But the first time you appeared before me,
the only thing I could think was,
'Are you doing okay?'
Xiao Chen.
When on earth are you going to wake up?
Let's go.
Xiao Chen.
I have some good news to share with you.
I finally succeeded in acquiring
our company's biggest competitor.
Now, our company's market value...
is number one in the entire province.
In my entire life,
whatever I've wanted to do,
whatever I've wanted to get,
I've always been able to.
Except for you.
No matter what I do,
how much I give,
I still can't have you.
Now...
isn't this pretty good too?
Lying here quietly.
You won't suddenly disappear.
And you won't suddenly leave me.
It's as if...
you truly and completely belong to me.
But, Xiao Chen,
if you never wake up,
then what's the point of me being alive?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Yichen.
Xiao Chen.
The doctor said...
you can actually hear everything.
It's you who doesn't want to wake up yet.
You must still be angry with me, right?
When I thought about you
being someone else's husband,
I lost all reason.
I arranged for those people
to put on an act with me.
It was all to make you angry.
I'm not actually into men at all.
I only like you.
From the very beginning,
I've only ever liked you.
What I want is...
only you.
Why do you always want to leave me?
Xiao Chen.
Please, wake up soon.
Even if you wake up
and tell me you hate me,
that would be fine.
I just want to hear your voice.
I haven't heard your voice in so long.
I just want to see you smile.
Where on earth do you think my brother is?
He must be in Xincheng.
But we've been looking for so long.
How can there be no news at all?
Qin Lang.
This makes no sense.
Do you think my brother
is hiding on his own,
or did someone hide him?
It's hard to say.
How about this?
I'll contact Shen Chao later.
See if he has any connections.
Are you hungry?
Want to get something to eat?
I don't have an appetite.
I don't want to eat.
You have to eat even if
you don't have an appetite.
I saw a restaurant nearby.
It has pretty good reviews.
Don't you love spicy food?
Get changed.
I'll take you.
My brother likes spicy food too.
What?
I said my brother likes spicy food too.
His taste is the same as mine.
We'll find him.
Don't you love apples the most?
I've been practicing every day.
Now,
I can peel them really beautifully.
This is your favorite rabbit shape.
I peeled this apple for you.
Can you please wake up?
Xiao Chen.
If you wake up,
we'll never be apart again.
Whatever kind of Valentine's
Day you want to celebrate,
White Day, Green Day,
I'll celebrate them all with you.
The lifetime I promised you,
I'm still waiting for you.
Lu...
Feng.
Boss, I'm heading out.
See you tomorrow.
Be safe.
Okay.
Sorry, we're closed.
Yichen.
I'm really sorry.
You're at it again.
I already told you.
We don't say things
like that to each other.
Besides, if we're really keeping score,
I'm the one who should be sorry.
I wasted you...
and held you back during
the best years of your life.
You didn't hold me back at all.
In fact, you helped me a lot.
If it weren't for all these years together,
I'm afraid I never would have
been able to move on from you.
I've completely made peace with it.
You need to as well.
Just running away...
won't solve any problems.
We took in a lot of cash this month.
So I won't deposit it.
This is the part to pay you back.
You should count it.
Xiao Chen.
Can you please...
not be so formal with me about money?
You've already helped me so much.
You don't have to pay for my
hospital bills on top of everything else.
Can I use your restroom?
Sure.
Do you have any news
about Yi-chen and the others?
I only know they're abroad.
I haven't found out
which country specifically.
It's all my fault.
I deleted all their contact
information back then.
And deactivated all my accounts.
Don't worry.
I'll keep looking.
I'm sure I can find them.
Sorry to trouble you.
The restroom is over there.
The lightbulb seems to be out.
Let me get it.
You just recovered.
You shouldn't be
climbing all over the place.
There.
I just saw...
there's instant ramen over there.
Can you make me a bowl of instant noodles?
Thank you.
Xiao Chen.
It's okay.
Today is Valentine's Day.
I'll always be waiting for you.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Boss.
Order whatever you want.
They have your favorite,
the hot and sour kind.
Don't be shy.
How's the interview prep going?
I'm feeling confident.
You've got this.
Boss, you're too kind.
I quit so suddenly,
but you didn't dock my pay.
You even paid me my salary in advance.
I'm sure you'll have nothing
but good fortune ahead.
You've helped me out so
much these past few months.
I'm already very grateful.
There's no reason for me to dock your pay.
Thanks, Boss.
What do you want to eat?
Hot and sour pork intestines.
Sure.
Let's see what else they have.
Yichen, are you okay?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm so sorry.
Watch where you're going!
It's fine. It wasn't hot water.
It's okay.
Yichen.
Bro.
Bro, look. My leg is really all better.
Alright, you two.
If you two keep crying,
you're going to flood the whole hotel.
Go get your own room.
Don't bother us.
I haven't seen Xiao Chen in years either.
Can't we all catch up?
Let's go, Bro. Upstairs.
Xiao Chen.
Bro.
Why are you so thin?
I was sick for a while.
But I'm all better now.
By the way,
what brings you to Xincheng?
I came looking for you.
Why did you cut off
contact with me back then?
After Mom passed away,
you didn't want your
little brother anymore?
Of course not.
At the time,
my head was just a mess.
And I got married.
I was afraid Lu Feng
would come back for me.
I was even more afraid he would hurt you guys.
So...
Wait.
You really got married?
You know...
Mom's situation at the time...
I had no choice.
But marriage isn't something
you can just jump into.
Who did you marry?
It's not important.
It was in name only.
And we're already divorced.
She's found her own happiness now, too.
Bro.
What happened with you and Lu Feng?
Did you know?
He's in Xincheng, too.
How did you know?
He's so famous.
A self-made tech mogul.
He's made headlines many times.
Qin Lang did wonder...
if you might be with him.
But I didn't think so.
After everything that happened.
Bro.
After you came to Xincheng,
you haven't seen him again,
right?
Actually, I've thought about it since.
The thing with me and Qin Lang...
Mom would have found out sooner or later.
Lu Feng just brought
it to light a little earlier.
I can't blame it all on him.
He didn't push me on purpose.
I provoked him, too.
Bro.
You can't always try
to be good to everyone.
Trying not to hurt anyone's feelings.
No one can be that noble.
Be a little selfish.
You'll be happier.
Bro.
Come abroad with me.
Since you're on your own now,
it would be better for you to be with me.
From now on,
I'll take care of you.
Okay?
Let me tell you,
I spent a long time looking for this house.
I thought the environment here was nice,
and you can see the blue sky so clearly.
Shen Chao has connections in Xincheng.
I can entrust the coffee shop to him.
If he can run it, great.
If not, he can sell it.
Xiao Chen.
How did you find this place?
I knew there was a reason
we couldn't find Yichen.
You were behind it, weren't you?
Are you here to take him away?
Do you have any news
about Yichen and the others?
I only know they're abroad.
I don't know which
country specifically yet.
You knew where they were all along.
You found them,
just so you could leave with them.
Isn't that right?
Can't I leave?