♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 42=
They say at this age,
we don't have to spell everything out.
We just get each other and get by.
We've understood each other
for half a lifetime.
But that doesn't mean
we settle for everything.
No.
Today, I've got to speak my mind to you.
Well,
the two of us
should get married.
Yeah, I'll marry you.
And you'll come live with me.
Proper and formal.
Say something.
Too shy to speak?
Here's some advice.
Alright?
You can't afford to be picky
at your age.
You don't have many options.
Right?
If you miss your chance with me...
You know.
Think about it.
You won't get another chance like this.
Weigh this carefully.
What's wrong?
Too much booze. Head's all fuzzy.
Want me to hold you?
Yeah.
How is this a proposal?
I have a ring.
Here.
I bought it ages ago.
Qin'e helped me...
Qin'e helped me pick it.
Then the kid got sick,
so I never got the chance.
If you say yes,
we'll get the marriage certificate
in Ningzhou next week.
Proper and formal.
No messing around.
What is this?
It's Liu Yi's longevity lock.
I'll exchange it.
I will marry you.
Come over.
You need to live a long life.
So we can
keep tangling with each other.
It's heavier than the ring.
Go home.
So lame.
Why did I come here?
Hua.
Let me stay.
Get lost.
How long does it take to get
a pass to Hong Kong & Macau, China?
I'm not sure.
You need to ask them.
Get this form stamped
at the Youth League Office.
Qin'e.
Driving a taxi
doesn't require much skill.
(Drive safe. Follow traffic rules.)
Just remember.
Get more jobs. Drive faster.
You know the roads in Chang'an?
Yeah.
There's no turning back once you start.
You have to make 2000 a month
just to cover your lease.
Once you get the car,
you drive every day.
Follow the rules.
If you get a complaint, you'll be fined.
That won't happen.
I'm driving to make money.
Rest assured.
Work hard, and you'll surely make money.
Awesome.
Here we go. Chopsticks.
So elegant.
Qin'e.
I'm sorry.
I was talking nonsense.
Forgive me.
Don't worry, we'll work it out.
This won't do.
You look good.
What are you doing?
Idiot.
Qin'e.
I found a new job,
driving a taxi.
Base pay is 500 a month.
There's a commission on every fare.
As long as I get more jobs,
I can save up money.
Trust me.
We'll cure the kid.
We can cure our son.
Yes, we can.
Master Chen.
Has Qin'e been back since the morning?
She came back and then left again.
Let me use the phone.
(This is the Diaojia Village Clinic.)
(The National Forum)
(on Pediatric Congenital Heart Disease
is being held in Guangzhou.)
Hello.
(Dozens of)
(the country's
top pediatric cardiology experts)
(are attending the meeting.)
(This forum marks new progress)
(in our country's achievements
in the treatment)
(of children's
congenital heart disease.)
Hurry up.
To Shanxi.
Faster, please.
Why the rush?
Just hurry.
How much is it?
Six yuan.
8:40 PM.
Excuse me.
Any tickets to Guangzhou?
Nothing in the next three days.
Come on, I want a ticket.
Anywhere near Guangzhou?
Check the schedule and come back later.
Go.
- Next.
- No.
Wait a minute.
Madam, here's the thing.
Could you check
for any stations nearby?
Any station.
Southbound. Anywhere is fine.
Okay?
Just the earliest train.
(First National Forum
on Pediatric Congenital Heart Disease)
We must stick to the rules
and the spirit of the meeting.
Understand?
Okay.
Like this...
Are you Dr. Zhang Haiqiang?
Me?
Yes.
- You...
- Please save my child.
What are you doing?
Why are you kneeling?
Please help us.
Please stand up first.
Stand up, and let's talk.
Where are you from?
I'm from Chang'an.
How old is the child?
One year old.
One year old?
Can I take a look?
You came at just the right time.
The first surgery
for a similar case in China
has been successful.
But
your child's condition
hasn't stabilized.
Surgery carries risks.
Let's wait for now.
Let him grow a little more,
and let the techniques develop.
So, there's still hope, right?
Be patient.
Let your kid grow at his own pace,
normally.
There will be hope.
Complete the hospitalization procedures.
Get your child a comprehensive check-up.
Go home and feed him well.
That will help him grow.
Let the baby have it for a while.
Is it fun?
Sis.
Could you watch him for me?
I'll buy him some food.
Okay, go ahead.
Thank you.
Is it fun?
Not for eating.
Excuse me.
A congee, please.
Okay.
How much?
Fifty cents.
Okay.
Okay, thanks.
Here's a bag for you.
Pick three.
Anything.
(Inpatient)
(Yi Qin'e decides to divorce.)
(She excels at playing roles on stage)
(but struggles to live well off stage.)
(All the unspoken affection)
(becomes debts.)
(Perhaps divorce)
(is the last dignity
she could give Liu Hongbing.)
(From now on,)
(she will bear these debts alone.)
(She chooses the single-plank bridge.
If it broke, that would be her fate.)
Why's he sitting there?
What happened?
Why did you have to get divorced?
Just like that?
What were you doing?
You pursued her so passionately.
And now?
The kid is sick.
And you're abandoning them?
What are you thinking?
Where's Laidi?
So you got divorced.
It's no big deal.
Don't cry.
Should I not have gotten married
and had this baby?
Don't speak like that.
Don't dwell on the past. Look ahead.
Focus on your opera singing.
Leave the kid to your uncle and me.
Three adults can't handle one kid?
None of the doctors we've seen
can cure him.
I can't just watch him...
He is my child.
Stop crying.
I know you're suffering.
But
you must take care of yourself
for the sake of your child.
Well,
life can be tough, but we'll get by.
Can my kid pull through this?
We can't submit to fate.
We have to believe in ourselves.
Don't cry.
Stop crying.
We'll be fine.
Why didn't you tell us
about the divorce?
It's not something you do on a whim.
She wouldn't let you tell us?
She wouldn't let you pursue her,
but you did anyway.
I didn't know
what she might do
if I didn't divorce her.
She's a woman with a baby.
What can she possibly do?
You know what she's like.
When she's determined,
no one can change her mind.
What can I do?
Save your excuses.
I liked you back then
for your persistence.
But now, you're abandoning
your wife and child.
I'm not abandoning them, Uncle.
Don't call me Uncle.
You already divorced her.
I have to...
I have to cure the kid.
I found a new job, driving a taxi.
But I'll still be at their service.
I won't be living here.
But everything else will be the same.
You're both saving the kid.
Why can't you live together?
Why must you divorce?
It's for the kid.
She won't have to
worry about me anymore.
If she tells me
that she's taking the kid somewhere,
I'll be here watching them.
I-I'll be right here...
I don't understand you people.
(From that day on,)
(Yi Qin'e and Liu Hongbing)
(Late 1990s)
(focused on making money to cure the kid.)
(Driving a taxi was hard,)
(but it brought in some money.)
(Liu Hongbing scrimped)
(and saved every penny he earned.)
(Though opera singing
wasn't as popular as before,)
(as long as there were elders,
someone would hire the troupe.)
(When going to perform,)
(Yi Qin'e had to bring Liu Yi along.)
(Life and the stage
became increasingly inseparable.)
(She also began to adapt.)
(Finally, one day,)
(Yi Qin'e returned here.)
(To Xiangyang Commune.)
Laidi.
Say hi to Mom.
Let Mommy hold you, okay?
Look at this stage.
It's where your mom first made her name.
Where she started.
Give me a hand.
Watch your step.
No real blades.
Isn't your mom amazing?
She's playing the general.
These people are all afraid of her
and listen to her.
Bravo!
That's my daughter.
Sis.
I've sprayed Qin'e's costume.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
- Anyone else's need spraying?
- No.
That's it.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- Okay.
Liu Yi.
See who I am.
Are you hungry?
Mommy will pour you some water.
Da.
You can say "Dad" now?
Dad bought it for you?
Say it again.
Da...
Say "Dad".
Da, da, da.
Dad.
Say "Mom".
Mom.
Get some rest.
Come on.
You must be tired.
Your uncle bought this for you.
Have it when it's warm.
Don't worry about me, Aunt Hua.
How can I not worry?
Don't be sad.
Didn't the doctor say?
The kid's just a little slow to develop.
Might be later than other kids.
No rush.
He's grown this big.
You two have had it tough.
It will get better.
Yeah.
One more thing.
My nephew
is studying computers at school.
He told me
that many people
will do business online.
I find this quite new.
I want to learn about it.
Do you know anyone
to get me a computer?
Alright.
Call me back if you find someone.
Okay, ask around for me.
Buddy.
A bitter gourd? That's fancy.
- Want a bite?
- No, thanks.
Keep it for yourself.
My life is plenty sweet.
Stop eating. Will you help us?
Have you ever seen a boss work?
Don't be cocky.
You're a boss?
You're still wet behind the ears.
- I'll be the boss...
- Seriously.
sooner or later.
You're just so special.
Everyone's working.
Only you're idling about
in that stupid hat.
Exactly, no manners.
Dachui is a mutt acting like a wolf.
You people...
He's putting on airs.
What are you doing?
How did you just pop up?
You scared me.
Everyone took some.
Why are you picking on me?
Still, you shouldn't.
You're the Troupe Leader's mom.
Set an example.
So high and mighty.
You think I'm money-obsessed?
Back when I was in Jiuyangou,
I never took a thing from others
no matter how poor we were.
Alright.
I'm taking these back for Liu Yi.
Think about it.
Laidi is working herself to death,
saving money for the child's surgery.
She's been singing day and night.
She takes after you.
So high and mighty.
What a fool.
Suffering just to save face.
Tell me.
Why did she have to get divorced?
So determined.
Now what?
Liu Hongbing is living it up
while she suffers here.
Stop rambling here.
Bring the kid. It's time to eat.
Why is my daughter
suffering like this?
Seriously.
The rich get richer,
and the poor poorer.
We're working ourselves to death
just to make
some petty money.
Some people go to those fancy teahouses
and sit on laps,
sweet-talking someone over wine.
Singing opera doesn't matter anymore.
I have big thighs.
So sit on my lap. Come on.
What nonsense.
- Seriously.
- Enjoy.
Uncle Sanyuan.
Do you know about that teahouse?
I heard they get paid 10,000
or even up to 100,000 for one show.
Great deal. You should go.
I'm not good enough.
They disgrace the profession.
They have no self-respect.
No one will respect them.
Dignity can't fill your stomach.
Auntie, you played Yang Paifeng, right?
Yes, I'm Yi Qin'e.
What's your name?
I'm Song Yu.
Daughter of the head cook.
The fire-tending girl.
I think I could be Yang Paifeng too.
You tend the fire?
I used to do the same.
Really?
Little girl.
Come here, let me talk to you.
Yang Paifeng can fight. Can you fight?
Of course.
That's not enough.
You have to take beatings too.
Can you?
My dad hits me every day.
What a strong alkaline taste.
It tastes just like the Mo
of our County Troupe.
What's your name again?
Song Yu.
Your dad's also surnamed Song?
Do you hear yourself?
What else could his last name be?
Hu, like yours?
Get your dad here.
Dad.
What is that for?
The Mo reminds me of Master Song
from the County Troupe.
I want to see if it's him.
Master Song.
Sanyuan.
It really is you.
Master Song.
I knew you were coming.
Seriously?
You knew we were here
and didn't come out to say hi?
Why were you hiding?
Caixiang.
Master Song.
Laidi.
You've become a big star.
Excellent.
Sir.
One Mo, please.
Alright.
Put some dried tofu and egg.
And shredded potato.
Forget it. Skip the egg.
Add extra dried tofu.
Alright.
How much?
Fifty cents.
Here.
Okay.
Young man, your Mo is ready.
Sir.
Thanks.
No problem.
Sir.
Where's the dried tofu?
At the bottom.
I want this one.
Okay.
Nirvana and the Eagles.
Here's your five yuan change.
Thanks, handsome.
Thanks.
Take a look at this one.
Take a look. Handsome, want one?
Okay.
Here, ten yuan change.
Look at these two.
Got the latest ones too.
Have a look.
What bands do you like?
Linkin Park.
No?
Okay, thanks.
- Come on.
- Young man.
Who said you could set up here?
What's wrong?
"What's wrong?"
You're blocking my business.
Don't you know the rules?
What do you mean?
Take a look.
I own that audio shop over there.
How am I supposed to do business
if you sell tapes here?
You sell pirated copies too?
No, I sell the real thing.
I sell pirated copies.
We'll just keep out of
each other's business.
Get lost.
Go somewhere else.
No way. I'm selling right here.
Young man.
You're tough, huh?
Come and take a look.
Come on.
Two discs.
Come to me for more.
I'll be right here.
Just up ahead.
Right there.
That's him.
Blue jacket.
Stop.
Don't run.
Brat.
What's going on?
Don't run.
Excuse me.
Police.
Coming through.
We're after him.
It's urgent.
Don't run.
What are you
cheering for?
Huh?
Not the head.
Don't hit my head.
Skipping classes wasn't enough?
You've started this?
Why was I running
with you?
It made me an accomplice.
Come on.
Turn yourself in.
For what?
I'm selling cut-out tapes.
They chased you
because of some tapes?
Those hicks have no clue.
This is heavy metal rock music
from abroad.
They thought I was selling scrap metal.
Stupid, huh?
Idiot.
Still no.
We got you into that technical school.
And you're skipping class,
selling "metal"?
I'm just trying to make money.
What for?
Just tell me if you want something.
Have we treated you badly?
No, you haven't.
That's why I can't ask for money.
I'm not like Gao Wufu,
who's draining you.
Gao Wufu.
Not on my head.
Show some respect.
You'll call me by my name
once you graduate, huh?
That's different.
That guy shows up, asking you
and my sister for money.
I won't be like him.
How many times have I told you?
Don't worry about the money.
Tell me if you need anything.
Your sister has been exhausted lately.
Give her some peace of mind.
Stop messing with that junk metal.
This is heavy metal.
(Study Hard, Mao Zedong)
Zhang Guangrong wrote to me,
asking me to go back.
What's wrong?
He's going south for work.
Zhang Hao
is taking the Gaokao this year.
Someone should be home
to look after him.
I bought a ticket for tomorrow.
Go ahead.
Look after the kid.
And about Qin'e.
Don't interfere too much.
Don't meddle with it.
If something really comes up,
then lend a hand.
I'm her uncle. I know.
I'm not afraid you'll do too little.
It's quite the opposite.
She's grown up. She can make decisions.
And you.
Don't push yourself.
Hongbing.
Have you been staying up late?
You look even more worn out.
Save your breath.
Just worry me less. That's all I ask.
Get off.
What's wrong?
Get going.
Hongbing, how is Liu Yi?
Same as always.
Will he have surgery?
My mom said
there's a cure for his illness now.
Exactly.
The first surgery was successful.
There's a bit of hope now.
That's why I must work hard
to earn money.
How much are you short?
Why? Are you covering the gap?
Mind your own business.
Do you regret having the kid?
What do you mean?
Have you ever thought
that Liu Yi
is destined to be like this?
You little brat.
Do you even hear yourself?
Y-You're starting to speak for fate now?
Aren't you?
I'm off.
Leave the metal.
What?
Why?
"Why?"
Why does a student need those?
Still thinking of selling them?
These are hard to come by.
I paid for them.
Fine, I'm buying from you.
Here.
Hongbing, listen to me.
Not interested.
This isn't about money.
Hongbing.
Just take it.
- Stop nagging.
- Hongbing.
It's not enough.
(Diligence is the path
to the mountain of knowledge)
Mr. Zhu, it's getting late.
Let me toast you
with tea instead of wine.
No, no.
I should be toasting you.
You're the Queen of Qinqiang opera.
I can never get enough
of your performances.
Stop toasting each other.
It's getting late.
Let's finish this last drink and go.
We have a show tomorrow.
Yeah.
Who do you think you are?
I'm talking to the lead.
What's it to you?
I'm the Northwest Drum King...
Enough.
Stop talking.
Sorry, Mr. Zhu.
He's a bit drunk.
Sorry.
Mr. Zhu, you're too kind.
Just call us
if you want to hear me sing.
We'll come to sing for you.
- Yeah.
- Serving the people.
- Anytime.
Here's to you.
Yeah.
Alright.
You know,
this time,
I didn't see the fire breathing.
- Not so perfect.
- I know.
Mr. Zhu, take care.
But "You Xi Hu" isn't suited
for a joyful occasion.
Next time, host a cultural special.
We'll showcase all the special skills
of Qinqiang opera.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- It's your contribution.
- Yeah.
We're very grateful.
Such bootlickers.
Money doesn't make you special.
- Take care, Mr. Zhu.
- Take care.
Mr. Zhu.
Sanyuan.
Laidi looks like
she's been exhausted.
Her child
has a congenital disease.
Heart problem.
Some developmental delays too.
And she's running such a big troupe.
That's why.
She's such a good kid.
Why is it happening?
What about your son?
Has he come back?
Yeah.
He did well in the army after enlisting.
He got a commendation and a promotion.
He's settled there.
A few years back,
he said he'd bring me over.
But you don't want to go anywhere
when you're old.
Exactly. At our age, best not to travel.
Yeah.
Wait, you're not old at all.
You have a young daughter.
You've still got it.
What were you thinking?
I adopted her.
I'm adopted.
It was raining the day my dad found me.
That's why I'm called Song Yu.
Uncle.
How were those moves I just did?
Can I play Yang Paifeng?
Yes, you can.
But kiddo,
this path is very tough.
I want to learn from Aunt Qin'e.
Alright.
Have your dad bring you to Chang'an.
Stay at Aunt Qin'e's house.
I'll have her take you in.
Dad, let's go to Chang'an.
Bring her.
Okay.
Check on the fire.
The banquet will start soon.
Take it easy.
Things have changed so much
over the years.
The County Troupe has little work.
Everyone's on their own now.
The young ladies
don't sing opera anymore.
They sing pop songs.
Or they get married and have kids.
Men go back to the countryside.
Machines farm the land now.
Not much use for them.
So they go out to work.
All sorts of jobs.
Hardly anyone sings opera now.
Same thing.
You know how glorious
the factory workers were in the city.
Same thing.
You know, Gu passed away.
If he hadn't,
seeing opera decline like this
would've broken his heart.
It's fine. Life goes on.
Dada...
Watch him. Don't let him fall.
Here, have some water.
Tired?
I'm used to it.
I didn't expect Song Yu and Yi
to get along so well.
You were about her age
when you first joined the troupe.
You performed here, right?
Yeah.
Yang Paifeng.
That was my first time on stage.
So abrupt. I never imagined
so many people watching.
Then this is your lucky place.
Maybe you'll have good news
about the kid when you go back.
Bang...
♪Waiting for dawn♪
♪At midnight♪
♪Longing for the spring breeze♪
♪In winter♪
♪Longing for the Red Army♪
♪To come♪
♪The hills are ablaze with azaleas♪
(Liu Yi, March)
♪The wind howls♪
♪The mist is thick♪
(Preview)
Heavy metal from abroad.
You want to watch movies too?
No wonder nobody watches opera anymore.
How come the cost is so much higher
than what you showed me last time?
I know a gig organizer.
He's got plenty of jobs.
A beautiful song for everyone.
Have some standards.
You're ruining the craft, you know?
I'm the deputy leader
of the Youth Troupe.
I'm doing this not just for Liu Yi,
but for everyone.
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪