♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 41=
Let me tell you.
It's been ages since
we've seen such a grand spectacle.
Exactly.
That's right.
We really ought to thank Ms. Yi
giving us opportunities.
Right?
You're right about that.
We truly need to thank Qin'e.
Qin'e.
This shows there are still people
enjoying Qinqiang opera.
Exactly.
Really.
We should also thank Sanyuan.
His drumming was superb.
He played the very soul out of it.
Exactly.
Mr. Hu's drumming skills
are worthy of a solo performance.
Right?
That's just too much, you!
This is nothing.
Today,
listening to his drum performance
is truly an artistic delight.
Exactly.
I'm flattered.
I still need more practice.
Let's learn from each other.
Why learn from me?
You've reached the peak,
why still learn?
There's no limit to art.
You should learn from him.
Actually, you'd
get tired of it over time.
Once we reach Chang'an,
don't rush home first.
Go with me to the Northwest Gold Store
on East Street to buy something.
What are you buying?
At a gold store, what else?
Who is it for?
For Hua, of course.
You're buying a ring?
Uncle, you've finally
come to your senses?
At my age, coming to my senses?
I figured it out long ago.
Just waiting for the moment.
Now it's the moment.
How do you know that?
It's a secret, can't tell.
All you know is this.
Look at the drumsticks.
♪My dear son pleads to go to war♪
♪You'll head to battle with your skills♪
♪I'm not worried♪
Who's my dear son?
Are you my dear son?
You're back.
Did it go well?
Very well.
My performance this time
was a huge success.
As soon as I stepped on stage,
I felt energized again.
I should get back on stage earlier.
Next, I'll refine my performance.
Look.
I put on makeup today. Do I look good?
So beautiful.
The kid's still here.
He's still little, knows nothing.
Mom will be back soon.
Let's seize time before she's back.
What's wrong?
We're legally married.
You're my wife, and I'm your husband.
What's the problem?
This isn't against the law.
Are you crazy?
How come?
This is normal married life.
I'm wearing my Mu Guiying costume.
I love seeing you in costume.
You insane!
What's wrong?
On stage, you're passionately in love
with others. Why not with me?
You act so convincingly.
Why are you avoiding?
Today, I have to sleep with you.
Are you insane?
Which one of us is insane, Yi Qin'e?
You're like a monster.
I am a monster.
Still want to sleep with me?
(Liu Hongbing is furious)
(because he sees Yi Qin'e)
(as the only light in his life.)
(But that light only shines on stage.)
(Yi Qin'e is enraged)
(because she thinks Liu Hongbing)
(desecrated Mu Guiying.)
(He doesn't know)
(the place Mu Guiying holds
in Yi Qin'e's heart.)
(But neither speaks their mind.)
(Chang'an Youth Palace)
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Okay, everyone, take a break.
Have some water.
How's it?
You look so beautiful in that costume.
Did it go well?
Very well.
You're just sugarcoating the bad news.
Nowadays, kids in trainee classes
are all signing up
for piano or dance lessons.
Who still watches Qinqiang opera?
Well,
this time, it really went well.
Qin'e makes a difference
once she's on stage.
It feels like going back
to the old days.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
She herself feels so motivated.
We've already set the time
for the next booking and everything.
That's really great.
When should I go see her and the kid?
How about today?
Well,
I have something serious to tell you.
You've been playful for half your life.
What serious thing could you have?
Where's the thing?
What's wrong?
I put that thing in Qin'e's bag.
When did you learn
to keep people in suspense?
Just tell me what it is.
No way.
Anyway, we're going to her place.
I'll tell you there.
When does class end?
Kids, how about we end class now?
Okay!
Why aren't you teaching seriously?
Not your business.
Hongbing.
Where's Qin'e?
She put the kid to sleep?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Why being in a sulk?
What's wrong?
Had a fight?
Anyway, he shouldn't treat me like this.
This...
What's wrong?
What happened?
What's this about?
Did you fight with Hongbing?
Where's the kid?
Wait, you had a fight, right?
Sanyuan.
Come see the kid.
What's it?
This...
Why is his face all purple?
Laidi.
What's wrong?
How is it?
Losing again.
Hongbing.
What an unusual day.
Didn't you go straight?
Why are you coming to us now?
What did you say?
Hongbing.
Didn't you say?
Don't even mention girls,
even if the Jade Emperor's sister came,
you wouldn't be interested.
Why are you here with us?
Enough now.
Why is it so quiet?
Don't panic.
The kid is so young,
it can't be anything serious.
Doctor, what's wrong with my kid?
He's stabilized now.
He lacked of oxygen.
- Mom.
- Don't let too many people in.
Yiyi.
My Yiyi.
Doctor, what's wrong with the kid?
Some test results aren't in yet.
But you need
to mentally prepare yourselves.
What do you mean?
Talk after the results are in.
How's the kid?
He's stabilized now.
They said he lacked of oxygen.
What's really going on?
Some test results aren't in yet,
so we need to wait.
Still haven't reached Hongbing?
No.
Where has he gone?
Mom.
Qin'e.
The kid has Tetralogy of Fallot,
which is a congenital heart defect.
His heart was malformed from birth.
He didn't develop properly in the womb.
With ventricular septal defect,
pulmonary stenosis,
overriding aorta,
and right ventricular hypertrophy.
Is it very serious?
It's a heart problem,
how could it not be serious?
If the child hadn't been
resuscitated in time this time,
he could be gone.
This condition isn't extremely rare,
but it is deadly.
Be mentally prepared.
Fifty percent of patients
don't live past three years old.
Seventy percent don't make it to ten.
Ninety percent
will die young.
What have we done wrong?
Why does the child suffer this?
Mom, maybe you all go wait outside.
Stop crying here, go outside.
L-Let's go out.
Let the doctor talk properly with Qin'e.
I thought there's something
wrong with him.
Even a little movement
and he'd be panting.
Don't rush, sit.
His face would be so red.
Besides,
other babies
lift their heads at two months,
roll over at three months,
and can sit at six months.
Yet our child couldn't do any of that.
What's the use
of rambling about this now?
Where have you been?
Didn't even reply to the message.
How many pages did I send you?
Where's Qin'e?
Inside.
We've never had
a successful precedent for performing
heart surgery on a child here.
So...
That means there's no cure.
For now.
But, you must have hope.
After all, the child is still young.
Technology has advanced rapidly.
Perhaps there will be a cure next year.
Then what do we do now?
Hang in there.
Observe him closely.
If you notice his face turning red,
or cyanosis appears,
seek medical help immediately.
The child's condition is stable for now.
I'll prescribe some medication.
You can go home then.
Qin'e, let me hold the child.
Qin'e.
Doctor,
why didn't our child develop properly?
Many possible causes.
Like smoking or drinking,
they could cause
congenital malformations.
Did you take any medicine
during your pregnancy?
Genetic mutations,
environmental factors,
anything is possible.
Give me the kid.
You go inside and rest.
I'll go buy something.
(Yi Qin'e simply couldn't figure out)
(why this happened.)
(Perhaps heaven really
granted her too much.)
(And now it is taking
them back bit by bit.)
(Yi Qin'e feels
all of this was her fault.)
No need to check.
Everyone's is the same.
Sign it properly.
What's wrong?
Sign it.
There you go.
As expected of someone
taught by the old leader.
You know the greater good
and the bigger picture.
Signed.
Liu, don't blame me.
This wasn't up to me either.
The nation must develop,
and human must progress.
See how well this calligraphy
written by the old leader is.
But times have changed now.
We must keep up with the times too.
Toss the calligraphy.
It's so ironic.
What a lowly vulgar.
(Never forget who dug the well.)
Gently.
Mom's got our child asleep?
Let's eat first.
I'm not eating.
At times like this,
you should eat properly.
We can't break down, got it?
Come on.
You go ahead and eat.
What are you doing?
I've decided
we can't give up.
We're taking our child
to Beijing, to Shanghai.
To other hospitals,
one injection might fix it.
I bought the train tickets.
We'll leave tomorrow.
Beijing has Children's Hospital
and the Pediatric Research Institute.
Then I'll go pack.
- What?
- It's so late now.
The kid is asleep.
Eat first.
Do we have enough money?
If not, I'll borrow some from Uncle.
Don't worry about trivial things.
I'll handle it.
I promise you I'll get our child cured.
Melon seeds, peanuts,
mineral water for sale.
Officer.
Could you please check
if there are any sleeper tickets left?
No tickets.
We're taking our child for treatment.
We're pressed for time.
Your old section Chief Deng is my buddy.
Could you make an exception?
I said no tickets.
That's tough.
How's it?
Happy birthday!
Xiao.
- Come on!
You guys cut it.
He's afraid I'll eat him.
- Alright, make a wish!
- Make a wish!
Jiahe!
Happy birthday!
Cheng, we're closed already.
What brings you here?
I thought we are close friends.
Didn't you even tell me
about your birthday?
You're such a busy guy.
Just a little gift.
A money bouquet for you.
- Wish you'll always have money!
- Good.
Here, take it.
Thank you.
Thank you, Cheng.
But this is too expensive to accept.
This is my sincerity.
Take it. Just take it.
No way. I really can't take it.
Handsome.
You take it for her.
I know the number of them.
Don't worry. I won't steal it.
Take a seat.
Today, I've brought
a few bottles of fine wine.
Let's have a drink.
Sit down.
Jiahe's friends are my friends too.
Let's all have fun.
- Come on, Jiahe.
- Good.
Cheers.
Cheng, we haven't cut the cake yet.
And the party hasn't started.
There's no rush.
Every time, you always sweet-talk me.
When we drank before,
it was always me who got drunk,
and you never got drunk once.
This time, I'm determined
to drink my fill with you.
Drink until we're drunk!
Okay, drink until we're drunk.
Absolutely!
I've learned a few new songs.
I'll go sing them for you, okay?
So you're rejecting me?
Not at all, Cheng.
How would I dare? Right?
You're asking for trouble.
I am just about to go sing for you.
How could we reject you?
Excuse me.
Cheng, I toast you.
Who are you?
I'm a nobody.
Cheng.
You know it.
Jiahe holds her liquor well.
Boring to drink with her.
But I can't hold my liquor.
I'll get drunk easily.
When I'm drunk, I'll be funny.
Today, I'll show you.
Allow me to toast you.
A toast to you.
- Listen...
- Cheng.
You've always listened to Jiahe sing.
But you've never heard me sing.
I sing just as well.
Come on.
I'll perform Orchid Grass for Cheng.
- Good!
Come on.
Today, on Jiahe's birthday,
I wish for the friendship
between Jiahe and Cheng
to be like orchid grass,
remaining pure and resilient.
Well said!
Forever resilient!
May our friendship last forever.
Cheng brought fine wine today.
No one is to spoil Cheng's fun.
Everyone must keep him happy.
Come on, let's drink!
- Okay.
Cheng, let me toast you.
Cheng.
Not enough wine.
Go get more.
We must keep Cheng happy today.
- Okay.
- A toast to Cheng.
- Cheers!
Here.
Are you alright?
Is Mr. Cheng okay?
They carried him away.
I've never seen him that drunk before.
You sang
that Orchid Grass song
for Yi Qin'e, right?
Right?
What a shame.
Such a huge birthday cake,
I didn't get a bite of it.
I just drank the whole time.
Didn't get a bite of it.
Just drank the whole time.
So you want birthday cake?
Of course.
Today is my birthday.
Okay.
You're the boss today.
Let's go.
Where to?
You want birthday cake, right?
Anyone?
Anyone? Need to buy a birthday cake.
Forget it, I was just saying.
Don't be serious.
Do you know
where all these cars on the street
are all heading to?
Home.
Among these thousands of lights,
someday, one of them will be mine.
Come on.
Make a wish.
Do you know why people make wishes?
Because
only after eating cake, making a wish,
and blowing out candles,
can we get the courage for next year.
(During this period,)
(Yi Qin'e and Liu Hongbing travel
all over the country with their child.)
(Whenever there's a glimmer of hope,)
- (they'd rush over with their child.)
- Have some. It's still warm.
- (But they always go with hope)
- I'm fine.
(and return with disappointment.)
(Time and again,)
(no one could endure it any longer.)
Hongbing, am I interrupting?
I'll come another time.
No, it's fine.
Troupe Leader Shan, sit.
Come on.
Don't move.
You messed it up.
Sorry, Troupe Leader Shan.
We just got back.
We can only offer you some water.
No problem.
Don't mind me.
You go ahead.
How's the kid?
We saw a specialist in Beijing.
The specialist said his former student
returned from studying abroad.
He's in Hong Kong, China now.
It's troublesome
to go to Hong Kong, China.
We're sorting out the paperwork
first, and then we'll go.
When are you going?
I'll go handle the paperwork soon.
By the way,
I need you to issue a certificate.
That's easy.
I can get it for you anytime.
The doctor said technology has
advanced rapidly these past two years.
In a couple of years,
there might be a cure.
As long as the kid could be cured.
Qin'e, I'm here
just to tell you that Mr. Qin is here.
Tonight,
your uncle, Director Feng, and I
want to host a dinner for Mr. Qin.
I wonder if you're available
to join us.
Just consider it a way to relax a bit.
Not far, at Weihua Barbecue.
I can't go. I have
to take care of my kid.
Troupe Leader Shan, please have a seat.
My child needs to sleep.
I have to put her to sleep.
Alright then.
Take care.
Okay.
Are you two going
to Hong Kong, China for treatment?
She just won't listen.
You should try talking her out.
You two need to talk things out.
Keeping everything bottled up inside
would drive you crazy.
Don't worry.
I'll talk to her later.
Okay, no need to see me out.
Bye. Take care.
Okay.
Not far,
just at Weihua Barbecue.
Come join us if you have time.
Is the kid asleep?
Aren't you having barbecue tonight?
Qin'e,
want some food?
How about some noodles?
Whatever.
Qin'e.
Can our family really afford
to Hong Kong, China for treatment?
The doctor just mentioned it offhand.
He didn't say it was a guaranteed cure.
Even if we go,
I mean...
Maybe we should take a break.
Going a day or two later
won't delay anything.
It's been almost half a year.
You're exhausted,
and we're out of money.
What's wrong?
Are you just going to watch him die?
How can you say something like that?
That's not what I meant.
I'm just saying we should take a break
and save up some money.
Moreover, I'm exhausted too.
You're exhausted?
Remember that lousy
basement hotel in Beijing?
Our child cried nonstop,
wouldn't sleep all night.
When others annoyed,
and the owner wanted to kick us out,
who was the one
holding him outside all night?
Did I complain anything?
Fine.
You can just leave us.
What did you say?
How can I leave you?
We've been fighting
for the past six months.
Just stop. I'm sick of it.
I didn't mean we aren't
going to Hong Kong, China.
But given our current situation,
we really can't go
to Hong Kong, China right now.
We have to go, anyway.
Can you be realistic?
You're an out-of-work actress.
And I'm an out-of-work driver.
How can we afford treatment there?
Say that again.
I have to get treatment for my son.
You're insane.
Completely insane.
Look at you.
Still remember who you used to be?
If you despise me, why did you marry me?
I shouldn't have married you
and had this child.
In the past, if you ever
said something like that,
it would break my heart.
It's strange.
I feel nothing.
Nothing in my heart now.
(Yi Qin'e doesn't know
why she said something like that.)
(She just thinks she's truly gone mad.)
(Her life, just like the Qinqiang opera
she performed on stage,)
(in just a few years,)
(had been thrown from its highest peak)
(straight down
to the lowest valley by fate.)
(Taking the kid to see the doctor.)
(If without that belief supporting her,)
(she's really going to collapse.)
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Mr. Qin.
Your provincial troupe
ruined the script
I poured everything into.
- Why bring this up now?
- The Qinqiang opera
got turned into Qin songs!
You're drunk, really.
This...
What is this about? You...
Mr. Qin,
whether it's Qinqiang opera
or Qin songs,
we at least won an opera award.
- Right?
- Yeah.
The quality of an opera
can't be decided by one award.
But an award
surely represents
that some aspect of the opera
is outstanding.
Otherwise, why is
the award so sought-after?
Exactly.
I don't seek one.
You don't?
Then I'd like to ask,
who
wrote three full pages
of an acceptance speech
and stayed up all night,
only to lose his voice
from excitement the next day
and couldn't read it?
Who is it?
Why argue about it?
Who enjoys Qinqiang opera these days?
Who even cares?
What do you mean?
Exactly.
Plenty of people enjoy it.
Mr. Qin,
don't let that acceptance speech
go in vain.
Recite it for us here.
Let us know
what you wrote.
People love to say,
"The opera matters most."
But I say it's deceptive nonsense.
No opera
matters more than life.
Life matters most!
I'm about to write a new script
about life.
I'll have Yi Qin'e perform it.
Let's perform it in Beijing!
Let's perform it at the United Nations!
This opera will be called
The Fox Immortal's Whimper.
The Fox Immortal's Whimper!
Good!
- Good!
♪The broken cliff edge
holds the waning moon♪
- Good!
(Barbecue)
Hua.
It's so late.
Where has she gone?
I had a bit to drink,
and wanted to tell you something.
I hold it in my heart for half a year.
More than it, almost half a lifetime.
I never said it out loud.
At this age,
without confirming
our relationship clearly,
we've just muddled through like this.
We've muddled through
like this for half a lifetime,
without confirming anything.
That won't work.
Today, I must speak my mind to you.
Well,
the two of us
should get married.
(Preview)
(Dozens of the country's
top pediatric cardiology experts)
(all attended the meeting.)
Please save my child.
The surgery has risks.
Can my kid pull through this?
No matter how, we'll overcome them.
We can't submit to fate.
We have to believe in ourselves.
Driving a taxi doesn't need much skill.
Remember,
get more jobs, drive faster.
I found a new job.
Believe me, we can definitely
cure the kid's illness.
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪