♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 43=
(Outpatient)
- Age?
- Eight.
Next.
- Second floor.
- Next.
Which department?
Cardiology.
All his test results are normal,
and his intellectual development
has improved since the last time.
Thank you, doctor.
Don't thank me.
Thank yourself.
You've put in tremendous effort
as a mother.
We set a date for the surgery.
Take a look.
Okay.
Doctor.
Why are the costs
so much higher
than what you showed me last time?
Because we're conducting
a valve replacement.
Domestic ones
haven't worked well
in clinical applications.
So we have to use imported ones.
We've got no choice.
Then, after the surgery,
there will be costs for the ICU.
That estimate might be on the low side.
So
does this surgery time work for you?
Shall we delay it?
No, we'll figure something out.
Okay.
Qin'e.
Yuzhi.
Where are you going?
We're heading home.
Get in.
Yuzhi, I'm so lucky I ran into you.
It's scorching today.
Don't be so formal with me.
(Carboprost Suppositories)
Don't touch Auntie's things.
I went for a checkup today too.
How's the kid?
He's doing well.
He can probably
get the surgery next month.
You've been through a lot.
Seeing light
at the end of the tunnel, huh?
Almost there.
Just one last push needed.
Everything's going to be fine.
Don't overthink it.
With your fame now,
it's easy to make money.
I only know opera.
Did you hear something from Wei Xiaohui?
From a filthy mouth
comes no decent speech.
You got me wrong.
You know what?
Those people
are just being sour,
each one green with envy.
Nowadays,
if you want money, drop the artist act
and the attitude.
It all comes down to mutual agreement.
You know,
compared to singing
at rural weddings or funerals,
it's just a different approach,
different venue,
and different audience.
What's the real difference?
Seriously, these people...
What?
Do you also look down on me?
No.
We're just making ends meet.
Who gets to be judgmental?
You're absolutely right.
I know a gig organizer.
He's got plenty of jobs.
If you're interested,
I can connect you.
Sing something like "Northwest Wind."
No problem at all.
Thanks, Yuzhi.
Alright, think about it.
Son.
Look.
We're ready for the cartoon.
The last move.
Come on, last one.
Let's see.
Look.
Isn't it the cartoon?
The Blue Mouse.
Your favorite cartoon.
A hug from Daddy.
Here we go.
Fly.
- Put him down.
- Fun, huh?
It's too much for his heart, okay?
Are you okay?
Are you feeling unwell?
We set up the TV.
He was excited, so I got carried away.
You're so reckless.
Thanks for coming today, though.
Give me a second.
Come on.
What is it?
I'm the Employee of the Month.
You've given me money this month.
You're working hard every day.
I worked a lot last month.
I don't spend much, anyway.
Keep it
for Liu Yi's surgery.
Stop playing the hero.
Besides, this isn't enough.
The doctor said
the surgery cost
plus all the other expenses
is going to be six figures.
That much?
Alright then.
I'll figure something out.
Don't do anything illegal.
What do you take me for?
You've been performing a lot.
Get more rest.
You too.
(No Stage)
Thanks.
(Roses, Greatest Hits)
Feifei.
Work hard here.
I will definitely give you a raise.
Who are you looking for?
Mr. Hei?
Aren't you Liu Hong...?
Bing.
Liu Hongbing.
Why are you here?
I run this place.
So classy.
What brings you here today?
I have some bootleg tapes.
Heavy Metal from abroad.
Is anyone interested?
From abroad?
Let me ask around.
Guys.
We have some bootleg tapes from abroad.
Come and see.
Bootleg tapes. Let's go.
- Go.
- Let's see.
Feifei.
Heavy Metal from abroad.
You name it.
- Let's see.
- Nirvana.
Not bad.
Pink Floyd.
Any Van Halen?
The Smashing Pumpkins?
One by one.
Slow down.
Buddy.
Get me a pen.
Hurry, get a pen and paper.
Let me write this down.
How much is it?
Fifteen each.
This one.
Sir.
Bro.
Who is this?
Easy. He's one of us.
Mind your head.
Alright.
Rock music here.
Classical over there.
Those are the only two types.
They are all imported.
I sell whatever they import.
These are very hard to pick.
They are all sold in bulk.
Listen up.
This is all we have now.
It's hard to say when we'll have more.
I want them all.
Two thousand.
Why are you here again?
Uncle, you're back.
Go inside.
I'm making noodles.
Peeled the garlic?
I'll help you.
Don't you have things to do?
Why are you idling around here?
Qin'e is busy singing opera.
Aunt Hua isn't here.
Someone has to look after you.
Here.
How is it?
Amazing noodles.
I'm asking about you.
I'm doing great.
I roam around and earn money.
Isn't that great?
Is the taxi company still hiring?
Who wants to go there?
Me.
You?
Stop joking around.
You might work a pedicab.
Cars require a driver's license.
I can learn to drive.
You'll teach me.
What's so hard about it?
Come on, stop kidding.
I'm serious.
The treatment costs over 100,000.
When will you and Qin'e
save up enough?
Don't worry, I've got a plan.
We can't do anything illegal.
We've got principles.
What are you worried about?
Besides,
Cungen follows me everywhere.
How am I going to break any laws?
When will you two remarry?
It doesn't change anything.
I'm taking care of everything at home.
You've got a big heart.
You married a wife
and only wished to take care of her.
Seeing them happy makes me happy.
If you decide to
run a small business,
count me in.
I can't afford to hire you.
Why don't you
join those provincial troupe performers?
♪Old brother♪
♪Let him kneel there♪
♪After all those pleas from Xue Bao♪
♪I can't stop mulling it over♪
♪I'd rather give up
on this worthless brat♪
♪But the neighbors
would call me a heartless stepmother♪
♪Forget it, for my late husband's sake♪
What's up?
What are you doing?
Why are you startled?
You almost scared me to death.
You made no sound at all.
I thought you were a thief.
What's worth stealing
in this rundown troupe?
Scared of thieves?
Why are you
wearing a woman's costume?
I switched to Laodan last year.
Laodan roles suit me better
than Xiaosheng roles.
Alright, whatever you think.
Why are you rehearsing here?
The Rehearsal Hall
is leaking like a bathhouse.
We can't practice there, you know?
We have no money for repairs.
What about the others?
The Troupe Leader?
Come closer.
I'd rather keep some distance.
I have no idea.
You rascal...
♪I'd rather give up
on this worthless brat♪
♪But the neighbors
would call me a heartless stepmother♪
♪Forget it, for my late husband's sake♪
(Chang'an Department Store)
Dear audience.
Good afternoon.
A beautiful song for everyone.
Hope you enjoy it.
Come on, wave your hands.
One, two, three, four.
Hands above your heads.
Come on.
Raise your hands and dance.
One, two, three, four.
You over there, raise your hands.
What are you doing?
I got a gig here.
I'm asking what you're doing.
I'll sing opera.
What are you wearing?
You'll perform in that?
What are you performing?
"Northwest Wind"?
It's harvest season. No opera bookings.
We can't just sit around and starve.
Have some standards.
I won't allow this.
We have an agreement with our client.
You're ruining the craft, you know?
You're disgracing Qinqiang opera.
Have you no respect for anything?
Uncle.
You brought me into this opera world,
and I made it.
But the business is declining.
I'm not disgracing Qinqiang opera.
It has failed me.
I owe it all to everyone's support.
But I'm not just a performer.
I'm also the deputy leader
of the Youth Troupe.
Dozens of people rely on me
for their livelihoods.
I'm doing this not just for Liu Yi,
but for everyone.
(Hu Sanyuan scolded Yi Qin'e)
(for putting on a "monkey show")
(and disgracing the founders
of Qinqiang opera.)
(But at that point,)
(even if those founders
really came to settle scores with her,)
(she'd just drag them onstage
to perform with her.)
Why isn't Feng Xiaoxiao back yet?
He got promoted
from stunt double to action director.
He's swamped.
Many known directors want him.
Mom, the food's getting cold.
Eat first.
Don't you have a flight to catch?
Back home, you couldn't even
cook noodles properly.
Now you can make dishes.
I just quit my job recently,
planning to find something new.
Till then, I'll manage household stuff.
It'll be useful once I get married.
Mom, eat up.
The food's getting cold.
I'll join you soon.
If he truly wanted to marry you,
he would have been here.
Mom, dig in.
What are you waiting for?
Dig in.
Take this.
You never listen to me.
I know I can't tell you what to do.
Never live on handouts.
Come home if things get tough.
You're always welcome home.
Just go to bed.
I told you
not to wait for me for dinner.
What's wrong?
Did you forget what today is?
What is it?
My mom went back to Ningzhou.
We were supposed to
have dinner with her.
I called you so many times.
Why didn't you answer?
I honestly forgot.
There was a crucial scene today.
No phone calls allowed on set.
How convenient.
My mom came to Shenzhen,
and you've been busy.
We've been dating for over a year.
What's your plan?
I'm exhausted. Let's talk tomorrow.
No.
Nobody sleeps until we settle this.
My mom never approved of us.
What are you trying to say
by acting like this?
Nothing.
Let's break up then.
Fine.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lost my temper.
Please don't leave me.
I'm not leaving you.
Then why are you packing?
I'll be in Huizhou for three months
for a new job.
Will you come back?
I just want to focus on my career now.
Marriage isn't in my plans.
Do whatever you want.
Just don't leave me.
♪I go 145♪
♪Rushing down the line♪
♪Six strings screaming♪
♪I feel good♪
Why are you shouting?
So loud.
Why do I have to suffer this
to make money?
Living is suffering.
♪Keep driving♪
♪Next blues child♪
Rock and roll never dies.
What's your name?
I'm Yi...
Easy.
Innovative.
Innovative, huh?
- Easy it is then.
- Easy.
♪I go 145♪
Why is it soda?
Take it or leave it.
Hongbing, I'm already twenty.
Give this 5000 yuan
to your sister tonight.
The remaining 200 is your commission.
Okay.
Thank you, Hongbing.
You'll always be my dearest
brother-in-law.
Enough.
Let go.
What was that name again?
Easy.
Is it English or Chinese?
What does it mean?
It means simple.
Life is too complicated.
Let's return to simplicity.
Why don't you
call yourself "Yi" as in "One"?
So simple. Just call yourself "Yi".
Living like you and my sister
is quite boring.
Someone's ambitious.
What do you want?
To bloom.
To burn out.
I want to do rock music.
Stop mocking us.
How many guys back in there
can afford to eat?
At least they are living.
Erupt in silence,
or perish in silence.
I won't lower my head.
Life is about keeping your head down
and getting through one obstacle
after another.
You'll understand when you grow up.
I'd rather die.
You, my sister,
my dad, and my mom
are all walking corpses.
You know why
so many Shaanxi people love rock?
Why?
What's the essence of rock?
If you can't fly, run.
If you can't run, walk.
If you can't walk, crawl.
Crawling is still moving forward.
When you don't feel sad
even when crawling,
then you've grown up.
If one day you become famous,
write a song for me.
Zhang Chu from Shaanxi
wrote a song called "Sister".
Write a "Brother-in-law".
No problem.
Hey, buddy.
Zheng Jun's
"Cinderella".
Sure, let's do it.
♪How did I fall for you♪
♪I'm asking myself♪
♪I can give up anything♪
♪Yet today I can't bear to leave♪
♪You're not beautiful♪
♪But you're utterly adorable♪
♪Cinderella♪
♪My Cinderella♪
♪How did I fall for you♪
♪I'm asking myself♪
♪I can give up anything♪
♪Yet today I can't bear to leave♪
♪You're not beautiful♪
♪But you're utterly adorable♪
Marry me.
♪Cinderella♪
♪My Cinderella♪
♪I keep breaking your heart♪
♪I'm always so cruel♪
♪I tell you not to take it seriously♪
♪Because I dare not believe it♪
♪You are so beautiful♪
♪And you're utterly adorable♪
♪Cinderella♪
♪My Cinderella♪
(Qinchuan Qinqiang Opera Theater)
♪Perhaps you never♪
♪Thought that my heart would ache♪
♪If this is a dream♪
Want to watch a movie?
(Chang'an City Cinema)
Twenty per person.
No need to buy tickets.
Go right in, okay?
No need to queue up.
Twenty per person.
Go right in.
Twenty per person. Go right in.
Want to
watch a movie?
How much?
Twenty.
Twenty? So expensive.
Come on.
This is "True Lies", a blockbuster.
You look like a liar to me.
Go away.
You can get in right away.
You want to see a movie too?
Not really.
But I'm really curious
how you get people in.
It's a movie, not an opera show.
No more stage rigging crew.
Well, pay me twenty yuan.
I'll satisfy your curiosity.
Twenty yuan?
I'm not curious at all then.
Ten yuan.
We go way back.
- 50% off, okay?
- Enough.
Five yuan.
I'll let you see the movie.
I guarantee you a good spot.
(True Lies, 20 yuan,
Chang'an City Cinema)
Busy?
Master Yang.
This is my uncle.
First time seeing a movie.
Okay, sit.
Sit here.
Well, isn't it great?
Enjoy the movie. I'm off.
See you, Master Yang.
Okay.
See you.
What cigarette does he give you?
Jinsihou.
It's only a dozen cents,
and he charged me five yuan.
(That day,)
(Hu Sanyuan came to his senses.)
(The "corpse fall"
and somersault he performed)
(for years)
(mean nothing next to
a foreigner's trigger squeeze)
(and blazing shot.)
(The times aren't interested
in a new costume.)
(They've ripped the whole stage
from the ground.)
(Double Afterglow)
Sanyuan.
Troupe Leader.
Here for the movie?
Yeah, I just watched it.
I didn't see you.
It was dark in there.
My face is dark too.
How could you see me?
Was it good?
Yeah, it was really good.
No wonder everyone's watching movies,
and not opera now.
It's scorching.
Let's grab a beer.
Okay.
(After nine years of construction,)
(the entire 119-kilometer-long channel)
(of the Chang'an Heihe
Water Diversion Project)
(has been completed.)
(Heihe River and Shitou River...)
They keep talking about
getting the Heihe River water.
Where's the water?
It's been so many years.
I haven't seen a drop of it.
They say the eight rivers
flow around Chang'an.
Right?
Now it should be,
"Across Guanzhong I've searched,
to where Chang'an's eight rivers end."
Everything has its pattern.
The same goes for Qinqiang opera.
Everything has its ups and downs.
Qinqiang opera may be declining.
But someday,
it will rise again.
What I care about now
is whether I can
see the water of the Heihe River
in my lifetime.
(No Stage)
Is that enough?
Keep the money for Liu Yi's surgery.
I found a job at this bar.
Just take it.
You have another task tonight.
No need.
I have money.
You think you're so capable now, huh?
Here.
Give it to your sister tonight.
I won't go.
You think you're tough, huh?
Being tough, are you?
You won't even listen to me, huh?
Take it.
Why don't you go yourself?
You're clearly not over her.
You're hoping for her gentleness,
reluctant to see her staying silent.
You're so full of it.
Where did you learn it?
From the lyrics.
You can learn from the songs.
Take it.
You'll keep suffering like this.
Either you break it off,
or go see her yourself.
Come on.
Daddy will put some lotion on you, okay?
Is the water cold? Try it.
Can you stand it?
Is it cold?
Liu Yi.
You're amazing.
You get more amazing by the day.
Dada...
You're saying "Dad"?
Liu Yi.
You just called me "Dad", huh?
Say it again.
Come on.
Come on, Liu Yi.
Qin'e.
Liu Yi just said "Dad".
Dada...
Right?
Come on.
Say "Mom".
Nobody in this family
is greater than Mom.
Say "Mom".
Don't pressure him.
I'm happy no matter who he's calling.
Sit down and eat.
Come on.
How come you have time to come today?
Did you swap shifts?
I just won
the "Outstanding Individual" title.
Look.
A bonus.
Liu Yi, look.
Mommy made you some yummy food.
Here, have a bite.
What's wrong?
Something on your mind?
Nothing. Let's eat.
Tell me.
I'll cheer you up.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Try the shredded potatoes Mommy made.
Here.
The vinegar-fried shredded potatoes
are amazing.
The shreds are cut like carvings,
each one distinct.
Qin'e, you're amazing.
You're getting more and more capable.
Isn't that right, Liu Yi?
How am I capable?
I'm in my thirties.
But I can't do anything
besides singing opera.
Sometimes I feel I don't sing opera
with the same energy as before.
Don't say that.
Look at you.
You've taken one thing and perfected it.
That's really amazing, you know?
There's something
you really have to learn from me.
Learn to praise yourself, okay?
What's that big mirror for?
You should look in the mirror.
"How did I get so pretty?
How come my voice is so mellow?
My slender waist.
When I do the Woyu posture,
my head touches the ground."
Right?
Mommy makes the best shredded potatoes.
So authentic.
That's enough.
I'm not as thick-skinned as you.
What's wrong with it?
Being thick-skinned makes one happy.
Right, Liu Yi?
Doesn't Mommy
make the best shredded potatoes?
Praise Mommy.
Say "Mom".
Okay.
Besides the potato shreds,
the stir-fried tomato and eggs
is also amazing.
Alright then, I'm off.
Take care.
Oh, right.
Qin'e.
Rest if you're tired.
Stay where you are
if you're lost.
Or turn around.
I promise, if you turn around,
I'll be right behind you.
I'm off.
(Qinqiang Opera, Bai She Zhuan)
♪yet trust that vile monk♪
♪I tend to you in every heat and chill♪
♪I cook for you every single day♪
♪I braved the sacred mountain,
risking death to bring you remedy♪
♪I flooded Jinshan Mountain
to fight that vile monk for you♪
Uncle.
Are you still mad at me?
Wedding and funeral opera performances
had strict rules back then.
The drummer was the most important.
Musicians had to arrive before breakfast
and lay out the instruments
on the Eight Immortals Table.
After setting off firecrackers,
the performance began.
Once the opening drum sounded,
the host had to hand out red envelopes
as gifts for the musicians.
Just as there was an opening drum,
there was also a closing drum.
The hosts want
a proper beginning and end,
hoping for
smooth sailing
and calm handling of affairs,
turning misfortune into blessings.
I've said too much.
These are old traditions.
Young people are no longer interested
in those customs.
What are we really watching
when we watch Qinqiang opera?
We're watching a struggle.
Survival.
Defiance.
You did nothing wrong.
You're tougher than anyone.
You fully understand Qinqiang opera.
But I misspoke earlier.
Qinqiang opera hasn't failed me.
Rest assured, I won't disgrace it.
Sink your roots deep.
Hold on. Stay alive.
Then you'll see the rain come.
Then you'll see
the Heihe River water flowing in.
Okay.
The water came.
Get the water.
Hurry up.
The water came.
(Good news
from the key construction site.)
(After the hard work
of countless builders,)
(the main structure has been completed)
(six months ahead of schedule.)
Thirty thousand, not a cent less.
Count it.
No need.
I trust you.
Let's make it clear.
You get six months interest-free.
After that, we follow standard terms.
Three percent monthly interest.
Understood.
Thanks, Hei.
You borrow money from me
and ask me to buy you food?
Regular quality only. No premium stuff.
The tapes you ordered last time.
Take a look.
We've got everything.
Fifteen yuan per tape.
This one's huge.
I like it.
Yeah.
What's it called?
Pink...
Uncle.
Floyd or something.
This is good.
Queen, right?
- Come here.
- Uncle.
Why are you here?
Don't you know whose turf this is?
I knew you were here from day one.
If I hadn't put in a word with Hei,
you think you could do this here?
Aren't you love rivals?
You're working together?
You talk too much.
Well, why are you here?
The kid's surgery is coming up.
Got any plans?
Of course.
But my plans don't count.
What happened to that persistence?
You can't get a wife
if you care about pride.
Now you care about pride?
Whether I care about pride,
life must go on.
How?
I haven't figured it out.
I don't even know
if I like Qin'e on stage
or off stage.
She's who she is on and off stage.
You two are so full of drama.
I haven't figured it out.
You can take your time.
But do your job.
What do you mean?
Remarry her.
Get the kid treated.
Do what needs to be done.
Uncle.
Take it.
Cut.
Good.
Cut. The director called cut.
Scene 25, get ready.
Move!
Scene 105, shot 12, take 5.
Hurry up.
- Stop staring.
- Where is everyone?
Cameras, speakers, and props.
Hurry up! Everyone move!
- Costumes.
- Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oh, right.
Someone keeps calling you.
Thank you.
Hurry, don't stop.
Hurry up!
(Chu Jiahe: 12 missed calls)
Next scene.
Feng.
Let's go through it.
(Chu Jiahe calling)
(Preview)
Dear Miss Yi,
may I dance with you?
I-I came today
to tell you something.
You don't love me?
Then who do you love?
After this performance,
the surgery will go well.
(Qinqiang Opera Performance)
I've talked to the bouncers.
Exclusive sales rights for you.
City CID.
Come with us.
Qin'e, something went wrong.
Qin'e!
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪