Lal, you have your own team
to take care of,
and I have mine too.
So this is really just
about protecting yourself, right?
What do you want me to help with?
Tangkwa, do you know who Wine is dating?
You said I did it for myself.
I’m sorry. I spoke too harshly.
You messed up again, didn't you?
Then go tell her yourself.
I'm not telling her.
-You go tell her yourself.
-You go ahead.
-If she comes over here…
-No, no.
There she is. She's coming.
Go tell her.
Come on. It's your responsibility.
Lal… I'm sorry.
I put the wrong figures in the report
I submitted to Accounting.
But I'll go apologize to Wine myself.
Dude, I love bubble tea.
If I end up dead,
offer some bubble tea to me, okay?
It's okay.
I'll talk to her—
Uh, I'll talk to Wine, for you.
Okay?
Here. I'm done with this.
Throw it away for me.
Why has Lal been
in such a good mood lately?
Is she in love? Do you think so?
I do…
…think you've got some nerve
prying into her personal life!
Why don't you focus on your work for once?
Then Lal wouldn't have to get scolded
on your behalf.
I feel bad for her.
Wine, my team member—
Wine is in a meeting.
Is there anything
you'd like me to pass on?
That's okay. I can come back later.
So, are you here for an audit?
Didn't Wine tell you, Lal?
I've transferred here
as a Senior Accountant.
I just started.
I thought Wine told you everything.
Um, Wine.
Wine, I’m putting the laundry
in the dryer.
Hey, can you grab the cleansing water
on the table for me?
Thanks.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's my fault too.
I showed up without telling her first.
But if I had told her,
I never would've found out that my friend
has been secretly hiding a girlfriend.
You scared me to death.
I texted you, and you didn't reply.
I thought that crazy Wine
had pulled your hair out
and killed you or something.
Every time you call me,
all you do is complain about
how toxic and insane Wine is.
This is Wine.
Nonsense.
You said it yourself
that Wine always looks unapproachable.
That she looks like
a giant from a Thai folktale.
That she looks grumpy all the time.
But look at her. She's gorgeous.
Wine?
Yes.
She wasn't criticizing you at all.
She was complimenting you.
She didn’t scold you or anything.
Maybe you’re a little picky.
Maybe you’re meticulous.
Maybe you’re a perfectionist.
But that's just part of being
a working woman type.
Have you said enough?
Honestly, I'd love to stay
and hear more about
what you have been saying behind my back.
But I need to get dressed first.
Sis.
I mean…
It's not what you think.
Her room is being renovated,
so she's just staying with me for a while.
Are you Rapper Milli or what?
You're defending yourself pretty hard there.
I haven't even asked a single question.
She’s staying with you.
If she's not your friend,
then she must be your girlfriend.
Well…
Not really either.
Wait!
Your friend-with-benefits is Wine?!
Yeah.
No!
No, no. That's my friend’s story.
Oh, please.
Stop pretending.
With my brilliant mind,
I figured out it was Wine
from the very beginning.
Fine.
We're just friends with benefits.
That's all.
That's all?
What exactly do you do together?
We have sex.
We cook together,
watch movies, go to the spa,
and visit cafés.
Stuff like that.
Do you have to take out
a mortgage together and have kids
before you'll call her your girlfriend?
How could it possibly be like that?
I don't think of her that way.
Lal, you little girl.
You should stick to sales.
Don't ever join a call center scam gang.
You can't fool anyone.
The only person you're fooling is yourself.
I'm serious.
Wine and I started out because of passion.
There's no way it could turn into love.
Love starts with passion, doesn't it?
Think about it carefully.
Do you really not feel that way,
or just not realize it yet?
No way.
Absolutely!
There's a thief in our office.
My bubble tea goes missing
every single day.
How many times have I told you?
Put some laxatives in it.
Whoever comes sprinting to the bathroom
will be the culprit.
Just wait until we get back from the outing.
The company outing is coming up already?
The fact that you're asking that means
you still haven't voted for the team shirts
in the group chat, have you?
Uh-huh.
SALES TARGETS? NEVER.
THE BAR? EVERY DAY.
CLOSING DEALS IS EASIER
THAN OPENING YOUR HEART.
Can I just not vote for any of them?
Lal,
there's one woman left
without a roommate in our department.
Would you rather have a room to yourself,
or share with someone?
Who else would I room with?
Of course I'm staying with you.
Um…
Wine.
Don't be ridiculous.
How could I possibly room with Wine?
Wait… or could I?
That's not what I meant.
I meant Wine is right there.
Wine, over here!
I actually audited this company
two years ago.
I remember the workload being brutal.
As soon as I completed
my required hours, I left.
Right now, I'm working toward
my CPA certification,
and Wine invited me to join the company.
Proud is talented.
I saw potential in her,
so I convinced her to come help us out.
Come on. Drink a bit.
Wine can't hold her liquor.
I'll drink on her behalf.
Wow.
If you hadn't told me
you were senior and junior colleagues,
I would've thought
Wine brought her girlfriend to work.
The chemistry is chemistry-ing.
Numnim, save your mouth
for throwing up later, okay?
Why is she mad at me, huh?
I heard this company doesn't allow
employees to date each other.
Or do you have someone, Wine?
No.
Wine follows company policy very strictly.
But feelings aren't exactly something
you can control, are they?
I don't want a relationship.
Taking care of myself
is exhausting enough as it is.
Then there's work.
I don't have time
to take care of someone else.
And I don't believe anyone can love me
better than I can love myself.
Besides, every relationship I see
ends the same way.
People cheat.
They fall out of love.
They stop being loyal.
To me, being in a relationship feels
more like a burden than happiness.
I'd rather be alone.
Wow. That was cool.
Let's drink to Wine's
unwavering independence.
Come on, cheers.
Even water counts.
Lal!
Come on, give us a toast.
Wow, dead silence.
Come on, cheers.
That was seriously cool.
I don't know why you're trying
to find fault with Wine,
but don't let me hear you
badmouth her again.
Why do you think
I'm trying to find fault with her?
You're the one who accused her first.
Do you have feelings for Wine?
No, I don’t.
Then why are you so protective of her?
She's a boss I love.
Then you should know better.
What I'm doing isn't nitpicking.
I'm worried about her.
Worried about her?
Let's just say…
I know some of the bad things
Wine has been through.
I just don't want her to go through
the same thing again.
(Taking care of myself
is exhausting enough as it is.)
Then there's work.
I don't have time
to take care of someone else.
And I don't believe anyone can love me
better than I can love myself.
No wonder you've never dated anyone.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Why aren't you asleep?
I just finished pickling some vegetables.
Did you finish showering already?
Yeah.
Tomorrow I'm going back to my room
to grab my portable fan.
I want to bring it to the outing.
So you're rooming with Tangkwa, right?
Maybe Proud.
I'm worried I won't be able to sleep
in a new place.
I don't want to bother Tangkwa.
Really?
You fall asleep before I do every night.
That's because I'm afraid
I'll toss and turn and wake Tangkwa up.
Proud sleeps like a log, so it's fine.
Wait.
You've shared the same room before
so you know?
Yeah.
Back at a faculty camp.
A bunch of us shared a room.
I see.
Then why don't you room with me?
I'll talk to Jantra.
No way.
If the two of us
suddenly start sharing a room,
people are going to get suspicious.
Wake up.
We have the company outing today.
What time is it?
Oh!
See you at the office.
Wait, Wine!
Wine!
You forgot your lunch.
Lal.
Yes?
Your team has one person left
without a roommate.
Can she room with someone
from Accounting?
They have one extra person too.
Sure.
Who's the other person?
Wine.
Proud has a stomachache.
She called in sick this morning,
so Wine's room is available now.
Well…
I guess it can't be helped.
We're just sleeping, right?
Then I'll take the room.
Let's go with that.
Jantra!
Are you feeling okay now?
I went to the doctor and got my medicine.
I'm ready to go.
Your health comes first, you know.
Wouldn't you rather get some rest?
It's my first company outing.
I want to go.
I'd like to get to know
everyone better too.
That's the spirit.
But if anything comes up,
let us know right away.
Sure.
Alright then. Let's get on the bus.
Okay.
Wine.
You forgot your lunch this morning.
That looks really delicious.
See you around.
Alright, everyone.
Our company outing officially starts now!
Just like every year,
we'll have a series of team activities.
Each team will earn points
at every station,
and the team with the highest score
wins the prize.
Two baht worth of gold!
Whoa!
Two baht of gold!
Gold is super expensive these days!
-Hey, Numnim.
-What?
Do you think I spent a whole week
doing squats just to get nice thighs?
Come on. What?
Are you seriously taking this
that seriously?
Of course I am. It's gold.
Gold!
Wow.
They’re even more serious than I am.
Okay. So this is the company culture, huh?
Lal, the Sales team has lost for years.
This year we have to reclaim our honor.
You just want the gold, I can tell.
But well, don't worry.
There she goes again.
If it involves physical strength,
I don't lose to anyone.
We're definitely winning.
What's wrong with you?
And our first game is…
Chairball!
The very first game
is already a tough one.
I'm terrible at sports.
Same here.
I'm not good at sports either.
Eh?
I thought they'd make us run or something.
Can you handle this?
Kids, I used to be a chairball athlete.
Trust me. We're going to win.
Players ready?
Block it, Lal!
Hey, Wine!
Hey!
Wine!
Are you okay?
This was supposed to be a friendly match.
At this rate, we're going to leave
with enemies instead.
Wine, are you okay?
I'm fine.
What are you spacing out for?
Pass it over here! Come on!
-Proud!
-Lal, watch out!
Wine! Wine!
Wine!
Something's definitely going on.
Awww, I'm shipping them.
Wine!
Maybe you should be the basket instead?
Your bones can still handle it, right?
Let's keep going!
The second half starts now.
Hey, Tangkwa!
Wine!
Hey!
Hey, Wine!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Seriously, which team
is Lal actually playing for?
Everyone!
The ball's in the basket!
Wow, seriously?
Your leg already hurts
from playing that little?
It doesn't hurt nearly as much as
watching my boss care more
about the competition than me.
That's not it, Bas.
Honestly, I was worried.
I was worried that Wine would fall on you
and hurt you even more.
Come on.
Stop sulking like a child.
We need to start thinking strategically.
We already lost this game.
We can't afford to lose the next one.
Who would've thought
Proud would be the game changer?
She's tiny, but she runs faster than I do.
Seriously.
Come on. Let's go eat.
Lal, let's eat. Come on.
Let’s go.
-Get up.
-Can you walk?
Help him out.
Carry Bas.
-Look at him.
-I'm done for.
Every man for himself.
What should we eat?
Wine, I need to pee.
Do you want to go to the restroom with me?
I already went.
You go ahead.
Okay. I'll be back.
Have you eaten already?
Yeah.
Well,
did the lunch box I gave you
go bad or something?
I just didn't have time to eat it.
So I had the office lunch
with Proud instead.
I didn't want people asking
where the lunch box came from.
Why?
Was it really expensive?
If so, I'll pay you back.
That's not the point.
Forget it.
Lal, if something's bothering you,
just say it.
What's wrong?
Wine.
You said you don't think
you can take good care of someone else.
But maybe the real issue is that
you've built your walls so high
that you're hurting the people
who genuinely want to care about you.
(Do you know why?)
Whenever I’m with you,
I feel really uncomfortable.
(Who can talk to you
without feeling uncomfortable?)
I…
I never asked you to do any of this.
If it's something you don't want to do,
then don't do it.
Why should I be responsible
for your feelings
when I never asked for them
in the first place?
Is everything okay?
The Sales team had a question
about the quotation.
I'm rejecting it, by the way.
Wine, wait!
Every problem has a problem.
Why are our team and that team
so different?
Yeah!
We have to win this!
Hey.
No slacking off in this game.
If we lose this round,
the score gap is going to be huge.
Got it.
Let's begin our afternoon activity.
Each team will need to fill
this jar with water.
You may use any tool you'd like,
but it has to be something
you're already carrying with you.
Alright. If everyone's ready…
game start!
Yay!
Lal’s energy is back!
-Tangkwa!
-Wine, keep fighting!
Wine! Wine!
Lal.
What do we do?
They're pulling ahead.
A cap alone isn't enough. What do we do?
-Numnim!
-Huh?
Go, Lal!
Wine!
And the Purple Team takes the win!
Yay!!
We won!
Awesome!
Here you go.
The room key cards for the Sales Team.
Thank you.
Wait.
I have a room all to myself?
Well, the Sales Team has one extra person.
You can work out
the room arrangements yourselves.
Lal, you can have the room.
I'll stay with one of the juniors instead.
I toss and turn in my sleep.
I don't want to bother you.
Looks like someone's planning
to binge-watch a series before bed.
You know me too well.
Have you checked the gold price lately?
I already bought some.
Huh? Whoa.
I HAVE THE ROOM ALL TO MYSELF TONIGHT.
DO YOU WANT TO COME SLEEP WITH—
Let’s get some more.
There might not be enough later.
Do you want some?
Cheers.
Come on, cheers.
And now,
it's time to announce today's winner.
We have two teams
tied for the highest score.
The Purple Team and the Yellow Team!
But don't worry.
We're going to settle it
with one final challenge.
I'd like one representative
from each team to come up on stage.
-Lal, go.
-Our ace!
Go ahead.
-You can do it!
-Alright.
Anyone can volunteer.
The Purple Team is ready.
Yellow Team?
Proud, come on up.
We're Thai, you know.
Never back down
when there's still a chance to win!
This game is simple. It’s not hard at all.
Here’s the rule.
The person with the most photos
on their phone wins.
-Alright.
-Here we go.
Let's start with the Yellow Team.
Okay.
Don't worry. I love taking selfies.
I have tons of photos.
Get ready to lose.
How would you know?
And Proud has…
8,777 photos!
That's quite a lot.
Wait. Hold on a second.
Let me see this one.
Excuse me.
Proud, what were you doing
in your latest photo?
I…
I was pooping.
Excuse me?
Doing what?
Have you never pooped before, huh?
You even take selfies in the bathroom?
Well, I like selfies.
I like taking pictures.
Fine. You’re cute.
Shit!
You’re kind of cute.
Just kind of? I’d say I’m really cute.
Lal, no secretly taking extra photos.
Alright.
Now let's see the Purple Team's total.
Let’s go.
Huh?
Why did the lights go out?
Could it be a ghost? A ghost?
What's going on? Can somebody check?
Nho threw up on the power strip.
That's why the electricity went out.
Oh no!
Just handle it, anyone.
Do something.
Okay.
Let's continue.
Let's see how many photos Lal has.
And Lal's phone contains…
10,132 photos!
And that means the Purple Team wins!
Ten thousand photos?!
Come on up.
Let's present the prize.
Let's crown our winner.
Congratulations.
Let's hear it for the Purple Team!
And this one is for Proud.
The runner-up crown is a must.
First runner-up.
Or you could just call it last place,
since there were only two teams competing.
Dead last.
How did you know?
You've been holding your stomach all day.
And you've been acting cheerful
to cover it up.
I also saw a photo of medicine
on your phone earlier.
What's wrong?
Can you tell me?
Maybe I can help.
It's PMS.
I get really bad cramps before my period.
Sometimes the pain is so severe
that I have to take time off work.
I've been treated for it before,
but all they can really do
is manage the symptoms.
If it's that bad,
why didn't you skip the outing?
Why did you push yourself?
Actually, Wine understood,
so she offered to let me
take the day off this morning.
But I didn't want to become an issue
at my new company.
What issue?
Well, at my previous company,
I took sick leave because of this.
But people gossiped about me,
saying I was being dramatic.
Others said I wasn't tough enough.
They'd say, "We get periods too.”
Especially the men.
Some of them think
periods are just an excuse women use.
So…
I wanted to give it my all.
Thanks for the medicine.
It's nothing.
I understand.
Proud, at work,
we all have roles and responsibilities.
But outside of that, we're still humans.
There will always be people
who don't understand.
But trust me.
There are people who do.
And you did an amazing job today.
If you're not feeling well,
go get some rest.
Got it?
Okay.
Alliance!
Cheers to that.
Let's keep going.
And now it's time for the golden moment.
The person whose dance
impresses the judges the most
will win 2,000 baht!
Whoa! Two thousand baht?
That prize is mine!
No way.
It's mine!
Wow.
Confident much?
Of course. I'm gorgeous.
Bring it on.
Music!
Ouch!
I’m sorry, Wine!
Tangkwa, are you okay?
I'm fine.
That is nothing.
Well then, I'm heading to bed.
I can't stay awake anymore. I'm so sleepy.
Okay.
Come here.
Let me give you a hug.
Take care of yourself.
Are you drunk?
Not yet.
If I do get drunk,
I'll let you know, pretty girl.
Okay, okay.
And you said you’re not even drunk?
Why aren't you having fun
with everyone else inside?
I just wanted some time alone
with my thoughts.
I'm sorry. I’ll go back then.
Hey. It's okay.
You can sit here.
But if you're worried
someone might see us—
Everyone's drunk.
I don't think anyone's paying attention.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize to me.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Because…
I crossed the line.
No.
I wanted to apologize to you.
I thought you bought that lunch box.
But you actually made it yourself,
didn't you?
What are you doing?
Hey!
Why aren't you asleep?
I just finished pickling some vegetables.
The lunch looked so good.
It looked so good
that I assumed you bought it.
That's why I thought
throwing it away wasn't a big deal.
But that's not an excuse.
Whether you bought it or made it,
I should've been more considerate
of your feelings.
I've never really learned
how to be with someone.
People always tell me that
I'm difficult to be around.
Being with me is uncomfortable
because I keep my walls up.
They say that
I make people around me feel tired.
I don't care enough about how they feel.
Honestly, it hurts hearing that
I've made people around me feel this way.
Then it's like I automatically cut
every relationship out of my life.
And after a while,
I convinced myself
that being alone was easier.
And when you're with me,
do you feel uncomfortable?
It's the opposite.
When I'm with you,
I feel incredibly comfortable.
I feel so comfortable that it scares me.
I'm afraid I'll do something
that makes you feel uneasy.
I've been confused this whole time.
I kept wondering if I'd end up
making things difficult for you
the way I have for everyone else.
Or if I should just end this relationship
and go back to being alone.
But I finally figured it out.
When it comes to you,
I want to try.
Try what?
I want to learn how to be with someone.
But I'm slow
when it comes to things like this.
You'll have to teach me.
Of course.
I'd be happy to.
Honestly, at first
I thought you were about to cancel
our exclusive
friends-with-benefits subscription.
Are you crazy?
Of course not.
Wine,
you're not the only one learning here.
I want to learn about you too.
I want to get to know you better.
Let me get past those walls.
Which room is it?
902.
Wine.
Proud.
I'm sorry.
What do we do now?
How are you supposed to explain
this to Proud?
I don't know.
I feel like a bad kid sneaking out.
I was thinking of telling her
I got drunk and don't remember anything.
Come on.
Who's going to believe that?
Or maybe…
Proud and you are actually close enough.
Why don’t you just tell her the truth?
I don't think she'd judge you.
I don't even know how to bring it up.
Then do you want me to help?
No. It's okay.
I'll figure out a way to tell her myself.
I'd better get going.
Wine.
About what you said last night…
When you said…
you wanted to learn
how to be with someone,
does that mean that
if we learn how to be together,
we'll end up dating?
That's not what I meant.
But that's what I meant.
I want to try learning about you.
I want to know the real you.
And…
I want to try loving you.
I'm sure of how I feel now.
Lal…
I like you, Wine.
I like you in a way that goes beyond sex.
I like you in a way that's more than
sneaking around like this.
I want to be with you all the time.
And…
I want to take the best care of you.
You don't have to answer right away.
I know you'll need time to think.
I'm sorry I caught feelings.
You can give me your answer
when you're ready.
I can wait.
So you've finally
got yourself a husband, huh?
Tangkwa!
I just wanted to make
some porridge for you.
You can lie to anyone else,
but don't lie to me.
Thank you.
I'll be by your side through everything.
You think I'm easy,
so you can do whatever you want to me?
The reason I don't want a relationship
is because I'm afraid
my past will come back to haunt me.
We'll get through it together.
What a coincidence
that we saw each other again.