I don't want anyone else to have you.
I want you to be mine.
I ran into a girl I used to like.
Ever since I hurt you,
it's always been weighing on me.
Please, don't worry about it anymore.
What do you think of me?
Tell me.
If you don't say it out loud,
I'll get anxious.
I like you, Chiaki.
Promise you'll never stop liking me.
I'll always be by your side.
Ama, I love you.
Really?
Yeah, Director Tanuma asked
if you'd be the heroine's best friend.
I'll do it!
Please give me the role!
Alright, I'll pass the word on to them.
Good for you.
Thank you.
I'm going to appear in Director Tanuma's
movie as the heroine's friend!
[I'm happy for you. You earned this, Ama.]
Everything is going perfectly.
Terrifyingly so.
Have a good day.
Hey there.
Hello.
Hey...
You're dating Chiaki, right?
Yes.
And you even stood up to his mother for him?
You even heard about that?
Chiaki told me about it happily.
I'm glad someone like you
ended up being Chiaki's girlfriend.
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
Well, see you later!
[The Insomniac Woman's Love Discussion]
[Dressing Room]
Chiaki Hosho's that awful?
Yeah, a one-and-done kind of guy.
- He never keeps a steady girlfriend at all.
- What?
But wasn't there a rumor
of him previously dating the model Seira?
Seira? The one who went to Hollywood?
I expect nothing less from Chiaki Hosho.
I'm glad to see you.
You look well, Chiaki.
How about you, Seira? How's life abroad?
Every day is full of auditions,
but it's way more relaxed
than being in Japan.
I see.
What?
- Director, hello.
- Hey there.
Is that your next project?
Yeah. Have a look.
- May I?
- Sure.
Wow.
Rin's in this too?
The minor roles aren't cast yet.
[Ama Minase]
Gotta cast them quickly.
Filming starts soon.
Well...
Director?
Yes?
Where are you right now?
I'm heading to the cast meeting
for Director Tanuma's movie.
I see.
Text me when it's over.
Got it.
I'm here now.
Alright, do your best.
Okay, bye.
Huh?
Ama?
Are you in Director Tanuma's movie too?
You're in it too, Kairi-senpai?
Yeah.
I never thought
we'd get to act together this soon.
I'm so surprised.
What role are you playing?
Kengo.
Huh?
You're playing my lover.
Oh...
I see.
Director,
I hope to appear in this movie too,
even if it's just a tiny part...
Well, the producers would be thrilled
if you joined,
but you wouldn't take a minor role.
No, I really want to join.
Really?
Yes.
Anyway!
I'll be in your care.
Okay. I can't wait.
See you soon.
[Tanuma Productions]
[Cast Meeting]
We want to make this an amazing film,
so everyone, please give us your support.
Let's do our best!
What do I do?
Did I do something wrong?
- Excuse me...
- Oh, my God.
You're so adorable!
- Huh?
- Ms. Minase, you're an idol too, right?
Your eyes sparkle!
I couldn't look away this whole time!
Hey, cut it out.
You're scaring Ama.
Hey, don't get so chummy.
Do you know her?
She was my junior back in school.
Sorry for startling you.
Not at all.
I was shocked at how beautiful you are.
I'm going out for drinks
with the Director later.
Wanna come along?
Huh? Is that okay?
Of course!
It's fine, right? Director.
- What's up?
- Can she join us for drinks?
Sure, that's fine.
You can come too, Kairi.
Oh, thank you so much.
Ama, do you have a boyfriend?
If not, you and I can...
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Rin, you're way too drunk!
Quit being clingy and annoying!
Some things never change with Rin.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Here's your order.
- Who ordered this?
- Me.
[Mr. Chiaki]
Looks good.
- This is so good.
- Excuse me for a moment.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm with the Director
and some cast members for dinner.
I told you to contact me when it's over,
remember?
Did you forget about me?
Of course not.
I just never got the chance.
Come home right now.
But, I'm the newest one here.
Where are you?
I'm coming to get you.
What?
Ama?
I'm sorry.
I need to head out now.
- Sure.
- Are you leaving?
No!
Rin.
It's alright, Ms. Minase.
I'm sorry.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Sure, likewise!
Well, I...
Chiaki?
Ama, why can't you understand how I feel?
Huh?
Even when we're apart,
I'm always thinking about you, Ama.
It drives me crazy.
But...
you're not like that, huh?
I'll be more careful from now on.
I'm scared.
We're on different sets now.
I worry about what you're doing
when I'm not around.
I'm such a clingy guy.
That's not true.
I know I'm being irrational too.
But,
that's how much I love you.
I need you to know
how worried I am about you.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
No,
I am, too.
I'm sorry.
How was the drinking party?
Ms. Rin livened the party up.
Rin, huh?
I've acted with her before.
Really?
Who else is in the cast?
Come to think of it,
I never asked who your co-star is.
Well...
There's nothing to feel bad about, but...
Here.
Good work.
Thank you very much.
Ama?
H-He's a really nice person.
But I don't think you know him.
It's just a minor role.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Of course.
Oh, right. Here.
Keep this with you.
Huh? Are you sure?
Yeah, come see me anytime.
Okay.
And let's share our location on an app
so I can pick you up more easily.
An app?
Give me your phone.
Here.
Wow, this is really handy.
I really love you.
I love you too.
Don't ever leave me.
Either way...
I'm not going to let you go.
You're the absolute worst.
Say something already.
Say it!
There's... nothing to say.
You always push me away like that.
I'm done.
Cut! Okay!
Cut!
Okay! Let's move on to the next scene.
I'm sorry, that hurt, didn't it?
I-I'm so sorry!
I'm just kidding.
You're so easy to fool, Ama.
Then I'll hit harder in the next take.
Sorry, please keep it at this level.
Long time no see, Rin.
Oh, Chiaki.
Still as popular as ever, I see.
Thank you.
Speaking of which,
you're in Director Tanuma's movie, right?
You heard about it?
Who else is starring?
Let's see.
Nakahara, Mr. Ueda,
and there's this adorable girl
who's also an idol named Ama.
Oh...
Do you know who her co-star is?
Huh? It's Kairi.
Why?
Kairi?
Kairi Asakura?
Yeah.
It's surprising such a big star
would take a supporting role.
Chiaki?
Ama lied to me.
He's a really nice person.
But I don't think you know him.
[Mr. Chiaki]
[Missed Voice Call]
- Hey.
- Hello.
You like this, right?
I'm surprised you remember, Kairi-senpai.
Hey.
We're not students anymore,
so drop the "senpai".
Just call me Kairi.
That's a bit awkward.
If you won't call me that,
then I won't use your first name anymore.
You're being mean again.
You've always had that side to you, Kairi.
Just kidding.
Hey.
Do you have a boyfriend, Ama?
A boyfriend?
You do, huh?
Please keep it a secret.
What's he like?
An actor?
Yes.
He's way too good for me.
Who is this actor guy anyway?
I'm definitely more famous than he is.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
Where's the filming set?
It's over there.
Need the director?
Yeah.
Over here.
Hey,
I told you that I reconnected
with that girl I liked before, right?
We started talking again
after she reached out,
but I was crushed
to find out she has a boyfriend.
If she's taken, you should give up.
Huh?
Wait a second, Chiaki!
I thought you liked the challenge.
You're a pro at stealing girls.
I've reflected. It's not a good thing to do.
Wow...
You must really love your current girlfriend.
Actually...
that girl is my co-star.
What?
I hurt her.
Now that we're acting and getting close,
this is my chance...
The girl you hurt...
Was it Ama?
Huh?
You know Ama?
Get up.
I'll kill you.
Could it be that you're...
- Hey, what are you doing?
- This is crazy!
- Let go!
- Chiaki!
This guy hurt you, right?
That's why I'm gonna kill him.
Stop!
Just get off him!
Please don't!
Chiaki!
Why did you lie to me?
It's because...
There's no way
I wouldn't know who Kairi is.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't want to make you anxious.
Chiaki?
No, stop!
Please.
No, no, stop.
Chiaki, stop, please.
I should've done this sooner,
to make you mine alone.
I'll never let you go until the day I die.
I want to break up.
Chiaki was the boyfriend all along.
If Ama ever belongs to anyone but me,
I want to die with her.
Don't touch Ama, don't get near her.
Die, die, die!