The girl you hurt... Was it Ama?
Why did you lie to me?
There's no way
I wouldn't know who Kairi is.
I'm so sorry.
Chiaki, stop, please.
I should have done this sooner,
to make you mine alone.
No, please, stop...
Please... No!
Stop.
It's your fault for lying, Ama.
No.
Please, stop it.
Now, finally.
I'm sorry.
I...
I didn't mean to...
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I really do love you, Ama.
I'm going crazy over you.
I'm going home.
Ama?
Wait!
I'm sorry I lied.
I didn't do anything bad with him.
I just didn't want to make you feel uneasy.
I should have been honest.
But...
was it bad enough...
for you to do this?
I'm truly sorry.
- I was...
- I want to keep some distance.
I won't contact you for a while.
No, Ama.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Please.
Don't go.
Ama...
Ama.
Kairi-senpai, good morning.
Morning.
Is your injury okay?
Yeah, it's nothing.
So,
Chiaki was the boyfriend all along.
Yes.
We've been close since way back.
We hung out a lot.
I see.
When did it end yesterday?
That was crazy yesterday.
So, does that mean
Ms. Minase is involved with both of them?
Right?
I didn't expect that from her.
Oh, man.
But she's cute, so it's okay.
No, you should keep that off set.
That's true.
Yeah, but it's cool knowing
what's going on behind the scenes.
Hey!
Would you stop with those rumors?
I'm sorry!
That felt good.
Ama.
Don't worry about them.
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
Thanks, Rin.
Well, let's shake it off
and do our best on set today.
Okay.
Alright, let's go.
[Mr. Chiaki]
Ama?
Sorry.
The number you dialed
is either out of range, or turned off.
is either out of range...
- Good work today.
- Good work.
Ama!
Saotome.
Disappear!
Disappear, disappear, disappear!
What do you want?
Geez, you don't have to be so guarded.
Oh, by the way,
that must have been rough on you.
Mr. Hosho punched Mr. Asakura, right?
I just happened to hear about it. That's all.
And I'd heard bad rumors about Mr. Hosho,
so I've been worried about you, Ama.
Bad rumors?
That he toys with girls
and then throws them away.
Chiaki is not that kind of person.
Don't say such baseless things.
Want me to introduce you?
To a girl who was hurt by Chiaki Hosho.
Ama, this is Hibiki.
Hey, Chiaki.
I don't want to break up.
Ama wants to know about Chiaki Hosho.
I don't really...
Don't be fooled.
Huh?
That guy is a scumbag.
I got close to Chiaki
after we worked together.
He asked me out to dinner,
and I fell for him.
It didn't take long
for us to become intimate.
But,
once I got serious,
his attitude changed completely.
Are you sure
you want me to spread that video?
Huh?
You were making quite the noise.
If that gets out,
you'll have to leave the industry.
What? Hibiki, I'm so sorry!
That Chiaki Hosho is a jerk!
He's the worst!
No way!
Chiaki would never...
Here's a photo of us.
Chiaki, are you okay?
I heard you bailed on work.
Things not going well with her?
Maybe...
I should die.
Huh?
Don't say that, even as a joke.
Drink some water.
I don't feel alive.
Huh?
I'm nervous not having Ama around.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
I love her so much, I can't help myself.
Honestly,
I want to snatch her up right now,
and keep her locked up next to me.
I want to ruin her
so she can't live without me.
If Ama ever belongs to anyone but me...
I want to die with her.
In the end...
this is the only way I know how to live.
Ready? Action!
Yu, you really are like that sometimes.
That's not true.
It's just that I...
Cut!
Are you okay?
Not feeling well?
I'm sorry.
Let's take a short break.
We'll resume in 15 minutes!
- 15 minutes.
It's no good.
I can't concentrate at all.
Alright!
Let's drink after we're done!
Ms. Rin.
That includes you who's glancing over here!
I'm sorry for stopping the shoot
so many times today.
Do you feel uncomfortable on set?
No, it's not that.
If anyone says anything weird,
let me know, okay?
I'll give them an earful.
Thank you.
Anyway, let's drink, eat,
and forget about it all today!
Oh no.
It's from my manager.
I forgot I had a magazine interview.
Seriously?
I'm so sorry!
- See you later, Ama.
- Okay.
Good grief. She's always in a rush.
Yes.
So how have things been?
With Chiaki.
I haven't seen him, or contacted him.
I see.
Actually, what kind of person was he,
from your perspective?
What do you mean by that?
I'm starting to have trouble
understanding who Chiaki is.
Depending on the answer,
are you going to break up with him?
From what I know,
he was a hopeless mess
when it came to women.
He'd target innocent-looking girls,
and take bets on them.
There was even a bet on whether
he could get you within three months.
He suggested it.
What?
Well, take care.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
See you on set.
Yeah.
[Mr. Chiaki]
[Ama]
Hello?
Ama?
I'm sorry I haven't been replying.
No, it's my fault.
I've been thinking a lot since then.
I want to break up.
Huh?
Because I found out that the Chiaki I know
was only a small part of him.
What do you mean?
That you hurt girls without a second thought.
You even bet on
whether you could get me, right?
I can't trust you anymore.
Thank you for everything until now.
I see.
She found out about the real me.
But I'll never let you go
until the day I die.
I can't live...
without you anymore.
I have to pull myself together.
I don't want to cause
any more trouble for everyone.
Come in.
Do you have a minute?
Yes.
Sorry to bother you.
It's fine.
So, what did you want to talk about?
I feel like both of you
aren't quite becoming your characters.
Yu and Kengo were lovers.
They end up breaking up,
but they loved each other deeply, right?
That kind of aura...
It isn't coming from you two.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm not angry.
I'm just wondering what we should do.
For example, how about spending time together
off set?
- Huh?
- Actually try acting like a couple.
That way, you might get a feel
for loving each other.
Wait...
That's...
I understand.
I'll give it a try before the next shoot.
What should we do?
I guess we'd have a date or something?
But outside, people might see us.
That's true.
Then come to my place.
No...
That's not right.
Sorry.
You're a popular actor, after all.
Going to your place is risky.
Yeah.
Oh, how about my place?
My family is at a relative's house right now,
so no one's home.
Huh? Is that okay?
Of course!
Then let's go.
Okay.
Alright!
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Hey.
What do you want?
I heard from Shiki.
Things aren't going well with her?
Shut up.
Chiaki, you hide it well,
but inside, you're still a kid.
Want me to tell you something good?
What?
I heard that Chiaki Hosho and Kairi Asakura
got into a fistfight over a new actress.
Go verify it for me!
Oh, I'll introduce you
to a staff member on set, okay?
Why is Kairi here?
It's a bit messy, but come in.
Thanks for having me.
I really wish Kairi would just die.
Don't touch Ama, don't get near her.
This is the worst.
Die.
Die, die, die, die!
Even now, I still love you.
I'm in love with you, Ama.
I could make someone like you
disappear anytime.
I still want to stay by your side forever.
I love you, Ama.