Hey, Zen!
-What? Are you mad?
-No, I'm not.
You're mad.
What?
Are you jealous?
Huh? No way.
You totally are.
Is it because I had a good time
chatting with those girls?
What do you mean?
Well, to be honest,
I didn't expect you to get jealous.
I'm just petty, alright?
I'm heading home.
I was wrong!
I'm not mad at you.
Eh?
I...
I didn't even know
what kind of music you like.
Well,
that's no big deal.
I...
I thought I'd be fine
no matter who you got along with.
You're friendly to everyone.
You really know how to win people over.
See? You really are mad at me.
No!
I just think...
it's embarrassing that I still get jealous
over something this trivial and can't
even keep my emotions under control.
Let's just call it a day.
I'll calm down after a while.
How could I possibly leave you alone?
Let's plan
our next date more carefully.
Date?
Still, it was really fun.
Making plans,
meeting up,
and going somewhere together—
things like that.
Sorry for ruining our date.
No, no.
I'm not talking about today's concert.
I know.
I was just joking.
Geez.
Then, let's go on a date somewhere
next time.
Mm, let's.
Maybe we should just take a trip overseas.
Don't be silly.
With our schedules, we can barely
manage a trip within the country.
You've got projects
on your plate too, right?
Yeah, true.
At most, we could probably
manage one night.
Well,
isn't that nice?
Doing things like that
when we've just started dating.
Yeah.
Your birthday
is coming up soon.
We'll just treat it
as a birthday celebration.
Eh?
What?
You...
You know my birthday?
What kind of person do you think I am?
That's exactly why I'm surprised.
Come to think of it,
no one's ever celebrated
my birthday before.
You haven't celebrated mine either, right?
That's because you never gave off any vibe
that made people want to celebrate it.
But don't worry.
From now on,
I'll celebrate your birthday for you.
No need. It doesn't matter.
I'm not a kid anymore.
But you still want to celebrate mine.
Got a problem with that?
Yes.
I want to celebrate yours too.
So,
since we're celebrating anyway,
let's make it a trip
to celebrate both our birthdays.
Let's find
somewhere nice to stay.
Well,
I like that idea.
It's settled then.
Now all that's left
is to see
whether our work schedules line up.
I'll make it work.
This time for sure.
It's a deal.
Me too.
[Development]
Hey, Shido.
It's been a long time.
Futami?
[Fake Fact Lips]
[Episode 7: I'm Joining This Rivalry Too!]
Futami's transfer was so sudden.
I heard he'd be transferred back
within a few years,
but he never contacted me.
Must have been swamped.
Oh.
Do you two keep in touch?
Eh?
I told you we went to
the same college, didn't I?
Eh?
Why are you so surprised?
You never told me that.
No way, I must've mentioned it.
No, I never heard you...
Wait, actually, maybe once.
See?
You really have no interest
in other people.
However,
now that he's back,
things are about to get lively again.
I've got a bad feeling he's
going to derail our travel plans.
Don't jinx it.
It'll be fine.
As long as he doesn't
get assigned to our section.
He was in our Section 1 before.
He'll probably go back there.
What?
You two don't get along?
Not many people do.
He's actually a good person, though.
I'm Futami Yuya,
transferred to Section 2
starting today.
I'll make full use of the skills
I learned at the Osaka branch
and become
a valuable member of the team
as quickly as possible.
I look forward to working with all of you.
Futami, welcome aboard.
-Looking forward to working with you.
-Mr. Futami,
it's been a long time.
Oh!
Haven't you grown taller!
No, I'm still the same.
Why our section?
He didn't go back to Section 1!
Is that the legendary colleague who joined
the company at the same time as you two?
Huh?
Is he a legend now?
Yes.
Word is he's a standout man with
a totally different style from you two.
Who said that?
Mr. Onishi.
Huh?
He and Futami are close?
They seem to be each other's wingmen
at those mixers.
I see.
Hey, Shido.
Starting today, we're in the same section.
Once again,
looking forward to working with you.
[Development]
Yeah, same here.
So cold.
-This is what I get after all these years?
-Futami,
last time we drank together,
you never mentioned
you were transferring back.
Surprise. It's a surprise.
Well, now that I see you,
have you gotten stronger?
No!
We just saw each other recently.
How would I have changed?
Hey.
You're still the same,
with that "don’t mess with me" face.
I don't make that face at everyone.
Huh?
Speaking of which,
you two met in Osaka?
-Mm.
-Of course.
We're buddies
who spent our youth together.
Oh, really?
Ah.
Don't grab me.
Haha.
Ah!
By the way,
I've heard rumors about you two.
Something about
the rivalry between you two sales aces
drives performance through the roof.
Hey!
I want in on this rivalry.
Are you two
free tonight?
No.
Go have fun without me.
That guy really hasn't changed one bit.
Let's go, just the two of us.
Okay.
[Sound Wave Bar]
-Please raise your glass.
-Okay.
Then...
-Looking forward to working with you!
-Likewise. Cheers.
Ah.
Still,
even though you're busy,
you made time to hang out with me.
That's what makes you so kind.
We're more than just colleagues
who joined the same year—we're friends.
Hey, you're making me fall for you.
Alright, alright.
Even so,
you never contacted me at all, did you?
Neither did you.
So,
how does it feel
being back in Tokyo after so long?
Well,
the handover isn't done yet,
so it's hard to say.
I'm still getting used to
the more aloof communication style here.
The atmosphere with clients in Osaka
was completely different.
Then
maybe that place is more suitable for you?
Maybe.
I came back...
because I wanted to work with you.
You're not even embarrassed saying that?
I'm not paying the bill.
Huh?
I mean it.
Eh? Really?
Why?
I
worked really hard in Osaka, you know.
I heard.
Do you know why I worked so hard?
Well...
Because of you two.
Huh?
You and Shido have been competing
with each other all this time,
even though you're in different sections.
We joined the company at the same time,
yet I was left on the sidelines.
It really got to me.
Oh, really?
Sorry. That's on me.
I didn't mean to...
Don't apologize.
I'm the one who chose to feel that way.
Besides,
I trained hard in Osaka.
All so I could join your rivalry.
No.
Even if you say so...
I'm serious.
I
have no intention of competing with you.
Why?
"Why?"
Because
that's a special way
of communicating between Shido and me.
No, I don't get it.
What do you mean
by "way of communicating?"
I mean,
you and I are already friends, right?
There's no need for us to compete.
Hmm... I don't quite get it.
But I understand.
What exactly do you understand?
In that case, I'll...
just compete with Shido.
You didn't understand anything.
I can't force you if you don't want to.
Besides,
he's in the same section as me.
It's perfect.
No, Zen...
Shido
won't accept the challenge either.
Really?
Eh?
You've
only had drinks with me once.
You don't really know my abilities yet.
The day I become Shido's rival
isn't far off...
-I think.
-Hmm.
Oh?
Not bad.
Not bad. Oh!
This is great! Down in one go!
I'll drink too.
You sure put that beer away, didn't you?
Not bad.
Ah, excuse me,
could we get another round?
Draft beers, please.
Thank you.
Looking forward to
working together from here on.
Likewise.
We're leaving now.
Excuse us.
It's gotten pretty late.
Sorry about that.
No, not at all. This was time well spent.
I'm really happy
I got to work with you again, Mr. Shido.
Me too.
Next time, let's invite Yotsuya
and have dinner together.
Sounds good.
Definitely.
Ah.
Speaking of which,
do you know a Futami at your company?
Futami from the Osaka branch?
Yeah, him.
I heard he got transferred back.
Mr. Mochida, you went to university
with Yotsuya and him, right?
Yes.
When you think about it,
I seem to have
quite a connection with your company.
Indeed.
Those two
seem to be having
a cohort get-together tonight.
Seems like it.
They're still as close as ever.
Are they that close?
At first, it was mostly
Futami clinging to Yotsuya.
Then, it felt like Yotsuya
warmed up to him eventually.
Warmed up to him?
Those two were together
all the time in college.
They even went on a trip together,
just the two of them.
A trip?
Ah, speaking of which...
The photos from back then...
Ah.
Futami just sent one over.
What a coincidence.
Look.
Yeah.
This photo brings back memories.
Haha.
[Are you home yet?]
Eh?
Why?
What?
Eh?
Why are you here?
I should be asking you that.
No.
You're the one who should explain.
Forget it.
Come in.
We got a little too carried away drinking.
He got pretty drunk,
so I brought him back.
Him?
Yeah.
Eh?
So,
why are you here?
Yotsuya called me over.
He said he was drinking with you.
Oh, I see.
Well, in that case,
let's grab a drink, just the two of us.
Haven't you had quite a bit already?
That little bit of alcohol is nothing.
I see.
You've always been able to
hold your liquor.
I'd almost forgotten.
I bought a lot. There's still plenty left.
Well,
he'll probably wake up soon anyway.
Here.
Then, just a little.
Still, you really surprised me.
You've become quite polished now.
What makes you say that?
Earlier today, I thought you were still
the same as before.
But after work, you actually came
all the way over for drinks.
The old you would've never done it.
I'm just a bit more composed than before.
Huh?
Composed, huh?
The sales ace really is something else.
Don't keep provoking me.
But that composure of yours
-will be gone soon.
-Hm?
You mean that talk
about you wanting to join our rivalry?
Yes.
-You and me. Let's compete...
-I refuse.
Why?
If you want to compete, do it on your own.
Huh?
It takes two people to have a rivalry.
Anyway,
just dealing with Yotsuya
keeps me plenty busy as it is.
You too, huh.
What do you mean?
Yotsuya turned me down too.
I
have no intention of competing with you.
Of course.
What do you mean, "of course?"
By the way,
why are you so set on competing with us?
That's because
I'm more suitable for Yotsuya than you.
What?
Where does that come from? Are you crazy?
You're drunk.
Ah.
I've been drinking.
But I've been perfectly clear-headed
this whole time.
What is that even supposed to mean?
Every single thing you say
just gets on my nerves.
Fine.
Then I'll just say it straight
while I have the chance.
I've
had a problem with you
since the day we joined this company.
I don't care about
your little "high-school rival" story.
But why does he only ever care about you?
I'm the one who was by his side
throughout university.
But why is he so fixated on someone
as dull and prickly as you?
Give you an inch, and you just keep going,
don't you?
What's wrong with telling the truth?
And you?
You've always looked at me
like I was a nuisance. So rude!
You are a nuisance. And you keep
provoking me at every turn.
And you always wear that calm expression,
looking down on me, huh?
You're being paranoid.
The moment you start thinking
you're being looked down on,
you've already admitted your own failure.
Ah!
You're so irritating.
Fine. Let's settle this.
You're so persistent.
Let's see which of us is
better suited to be his rival.
His rival...
It's you, right?
For now, maybe.
But if I become
the top salesman in Section 2,
he'll only pay attention to me.
You think I'd just
hand first place over to you?
Don't underestimate me.
Understood.
You've said your piece—
then I'll take you up on
that challenge.
Eh?
Ah.
What are you doing?
Well...
Zen, why are you...
Shido, why are you here?
Oh, right!
I called you! Sorry, sorry.
I drank too much and passed out.
More importantly,
you seem awfully concerned about this guy.
And he seems pretty happy about it.
Are you listening?
I am listening.
Happy?
For what?
Competing with me.
What?
Well, whether it even counts as
a competition remains to be seen.
Talking big, but secretly
terrified on the inside, aren't you?
I have no reason to get worked up.
Whatever.
I need a smoke.
Go to the balcony!
It's so hot outside.
The balcony!
Don't make me repeat myself.
That guy...
is staying the night, right?
Yeah.
He's really fond of you.
He's always been like that.
Well...
What?
Are you suspecting something
between Futami and me?
No.
I know you're only interested in me.
Then...
Why did you come over?
Do I need a reason
to come see you?
But I'm going home now.
Hey, Zen.
Don't take
what that guy said seriously.
Well,
now that we're in the same section,
there'll still be competition work-wise.
Besides,
I told you that competing with you
isn't interesting anymore, right?
Eh?
Then, see you at work.
Ah.
It's so hot.
Where's Shido?
He went back.
What a heartless guy.
He could've at least said goodbye to me.
What's wrong?
Haha.
Nothing.
Nothing's wrong.
Yotsuya,
let me stay here tonight.
Going home is too much of a hassle.
Okay.
Oh.
[In the Next Episode]
The great me will be heading off first.
[Episode 8: How Should I Put It? Geez...]
Why are you
so obsessed with Yotsuya?
I
really respect Yotsuya.
-Shut up.
I feel
things have been tense lately
between you and Mr. Futami.
You actually have a cute side to you.
Huh?
I
might want to get to know you better.
I have them—friends.
How rude.
Can't I take Shido's place
in your rivalry?
I'm fine.