"Double Helix"
(Episode 9: Never Disliked, Always Liked)
About the job...
I'd like to talk to you
about it one more time.
Of course,
if you don't want to see me again,
then forget it.
Sit wherever you like.
Have something to drink first.
Lu Feng.
I...
I came here to explain things to you.
I wasn't using Ke Lo.
I actually just met Ke Lo.
He knew I was looking for a job,
so he brought me to your company.
When I came to see you,
I wanted to apologize.
I remember orange juice
used to be your favorite.
Don't you like it anymore?
No, that's not it.
I've always liked it.
You just said you wanted to apologize.
Apologize for what?
What have you done that
you need to apologize for?
Five years ago...
I'm sorry.
My mind was a mess back then.
With what suddenly happened
to my brother and my mom...
I just didn't know what to do.
Back then...
In my life,
I was only ever sure about Cheng Yichen.
If you want to break up, then fine.
Lu Feng.
I heard...
you married Zhuo Lan.
Congratulations.
That's because...
I also heard...
you two got divorced.
The prized son-in-law
of the richest family.
Didn't that work out for you?
You're coming to me now...
is it because...
Zhuo Lan dumped you?
Or is it because you found out...
that I'm more powerful
than the Zhuo family,
so you dumped her?
What's wrong?
You look so pale.
Are you not feeling well?
I need to use the restroom.
Did I say something to scare you?
You don't have to be afraid.
The past...
I've mostly forgotten about it.
Back then,
I really had nothing.
I certainly couldn't
compare to the Zhuo family.
So for you to change your mind...
it's not surprising.
But...
why didn't you just talk to me?
You made me run off to America,
give up everything,
and completely cut ties with the Lu family.
When I came back looking for you,
you were already married.
I couldn't find you no
matter how hard I looked.
What exactly do you want now?
First, you tell me.
Have you been waiting
for me all these years?
Have you always loved me?
And now you want to rekindle our old flame?
You're burning up.
Do you have a fever?
You're so manipulative.
Still carrying this piece of junk around.
Lu...
Lu Feng.
Lu Feng!
Your house is huge!
Lu...
Mr. Lu, why is there someone in your house?
Don't mind him.
Mr. Lu, who is he?
Laugh.
Go on, laugh.
Lu Feng.
Let's talk.
Talk about what?
About how you betrayed me?
It was because of my mom
and my brother back then.
I had no choice.
Your mom and your brother?
What are they to me?
Why should I have to consider them?
So you tricked me into coming here...
just to get revenge on me?
Revenge?
As if you're worthy.
Then what is it you want?
You're awful.
Mr. Lu.
Slow down.
Don't.
Mr. Lu.
Naughty.
Don't.
Mr. Lu.
Slow down.
Don't.
Naughty.
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu, it's my first time at your place.
I'm so happy.
Mr. Lu, there's someone else here.
Why did you ask me to come over?
You don't have to treat him like a person.
You stepped on my foot.
Mr. Lu, look at him.
He's not watching where he's going.
Apologize to him.
That's not necessary.
I said,
apologize to him.
I'm sorry.
Forget it, forget it.
Was that fun?
Suddenly, it feels like in this world,
it's just the two of us left.
Swear to me now.
Swear it.
That no matter what happens,
you will never leave me again.
What if...
you're the one who tells me to leave?
You still can't leave.
You're being so unreasonable.
Yes or no?
Yes.
As long as it's a request from you,
no matter how unreasonable,
I'll accept it.
But if you leave me,
I'll stop at nothing to find you
to drag you back.
I'll lock you up,
so you can never escape again.
Understand?
What does that matter?
As long as...
you love me.
Lu Feng.
What were you dreaming about?
You were talking in your sleep.
What are you doing here?
This is my house.
How long has it been
since you've had water?
Drink.
You're not drinking?
Suit yourself.
Lu Feng.
Don't touch me.
What do you want from me?
This feeling of being utterly helpless,
where your pleas go unanswered...
seeing me be intimate
with other men every day...
how does it feel?
It feels terrible, doesn't it?
What right do you have to feel terrible?
Who are you to me?
Mr. Zhuo.
Looking at your face now,
it makes me sick to my stomach.
Then why are you keeping me locked up here?
Let me go.
You want to leave?
In your dreams.
This is false imprisonment.
Then call the police.
It's not like you haven't done it before.
Or...
you could kill me in my sleep.
Kill me.
After all, me being alive right now...
is no different from being dead.
I don't lock my door when I sleep.
There are plenty of knives
in the kitchen downstairs.
Each one sharper than the last.
Or...
you could use this.
Take it.
Just like this...
plunge it in.
And you'll be free.
And I'll be free.
Come in.
Mr. Lu.
Should I arrange for someone for you today?
That won't be necessary.
Was the person I picked
before not good enough?
Xiao Cheng.
Have a few drinks with me later.
Okay.
I'll wait for you downstairs then.
Yichen. Yichen.
Hey, you, come here.
Give me a hand. Help me out.
Sorry to bother you.
He's had too much to drink.
Mr. Lu's room is upstairs.
Well, I'll be going now.
I'll leave Mr. Lu to you.
He's all yours.
Xiao Chen.
Get off me.
What's with the reluctance?
It's not like we haven't done this before.
How could you be so cruel?
Cheng Yichen.
Maybe...
after we sleep together,
if I think your performance isn't too bad,
I might just let you go.
What do you want from me?
I'm willing to touch you.
You should be happy about that.
Why don't you consider this?
Maybe I'm falling in love
with you all over again.
Don't do this.
I'm begging you.
Lu Feng.
Why did you kiss me?
Cheng Yichen.
Let me tell you something.
All these years,
while you were off having
fun with someone else,
there was someone...
who was waiting for you.
And...
they were living like a dead man.
Just think about it.
How...
ridiculous my life has been...
all these years.
Xiao Chen.
Lu Feng.
Just a few deep kisses.
Just him whispering my name a few times.
And the walls I'd built
up suddenly crumbled.
The cracks between us seemed
like a figment of my imagination.
It was as if the years of
pain had never piled up.
As if he had never hurt me.
As if I could be like I was before,
giving myself to him without reservation.
I guess longing and forgiveness...
are never decided by logic.
Lu Feng.
I've really missed you so much.
Get out.
So all the caresses,
all the kisses,
they were all fake.
It was all in my head.
He just wanted to make me suffer.
Mr. Lu.
Should I arrange for someone today?
Yes, arrange it.
Get me the best-looking one you can find.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
On second thought, forget it.
Understood, Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu, someone from the
Zhuo family came to the office.
They said they have business they
want to discuss with you personally.
Business?
Those were their exact words.
You tell them...
that FC Corporation...
will never have any business
dealings with the Zhuo family.
Yes, sir.
You should stay here for now.
It's better for both you and Mr. Lu.
- Hello, Mr. Lu.
- Where is he?
He's inside. Hasn't come out.
Cheng Yichen.
What the hell are you doing?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
Taking a bath.
How long have you been in there?
Are you trying to die?
If you want to die,
don't do it in my bathtub.
Are you afraid of what I might do to you?
Nothing's going to happen.
You don't have to worry at all.
Brother Chen.
Brother, it's really you!
What are you doing here?
What happened to your neck?
I just hurt it by accident.
Hurt it?
It'll be fine in a couple of days.
By the way,
what are you doing here?
This is my uncle's place.
You know, Mr. Lu.
He said he'd take me to play tennis today.
I have a school tournament next week,
so I need the practice.
Brother, why don't you come with us?
I... I don't know how to play.
That's okay, you can learn.
Mr. Lu isn't just a good player,
he's an even better teacher.
And he never gets mad.
Even with someone as unathletic as me,
he's never discouraging.
Lu Feng is really good to you.
Of course.
That's mainly because he's a great person.
By the way, Brother,
you still haven't told me...
why you're here today.
Did you start working at his company?
How's it going?
I...
Ke Lo.
I got you a new racket.
A new racket?
It's custom-made from overseas.
That outfit really suits you.
Mr. Lu.
Should we take Brother
Chen to play with us?
No, thanks. I don't know how.
Don't worry about him.
But... him...
The car is here.
Let's go.
But... but...