In the end, you chose me.
You've got such a mouth.
Let me teach you a lesson.
A boy!
We got a boy!
If you want to quit your job
and start your own company, you can.
Then you deserve a reward.
I can't. I can't do it.
I can't do it.
-Nueng.
-I can't.
-What do I do?
-Nueng.
-I'm here.
-How am I supposed to live?
It's okay.
You're okay.
Let's take deep breaths together, okay?
Take a deep breath.
I can't clean up the vase.
It's okay. I'll clean it up for you.
Do you want to take your medicine?
Medicine? Take medicine?
No, I can't.
Phupha's here. I can't take it.
Oon, can you make her
something sweet to drink, please?
Then how am I supposed
to raise him properly?
I can't take medicine.
-Try touching your baby.
-I can't do anything.
Touch your baby. Touch your baby.
Can you feel Phupha?
-Can you feel him?
-Yeah.
Phupha's moving.
I'm sorry. Mommy's sorry.
Mommy can't take care of you properly.
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
I can't raise you well.
It's okay, Nueng. Take a deep breath.
Deep breaths.
Breathe with me, okay?
Alright.
Here's the sweet drink.
Thank you.
Take a few sips.
Just a little.
Good job. You're doing great.
Alright.
Breathe in. Take a deep breath.
One, two,
three.
Hold it. One,
two,
three,
four.
Now slowly breathe out.
Panic disorder? Since when?
Probably around two or three months ago.
Back when I would take Nueng
to her prenatal appointments,
she'd get really anxious.
Her hands and feet would go cold,
and her heart would race.
So we consulted a doctor.
But after the physical examination,
nothing seemed physically wrong.
So the doctor suggested
we see a psychiatrist instead.
That's when we found out
she has panic disorder.
How did she get that?
I think the main reason is because
she can't rely on herself right now.
Nueng probably planned to move back
to Thailand and start working,
but then her morning sickness
got severe, so she couldn't work.
And once she started feeling better,
her belly was already too big.
Moving around became difficult.
Most importantly,
she's scared she won't be a good mother.
I've been living in the same house as her,
but I didn't notice any of this.
I'm sorry, Fun.
It's okay.
Didn't you once tell me that
we were going to build a family together?
You'd build from the front of the house,
and I'd build from the back.
And one day, we'd meet in the middle
and become a complete home.
Our family.
I'm really lucky
to have you as my life partner.
-Oon.
-Hmm?
I think I'm going to resign.
Everything in our life right now
feels like it's falling into place.
I'm finally about to start doing
what I've always wanted to do.
And most importantly,
our house is about
to have a little one too.
I'll finally have time
to help take care of Phupha.
Such a planner.
Oon-oon, are you sure you'll be okay?
Maybe I shouldn't go after all.
I'll be fine.
Now that I know what's going on
with Nueng, I can handle it.
I survived dealing with you, didn't I?
Oops, that was the voice in my head.
Hey!
Oon-oon, how much cash
do you have left right now?
Cash?
Probably around 500 baht.
Then make it last until the end
of the month. I'm not giving you more.
Huh?
Fun, it's only the middle of the month.
I thought you said you could handle it.
Not this.
Fun, are you serious?
You're joking, right?
That's all I'm saying. I'm off now.
Five hundred?
Sit here.
Careful. Slowly.
-I'll do it for you.
-It's okay. I can do it.
I'll do it.
Nueng,
from now on,
if there's anything you can't handle,
tell me, and I'll do it for you.
No matter what it is, I'll do it.
Okay?
If I had an older sister,
she'd probably be like you.
Older sister is fine.
But if you call me grandma again,
you can get out.
Whoa.
SINGLE MOTHER WITH NOWHERE TO TURN
STEALS FROM CONVENIENCE STORE
TO KEEP 7-MONTH-OLD BABY ALIVE
Nueng.
Nueng, I'm here.
I'm here.
Nueng.
Nueng, Nueng, Nueng.
Can you feel this?
This is your hand.
This is your arm.
Your arm. Can you feel it?
Arm…
Do you want to hold my hand, Nueng?
I'm here. I'm right here.
Remember what I told you before?
If there's anything you can't handle,
I'll do it for you.
No matter what it is,
I'll take care of it.
Throw it all at me.
Just tell me.
Let me carry it all for you.
Just don't let go of us, okay?
Now let's breathe together.
One,
two,
three,
four.
Hold it…
One, two,
three,
four, five.
What happened?
You couldn't hold it in?
I think my water just broke.
Your water broke?
Her water broke! What do we do?
-I'll get the car ready.
-Get the car ready.
-I'll go get the keys.
-No, Fun.
You need to grab the bag.
I'll get the keys myself.
Okay. Hey, Oon.
The key is not there.
Oh, right.
I'm going to get the bag, okay?
Stay right here.
Wait.
-Clothes.
-Clothes?
-Okay, okay. Clothes.
-Yeah.
-I'm back. Here are the keys.
-Okay.
I got clothes.
Fun, these are your clothes.
I'll go get them. Here, the keys.
Oh.
Oon, bring the other bag too, okay?
Okay.
The bag. The other bag.
Here, clothes. Change now.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'll change in the bathroom.
Bathroom.
-Let's go.
-I'll carry this for you.
Oh.
Slowly.
Be careful.
No, you can't come in.
Here.
Be careful.
Thank you.
Alright. Okay.
Wait. Where's Nueng?
Nueng!
Wait for me. Where are you going?
-You didn't even wait.
-Nueng.
Hold on.
-Wait.
-I can't.
-Slowly.
-Open the door.
-Wait.
Open the door.
Get in.
-Alright.
-Wait!
The bag!
Go get the bag.
The bag.
-Got it.
-Okay, the bag.
We're going now, okay?
Okay. Go.
You're doing great, Mommy.
We can see the baby's head now.
Push, okay?
Deep breath, hold it, push.
Nueng's here.
How are you feeling?
It hurt like crazy.
But
once I saw my baby's face,
all the pain just disappeared.
So this is what they call
"beautiful pain."
You did great, Mommy.
Mommy…
The baby's here.
He's so tiny.
So cute.
Oon, you're supposed
to say "adorably ugly."
So adorably ugly, little one.
You should try breastfeeding now, okay?
It'll help stimulate milk production.
Okay.
The first milk that comes out
after giving birth is called colostrum.
It's the best thing for the baby.
I see.
Fun, do you want to hold him?
You're so adorably ugly.
Welcome to the family, Phupha.
We finally get to meet you, Phupha.
He's full now.
-All full and already sleepy?
-Already sleepy.
He's asleep.
-Oon, Oon.
-What's wrong?
I don't know what's happening.
I can't breathe. My chest feels tight.
You can't breathe?
Oon, go get the nurse now.
Hang on.
I'll get the nurse right away.
Oon.
The patient's having trouble breathing.
Can someone come check on her, please?
Yes.
Oon, Fun.
I'm here. I'm right here.
I'm here.
Doctor, the patient in Room 101
is experiencing respiratory distress.
BP 94/62. Heart rate 110.
Oxygen saturation 90 on room air.
Yes, Doctor. Oxygen mask with bag at ten
liters per minute. Transferring to ICU.
Nueng.
-Oon.
-I'm here.
Take care of Phupha for me.
-Nueng.
Nueng!
No pulse. Patient's having cardiac arrest.
Nueng.
-Nueng.
Excuse us.
She'll be fine.
Checking pulse.
No pulse detected.
EKG shows V-fib.
Nueng has to be okay.
Prepare to shock.
Defibrillation, 200 joules.
Shock. Start CPR.
Prepare defibrillation, 200 joules.
Shock.
Are you relatives of Ms. Kanyawee?
Yes.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
The patient passed away
at 3.10 p.m. The cause of death
is suspected to be
amniotic fluid embolism,
which is a severe condition
that progresses very rapidly.
Our medical team did everything we could,
but unfortunately,
we were unable to save her.
Please accept our condolences.
Nueng…
Oon…
It's not true, right?
It's not true, right, Oon?
Oon.
-Mom.
-What happened?
Nueng already gave birth, right?
Nueng…
Nueng's dead, Mom.
Mom. Mom.
Mom.
Can we get some ammonia, please?
Thank you.
If you need anything,
just call for a nurse, okay?
How could this happen?
How did Nueng die?
She…
The doctor said
it was an amniotic fluid embolism, Mom.
Oh, Nueng…
What about the baby? How's the baby?
The baby's safe.
He's in the nursery right now.
Nueng, why was your fate so cruel?
Nueng…
Fun,
we have to stay strong.
We have to do
this one last thing for Nueng.
I'll…
handle the temple arrangements.
Fun, you take care
of the hospital paperwork.
Nueng…
Okay.
We'll do this one last thing for Nueng.
How can I help you?
I wanted to ask…
if I'd like the hospital to care for him
during his mother's funeral,
which department should I contact?
You can report the details here first,
then contact Medical Records afterward.
This way, please.
I'm going to rest now.
Tomorrow, we'll go pick up Phupha.
Fun…
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
What is it?
I want the two of us to raise Phupha.
I feel so attached to him.
We've been with him
since he was still in the womb.
I want to take care of him
and watch him grow up.
Can you do this with me?
I feel the same way.
To me, Phupha is a precious thing…
that Nueng left behind for us.
Thank you.
Oh, my goodness.
-Baby Phupha is here.
-Phupha, sweetheart.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
PHUPHA SRIPITICHOTE
JUNE 5, 2026 - WEIGHT: 2,999 GRAMS
Look at him.
So adorably ugly.
Little Phupha,
come stay with Grandma, okay?
Let's go.
I think I'll stay here
for another couple of days,
then I'll take Phupha back home
with me to Ayutthaya.
Mom.
What?
What are you two doing?
I…
I want to raise Phupha myself.
I want to raise Phupha too.
How are the two of you going to raise him?
This isn't easy, you know.
Raising a newborn is hard.
Both of you work outside the house too.
At night? Forget it.
There's no way you'll get
a full night's sleep,
because babies cry constantly.
And going out together alone?
Going to dinner? Relaxing?
Don't even think about it.
You won't have the chance.
Can you give us a chance
to take care of Phupha?
Please, Mom.
We'll prove to you
that we really can take care of him.
Please, Mom. Please, please.
-Please.
-Can you really do it?
-Please, Mom.
I'll think about it first.
That works.
Here you go, sweetheart, your milk.
Hello, yes.
Oh, sure. I'll send the revised draft
via email right away.
There we go. All clean and dry now.
You're comfortable again.
You can sleep, Mom.
I'll take care of Phupha.
-Can you handle it?
-Yes.
That's right. Hold him.
Let's change your diaper.
Fun.
-Yes?
-Did you clean Phupha's belly button yet?
His belly button…
-Oh, right.
-You have to clean it properly.
Otherwise, it could get infected.
You have to be careful,
or Phupha could get a stomachache.
Here, let me explain.
When the umbilical stump is about
to fall off, you have to be extra careful.
Come on.
There, there.
Sweetheart.
I'm cleaning your little belly button.
Didn't they teach this
in the class you attended?
They did. I just forgot last night.
You didn't get enough sleep, right?
I told you already,
raising a baby is exhausting.
Go get some rest. I'll handle things here.
Hi, Fun.
-Aunt Wi, hello.
-Hello, dear.
How's the little one doing?
He's doing well.
If everything's fine,
why do you look so down?
Aunt Wi, raising a child
really isn't easy at all.
I guess you need experience
to be able to do it properly.
You don't need experience at all.
Otherwise, how would
first-time parents raise their kids?
Look at me.
I raised Pa since she was tiny, since she
was only two months old. Nobody taught me.
I watched videos and read books,
but in the end, the best thing
is to use your heart to raise them.
Trust me.
Aunt Wi, you're amazing.
Is there some kind of fixed rule
when it comes to raising kids?
Absolutely not.
You just follow the child's lead.
If they're hungry, you feed them milk.
After that, you burp them.
If they fart, poop or pee,
you change their diaper.
And if they seem uncomfortable,
you check if they have a fever
or a stomachache or something.
It's not that hard, dear.
You just get to know them more every day.
You'll start understanding their signals.
It's like a kind of body language
that only the two of you understand.
I want to have that kind of bond too.
It'll happen eventually.
You're the one raising the child,
after all,
so the bond will naturally form
on its own.
Honestly, I don't think
raising a child to adulthood is hard.
What's difficult is raising them
to become a good person. Don't you agree?
That's true.
That's probably much harder.
Oh, Fun, after this,
I won't be home very often anymore.
I'll have to travel back and forth
between Bangkok and Ang Thong
because my sister isn't feeling well.
Make sure you lock your doors
and windows properly.
Thank you so much, Aunt Wi.
You stay strong too, okay?
I hope your sister gets better soon.
I should go check on the baby now.
I'll update you if anything happens.
-See you.
-See you. Take care.
See you.
Please receive this blessing.
For those who always
pay respect to their elders,
four blessings shall grow.
Long life, beauty, happiness
and strength. Blessings upon you.
Nueng, I've made merit for you now.
Don't worry about Phupha.
We'll help raise him well.
It's already been 49 days
since Nueng left us.
I think we should start
packing up Nueng's belongings soon.
AIOON AND PAFUN
-Oon.
-Hmm?
Come look at this.
To Aioon and Pafun,
If you two are reading this letter,
then I'm probably no longer in this world.
Originally,
I planned to come back, find work
and build a small family
with just me and Phupha.
But everything fell apart,
completely.
My panic disorder never seemed to improve.
It felt like
it would stay with me forever.
Every time I had an episode,
it made me feel like
there might not be a tomorrow.
I tried to be strong.
I wanted to become
a good mother for Phupha.
If I don't get the chance to do that,
please take care of Phupha for me.
Please take care of him
and tell him you love him
and hug him on my behalf too.
I know both of you love him
just as much as I do.
Thank you
for staying by my side, taking care of me,
understanding me
and encouraging me all this time.
I love you both so much,
Aioon, Pafun.
NUBNUENG
What are you two doing?
It's a letter from Nueng.
Did the baby fall asleep already?
‎Yeah.
Once he was full,
he fell asleep pretty quickly.
Then eat while you can.
If he cries, I'll go check on him.
Oon.
I'm heading home this afternoon.
I already asked Priaw to call me a car.
‎What?
Mom,
can you not go yet? Please don't take
Phupha away. Stay with us a bit longer.
-Please, Mom.
Please, Mom. Give us another chance.
If I do something wrong,
you can scold me. You can even hit me.
Just please don't take Phupha away.
-Please.
-I'm begging you.
Stop.
Did I ever say
I was taking Phupha with me?
I only said I was going home.
-I love you so much, Mom.
-Thank you.
Thank you so much, Mom.
There, the baby's crying.
-I'll go check on him myself.
-I'll go.
-You barely touched your food.
-It's okay.
See?
Having and raising a child isn't easy.
You can't even enjoy a proper meal
or sit peacefully for a while.
I know, Mom.
This is my family,
the family I've always wanted.
No matter what happens,
I'll get through it.
Good. As long as you understand that.
But if it ever becomes too much, tell me.
Thank you, Mom.
Why are you hugging me now?
I'm not even done eating yet.
Let go.
Look at you.
I love you the most, Mom.
Nueng.
What are you looking at?
Oon…
Thank you so much
for taking such good care of both me
and Phupha.
What are you thanking me for?
I already told you,
if there's ever anything, just tell me.
I'll handle it.
No matter what it is--
I'll do it for you.
Thank you so much.
Please take care of my son for me.
Where are you going?
Nueng.
Thank you.
Nueng, Nueng.
Nueng.
-Nueng.
-Oon.
You were so loud. You woke the baby.
I'll go check on him.
Mommy's here now, sweetheart.
I'm gonna change your diaper, okay?
I'm gonna change your diaper.
You'll feel much more comfortable
after this.
It's okay, sweetheart.
Once we change your diaper,
you'll feel all better.
Let me see.
Let me wipe you clean, okay?
Then you'll be comfy again.
Okay.
-Wait a second.
-Okay.
I'm wiping you,
so you'll feel comfortable.
Oon, don't scream.
He hasn't finished peeing yet.
I can stay home with him.
Don't worry.
Are you sure?
Why is your face all messy like this?
What were you two playing with?
Aioon!
I think some things
are just too intense for a child this age.
It hurts here, here
and here too.
You have a headache, right?
Am I a bad mother, Oon?
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon