Sir
Is this your first time here?
Would you like me to introduce
our hosts?
No need
I want him
Sorry, Sir
his time tonight
has already been reserved.
Double the price
No problem. I'll arrange it right away.
Please, have a seat. This way.
Lily
I'm sorry, Miss Sun
Jay's already been booked tonight.
Who dares to take my guy?
Handsome guy here for male companions too?
Come on, Tony
Rourou came to see me first
Who knows what kind of luck you're having,
someone paid double for your whole night.
Double?
Since when
did my face become that valuable?
Miss Sun, I'm truly sorry.
It's fine, since it's a guy,
I won't make a fuss. Go ahead.
But I don't want to
After my shift—
Alright, don't keep the guest waiting.
I'll make it up to you later
Hello, I'm Jay.
and you are?
Hello
David
Hi, David
Miss Sun, I'm really sorry.
Actually, other hosts in our club
are excellent too
Maybe you'd like to try someone else?
Tony, don't worry about me
I'll manage
David
it's your first time here, right?
Come, let's have a drink first.
Ah-Jie
Sorry, it's Jay
J-A-Y
in English
Fine, Jay
Put the drink down
Sit closer
Pan Hao isn't gay, right?
Definitely not
I didn't book you
I know
After all, you're Pan Hao's girlfriend now.
I just came to say hi.
you must've helped a lot of old ladies cross the street
in your past life
your boyfriend
is a billionaire diamond tycoon.
According to my dental appraisal,
the diamonds are real.
Even he knows about Pan Hao's diamonds?
If you don't know
how to spend all that money,
invest in me setting up another Men's Club.
How did you know about the diamonds?
This morning, one of our guys, Ah-Jun,
tried to swipe Pan Hao's diamonds
but got caught red-handed.
Pan Hao kept it from us all this time
without a single hint
Not cool at all.
Hunter, stop slacking off.
you've got a "takeout" order.
Copied that
Hey, friend
Don't forget about me
Someone else is after his diamonds too
What is it?
Did you send someone else to steal the diamonds?
Of course not
But one of Pan Hao's friends
just told me
there's a host named Ah-Jun
who tried to steal his diamonds
and almost succeded
I thought you sent others for the mission
Give the situation
Pan Hao's going to be on high alert
I need a bit more time to handle this
I see
Sun Rourou just called
a guy named Ah-Jun
at the club
was trying to steal Pan Hao's diamonds
Can’t even pull off a simple job—
and got caught
So… you sent the guy?
He owes me a lot of money
and you haven’t made any progress,
I figured more hands would speed things up.
Now, you're saying I'm incompetent
or planning to keep the diamonds yourself?
didn't even give me a heads-up
Come on
I wanted to surprise you
after I got the diamonds
what's with
the temper?
Don't be mad
Hey...
are you okay?
Ah-Jie
Sorry
I'm sorry
I failed to protect you
You did well.
Everything is okay
Sorry
It's okay
I'm sorry
Excuse me
Is Jay not taking good care of you?
would you like to switch?
No—don’t replace him.
He's excellent
Please don’t replace him.
Alright, sorry for the interruption
let me know if you need anything
hey, I'm not going anywhere
why don't you wipe...
your tears first?
Sorry—
I lost my composure.
No worries
If something’s bothering you,
you can tell me.
I can keep you company.
I’m working on a new series
we're looking for a lead actor.
I think you’d be perfect for it.
me?
But I've never acted before.
Don't worry. We have professional acting coaches.
The only issue is
you might need to make a small sacrifice.
Small sacrifice?
I don't think I'm cut out for this.
how would you know
if you don't try?
No
David, No
David No
Not David
No
David  No
David
No
David, No
I know what you're thinking
Not that kind of “casting couch” sacrifice.
We're shooting a BL drama
A lot of actors avoid this genre now.
But I'm straight. I like women.
The character starts out straight too.
But then he falls in love
and gender stops mattering.
Take your time thinking about it.
The series will be filmed in Thailand.
If you're in,
we'll bring the main cast over for training.
next month
Just let us know before the end of the month.
Thailand...
I own a private island
in Thailand
Most of the scenes will be shot there
The environment is amazing
The ocean view is unbeatable
After filming, if you'd like,
you can stay there
as long as you want.
Totally up to you
If I go to Thailand…
Chiang won't be able to find me.
But what about Rourou?
Think it over.
I'll wait for you answer
It's fine, I've got it.
I'll be waiting
Careful, David. steps here
Here
Another one.
There
See you tomorrow
Sure, see you tomorrow.
Bye
Bye, David
You're really not considering Thailand?
Earsdropping on my conversation with a guest?
Trying to steal my client?
Honestly, going to Thailand might be good for you.
you could lay low for a while
If you stay here,
the gang will find you sooner or later.
True
I think so
Staying in the club is like sitting on a time bomb.
One day it might just blow up
and drag you guys down with me.
It's just...
Can't let go of Sun Rourou?
You're barely keeping yourself afloat.
Take care of yourself first.
Also,
there are a lot of scams lately,
you've never acted before,
Why would someone cast you as a lead?
But after thinking it over carefully…
the way David
looked at me…
there's love in his eyes.
Should I book you a neurologist or an eye doctor?
You look handsome to me - What doctor do I need?
Now, you're pretty normal
hey
YuChuan
Can I use your car?
What for?
Don't ask questions now
Just lend it to me first
and cover for me.
Don't let Tony know
I'm sneaking out.
cover what?
Where are you going?
Meeting a friend.
for late night snack
You're going to see Sun Rourou, aren't you?
Seriously?
You're already catching feelings?
Tony, it's my first love,
hard to resist.
First love or not,
it's been years,
how do you know she hasn't changed
that she's still the same person?
Don't let love fool you
Even love loses value over time.
Wake up
Tony
Rourou is really innocent
and she's good to me.
So,
could you cut me some slack?
Let me experience
what love feels like.
Fine. Since you handled
David so well earlier
go ahead.
Yes
Tony
Zhen, your cooking is amazing.
One sip of this chicken soup
warm up my soul
Are you flirting again?
By the way,
that girl who came crying here before—
the club she mentioned got raided
Too bad the mastermind Leo escaped.
That guy is disgusting.
He scammed so many girls
and just walked away.
What a coward.
With things like this,
it takes two
Someone lies, someone chooses to believe
You can't control that.
But...
We can't just do nothing.
Of course not.
But some things
aren't yours to fix.
I've always believed
everything happens for a reason.
So meeting you was fate too?
Can you not use
your work lines on me?
I'm serious.
Speaking of which,
is your compulsive behavioral disorder thing—
getting any better?
Much better than before.
Must be because of you.
You're always here with me.
You're such a smooth talker.
Go shower. I'm going to bed.
So early?
No more chatting?
Go already
Pan Hao
There's something I want to ask you.
What is it? Go ahead.
Are you hiding something from me?
A secret?
No
Besides,
I always tell you what happens with my clients.
Why would you ask?
Yesterday,at the club,
Chang Yihao told me that you're a diamond millionaire.
That bigmouth…
Baby, I wanted to tell you
I just couldn't find
the right time.
If someone suddenly gets that much money,
people would think it's suspicious.
I was afraid you'd think I'm dangerous
that you'd stay away from me.
Is that so?
I thought you were just playing with me
for not telling me.
Of course not.
I've liked you since high school.
I swear to god
My feelings for Sun Rourou
are completely genuine.
may I get hit by a car, if I'm lying
Then I should buy you more accidental insurance
so your death would be worth more.
huh, you only want my money
not me
I'm just teasing you.
So where did the diamonds come from?
I stole them.
You stole them?
No wonder whenever we go out
you're always so covered up.
You should've told me earlier,
I wouldn't have
asked you to meet outside.
I also heard
a host at your club tried to steal them.
There are so many people going in and out,
isn't it dangerous?
Maybe I should buy you a safe
to put in the club.
No...
That's too conspicuous.
Or...
How about this—
the safe we bought,
let's keep it at your place
which would be safer
and proof of how much I love you.
What do you think?
Do you really think that's okay?
What if I sell your diamonds?
I trust you wouldn't do that to me.
baby
One day, if I wanted to take you away from here,
would you come with me?
why?
Planning to hide on a deserted island?
Those diamonds are stolen after all.
I can't hide forever.
I need to find a chance
to lay low somewhere else.
Do you even need to ask?
I've already given myself to you.
Wherever you go, I'll go.
About that safe—
I've already ordered it
which should arrive in a couple of days.
So fast!
Otherwise,
should we wait until they get stolen?
Once they're in the safe,
you won't have to worry all day
for losing it
See? I'm smart.
Fine. You're so smart, we'll do it your way.
So, can I
put you in the safe too?
Why do you want to do that?
I worry you might be stolen by others
I'm leaving with you
and you worry about that?
Of course
Don't worry
You should get to work
you're going to be late
Off to work now - bye
Bye
It's time to talk to David
Ah-Jun
I really don't understand.
Stealing the diamonds should be easy.
How did you mess it up?
Talk
B-Biao…
I almost got it.
But Pan Hao…
he's too cautious.
I didn't realize…
Ow! That hurts!
Ah-Jun
do you realize
what will happen to you
if this traces back to me?
Biao...
I know I messed up!
For real, I do
Give me one more chance!
I know how to fix it!
Seriously
I know how
How?
Let me tell you
this definitely will work
Pan Hao will hand over the diamonds.
Just give me some more time.
Please, Biao
Please...
I'm giving you one last chance.
Very last time
Thank you
Thanks, Biao
Didn't expect you to ask me out.
I wanted to talk about
that BL series you mentioned last night.
I thought about it all night
and had made up my mind.
I want to be a good actor.
I'm going to Thailand.
Whenever you're available to sign the contract
I'm ready anytime.
Wait, really?
Last night you said you weren't suited for it.
What changed?
Because I figured it out.
You did?
By the way…
Can I take my agent with me?
Since when do you have an agent?
Compliments of the boss
I'll let the wine breathe
Enjoy.
David, you have connections everywhere.
I come here a lot.
You were hesitant yesterday
why the sudden change?
I want the truth.
Because I want to leave Taiwan
and develop my career elsewhere.
I hadn't met someone like you—
with such a great opportunity.
Is your girl…
Is your agent going with you too?
How did you know?
I saw her at the club that night.
She's pretty.
Very pretty.
I'm open-minded
I don't care if you're seeing someone.
I like you
that doesn't mean you have to like me back.
David...
I'm a bit traditional about that.
Mainly because of my girlfriend,
she's really a wonderful person.
I finally found her again.
I want to make her happy,
if possible
I don't want to be someone who's unfaithful.
She's a lucky girl.
If she ever treats you badly,
tell me right away.
I'll send her straight back to Taiwan.
6 7 8
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
2 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
3 2 3 4
Boss
5 6 7 8
4 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
Ma, sorry for
calling so suddenly.
There's something
I need to tell you
Go ahead
Are you aware there's a host
worth hundreds of millions working at your club?
Get to the point
Stop beating around the bush
Pan Hao was part of our gang member
Last month we had a deal with  F.T. Crew
Things went sideways.
He's the only survivor
and he stole their diamonds.
So?
Ma...
you know our gang rules.
Normally I'd handle this myself
but due to the rules…
you'll have to take care of it.
You're forcing this job on me.
I didn't set the rules,
yet I have to clean up your mess?
Come on
I'm asking your help to solve this problem.
Pan Hao works for you now
wouldn't it be easier if you handle it?
Let me think about it.
He's here at the club
no need to worry he'd run away.
Thanks for your help in advance
Even though it's been less than a week
since Zhou Qin set the sales target,
we've already hit it!
To thank everyone for the hard work
I brought you all here
to hand out bonuses.
Chang Yihao, top sales.
Here!
Good job.
adding 10% on the bonus
Tony, if you make it 20%
I'll work even harder.
Lee Xun
You can't drink,
but you did alright.
Here's yours.
Thanks, Tony
Yu Chuan…
Even though you're part of the family
your sales dropped this week.
That won't do.
You should save up some money.
Got it
Thanks, Tony
You two will start officially next month
Learn as many tricks from them this month
Thanks, Tony
Next..
Pan Hao
Tony, I'm sorry.
I can only stay until the end of the month.
What do you mean?
You're really going to acting business?
Yeah.
Ma, Tony,
Sorry
Tonight,
I mainly want to tell you
I'm leaving the club soon
Thank you for taking care of me.
Is it solid with David?
Is everything settled?
We're finalizing the details.
It's fine.
Didn't the news report recently
people being tricked into acting jobs in Thailand
and once they landed
they were taken to scam compounds?
Be careful.
Acting is good
but check their background carefully
to make sure the production is legit.
I did
David's really famous in Thailand.  It's solid.
If you've got a better opportunity,
we won't stop you.
But...
when you become successful,
bring more customers to the club.
You bet!
Will your girlfriend go with you?
Pan Hao
If you become a big star,
don't forget us.
Give us a hand too.
OK
Bonuses are done.
Back to work
Pan Hao, even if you're leaving,
do your job while you're here.
You still have to work hard
Yes sir!
all right
let's get it
ACE
A day's work for a day's pay.
Yu Chuan
These guys of yours here…
do you really know their backgrounds?
Well...
I don't even fully know
my own uncle's background.
What is it?
Chiang knows Pan Hao is hiding here.
Are you sure?
Yes
He called Ma Cheng-en this afternoon
and told him to deal with it.
Got it.
You can go.
Come in
Sorry for the wait.
Come
Hurry up
Chop-chop
Greet
Hello, beautiful
Jessica
These are our staff
No need to introduce them.
How are their figures?
Good
I'll take this one,
this one, this one and this one
plus the ones I picked earlier.
Bring them to the main hall
I'm going party tonight.
Yes
All right, let's get moving!
Jessica
has booked the whole place tonight.
Give it your best,
serve her well.
Just dodge the drinks as usual, okay?
Come on, let's drink
It's been a while…
I'll come back for you later.
Hey...
Come on, have a drink.
Thanks everyone for coming.
Just have a little,
it'll help you relax.
I'm not much of a drinker.
Then I'll get you some orange juice.
Thank you.
Orange juice, please.
Here you go.
Thanks
Come on, keep me company
Let's go.
Hey, Wei
Jessica
Come, have a seat.
Daniel, come here.
Have fun.
It's okay.
You look hot…
Let me take your jacket off.
Take a deep breath.
Come on
Let me help you.
Careful now.