Never thought
I'd run into my perfect type here.
And those arms ... the solid muscles
Miss Liao
Come
Let's have a drink first
Such firm chest...
Miss Liao
let me explain first—
The contract I signed with the club
only covers drinking and chatting
So if you're looking for other services,
I can find you another host.
Oh, come on
You're my type of guy
Why not reconsider?
I can tip you extra.
It's not about the money.
Ow, that hurts!
Ow… that hurts…
That really hurts!
Sorry, I'll drink as a penalty.
Ouch, that really hurts.
But it actually feels good.
So you like playing rough?
What a coincidence, I like it too.
No, Miss Liao—
Waiter, champagne!
Miss Liao, let me explain—
Come on
Miss Liao—
Cheers, everyone
It's been a while…
I'll come back for you later.
Okay.
Hey...
Cheers… Thanks for coming
Just have a little,
it'll help you relax.
I'm not much of a drinker.
Then I'll get you some orange juice.
Thank you
Orange juice, please.
Here you go
Thanks
Let's go, keep me company
Hey
Hi
Cheers
Have some more, let's chat later
Wei
Jessica
Come over and sit
Your parties keep getting better and better.
So your style…
Thank you
And this is…
Daniel, a host here at the club. Nice to meet you.
Daniel
Daniel, come
Sit
Have fun
Okay, thanks.
Are you nervous?
No
It's okay, relax.
Here, wanna smoke?
No, thanks
Have some fruit
Here
No, thanks
Shh…
It's okay.
You look hot…
Let me take off your jacket.
Take a deep breath.
Relax
It's okay
I'll give you a massage
Where are you going?
Do you want to lie down?
You should lie down.
Come on
lie down.
Go get Tony
It's okay.
Excuse me
It's fine, go do something else.
I'll give you a massage.
Breathe.
Relax, take a deep breath.
I'll help you relax.
It's okay.
Is your belt too tight?
Youth is wonderful
Give me your hands
Leave it to me.
Don't be nervous.
Relax
Tony
I didn't get picked
and the main hall got booked
A hero with nowhere to shine,
can I go practice with Rou-rou?
Practice what?
Aren't you leaving at the end of the month?
Once you're gone
then you'll really have nowhere to shine.
Come on, please.
Alright, go.
Stop annoying me.
Tony, you're the best!
I  love you
Good thing I didn't return the car key this morning.
Rou-rou baby, I'm coming!
Excuse me
Another one passed out drunk.
Tony, something's wrong!
Just now in the main hall
Lee Xun was forced down on the couch
and they even started unbuttoning his shirt.
He completely lost it?
Go notify Ma
I'll go first in case things get worse.
Okay
What the hell happened?
Asa
What are you doing?!
Stop it right now!
Watch out!
Yuchuan!
Call an ambulance!
Hurry up
Yuchuan!
Hurry
Didn't expect safes these days
to be made this elegantly.
I wouldn't even know it's a safe
if you hadn't told me
Looks like our diamond babies
can rest comfortably inside
and we can relax too.
We don't have to worry anymore.
You're so clever.
Of course.
Hey, do you remember last time at the club
that handsome guy who picked me,the handsome guy?
His name is David who is a director.
He wants me to go to Thailand to film a BL series.
I want to take you with me.
Is he certain you’ve got what it takes to act?
I'm not quite sure either
But since someone believes in me that much,
for our diamond babies
and our future,
I think it's worth giving it a shot.
Does he know about the diamonds?
Of course not.
That's good then
At least he’s not trying to trick you out of the diamonds
by asking you to act.
I doubt it.
David seems pretty sincere to me
The way he looks at me…
it's full of love.
Then maybe I should keep a closer eye on you
so you don’t get swayed by his “love.”
Don't worry
I'm a straight guy through and through.
Besides,
You're the only one I love
What are you up to?
Andy, what happened?
I just walked out of the VIP room,
the main hall looked like hell broke loose.
Among tonight’s guests,
someone had bad intentions toward Lee Xun.
Looks like he's drugged.
What kind of trash does that?
Drugging someone just because they couldn’t get him.
No wonder Yuchuan went crazy.
By the way, how’s Yuchuan?
Is he hurt badly?
I'm not sure
But Tony and Ma took him to the hospital themselves.
He should be okay.
Thanks for taking care of Lee Xun.
I'll go help clean up the main hall now.
Alright, leave it to me here.
Go ahead.
Careful. Watch your step.
Yuchuan.
Sit down first.
Are you okay?
You're badly hurt.
Yuchuan, get some rest.
Let's step outside.
Let them talk.
Why were you so reckless?
What if something had happened?
You're a grown up man
Why don't you know how to protect yourself?
Don't drink anything given by others,
Even a three-year-old knows that.
How could you be so careless?
If I had been a moment later…
Do you know how bad it could've been?
If something had happened to you
I'd blame myself.
How would I face your parents?
If you just worried about explaining to my parents
you didn’t have to risk yourself like that.
You think I fought that hard
just so I could explain to your parents?
Isn't that so?
Next time, don't be so reckless.
You're all I have got
I can't lose you.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
I'll always be here.
Don't worry.
Lee Xun is with him.
Let the two of them
get some rest for the next couple days.
I never expected
Yuchuan would get hurt at my place.
Don't blame yourself.
You can't protect him forever.
He's grown up.
He needs to learn to rely on himself.
By the way…
Chao De-chiang called,
he said Pan Hao stole his diamonds.
Pan Hao?
Does he look like someone
who'd dare steal diamonds?
Do you think
I should help him handle Pan Hao?
Of course not.
How is that our problem?
That's the ADS's business.
They should handle it themselves.
You should know their gan rules
stop them from touching anyone from the club.
Then it really isn't our problem.
We didn't make their rules.
Chao De-chiang can figure it out himself.
Still...
Yuchuan should probably know about this.
After all, he brought Pan Hao here.
If he doesn't know his background
there could be more troubles later.
Yuchuan,
these guys you brought to the club
do you really know their backgrounds?
Well...
I don't even fully know
my own uncle's background.
5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4
2 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
Boss Chiang, you wanted to see me?
3 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
What are you doing?
I told you to deal with Lee Xun and Pan Hao.
Not only did you fail
you forced them to hide in the club.
Ah-Biao…
Now...
how are you going to explain this?
Talk
Every single one of you is useless.
Who was it
making you angry so early?
I'll be heartbroken
if you ruin the health from anger
Get out.
Don't be mad.
I made soup for you.
Have some to nourish yourself.
I'm fine
Take a look
Go ahead and sign it, if everything looks good,
Okay
Where’s your agent?
Shouldn’t she be here to review this with you?
She’s still at work.
Hey...
Do you really want to go to Thailand?
So… when are we leaving?
I’m flying to Thailand tomorrow for pre-production.
I’ll bring you guys over for training
around the middle of next month…
We’ll start filming two months after that.
So we have to wait until next month?
Are you in a hurry?
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
You suddenly changed your mind…
Is it because of your girlfriend?
If so, I should take her out for dinner
to thank her properly
Of course not.
This is my own decision.
Sorry, I need to take this call.
Can I ask you a question?
Why does David
want me for this role so badly?
You look a lot like his ex-boyfriend.
Not just a little…
We look identical
Then why did they break up?
They didn’t break up.
His boyfriend had a car accident last year
and passed away.
They were supposed to go camping that day.
But David got stuck with work.
His boyfriend got upset and went alone,
the accident happened on the way.
The script
was originally written for him.
After the accident,
the whole project stopped.
So restarting it now…
wouldn't that bring back his painful memories?
He’s stronger than you think.
Yes,
you remind him of his boyfriend.
But maybe this is also his way of saying goodbye.
Everything okay?
I’ve got another meeting shortly
No problem.
Looking forward to working together.
Likewise.
David, thank you.
What’s this?
Getting all sentimental now?
Aren’t you flying to Thailand tomorrow?
Safe travels.
See you there.
Alright,
I’ll be waiting…
See you in Thailand.
An exclusive contract
That scared the hell out of me.
What's wrong with you?
So... you finally decided to come back.
No,
I mean what happened to his head?
Lee Xun got drugged
at the party last night.
Yu-chuan got there in time
and knocked that creep out.
But one of that creep's friends
Clang!
smashed a bottle
over his head.
That’s how he ended up like this.
Luckily Tony and Ma
got him to the hospital.
Otherwise…
Anyway, it's how he looks like this now
I’m gone for just one night…
and missed all the actions?
Sounds like…
you're disappointed you missed it
on site
or are you glad you didn’t get dragged into it?
Hey… that’s not what I meant, Yuchuan
But those guys from last night…
they probably weren’t connected to ADS?
I don’t think so.
I didn’t see any of their Gang tattoos.
I got something!
Now we just need the key evidence from the accounts.
Once we get that…
We can report Chao De-chiang right away.
Alright, when I go to Ah-Zhen's place next time…
I’ll keep an eye out for you guys.
If Chiang really goes down…
Does that mean I won’t have to run anymore?
Wait…
Even if the ADS is gone…
there’s still the F.T. Crew
You said you just signed the contract?
Oh right.
I’m flying to Thailand to start training
around the middle or end of next month.
Speaking of which…
Didn’t we catch that guy Ah-Jun …
stealing your diamonds?
He just disappeared.
What happened to those diamonds?
You should really be careful.
You might end up losing both the girl and the money.
Hey,
money aside…
Why would I lose the girl too?
Bro...
What girl
would stay with her boyfriend who
goes from billionaire to be broke overnight?
Story like that
only happens in novels.
I believe Rourou would.
That's okay
You've still got David.
That's right
If Rourou leaves,
I still have David.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm telling you
Guys,
are definitely not my thing.
What’s wrong with guys?
Why not?
These are the profiles of our companions
Judging from how she’s dressed…
She’ll probably pick Jay or Justin.
With that taste, I bet she’ll go for Jay, the bad-boy type.
Welcome to A.C.E.
May I introduce our hosts to you?
This one.
Sure,  I’ll arrange right away.
Go inform Jay.
Don’t keep the guest waiting.
Got it.
Without Yuchuan and Lee Xun…
how many customers do I have to cover tonight?
I’m already seeing double.
Chenghan
I miss you so much.
Miss Hsu Chenghan?
Want him to come scare your customers away?
I’m going to die
If I keep drinking
I don't want to drink anymore
How much did you drink?
Just three bottles?
Three bottles of whisky!
And you’re still alive?
Jay
you’ve got a client.
Again?
Lily, are you trying to kill me?
Tony said
she’s a big spender.
So hurry up.
A rich client?
Lucky you.
Yihao
We can go to Tony if you want this client
Let's switch, okay?
Please…
nuh… you go ahead.
I can't drink as much as you do
You go
Go make some money!
Let's go
Where did this old lady come from...
roaming around this late disturbing people?
Call Chenghan to rescue me.
Sure, no problem.
If you break the sales record tonight,
I’ll pop champagne for you.
What is it?
I need you to catch someone
alive.
Alive?
No can do.
I’m not interested in live targets.
Wait...
I’ll pay a 500 deposit right now.
the remaining 1,000 will be transferred once it’s done.
Yu…
Money doesn't matter,
either 500 or 1000...
The point is, I only take jobs that interest me.
At that place…
There’s someone you’ll be interested in.
Who is it?
The elder
Hey, look—buy one get one free!
What is it?
Drinks
You want one?
I can’t drink that yet.
Soon, though.
I’ll get it for you once you’re discharged.
Okay… but that’s still a long way to go
Look at this.
It looks so delicious
Such a good deal too.
Buy five, get two free.
Why is there a "buy four get four free"?
No idea… maybe because it’s Children’s Day.
I went to the club looking for you several times
but you were never there.
I had to nag Tony for ages…
before he finally told me you're here.
Is something wrong for
you to look for me so urgently?
I really like you.
You saw it yourself
I have a sister who needs me,
the only thing I can do is to make more money
to cover her medical bills
and to take care of her.
I really..
can't afford taking care of another person
I'm sorry.
Who said I wanted you to carry the burden?
I really like you.
I’m not asking you to take care of me.
I ask for nothing
If you’re willing…
Shall we give it a try?
What are you looking at now?
Where’s that lady from earlier?
Where did she go?
She left. Why?
I actually wanted to ask her to take you away.
Why?
Hsu Xiaoxi, I’ve treated you so well…
and you want to push me away?
No, that’s not it.
It’s because you’re too good to me.
I don’t want to keep being a burden to you.
What are you talking about?
You’re my sister
and you’ve never been a burden to me.
Hey,
I already have a healthy heart.
I’m recovering bit by bit.
You don’t have to live your life
around me anymore.
So you can go pursue…
your own happiness.
What about that lady makes you think…
that I'd be happy with her?
The way she looks at you…
I can tell she's really into you.
How would you know?
I just do
I can feel it.
With such a high fever and still say you’re fine.
You must have been overloaded lately.
Your body finally gave out.
Here, take the med.
I'm okay…
just need some sleep.
Then get some rest.
Call me if you need anything.
Zhen,
make sure you eat properly while you’re sick.
All the food on the table
I prepared for you
and the chicken soup in the pot
that took me all afternoon….
Make sure you finish it.
I’m heading back to the club for work.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll come over right away
And really—finish it.
Thank you.
Drink as much as you like. Have fun.
Let me know if you need anything.
Enjoy yourselves.
Welcome to A.C.E.
Is this your first time here?
Would you like me to introduce our hosts?
I want him.
VIP room.
I’ll arrange it right away.
Lily
Get Room A ready
Right this way.
Pan Hao.
Ma? What are you doing here?
The lady inside is a very important guest of mine.
Since you’re the one serving her…
you should give her the best.
Go find Tony.
Bring the best bottle in the house.
Yes
Go
Shouldn’t you be entertaining your guest?
Ma asked me to grab a bottle of wine
He said the one who picked me is his VIP guest.
VIP guest?
He even told me to go to the wine cellar…
and bring the best one for her.
Miss,
I suggest you don’t cause trouble in my place.
Otherwise...
It's really you
The elder.
I have no idea what you’re talking about.
All these years…
every piece of information I could find about you…
I’ve studied it hundreds of times.
No one’s ever captured your face on camera…
But your fighting style…
I’d recognize it anywhere.
You’ve got the wrong person.
I’ve been an assassin for five years…
waiting for you to return.
Today, I finally found you.
Who sent you?
What do you want?
That’s not important.
What matters is…
Nothing in this world…
is more thrilling than destroying someone
you once worshiped in person.
You think you can do that?
Try and find out