[Third Stem Room]
Master.
We gave the business between Talhan
and the Central Plains
to Boss Lin.
Only then did she agree
to let us run her restaurant.
Do you think it's worth it?
It doesn't matter.
In this way,
with these restaurants,
we can be said to
have our own territory in the capital.
When it comes to sending
messages in the future,
it will also be more convenient.
By the way,
did Boss Lin bring any news
when she came back this time?
The fourth prince who was previously
sent to the Northern Frontier
was assassinated some time ago.
Although he didn't die,
it seems that his legs were left disabled.
I remember that two years ago,
the third prince
was also poisoned by miasma in his fief.
If it were only the third prince,
it could be said that he was unlucky.
But the fourth prince
also ended up like this just
one year after going to his fief.
It seems like,
it's all Yin Zhou's doing.
Yin Zhou is truly ruthless.
These third and fourth princes
are his own younger brothers.
A Qi
is in danger.
Wenjie,
arrange a meeting with Boss Lin
for me as soon as possible.
The sooner, the better.
Yes, Master.
Come in.
This must be Boss Lin.
I'm Pei Yanzhi, a junior.
I've long admired your reputation, senior.
Pei Yanzhi.
As far as I know,
your name is Feng Sun, isn't it?
Indeed, nothing can be
hidden from you, senior.
Let's get straight to the point.
So,
what do you want from me?
You're indeed a
straightforward person, senior.
Then I'll be direct.
I'll help you make money, senior.
But at the same time,
I need you
to help me train a group of death warriors.
You're from Talhan.
Why should I trust you
that you won't use me against Daxing?
Because I need this group of death warriors
just to protect someone.
Yanzhi,
you're a good child.
I know this request is a bit excessive,
but as a mother,
I must arrange things
properly for my two children
before I can rest easy.
I left Granny Su with Heshu,
and I feel somewhat at ease.
But Qi'er is different.
He's a prince.
The slightest mishap
could cost him his life.
Don't worry, Imperial Concubine Chen.
No matter what situation we're in,
I will protect the Fifth Prince.
For the rest of my life,
I will never go back on
my promise.
"Journey With You"
(Episode 6)
Yanzhi,
I will definitely change
our fate.
This time,
no one can stop us from being together.
What's wrong?
Has your wound opened again?
It's not the wound that hurts.
Yanzhi,
this time,
we can be together
without any reservations, right?
It's just that
we still have to put on
a big show for Yin Zhou.
If you were to join a theater troupe,
you would definitely be
a master at acting.
Your Royal Highness, the Crown Prince,
is unwilling to go to the
banquet at Yanbo Tower.
Why is he putting on such airs today?
What does this mean?
I don't trust your good nephew.
The Khan's intentions
are also beyond my comprehension.
Since that's the case,
I won't beat around the bush.
Nowadays, the Fifth
Prince is in the limelight.
What do you plan to do?
What do you need me to do?
I don't understand what
the Khan means by this.
I want to get to know the Khan
because the Khan is a hero.
But in the Khan's words,
I've become a scheming person
eager to use the Khan's power.
We all know what's going on.
There's no need to hide it.
With my full support,
soon,
you will go from being the Crown Prince
to the Crown Prince Consort.
These past few days,
my fifth brother has been very restless.
He's been gathering troops everywhere,
attempting to rebel.
I wonder if the Khan
would be willing to give
me a group of troops
to accompany me to protect
my father, the Emperor,
and come to the Emperor's aid.
Hiya!
Now I finally understand your plan.
You deliberately let Yin
Zhou and Su He join forces.
When their ambitions are exposed,
you can kill two birds with one stone,
using my father to eliminate them.
But Yanzhi,
your plan has failed.
They even deceived you.
A Qi,
why are you so sure?
Yanzhi...
Do you trust me?
Of course I trust you.
Since Concubine Chen's death,
you've been like a different person.
You can see through everything I do.
You ask me
why I'm so sure you'll fail.
Because
we've already died once.
In my previous life, I went to the border.
You carried out your plan.
In three years,
Yin Zhou and Su He planned everything.
They made me believe
that you were a spy sent by Talhan.
They plotted to make me
return to the Central Plains.
I mistakenly thought you had killed my
father, the Emperor. So I turned against you.
That battle was extremely fierce.
In the end, we both died
under Yin Zhou's sword.
When I woke up again,
I had returned three years in the past,
the day before my mother's death.
A Qi,
if you want to persuade me to give up,
there's no need to
make up such a bizarre story to deceive me.
I know it's hard to believe,
but it's true.
Let me ask you,
Su He,
does the left cheek of his confidant
have a scar?
In my previous life,
during the battle at the imperial villa,
I saw him.
Pei Yanzhi, you traitor!
A Qi,
You're delirious from illness.
Your son has a request to
seek the Emperor's approval.
Before Mother passed away,
Heshu, shut up!
A Qi,
What on earth are you trying to do, A Qi?
Rather than let you go
down an irreversible path,
it's better to
keep you in Yunhe Palace all the time.
No wonder
you planned everything so early on,
how to send Concubine
Chen back to Jiangnan,
and also planned
how to make the Emperor
keep you in the palace,
and even gradually
gain the Emperor's trust.
So,
the rumors in the palace
about you becoming the Crown Prince
were also spread by you yourself.
You wanted to alarm Yin Zhou.
Yanzhi,
Don't you understand yet?
To deal with them,
relying solely on you won't work,
nor will relying solely on me.
We must unite to have a chance of winning.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
But
why was it only you that was reborn?
I think it's because of this.
Before I died,
I was clutching this
wolf's tooth in my hand.
So,
what the White-Eyed Wolf King
told me in my dream was all true.
Yanzhi, stop!
Why won't you let me touch
your wolf's tooth pendant?
This is a token that the White-Eyed
Wolf King asked me to give to my beloved.
It can bless the two lovers
to be together for all eternity.
How is that possible?
Do you remember
when I first arrived at the Daxing palace,
the people in the palace
all said I was a barbarian
from the grasslands
because I had killed the
White-Eyed Wolf King,
and took the opportunity to bully me.
Actually, I didn't kill the Wolf King.
On the contrary, I once saved him
and treated his wounds.
Then one day,
he placed this wolf's tooth beside me.
That night, he told me in a dream
What?
He said he was the messenger
of the God of Longevity,
and in gratitude for saving his life,
he asked me to wear this wolf's tooth,
and when one day in the future
I met the person I loved,
it would bless us
to be destined lovers for all eternity.
Yes,
everything the White-Eyed
Wolf King said was true.
You ask me why I always interfere with you.
Even though I know the
outcome will be so tragic,
shouldn't I try to stop it?
A Qi,
You've told me everything
that happened in your previous life.
We can take the initiative.
In this life,
I will definitely save you.
It's us.
We must both survive.
Now, the Crown Prince
thinks we've completely split up.
Why don't we
play along with his plan
and make him think
that I've lost your support,
making him let down his guard
and reveal his true colors?
You've worked hard.
Your Highness.
I met with my uncle at Yanbo Tower.
He was eager to help Your Highness.
But for some reason,
Your Highness suddenly
broke the appointment.
It seems
that Your Highness doesn't
want to ally with my uncle.
Your uncle wants to help me,
of course, he wants to
gain something from me.
Since that's the case,
I naturally have to consider it carefully.
I came to tell Your Highness
that my uncle will soon leave Jiangnan.
Your Highness can take
your time to consider.
Wait.
You and Yin Qi
have become estranged so quickly?
From the moment I decided
to work for Your Highness
and win over my uncle,
A Qi and I
were destined to go our separate ways.
To save Yin Qi's life,
making you turn against each other,
Pei Yanzhi, Pei Yanzhi,
even I
can't help but feel sorry for you.
Your Highness,
Su He has assembled a
team of grassland warriors
for your disposal.
They have secretly entered the city today.
I've had them hide in the south of the city
to avoid drawing attention.
I know exactly how many
troops are in the imperial villa.
With Su He's men,
victory is within my grasp.
After all, Su He is a foreigner.
Can he be trusted?
Su He and Pei Yanzhi are
cut from the same cloth.
He won't miss out
on anything profitable.
Moreover,
he understands better than anyone
that once he's on my boat,
if he gives up halfway,
I won't spare him.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
You'll soon get what you want.
What did you feed me?
To make me believe you,
you naturally have to show
a willingness to be used by me.
Don't worry,
this poison won't cause you much pain.
As long as you come for
the antidote every month,
I'll ensure your safety.
Every time I see your eyes,
I can't help but want to gouge them out.
Your Highness is joking.
If I didn't have eyes,
how could I work for Your Highness?
Don't think that I really believe
the words of a foreigner like you.
If you want to live and
protect your Fifth Prince,
you'd better obey me obediently.
If you dare to betray me,
I'll make you know
what it means
to be torn apart.
This poison is really strange.
I can't expel it even
with my internal strength.
I can only delay its onset.
Yanzhi.
Didn't I tell you to be careful recently?
Why are you looking for me again?
I've been very careful.
No one has noticed.
Don't worry.
Come to think of it,
we haven't taken a bath
together for many years.
The last time was during the autumn hunt,
when we bathed in the river together, no?
In my memory,
I guarded the border alone for three years.
At that time,
didn't I stop you?
We had a big fight over it.
For three years,
neither of us was willing to give in.
Even through letters, we didn't
even want to hear about each other.
But all that is in the past.
You don't have to feel sorry for me.
I'm fine now, aren't I?
You are fine.
Even though you are
three years older than me.
What?
Don't you believe it?
I do.
I just think
being alone at the border for three years,
it must not have been easy.
Recently, I suddenly found
that for some unknown reason,
there's a red mark on my chest.
It's in exactly the same spot.
In our past life,
it was right here
that we were shot by arrows.
So it was here.
We've changed so many things.
We will definitely survive this life.
Yanzhi.
We won't let go of
each other's hands again
Right?
Although I don't have memories
of those three years in our past life,
but whether it was me in the past life
or me in this life,
my feelings for you
have never changed.
I came back to this life
just to make sure we survive
and stay together.
Survive.
What's wrong?
Are you cold?
A Qi.
I may only be able to accompany you
for a little while longer.
You have to live well for me.
Live as
the free and fearless Yin Qi.
In my humble opinion,
when Su He comes to Jiangnan this time,
he will definitely try his
best to meet with Yin Zhou.
Given his personality,
if there's something to gain,
he won't give up easily.
Has Yin Zhou made any moves recently?
He's been very quiet lately.
He's been accompanying
the emperor on trips.
And in his free time,
he stays in his palace.
But in my opinion,
his calmness
must mean he's planning something.
Your uncle hasn't left Jiangnan City.
He's also sent a group of
grassland warriors to Jiangnan.
They're hiding in the
southern part of the city.
I don't know
what he's up to.
According to what A Qi said,
Yin Zhou and Su He will
rebel together in three years.
Now, because of Yin
Qi's presence as a variable,
are they planning to
move up their schedule?
Senior,
I have a favor to ask.
As long as you don't tear
down my Jiangnan City,
just ask.
I'm afraid
it's not me
who wants to tear down Jiangnan City,
but Su He and Yin Zhou.
Although Yin Zhou is ruthless,
rebelling is a serious crime.
Does he really have the guts?
Now, Yin Zhou's position is delicate.
In the court,
he and the imperial uncle have
gradually lost the emperor's trust.
The queen is also not
favored in the palace.
If it weren't for Su He,
he might still be hesitating.
But now,
with Su He's full support,
it's very likely he'll take the plunge.
Given this,
it's indeed a good opportunity
for him to rebel now.
What do you need me to do?
Just tell me.
Why do I keep running into you everywhere?
The person I'm looking for today
is your boss.
Where is your boss?
My boss of Yanbo Tower
isn't someone you can
just see whenever you want.
To see her,
you have to tell me your name first.
I have important business with her.
How much silver do you want?
I'll give it to you.
Just tell her
that
I have business to discuss with her.
My Lin family of Jiangnan
wouldn't lack your little business.
I'm not going to waste my breath with you.
I'll go in and find her myself.
Brother Yanzhi.
Please help me speak up.
I want to go in and see the boss.
Excuse me.
Come back with me quickly.
Don't let your brother worry.
I'm not going back.
I want to know about my
mother.
Who in this huge Jiangnan City knows me?
I'll just stroll out confidently.
What danger could I possibly encounter?
Aunt.
There have been many
foreigners on the streets recently.
Could they be targeting them?
Heshu, slow down.
Good nephew.
Don't be in such a hurry to leave.
Stop eating and let's go.
Uncle.
What is the meaning of this?
I heard your elder brother
gave you the military talisman.
Such an important item
might not be safe with a hostage.
Why not let your uncle keep it for you?
Su He.
Your treacherous ambitions
can no longer be hidden.
Such an important military talisman
how could it be entrusted to you?
It's not your turn to speak.
Fengsun.
Out of consideration for our
uncle-nephew relationship,
today,
if you hand over the
military talisman obediently,
I, the Khan,
can spare your life.
If you
remain obstinate,
then don't blame your uncle
for turning my back on you.
Uncle once promised Father Khan
to send your own son
to Daxing as a hostage.
A few days ago, you also tricked me
by saying you wanted to return to Talhan.
It seems Uncle is even more fickle
than the Central Plains people.
You...
I knew it.
All along,
your humble demeanor
was just an act.
Today,
I'll tell you the truth.
For the past ten years,
I've wanted to kill you every moment
to eliminate future troubles.
Today,
I finally have the
chance to take your life.
Attack!
Wait!
You, guest,
this is Jiangnan territory.
If you really smash my Yanbo Tower,
I'm afraid you can't afford to compensate.
You, the boss lady,
have quite a big mouth.
It's just a tavern.
Do you think our Khan
is afraid of you?
We have a saying in the Central Plains,
"Even a mighty dragon
doesn't bully the local snake."
Although I'm just a woman,
in Jiangnan,
no one dares to disrespect Lin Jianshuang.
Lin Jianshuang.
What's your relationship
with the Lin family of Jiangnan?
The head of the Lin family
of Jiangnan is my aunt.
Khan.
Your subordinate didn't know
she was Boss Lin.
Fengsun.
You can hide for a while,
but not forever.
What belongs to me, the Khan,
I will take it back
sooner or later.
Let's go.
A Qi.
Why are you here?
The senior sent someone to fetch me.
I just found out
that Su He, in broad daylight,
actually fought with you in the city.
Are you
hurt?
Sit down and talk.
Today,
thank you, senior, for
saving my sister and Yanzhi.
I didn't expect
Yanzhi has such a connection with you.
However,
please forgive my boldness,
may I ask who you really are?
My aunt kindly saved your sister,
Not only do you fail to appreciate her,
yet you question her like this.
Do you think it's appropriate?
Although Brother Yanzhi trusts you,
we should still ask clearly
what your intentions are.
You...
May I ask, senior,
do you know my mother?
My mother
is the Imperial Concubine Chen.
The most beautiful woman in Jiangnan
you mentioned the other day
is her.
This handkerchief...
It's...
That's right.
Your mother
was my dear friend in my youth.
Back then, she
wasn't called Concubine Chen.
She was called
Su Tang'er.
Tang'er.
I stitched this myself.
For you.
You stitched it so beautifully.
I didn't expect you, who's
busy with business every day,
to have such skills.
By the way,
It seems Miss Liu from
West Street is getting married.
I wonder what kind of person
you'll marry in the future.
After marriage, you have to
take care of your husband and children.
I don't want to get married.
I want to be a female
warrior in the future.
Being a female warrior is great.
My father found me a master
to teach me martial arts.
After I learn it,
I'll teach you.
Okay, then teach me now.
Come on.
Look, your hair is all messy.
Okay.
Back then, Tang'er
So ticklish!
She was the happiest and most
carefree person in the world.
Slow down.
I thought we
would be best friends forever.
Until that day.
If we're talking about the
most scenic place in Daxing,
Jiangnan with its misty rain tops the list.
Although Jiangnan City is small,
it's quite exquisite.
Although the capital is prosperous,
you can't see the scenery of
small bridges and flowing water.
It's all thanks to His Majesty's wisdom
and capable governance
that the people of Jiangnan can
live in peace and prosperity.
Tang'er.
Take care of yourself in the future.
Not long after,
news came that she was to
enter the palace as a concubine.
I knew in her heart,
she was actually unwilling.
But how could she possibly
make decisions based
solely on her own wishes?
From that day on,
we were separated by a great distance,
and never heard from each other again.
I used to be with my mother day and night,
yet I never knew
what my mother was like
before she entered the palace.
No wonder
before she left,
she yearned to return to Jiangnan.
If only my mother had
never entered the palace.
She would surely
be very happy now.
My aunt never revealed
her identity to you before
firstly, because she was afraid the
emperor would be suspicious,
and secondly, to prevent
any unexpected problems.
Actually, all along the way,
we've been
secretly protecting you and your sister.
I didn't expect
that you and our mother
had such a connection.
After Tang'er entered the palace,
I tried every means to
find out how she was doing.
I heard
she was very favored
and even became a beloved concubine.
Then I was relieved.
But
too many people knew about her past,
which might not have good for her.
Fate is truly cruel.
For so many years,
I've always wanted to see her again.
Who would have thought
she would pass away at such
a young age and leave us...?
I'm so foolish.
With her personality,
the palace was a prison to her.
She was confined for so many years.
Now,
she's finally free.
When I first saw you,
I knew you were Tang'er's children.
That day at Yanbo Tower,
I really wanted to see Tang'er's children,
so I approached your father.
Aunt Lin.
Actually, mother
for all these years,
has been thinking of you too.
Really.
Mother always treasured her handkerchief
as if it were a precious gem.
Before she left, she even told my brother
to take good care of it.
We just never knew
what this handkerchief represented.
So mother
was once so helpless.
I must not let such a tragedy
happen again to Yanzhi and me.
Today,
Su He acted on his own to
seize my military talisman,
exposing his identity
without telling Yin Zhou.
I think...
He must have other intentions.
You mean
Su He's ambition is not
just to unify the grasslands...?
He dares to turn against me at this time,
which means
He intends to make all of us
die in Jiangnan City.
He's just dreaming.
As long as I'm here in
Jiangnan for one day,
this Jiangnan City
will not allow him to stir up trouble.
Senior,
Nowadays,
none of us knows
when Yin Zhou will make a move.
We need to be fully prepared.
The imperial guards
at the imperial palace
A Qi has already assigned personnel.
The imperial palace is
of utmost importance.
It must be well arranged to let
trustworthy people protect the Emperor.
I secretly transferred a troop
from Talhan
to Jiangnan this time.
Plus the death squads
you've trained for me, senior,
Yin Zhou may not have a winning chance.
I'm afraid that
Su He has some other tricks up his sleeve.
Leave Su He's whereabouts to me.
Royal brother,
What can I do?
Hearing you say this,
I'm getting nervous.
I also want to contribute to Daxing.
You,
just stay obediently
in the imperial palace.
No.
Stay in Yanbo Tower instead.
It's safer here.
As long as you're safe,
I'll be grateful to the heavens.
Why are you looking down on people?
This princess has also
learned martial arts.
The princess's martial arts
are probably not even
enough to protect herself, right?
You!
Heshu,
Follow your royal brother’s advice.
Only when you're safe
can he fully deal with Yin Zhou.
It's getting late.
We should go back.
Right now, Yin Zhou thinks
that Yanzhi and I have
completely broken up.
It's better for us to go back separately.
Heshu,
You go back to the imperial
palace with Yanzhi first.
I'll go back later.
Aunt Lin,
I have a request.
I hope Aunt Lin
can agree to it for my mother's sake.
Just say it.
If Yin Zhou and Su He
really join hands to rebel in Jiangnan,
even though Yanzhi and I have
made thorough preparations,
no one can predict
what the outcome will be.
If something happens to me,
I hope Aunt Lin
can take good care of Heshu for me.
Okay.
I promise you.
You trust my aunt too little.
Who's in charge of Jiangnan City?
You can ask around on the streets.
Xianyue,
Don't be rude.
I naturally believe in Aunt Lin's ability.
It's just that
we need to be prepared
for the worst in everything.
Xianyue,
Heshu hasn't had many
friends since she was a child.
I can feel that
you and her...
Stop, stop.
We, the martial arts folks,
can't stand such sentimental requests.
I don't have my aunt's broad mind
to take in Yin Heshu for a lifetime.
You'd better take care of her yourself.
Thank you, Aunt Lin.
No one saw us, right?
Don't worry, A Qi.
Today I saw
you talking with Aunt Lin in the corridor.
What did you talk about?
Since Prince Pei is so smart,
why don't you have a guess?
I guess
you still worry about Heshu.
Yanzhi,
even if in this life
I can't change the outcome of my past life,
I have no regrets.
My mother has also been
sent back to Jiangnan.
Heshu has also been entrusted to Aunt Lin.
The most important thing is
in this life,
I know your feelings for me.
I have no regrets.
What if, in this battle,
it's as tragic as what you
experienced in your past life?
Are you still not afraid at all?
As long as we recognize each
other and fight side by side,
I'm not afraid of anything.
Why am I still coughing up
blood after taking the antidote?
No.
I must get rid of Yin Zhou and Su He
before I die
and must not leave any
future troubles for A Qi.
Your Highness,
(All according to plan)
Burn it.
Yes.
Fu'an,
Do you know what kind of thing
is suitable to do in such weather?
This servant is foolish
and naturally doesn't know.
Since it's something the
Crown Prince wants to do,
it must be a wonderful thing.