♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 19=
Where do you think
we can hide that's both safe
and lets you keep
working on your experiment?
Beiyan.
Beiyan, Nange.
I heard
Nange's experimental data was stolen,
and they haven't found out who did it.
I happen to have a college classmate
working at a top data security company
in Silicon Valley.
This is
their latest tracking software.
I don't know if it'll help.
Who told you that?
Uncle Beixiang accidentally mentioned it
at dinner today.
I...
I'm not overstepping, am I?
Zichen, here's the thing.
Right now, the company's
tech department is
investigating
through our internal system.
If we bring in outside software now,
it could interfere with the process.
I see.
Makes sense.
The company's team
is pretty professional after all.
I was just worried.
As soon as I heard
something happened to Nange,
I wanted to come help.
Thanks for your concern.
Well...
You guys carry on.
If there's nothing else, I'll get going.
Well...
What Zichen said
did remind me of something.
The lab's firewall
really is too weak.
The whole lab isn't very secure.
But don't worry too much.
Danger often comes with opportunity.
Your research may
bring some losses to Huo Group and me.
But this could also
be our chance
to take over Ye Group.
Take over Ye Group?
For the past few years,
Ye Group has
been thriving overseas because of NIT-33
and crushing their competitors.
If we can prove
NIT-33 is
a massive scam,
they will collapse overnight.
When that happens,
Huo Group can buy them out cheap
and complete
a major part
of our pharmaceutical expansion.
Mr. Huo,
you're pretty ambitious.
Of course.
A soldier who doesn't
want to be a general isn't a good soldier.
But isn't
Ye Xin your childhood friend?
Aren't you worried about hurting her?
What kind of question is that?
I've disliked her since we were kids.
The way the Ye family
throws their weight around
has always annoyed me.
Now that we have a chance
to get rid of them,
why wouldn't I take it?
So you've never liked Ye Xin?
Of course not.
Are you jealous?
No.
I'm not jealous.
Not even a little.
You
sure?
Alright.
So where
exactly should we hide?
I thought of the perfect place.
You're hiding me here?
Relax.
It's all set.
Let's take a look.
Let's go.
Careful. Don't bump into anything.
Okay, slow down.
Put it here.
Here.
Alright.
Be careful.
Here.
Leave it here for now.
My room's way too small.
There's no way all
this equipment will fit in here.
Who said there's only one room?
Here.
Take this.
I rented the entire building.
From now on,
this is your lab base.
Then let's do it this way.
The first floor will
be the sample storage area.
The ventilation and drainage are great.
The second floor will
be the core lab area.
Quiet and free from distractions.
The third floor will
be for data storage.
Mostly because the lighting's good.
Alright. As long as you like it.
If you need anything else, just tell me.
Thank you.
Not enough.
Mr. Huo,
Mrs. Huo.
Well...
If there's nothing else,
I...
I'll head out first?
Get out.
Go.
You two carry on.
So you've hidden me here.
What about you?
There are a lot
of people outside watching you.
The board, the Ye family.
They're all waiting for an opportunity.
You focus
on the bigger issues.
As for me,
I'll deal with what I
need to handle.
Alright.
Then starting today,
I'm in research mode.
I won't let you down.
Good.
What do you mean you can't find her?
A living person doesn't just disappear!
Mr. Zichen, we've searched
Linhai Medical University,
the Xu family home,
and everywhere Ms. Xu
usually goes, but we found nothing.
According to Shen Yan's people,
Mr. Beiyan arranged for her to return
to her hometown to visit relatives.
Visit relatives?
Didn't I give you
her background report already?
Where would she suddenly get
a hometown and relatives from?
Sorry, Mr. Zichen.
This was our failure.
I don't care if you have
to dig three feet underground. Find her.
Yes.
Zichen.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing, Uncle Beixiang.
My people just messed up.
You're
starting to sound
more and more like Beiyan.
Compared to him,
I'm still far behind.
I've still got a lot to learn.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Get some sleep early.
The key issue isn't willpower.
It's the irreversible
synaptic nerve damage caused
by long-term use.
Exactly.
The three rounds of data released
by Ye Group clearly overlook
the long-term cumulative benefits.
We need to rebuild
the model and strengthen
the time-variable analysis.
(In her field,)
(she's completely different）
（from her usual self.)
(No playfulness.)
(No mischief.)
(Just pure focus.)
(Completely locked in.)
(It's like she's a different person.)
(Xu Nange, trust me.)
(I'll clean up)
(everything out there)
(and protect this peace for you.)
Hello.
Okay.
Got it.
Keep them occupied.
I'll be there in half an hour.
What?
Delay the new drug launch?
Do you realize what that means?
If our competitors launch first,
we'll lose the advantage!
NIT is our only moat
right now!
And if you're
delaying it,
there should at least be a reason!
Stopping it out of nowhere
is way too reckless!
Directors,
I have my reasons.
Mr. Huo,
don't gamble
with the entire group's interests.
This doesn't just
involve our group anymore.
It affects Ye Group's interests too.
How are you planning
to explain this to the shareholders?
Precisely
because this involves Ye Group.
This isn't a drug
we developed independently.
There are too many
stages we can't fully control.
That's why we need to be cautious.
This is ridiculous!
You're not taking us seriously at all.
Fine.
Since everyone opposes
delaying the launch,
then let's make a bet.
If NIT-33 is completely fine,
I'll personally cover
all of the group's losses.
At the same time,
I'll resign as CEO
of Huo Group and step down
from the board.
That's way too extreme.
I don't know much about business,
but I remember
Grandma always said,
"Better safe than sorry".
Beiyan,
the risk you're taking is huge.
Does this drug really have a problem?
Directors,
he's doing this
for the group's long-term reputation
and for the safety
of doctors and patients.
I think we
should trust his judgment.
How about this?
Two weeks.
If everything's fine in two weeks
and the approval
comes through on schedule,
we'll move forward as planned.
What do you all think?
Fine.
Two weeks.
What does everyone think?
Fine.
- Alright.
- Fine. No problem.
Mr. Huo.
Mr. Huo, this is bad.
There are tons of reporters downstairs.
- Reporters?
- The reporters are here?
Why are reporters here?
He's here.
Mr. Huo!
Please stop pushing.
Mr. Huo, why did you suspend
the new drug launch
with your partner?
Does this indirectly suggest
the drug has fatal risks?
Your decision may
harm investors' interests.
Do you believe you've fulfilled
your duties as CEO of Huo Group?
Are you confident you can successfully
lead Huo Group through its transition?
First of all, out of responsibility
to the product and to consumers,
we believe the drug needs
a stricter review process.
This has always been a core principle
of both Huo Group and our partner.
As CEO of Huo Group,
every decision I make
is based on the interests of consumers
and investors.
And...
As for Huo Group's transition,
thank you for your concern.
Let's wait and see.
I hope everyone avoids speculation.
If I see any
false statements regarding our company,
we reserve the right
to pursue legal action.
Mr. Huo!
Calm down!
(Beiyan,)
(your counterattack has already begun.)
("Let's wait and see," huh?)
(Then let's wait and see together.)
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪