♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 21=
(IP Trace Report)
Beiyan, you wanted to see me?
Zichen.
Why did you skip
the board meeting earlier?
Well.
I just thought I should
meet with a few more investors.
You know, more options
mean more open doors.
I saw how stressed you've been lately,
so I wanted to help.
You need to be careful
with choosing investors.
Pick the wrong road,
and there's no turning back.
I get it.
I really do.
I heard that you've been
getting pretty close to Ye Xin.
Well, she's our partner.
I'm still figuring out
how things work around the company.
I need to learn the ropes, you know.
Zichen.
As a Huo,
your loyalty
must always lie with the family.
Of course.
Beiyan,
you must've been under a ton of pressure
at the board meeting earlier.
Doesn't matter.
From now on, my main focus
will be the wedding.
I've put all board business on hold.
Moving forward,
planning the wedding
is my only priority.
I get it now.
You're throwing
a smokescreen.
You need
to play the part of a CEO
who's totally blinded by love
and completely
incapable of making
any rational decisions
to catch them off guard.
Smart.
However,
the whole "blinded by love" part
isn't an act.
Come on.
Help me pick.
The wedding invitations.
See which one you like.
Why don't you decide?
They all look the same to me.
Come on,
at least show a little interest.
I am interested.
Let's go with this. This one looks great.
You're not even trying.
It's like I'm the bride here.
When a STEM girl
hits a project deadline,
you'll just have to deal with it.
But have you found the point person
for the wedding?
Knowing you,
at a time like this,
I bet
you've already
got eyes and ears around us.
Don't worry. It's taken care of.
They're all people I trust.
What about the wedding dress?
Which one's better?
I designed all of these myself.
Aren't these dresses
a bit too out there?
Let's just leave the professional stuff
to the actual professionals.
Look at you.
Guess you do have
some standards after all.
I just don't want
anything too ridiculous.
Then what kind do you actually like?
I'll choose.
Actually,
why don't we save this
for when we're
planning the real wedding?
I think
the most important thing right now
is focusing on the...
Don't worry. I won't lose.
So you can
afford to look a little further ahead.
Wow, Huo Beiyan.
Pretending to catch me up on things
when you're actually just hitting on me.
Fine, I'll pick.
If I'm picking the dress,
you're setting the venue, okay?
I already picked it out.
The Swiss Alps.
♪You walked in
like you were still there♪
It's already so late.
Why isn't he here yet?
Has anyone called him?
- He has zero sense of time.
- Seriously.
Sorry about that. I'm late.
Everyone,
I have a major announcement to make.
What?
Finally come to your senses?
For the next ten days,
all corporate matters
will be handled by my cousin,
Huo Zichen.
As for me,
I'll be putting all my energy
into planning the wedding for my wife,
Xu Nange, and myself.
How can you be thinking
about a wedding at a time like this?
This is nonsense.
What kind of spell
did Xu Nange put you under?
Happy wife, happy life.
And I'm sure
the company will run just fine
even without me around.
Right?
What? That's...
- Beiyan,
- Is this some kind of joke?
you're planning the wedding by yourself?
Nange isn't even here.
Don't worry.
When the day comes,
she'll show up.
(Beiyan,)
(the experiment is now)
(at the final stage of data validation.)
(Everything is going smoothly.)
(Got it.)
Meeting adjourned.
You're leaving already?
- Mr. Huo.
- Mr. Huo?
This is an absolute joke.
What...
Come on.
Let's get moving, everyone.
Help me shift
that flower basket.
Move these flowers over a bit.
Keep an eye on this.
These tables have to be
perfectly lined up.
And the flowers over here.
Straighten them out.
- Keep them in a neat row.
- Got it.
Alright.
Listen up while you work, everyone.
Today is Mr. Huo's wedding day.
And for us
at Huo Group,
it's the biggest event of the year.
So let's give it everything we've got.
If we pull this off,
I'll personally hand out bonuses
to everyone,
okay?
Okay!
Do your best.
Mr. Shen,
sorry I'm late.
No worries.
Professor Liang,
how's your officiant speech
coming along?
Mr. Shen,
if you asked me to give
an academic presentation,
I wouldn't be sweating it at all.
But being a wedding officiant
is a total first for me.
Plus, I can never remember lines.
Don't be nervous, Professor Liang.
Your star student is marrying my boss.
This is cause for celebration.
Look.
You'll never have to worry
about research funding.
That's exactly
why I'm so nervous.
If I mess up my speech on stage,
it's going to be a disaster.
I mean, look.
The...
The wedding is about to start,
and I haven't prepared a single thing.
Don't worry.
I know
it's your first time
doing something like this.
So
I wrote a script for you.
You're a lifesaver, Mr. Shen.
I'm sure whatever you wrote is perfect.
Here, go ahead and look it over.
Alright.
Let me see.
Look, Mr. Huo.
This dress is straight off
the Paris runway.
The design concept
is rooted in natural aesthetics.
It features a structured,
tailored bodice with a skirt designed to...
Too cliche.
Next one.
This piece features
a unique texture woven
from Italian silk organza
and French duchess satin.
The skirt unfolds like a blossom,
layer by layer.
Next.
This isn't dramatic enough.
The inspiration for this dress
comes from the transition
of polar day and night in Antarctica.
- The shoulders feature...
- Next.
What about this one, Mr. Huo?
This is our...
Uncle Beixiang,
why are you
writing this yourself?
You don't get it.
It's been ages since our family
had something this big to celebrate.
We should take this chance
to make sure everyone has a great time
and enjoys themselves.
Uncle Beixiang,
Beiyan never said
he'd be coming home after the wedding.
And we don't have
a traditional bridal procession.
That's for me to worry about.
Just leave it to me.
Alright, Uncle Beixiang.
Save the lecture.
I'll get to work.
What are you rushing off to do?
Listen up.
The most important thing for us now
is Beiyan's wedding.
Get over to his room
and help set things up.
Later,
wheel your grandma over there too.
Let her get a taste
of the festive spirit.
Got it, Uncle Beixiang.
Off you go.
What should I write?
Soaring together
through life's open sky.
Bound in a love that time cannot untie.
(Xu Nange,)
(where on earth are you?)
(Ye Xin)
Hello?
Did you find what we were looking for?
Huo Beiyan is taking his sweet time,
even making a trip
to pick out wedding dresses.
We're running out of time here.
Where exactly is Xu Nange hiding?
What on earth is Huo Beiyan plotting?
You need to find a lead.
I know.
Everything is moving forward as planned.
Don't worry.
Xu Nange won't get in our way.
Huo Zichen,
once Xu Nange shows herself,
we won't have much room left
to make our move.
You wouldn't want Beiyan
to walk away with the girl
and keep a tight grip
on Huo Group, would you?
Stop poking at my sore spots.
I want this way more than you.
Don't worry.
Just wait for my update.
I hope I don't have to worry.
Alright.
Dinner's ready.
This is amazing.
Food right when I'm starving.
You bet.
What?
Aren't you going to compliment me?
You're absolutely amazing, babe.
You managed to whip up a feast
in this tiny apartment of mine.
It's honestly mind-blowing.
That is so over the top.
You don't even mean it.
I'm totally serious.
You really are incredible.
Come on, let's eat.
Let's dig in.
Has everything been going smoothly?
Don't stress over my stuff.
Here.
Have a rib.
No way.
We need to keep each other posted
and present a united front.
Come on, fill me in.
Right now,
the forensic accounting team,
undercover as wedding planners,
has already moved in.
As for the cross-referenced data
you need to get to Professor Liang,
Shen Yan has already passed it along
as the officiant's script.
I'm sure whatever you wrote is perfect.
Look it over.
I'll get back to work.
(Huo Group Internal Audit Report
Confidential: Internal Audit Use Only)
(Report on Anomalous
Corporate Fund Allocation)
(Clinical Trial
Data Cross-Validation Report)
We're going to do a deep dive
into the company accounts
and completely root out every single
corporate parasite,
leaving them nowhere to hide.
Then, we'll tuck the evidence
inside the invitations.
On the day of the wedding,
we'll expose them completely
right in front of everyone.
How's the auditing coming along?
- Any new red flags?
- We're still combing through everything.
But we've already caught a good chunk
of the corporate parasites.
Great work, everyone.
Give it one final push.
Expose every single one
of those old crooks.
Since Ye Xin and Zichen
are teaming up to spy on me,
I need to return the favor.
Over the past few days,
all the loopholes, evidence,
and dirty laundry on United Pharma
(NIT-33 Project Victims)
are steadily
making their way to me.
(NIT-33 Project Victims)
That's amazing.
Doesn't that mean...
We've got this in the bag.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪