ظآزLove's little quiz
takes seven parts sweetظآز
ظآزAnd three parts bitter,
till you and I meetظآز
ظآزI pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stayظآز
ظآزWaiting for youظآز
ظآزWe've got so many
romantic dreams to unfoldظآز
ظآزFinally hearing
the I love you I long to holdظآز
ظآزFalling fast
into the swirl of your eyesظآز
ظآزIt's just too tempting, so temptingظآز
ظآزNever could I have guessedظآز
ظآزMy heart's rhythmظآز
ظآزHow beautiful it is, meeting youظآز
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 17=
(Xu Nange is Dr. X.)
I'm rushing on my thesis.
I don't need money.
I need the entire lab
at Linhai Medical University.
I've decided to bring in
a neuroscience expert,
Dr. X to collaborate.
Actually, I just
remembered my thesis still isn't done.
I need to go work on it.
It's more than just
a graduation thesis to me.
I...
I think
you're a little too
invested in this thesis.
No, I'm not.
I'm just a little anxious.
I'm going to find Professor Liang.
Just go home and wait for me.
Just because we're married, I...
I think some things
are better left unsaid.
(Dr. X.)
(The first person in academia)
(to research the NIT drug.)
(To have gotten this deep)
(into the toxicity data this early,)
(they'd have to be an insider)
(or)
(a hidden consultant for United Pharma.)
(Xu Nange,)
(could you really)
(be connected to United Pharma?)
No wonder back then,
your comments on Grandma's treatment
matched their forum exactly.
(Xu Nange,)
(are you)
(the Dr. X)
(I've been looking for?)
Huo Beiyan!
Huo Beiyan?
He's not here?
(Huo Beiyan)
(We're sorry,)
(the number you have dialed)
(is not available.)
(Please try again later.)
(He's never been this late before.)
(Did something come up?)
ظآزDid I, did Iظآز
ظآزSo she saidظآز
Hold on!
ظآزSmile, I tryظآز
ظآزTo build it on my ownظآز
ظآزNever could have seenظآز
I have to honor our agreement.
I have to play my part as Mrs. Huo.
ظآزAll the while you know,
it's all for showظآز
Do you have feelings for me?
ظآزI made you my homeظآز
Yes.
ظآزYou waited, I fadedظآز
ظآزSo she saidظآز
Give me two weeks.
After that, whether my
research is finished
or this matter is resolved,
I'll tell you everything.
I promise.
ظآزSo I lie aloneظآز
ظآزNever could have seen,
never could have dreamظآز
ظآزAll the while you know,
it's all for showظآز
Sir.
Why are you still here?
Move the meeting tomorrow morning
to seven.
I'm staying tonight.
To...
ظآزYou save me, and build
a home for my soul.ظآز
Got it.
I'll arrange it.
Beiyan.
Huo Beiyan.
Huo Beiyan!
Nange!
Beiyan!
Come downstairs!
What a lovely place.
Dad!
Nange!
What brings you by?
You didn't hear?
The old madam is in
a great mood today.
At yesterday's birthday dinner,
she got so full on longevity noodles
that she had no room left for cake.
When she woke up this morning,
she insisted on having a bite of cake.
So here I am.
Dropping some off for you too.
Thank you, Dad.
You could've just called
me over to pick it up!
I'm giving myself an excuse
to get out and stretch my legs.
Where's Beiyan?
He...
stayed up really late last night.
Let him sleep in.
Nange,
you clearly don't know him very well.
That boy never stays in bed late.
If something's going on,
just tell me.
He...
didn't come home last night.
But I'm sure
it's just something at the company.
Out all night?
Don't tell me you two
had a fight.
No.
We actually had a really
good talk yesterday.
He's probably just
been really busy lately.
Really?
Nothing, Dad.
Alright then.
I'll be off.
Dad.
Do you know what Beiyan's
been working on lately?
There's quite a lot going on
at the company right now.
But the biggest thing is probably
the board seat situation
at United Pharma.
What?
He didn't tell you?
He acquired twenty-two percent
of United Pharma six months ago.
He's probably
in a power struggle with their CEO,
Ye Xin.
So you're saying
the Huo family is tied up
with United Pharma?
Tied up?
Very much so.
We're currently
United Pharma's
second-largest shareholder.
The FDA has received a report
from a neurosurgery expert,
(Corrupt Huo Group!)
Dr. X
stating that United Pharma's
upcoming drug carries a cancer risk.
Authorities have already
seized the Huo Group's
(Bring back our loved ones!)
affiliated pharmaceutical plants.
Based on evidence
provided by whistleblower Ms. Xu,
Huo Group is suspected of
manufacturing counterfeit drugs.
This is an arrest warrant.
We are hereby placing
Huo Beiyan under arrest.
Grandma!
Are you alright?
What are you doing?
Dad!
Beiyan!
Nange!
You can't take him!
Grandma!
Let's go.
Grandma, are you okay?
Dad!
Grandma!
(If my research)
(proves the drug is dangerous,)
(then the Huo family, a major)
(shareholder of United Pharma,)
(won't be able to)
(escape legal liability either.)
Nange.
Are you okay?
I need to find Beiyan.
Mrs. Huo, please stop.
I'm afraid you can't go up today.
I'm here to see Huo Beiyan.
You can check with him,
or with Shen Yan
if you prefer.
I understand.
But Mr. Huo gave
specific instructions today.
Without his clearance,
no one gets through.
He and Shen Yan are
extremely tied up today.
He won't be available to see you.
Is this new rule
specifically for me?
Of course not!
This policy has always been in place.
We appreciate your understanding.
You're welcome to try
reaching him directly.
If Mr. Huo approves,
I'll arrange it right away.
That's fine. I understand.
Thank you.
(How is it that after just one night,)
(you feel so far away?)
(What happened?)
Sir,
Mrs. Huo has left.
are you alright?
I'm fine.
Nothing's wrong.
But,
you've already signed this document.
(Huo Beiyan.)
Sir,
are you sure you're okay?
Do you remember when I told you
why I invested in United Pharma?
Why I was so set on finding Dr. X?
To get answers for Old Mrs. Huo.
Xu Nange
is Dr. X.
What?
Impossible.
I don't believe it.
Sir,
I mean,
how could Mrs. Huo be
behind making a counterfeit drug?
Besides,
Dr. X's latest published paper
is also targeting United Pharma.
Maybe Mrs. Huo was
caught up in it,
or being used somehow.
There must be a misunderstanding.
You're so sure?
Absolutely.
Ever since you two met,
I've watched everything
unfold.
I have complete
faith in her character!
That's exactly why.
If Grandma's getting worse
has anything to do with her,
how am I supposed
to face her after this?
Sir,
Miss Ye is here.
What is it?
Business only.
I'd rather not make small
talk and get scolded
by the chairman who's
too devoted to his wife.
I heard
you've been holding up NIT's
domestic approval process.
The delay
is due to updated FDA review standards.
I'm just an investor.
You're the developer.
It's on you to navigate
the process properly
and protect the Huo family's interests.
Fine. I'll follow up.
But your sought-after collaborator,
Dr. X has been putting
quite a bit of pressure
on United Pharma lately.
Surely you're aware.
I'll admit that was
an oversight on my part.
I never expected
them to turn out to be our enemy.
Have you found them?
No leads yet.
Do you have any?
I assumed
Dr. X had been working
with United Pharma.
That's a serious
misunderstanding, Mr. Huo.
But no matter.
You've been reaching out
to this person with goodwill.
I suggest
the Huo and Ye families join forces
and track down Dr. X.
And once we find them?
Once they're found,
wipe them out.
Ye Xin,
you're ruthless.
Just business.
Everything has a price tag,
even a life.
Fine.
To eliminate the threat for good,
I'll play along.
Deal.
Sir,
there's been a new development.
ظآزWhat destiny brought us to meetظآز
ظآزTwo different worlds, a love so sweetظآز
ظآزA wish we made
in a past life, it seemsظآز
ظآزDestined to cross time and dream ظآز
ظآزLike a fairytale story toldظآز
ظآزA gentle breeze feels so boldظآز
ظآزAs your hair brushes past your earظآز
ظآزI long to kiss your cheek, my dearظآز
ظآزAll my longing, all my love for youظآز
ظآزHas never changed, it's forever trueظآز
ظآزIt's the hand of fate
that we meet againظآز
ظآزLet me hold you once againظآز
ظآزResting against your chestظآز
ظآزYour warmth shines like stars at nightظآز
ظآزLet me kiss you once againظآز
ظآزNo reason neededظآز
ظآزMy heart belongs to youظآز
ظآزI'm not afraid
to cross time to find youظآز