♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 20=
As for Huo Group's transition,
thank you for your concern.
Let's wait and see.
I hope everyone avoids speculation.
If I see any false statements
regarding our company,
we reserve the right
to pursue legal action.
(Huo Beiyan,)
(that's not what you told me at all.)
(You're carrying all this pressure.)
(But every time you talk to me,)
(you act like it's nothing.)
(Are you overthinking again?)
(Stop watching so much news.)
(Focus on your research, Dr. Xu.)
(Those old guys on the board)
(are all bark and no bite.)
(The media won't just make things up.)
(The PR and legal teams)
(Huo Group spends
millions on every year)
(aren't there for decoration.)
(You just focus on staying calm.)
Hello, delivery.
I didn't order anything.
Your bubble tea.
Half sugar, light ice, extra boba.
Forgot already?
You're such a dummy.
Maybe we should come up
with a different code word.
You look ridiculous doing this.
No way. What if it's a bad guy?
You...
You don't even have a peephole.
Fine.
Now you have
to play delivery guy.
It's no trouble.
Come here.
Put that over there first.
Wait a second.
Don't judge it by how it looks.
I wasn't slacking off today.
While the equipment was running data,
I looked up
a recipe online.
It seemed pretty easy.
The only problem is...
It's kind of ugly.
But it actually tastes good.
I already sneaked a bite.
You're not lactose intolerant, are you?
I didn't think of that
until after I made it.
Let me try.
Wow. It's ugly,
but it's really good.
Good.
Have another bite.
Now that you've eaten my food,
you have to promise me
something.
From now on,
whenever you're sure about something,
whether it's through lawyers,
onnections, or whatever,
you have to tell me. Okay?
I don't want
to sit at home worrying
by myself anymore.
I'm really afraid
something might happen to you.
I understand.
First, I'll solve
the problem of you worrying.
Then I'll solve the problem
of you being home alone.
What's that supposed to mean?
We could go on a real honeymoon.
How's the mole investigation going?
We've made progress.
Don't worry.
We'll have
an answer
soon.
Checkmate.
I'm done. I haven't won a single game.
Play with Beiyan.
Where are Beiyan and Nange anyway?
I haven't seen them in days.
How would
I know?
Just asking.
I haven't seen Beiyan in days.
Feels weird.
Stop
worrying about them.
When are you
going to find someone yourself?
You think I don't want to?
I just haven't met the right person yet.
Don't worry, Uncle Beixiang.
Once I start dating someone,
I'll bring her home for your to meet.
Really?
That's more like it.
Come on. Set it up.
Let's play another round.
I'm out, Uncle Beixiang.
You can figure it out yourself.
Look at you.
(Huanfa Taste the World)
(First Financial Weekly)
As instructed,
I tracked Mr. Zichen.
I saw him and Miss Ye
enter the same restaurant.
Got it. Gather all the evidence.
Hello?
Hello.
Nange,
we've confirmed it.
The mole really is him.
Honestly, I had a feeling the day
the lab was compromised.
The system logs
were wiped too cleanly.
It was professional work.
Not something
an ordinary person could've done.
But I couldn't figure out the motive.
Not until he brought over
the flash drive.
I never even mentioned that
to my dad.
Turns out he was
behind everything.
Beiyan,
are you upset?
I'm okay.
Honestly,
I'm more scared than sad.
Scared he'll hurt you to get
what he wants.
You know,
Zichen has always been like the kid
who works his heart out for a 99.
But everyone
only notices
the one who gets 100.
I've always
been afraid of him getting hurt.
This is just
another case
of me winning.
Once again,
I've taken away what he values most.
So he did all this
just to prove he could beat you once?
I guess so.
He's always lived in your shadow.
But how could he
gamble with the company your grandma
built from scratch?
Nange...
I don't know how to explain it.
But...
I still want to give him
one chance to make things right.
So what's your plan?
I'm putting Dr. X
in the spotlight.
Beiyan hasn't noticed what I'm doing.
We've got enough time to bring him down.
I only have one question.
Where's Xu Nange?
If you'd told me from the start
that she was Dr. X,
I wouldn't be in this position.
You've got your own agenda.
Don't think I don't know.
You're afraid I'll push you out.
Huo Beiyan's been right
under my nose the whole time.
Even if I don't know
Xu Nange's progress,
they still can't stop us.
Right now, both we and Xu Nange
are working in the shadows.
Huo Beiyan's protecting her well.
You need to move faster.
He's making his move.
Today, Huo Group officially signed
a strategic partnership agreement
with Dr. X.
The two sides will work closely
in the field of neuroscience.
Dr. X remains anonymous.
The public will see the results,
not the person.
Mr. Huo, how did you
establish contact with Dr. X?
Dr. X is fully devoted
to research.
The decision to work with Huo Group came
from trust in our ability to support
and develop those achievements.
We'll do everything we can
to help bring Dr. X's work
to market.
Mr. Huo.
(The Irreplaceability of Dr. X)
That's all for today.
Thank you all for coming.
Huo Group will
continue striving
to deliver results
everyone can be proud of.
Thank you.
What's your next move?
I don't like being pressured!
Pressure leads to mistakes!
Relax.
All the pieces are already in place.
Mr. Wang and Mr. Li
have made their positions clear.
They'll challenge him at the next
board meeting.
They're really willing
to take sides that quickly?
Huo Beiyan has
deep roots in the company.
When money's involved,
there's no such thing
as absolute loyalty.
Suspending NIT-33 hit
the biggest source
of profit they had.
Add in the shares I privately
promised them,
and it's enough
to make them take the risk.
Huo Beiyan's persuasive.
Don't let him talk them out of it.
Don't worry.
Huo Beiyan,
I've prepared quite a surprise for you
at the next board meeting.
What's this?
What's wrong?
Mr. Huo,
this is our team's resignation letter.
Our vision no longer
aligns with yours.
We can't continue
with the upcoming R&D projects.
Leave it there.
Shen Yan will approve it.
If there's nothing else,
finish the handover and leave.
Let's go.
Come on.
Your turn.
Look what you've done
to Huo Pharma's stock price.
Do you have any idea
how much it's dropped?
Is this why we
backed you?
Why we invested in this company?
NIT is basically printing money.
And you're refusing to sell it?
Do you think investors are idiots?
Beiyan,
you have a responsibility
to this board and our employees!
We followed your dad and watched
this company grow step by step!
At this rate,
you're going to sink the whole ship!
And I'm not going down with you!
Beiyan,
if you keep this up,
the company's finished!
Huo Beiyan, I'm not negotiating!
This is an ultimatum!
Let me tell you something, Huo Beiyan!
You're destroying your dad's
life's work!
(Xu Nange's Menu of the Day,
Main Course: Red Wine Beef Stew)
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪