♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 18=
If you need space,
I'll give you space.
If you need time
to sort out what you want to say,
I'll be patient.
If things get dangerous
or too much to handle alone,
call me.
I promise.
It's a little gift to mark
our first month together.
There are two names on it.
One is Florence Nightingale,
and the other is you.
♪Just say yes♪
♪And I won't go♪
♪Don't leave me standing♪
♪All alone♪
We're really
together now.
From now on,
I want you to tell me everything.
Anything at all.
Just tell me.
I'll do everything I can
to help you through it.
That's what
a husband is supposed to do.
♪Just say yes♪
♪And I won't go♪
♪Don't leave me standing♪
Xu Nange,
don't run this time.
♪The warmth we shared,
the time we spent♪
♪Don't think you cry in love again♪
♪Say yes♪
(Work Module Setup)
The materials from
the tech team are now very clear.
Regarding the break-in
at Mrs. Huo's lab,
nothing was damaged,
nor taken,
but
files were copied.
(Cooperative Institution Plan)
You just mentioned
Dr. X's latest paper
is targeting United Pharma?
That's right.
Do you understand
what the worst case looks like?
If anyone finds out
that Nange is Dr. X,
and that she's
out to bring down United Pharma,
her life will be in danger.
Sir...
Just go home.
Keep an eye on her
and make sure she's safe.
But what about you?
You've been busy all day, haven't you?
I feel like I haven't seen you all day.
You know, it's always
been you giving me gifts.
So today I got you
a little gift too.
Fair warning though.
It wasn't expensive.
It's just from the heart.
I hope you'll like it.
Mrs. Huo
is not at home?
Hello?
Where are you?
I've finally reached you.
Tell me where you are.
I'm out shopping.
(Hello, the number you have dialed)
(is currently unavailable.)
Shen Yan, hurry up.
On it.
(Hello, the number you have dialed)
(is currently unavailable.)
Can you go any faster?
Got it.
♪All of my dreams, leading me here♪
♪Fueling the fire
that help me fight all the fear♪
♪All that I've got, and all that I am♪
♪All that I gave up
just to stand where I stand♪
♪Every step that I took was toward you♪
Huo Beiyan!
♪I found what I've been looking for♪
♪Don't have to keep searching anymore♪
♪I've never thought I'd have it all♪
♪But everything changed,
and anything is possible♪
♪I found what I've been looking for♪
♪Don't have to keep searching anymore♪
♪I never thought I'd have it all♪
♪But everything changed,
and anything is possible♪
♪I found what I've been looking for♪
What happened?
Why wasn't your phone going through?
I was going to go out this afternoon
to get you a gift.
And somehow I managed
to drop my phone in the water.
- After that...
- Xu Nange,
I have a question for you.
The two-week countdown is up.
You owe me a straight answer.
Come with me.
The order to the front desk
came from me.
No visitors, including you.
Why?
The day before, I received
an anonymous letter.
At the same time, I confirmed something.
It turned out
that the Dr. X I'd been searching for
had been right beside me.
I was going to bring it up in two weeks.
NIT-33,
did you develop it?
What?
Answer me.
Did you,
or didn't you?
Of course not.
Then three years ago,
that paper on NIT-33,
didn't you write it?
Access to NIT's
original molecular structure data
was limited to United
Pharma insiders only.
Master's internship at Linhai.
United Pharma New
Product Evaluation Division.
Six months.
What are you saying?
Yes.
I did intern at United Pharma.
I didn't just know NIT-33 was dangerous.
I tried everything
to gather evidence.
I wanted the public to know.
But United Pharma
used every trick in the book
to bury all the damaging data,
and pushed the clinical
trials through faster.
Until today,
I still haven't found
solid evidence to prove it.
That's why
NIT-33 is still selling
overseas to this day.
I've known about its
harm for a long time.
But,
I've done everything I possibly could.
I'm not powerful enough.
I can't bring it down that fast.
It wasn't until two days ago
that I found out
exactly who it had hurt.
Beiyan, did you know?
Grandma is the person
who's been supporting
me all these years.
On the transfer slips,
no real name was ever written.
Just a single
letter of the alphabet.
X.
So you believed
Dr. X was an accomplice
of United Pharma,
and finding her was
about getting revenge.
Yes.
I wanted justice for Grandma.
Under the name Dr. X,
over the past three years,
I've published seven papers.
They're all point to the risks
of NIT-33 and similar drugs.
I really want to bring
this into the open.
I'm sorry.
I misjudged you.
I should have told you sooner.
Because I knew
this isn't just an academic dispute.
United Pharma has
very powerful reach overseas.
My papers
strike at their core product.
It cuts off their revenue
and destroys their foundation.
Every person who knows
who I am
is another risk.
Beiyan, I didn't want to
drag you into this.
And I only found out today
that you'd become a
shareholder of United Pharma.
I became a shareholder of United Pharma.
Not to invest,
but to infiltrate.
I need to find from the inside
every piece of paper
that could put them in prison.
But once my next batch
of evidence goes public,
United Pharma will take a major hit,
and Huo Group will get
caught in the fallout.
Ye Xin is not a good person.
She will try to take you down with her.
That's fine.
Grandma's life's work
wasn't Huo Group's market value.
It was
the belief that medicine
exists to save lives.
When Grandma was still herself,
she set one rule for the family.
Huo Group
doesn't need to be the biggest company,
But it must be the cleanest.
We earn only honest money.
That's the foundation of who we are.
I won't forget that.
So,
I've got you.
Do whatever
you need to do.
You make it all sound
so effortless.
Doesn't it get exhausting,
carrying all of this alone?
Haven't you been carrying it
alone all this time too?
Don't worry.
We'll get through it,
one hurdle at a time.
The Huo Group isn't that fragile.
Neither am I.
So,
go focus
on your research.
Leave the rest to me.
Have you thought about
who told you my identity?
Not yet.
But as you said,
massive profits are involved.
Whoever it is could
be getting desperate.
So what's your plan?
Find somewhere completely safe.
Until this all comes to light,
I'm going to hide you
somewhere no one can reach you.
Okay.
I'll do whatever you say.
♪Darling, you go far away♪
♪Why don't you take me too?♪
♪We could go on a journey♪
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪