CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND INCIDENTS
IN THIS PRODUCTION ARE PARTLY FICTITIOUS
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED
Now you're asking for it!
- Let go!
- Stop!
Let go!
Let go…
How come you came with Mr. Pat last night?
It's a long story, Thee.
Yesterday I saw Mr. Anapat and Mook.
They seemed really close.
Does he have a crush on her too?
I'm really worried about you, you know?
Don't risk your life like that again.
I wouldn't know what to do
if something were to happen to you.
Where have I seen this kid before?
Ms. Narin!
Are you alright?
I just got a little lightheaded.
Let me make you a new cup.
It's alright.
I think you should sit down. Let's go.
- Watch out for the glass.
- Thank you.
Easy, okay?
I'm really sorry, Ms. Mook.
I wanted to take care of you,
but now you have to take care of me.
Don't worry about it.
Last time we met,
you didn't seem so well either.
Do you have a medical condition?
I have a heart disease.
I've been thinking, once I've done
what I always wanted to,
I'll finally retire.
Okay.
You're feeling better now, right?
I'm trying to contain my emotions.
About Mr. Thee, right?
Yes.
You know, sometimes it's like a test.
If it's meant to be yours, it'll be.
But if it's not meant to be mine,
I should take a step back, right?
Okay.
Prao, where's our son?
If you're home this late,
of course he'd be in bed already.
You told me Pun's sick.
Is he okay?
If I didn't use him as an excuse,
you'd never come home, would you?
Explain this.
Besides Mook, you're seeing
other girls too, Pat?
You've misunderstood me.
What?
Do I need proof of you two in the same bed
before you'll admit it?
In front of everyone,
you act like a good man,
but in reality,
you're just a scumbag
who left your family to have an affair!
Don't bother asking me, Prao,
if you won't believe a single word I say.
I'm not stupid!
I could tell from the photo
how close you two really are.
You've had too much to drink.
Let's talk later.
If you have someone else,
just admit it. Is that so hard, Pat?
The problem's got nothing to do
with anyone, Prao.
The problem is that you never trust me.
You never listened to me
or agreed with anything I said.
You just want me to be
what you want me to be.
You should ask yourself
if you still even want me.
Mook.
Mook, can we talk things out?
FAVORITES
MOOK - MR. PITAK
MOOK - CALLING…
You can cash out however much you'd like.
Think of it as a bonus
I'm paying in advance.
Then, come work with me
officially already.
As for your travel agency,
if you want to keep running it,
that's fine by me.
But do it as a hobby,
or ask someone you trust
to run it for you.
Please accept it.
Because if you don't,
who knows when you'll finally solve
your company's problems.
I'm not stupid!
I could tell from the photo
how close you two really are.
If you have someone else,
just admit it. Is that so hard, Pat?
CONTACTS
MOOK
Thank you for coming.
Aren't you going to ask me
why I called you?
It's because you feel comfortable
with me, of course.
I feel the same way when I'm with you.
How ironic.
I don't even feel this way with the one
I should feel it with.
My wife, I mean.
Ms. Veluree's already checked out, sir.
Okay.
MOOK
Ms. Mook's already left this morning.
Her friends picked her up.
Mr. Thee.
If you can't make her happy,
then you should let her go.
This is my problem.
I can deal with it myself.
You should get ready
to solve your own problems.
- Here's your coffee.
- Thank you.
Drank too much last night?
It's been a while since my last time,
so I'm a bit dizzy.
Is Mook here yet?
No, she isn't.
Can you tell her to see me
once she's here?
Of course, Mr. Pat.
Thanks.
I have a wife and a kid,
but my family's falling apart.
I've heard a bit of your background.
I wouldn't judge someone
because of this, though.
What do you really want from me?
I like you.
You're always helping me.
You're a kind person.
Sometimes you even worry about me
more than yourself.
I don't care what your past is like.
Because for me, who you are today
is the best version of yourself.
What have I done?
Are you hungover, Boss?
Is it that obvious, Mook?
How come everyone could tell?
So, how's the situation?
I made a list of all the changes needed.
I'll brief the team on it later.
I meant your situation with Mr. Thee.
It's really nothing.
I'll just keep doing my job.
Anyway, I should get back to work.
Boss,
need some hangover pills?
Okay. I'll go now.
So?
I found you some clients.
- Amazing, right?
- Maybe
- lobsters.
- Yeah.
You sure about this, Ma?
Yeah, Ma,
if they have a heart attack
and die during the tour,
then we're screwed, Ma.
Watch your mouth!
Isn't it you who made us lose clients?
That's why I had to find you new clients!
It wasn't my fault, Ma.
You should blame them for being so picky.
They kept asking for stuff.
They wanted everything free.
Enough, enough!
I don't want to hear it.
Just do a better job this time.
You're lucky you have clients.
Plus,
they're all my friends,
and they're loaded.
If you give them good service,
they'll tip you like crazy.
You hear me?
Come on. Let's get in our van!
- Let's go!
- Yes!
- In the van!
- Go, go!
- Let's go.
- Yes!
This won't be easy.
Thank you!
Don't worry, Kuk.
I'll handle them to compensate you
for losing those clients.
Okay?
Let's go!
Ugh!
Oh my!
- Fine, come on.
- Restroom!
What now, Ma?
- I need to pee!
Okay, please relax.
- The restroom's that way.
- Where?
- Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
- Ugh.
- Whoa.
Go take care of your clients, yeah?
Ugh.
- Give me one!
- Calm down, everyone.
- You can go light them over there.
- There?
- Oh, I'll get one from you then.
- Calm down, okay?
- Move.
- Move, kids!
- Elders go first!
- You can do it after.
Here we come.
Make way!
- Move, people, move!
- Come on.
- Let us get in there!
- Move.
- Let me walk there!
- Move!
- Okay.
- Move. Get out of the way!
Bless me with good health
and lots of wealth.
Good things only.
Bless me.
- What are you doing?!
- No!
I haven't finished!
- Hey!
- Don't fight.
What? Auntie!
How could you do that?
See, I'm all wet now.
What happened, Hua?
She said I splashed water on her.
I didn't! I was just washing my hands.
I'm sorry.
My friend probably didn't mean it.
Let's just forget it, okay?
Don't apologize to them, Tiansee.
Forget it. Come on. Let's get in our van.
Come on. Let's go.
Oops. Sorry, Auntie.
I didn't mean it either.
My goodness! How dare you?
Oh, Auntie.
Now you're asking for it. Sure then!
- You!
- How could you!
No, stop!
Don't!
- Ma'am, please stop.
- Stop it!
- Ma!
- Please stop, ma'am!
Hey!
Hey! You want this?!
Khim, I take it you've heard
that the company's put together
a committee to look into…
Yes, I'm well aware.
You have to admit that your story
and the word that got out
are very serious,
and they could damage
our company's reputation.
But on the other hand,
your story also started
something influential on social media.
People have made so many posts
to support you and commend you
for your bravery.
Plus,
Preaw already told me everything.
I heard you and Khim
were threatened by that man.
Is it true?
Yes, but please don't fire Khim, Kwan.
If it weren't for her,
I never would've dared
to stand up to that evil man.
But there's also a video
he took of her, isn't there?
Yes, but she isn't a coward like me,
who kept hiding
because I was too scared to see anyone,
and I allowed that evil man
to go on and hurt others.
I understand
that you were also a victim, Khim.
And we wanted to see you today
to inform you that our company's
reached a decision on your issue.
We agreed that…
you can keep working here,
and the situation won't disqualify you
from being considered for a promotion.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
But, Khim,
I hope what happened
can be a lesson and a reminder for you
to never repeat the same mistake.
Yes, Kwan,
I'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
What's up, Usa?
What? They got arrested?
Ugh! Please be quiet!
Please wait your turn. You first.
What's all this about, Ma?
Did you pick a fight with them?
They started it. I didn't.
Stop it. Quit fighting already.
Please be polite.
Kuk, let's talk to the police
and get it over with.
I'm already so embarrassed.
Don't worry about it.
We just need to pay the fines.
Let bygones be bygones, okay, Kuk?
I should've asked Mook for help
in the first place.
Our clients would've returned,
and we wouldn't have lost our time,
money, and reputation like this!
- Please?
- Quiet down. Please don't fight.
Excuse me. Hello.
I'll compensate for everything.
Here are your fines.
You'll be fined 500 baht each
on charges of affray.
I want to meet Mr. Thee's mom.
Why would you want to meet her?
Haven't you heard of that saying?
"Trample a man when he's down."
Once I tell her about Mook,
surely, it'll be over for Mook.
Good idea, Ma.
That way, we'll also tank her company,
and we'll replace them.
Now that's what I call
killing two birds with one stone.
I'll call Mrs. Anna tomorrow
to set a date for you.
Come on in.
Mook, Mr. Pitak's here to see you.
Sorry to bother you, Ms. Mook.
No worries, Mr. Pitak.
If you'll excuse me.
Sure.
What was he doing here? He looked serious.
Please call a meeting with the team.
I'll tell everyone.
It's not that, is it?
Or maybe it is?
We need to find a new model
for the wedding campaign?
Yes,
TJ group wants Ms. Bella to model
alongside Mr. Thee.
But both the pictures for the ad
and the content are almost done!
Our content stays the same,
but we'll need to reshoot the pictures,
because retouching them
would be too difficult.
Let's just reshoot the whole thing.
Can you schedule it?
Mook, but--
Just do it.
It's what our client wants.
Come to think of it,
Ms. Bella's better suited
for this campaign than me.
Scrap the pictures of me and Mr. Thee,
and make a new layout.
Please make those edits and let me know.
Got it.
Don't tell Boss about this.
If something comes up,
come to me directly.
Okay, Mook.
Okay.
For sure.
Mr. Thee's mom
ordered this change, for sure.
Isn't this going a bit too far?
Does she plan on hurting them so much
that it's awkward for them?
We can't help it.
We're just his partner,
but that's his actual fiancée.
Let's get this over with.
At least Mook can finally be free
from all this.
How harsh.
What do we need to redo now?
- A lot.
- Everything.
- We have to start all over.
- Just a lot.
From the beginning.
Did my mom tell you to tell Mook that?
Yes, Mr. Thee.
I'm really sorry.
It's no use, Mr. Thee.
Every time you refuse,
Ms. Mook's the one who ends up in trouble.
Mrs. Anna will do anything to get her way.
If you don't want Ms. Mook
to get hurt any more than this,
this isn't the way to go up against her.
Thank you for taking the time
to meet us, Mrs. Anna.
This is Mrs. Tiansee.
She's the mother of Mr. Apichart,
the CEO of Family Tour and Travel.
She also used to be
Ms. Veluree's mother-in-law.
So you both know Ms. Veluree too?
That's an understatement.
You could say
I know her from the inside out.
I wanted to meet you today
because my son's made the same mistake.
That's why I'm worried about Mr. Thee,
since I'm a mother like you.
That woman turned my son
into someone else entirely.
She did that to your son too, didn't she?
I made the wrong decision.
At first, I thought Veluree
seemed pretty innocent.
I always love whoever my son loves.
But once they got married
and moved in together…
it turned out that woman's very scary.
When I heard she's been nagging Mr. Thee,
I wanted to warn you.
Actually, I could kind of tell
what her intention was
for getting close to Mr. Thee.
Don't worry,
I won't let anyone fool my son.
If I can help you with anything,
please let me know.
I'd be happy to help.
Too bad we didn't meet earlier.
Otherwise, when Thee
was deciding the winner for his project,
Family Tour and Travel might've won.
How about this?
I have another project
you might be interested in.
I can send you the details
if you're interested.
Really?
- Would this work?
- It's good.
Let me take a look for you.
- Okay.
- Alright.
Mook, I could've handled this shoot alone.
It's just a few shots.
It's better for me to be here.
This way, we can finalize it,
and no one has to wait.
What, Whan?
Do I seem that weak?
No, Mook.
If all those crazy things
were to happen to me,
I don't think I can stay as strong as you.
Alright?
Good morning.
Is everything all set?
Yes, we're all set here.
Sorry for the changes.
If we published those photos
of you and Thee,
it'd cause misunderstandings.
After all, his real fiancée's
already made an appearance,
so we should do things properly.
The concept for today's shoot
is a couple who's soon to be married.
The vibe should be relaxed and natural.
Let's get it over with, Thee. Let's go.
Let's try this.
A bit closer to each other, please.
- Okay.
Let's try this.
How is it?
- The lighting's perfect. One more, please.
- Okay, one more.
Good. A little closer
to each other, please.
Hold that pose.
Look at the camera, please.
Can I see some romantic hand-holding?
They made changes?!
Yes.
Mrs. Anna wanted
all the couple photos to be changed
by replacing Mook with Ms. Bella.
I feel so bad for Mook, Boss.
She's clearly messing with her.
Why didn't I know about this?
Well, Mook told us not to tell you.
She doesn't want you to be upset.
Where is she now?
She's directing the shoot
at The One, Boss.
We're all set. Thank you.
It's just an ad,
yet you already look this good.
When you do your pre-wedding shoot,
you'll make a really pretty bride, Bell.
Boss!
Why didn't you tell me you made changes?
This is Mr. Anapat.
He's the CEO of A Round Trip Travel.
Good morning.
The other day, I was busy,
so we never formally met.
Good morning.
Could you tell me
why we needed to edit the ad?
If there's an error,
of course, you'd have to edit it.
If you wanted to have a model
alongside Thee for the shoot,
you should've told me first,
so you wouldn't have needed
a backup like Ms. Mook.
For every process and every step,
we always had meetings,
and we followed briefs.
In fact, I think the original photos
with Mr. Thee and Mook
already look great.
But you're our client,
so if you wish to make any changes,
I'm happy to oblige.
Making changes the way Mrs. Anna sees fit
is the right thing to do.
You're done, right?
Want to leave together?
Let's get changed so we can go.
I'm getting a bit tired.
Then, take care of her for me, honey.
Looks like I'll have to ask you
to organize their wedding too,
because it seems you're well aware
of what Thee likes or doesn't like.
Thank you, Boss.
You know, I can get you off this project.
No, it's probably for the best.
It made me see clearly
where I really belong.
Drive safe, Boss.
Mook.
I know that you're really worried about me
and that you don't want
to see me get bullied.
But don't worry, Boss,
I'll try to return to my old self.
Please give me some time.
If I can help you with anything,
I'm always here.
Thank you, Boss.
See you.
Let's go get changed, so we can go.
I'm getting a bit tired.
Take care of her for me, honey.
Hello?
- Good afternoon.
What happened?
The lady who came with you that day
came and canceled the reservation.
Who was she with?
She came with another man,
probably her father.
Where is she now?
She went to our sample room,
but I'm not sure if she's left yet.
Hey.
Thank you.
What happened?
Well, it's just what always happens.
This is not the first time
I had to do this.
Did your dad not like it here?
More like,
he never likes anything I do.
My mom really loved to draw.
I kept watching her draw
until her passion for art
rubbed off on me.
But then, I lost her when I was 14.
Since then, I've always lived with my dad.
My dad always works hard.
Even on the anniversary
of my mom's death each year,
my dad never went to her memorial.
Whenever he sees me draw
or appreciate a work of art,
I guess it reminds him of my mom
and makes him feel guilty.
When he found out I'm opening a studio
to design clothes here, he got so mad.
He told me to stop daydreaming
and marry Thee because he's made
an arrangement with Thee's parents.
So, you and Mr. Thee
will get married like they told you to?
I only agreed to it
so I can live my life
the way I want in exchange.
What about you? Do you love Ms. Mook?
Yesterday, you seemed
really worried about her.
Mr. Pitak's not at his desk,
but I already set a date.
Can you wait here a moment?
Okay.
You sure work fast, Mr. Chadchai.
So now I'm the largest shareholder.
Yes, I already handled everything for you.
Here.
Your compensation.
I hope it's enough for all your effort.
Okay, thank you very much, Mr. Thee.
What are you going to do next, Mr. Thee?
You can leave for the day.
I'll let you know what to do next.
Sure.
Mook!
Come on in.
- About yesterday--
- I'm here to present the edited work.
Has Mr. Pitak told you?
Yes, he has.
Mook, we need to talk. It's important.
I'll wait for you in the meeting room.
Are you ready?
It's our home, Prao.
I worked hard to earn money
for this house.
Isn't it a bit too small, Pat?
What if we have a child?
There won't be room for our child to run.
Plus,
my dad already arranged a house for us.
I actually like it here,
but if my dad saw it,
he wouldn't let me live here.
You know how much he worries about me.
How about this?
You could rent out this house.
That way, you can have some extra income.
We're late! Let's hurry
before the traffic gets bad.
Come on.
Whose house is this?
It's mine.
It looks cute.
Why'd you bring me here?
I wanted you to borrow it
and use it as your studio.
Really?
You'd really let me use this house
as my studio?
Yes.
I don't want you
to leave your goals behind.
You're the first person
to encourage me to do what I love.
Thank you for appreciating my passion.
But it would be better
if you'd let me rent it.
I don't want to bother you
and borrow it for free.
Let's discuss that later.
Why don't you take a look inside?
Won't it be too big of a risk?
Our company's too small for this project.
You're always so scared.
That's why our company never grew.
Yeah.
Fortune favors the bold.
If you keep being scared,
when will you beat Mook?
Please consider it.
I think it's the perfect time
and opportunity for us.
If we join the bidding
with Mrs. Anna backing us,
we'll win, no matter what.
But for a project of that scale,
our company still lacks
so many qualifications.
For the paperwork,
we just have to edit it however they want.
We'll have someone helping us anyway.
Once we win the project,
it's never too late for us
to make a plan later.
Stop thinking already. I've met Mrs. Anna.
I can tell from her face
she's got good aura.
She can definitely help us.
Kuk,
I can assure you, if we win this project,
Mook can never insult you again.
Mrs. Anna even told us
she'd get rid of A Round Trip
if we agreed to team up with her.
Right, Ma?
Here's the plan I made for next year.
Apart from The One,
we should look for more clients,
because many countries
have opened their borders,
and our regular clients
will probably start to travel again.
I agree.
Then, we can adjust our tours
according to the situation
and present them to our client as options.
Sure.
Yes, Ms. Bell?
Okay.
Ms. Bell called me.
Mook.
Don't you think Mr. Thee and his fiancée
seem a bit strange?
How so?
Well, the other day,
I saw Ms. Bella went
to see Boss at his office.
I wonder why.
They could've been talking about work.
But does Ms. Bella know about our work?
It doesn't matter what she was there for.
We should stay
out of Boss' business, got it?
Yes.
Alright.
Well, I ran into her in Phuket.
Back then, I didn't know her yet.
Until later, at that party at The One,
I found out she's Mr. Thee's fiancée.
She's a fascinating person.
She seems really confident,
but I feel bad for her sometimes.
You like Ms. Bell, don't you?
I could tell just from your eyes
how you feel about her.
What about Mr. Thee?
Are you sure about your decision?
You sure changed the topic fast.
Let's forget about that.
It's good to just let things be.
So.
What about Ms. Bell? What will you do now?
Does Mrs. Prao know yet?
Yes, Bee?
The rental unit told me
Ms. Bella already canceled her lease.
Really?
Okay.
Please keep an eye out.
Call me if anything comes up.
Got it, Prao.
Is this one good?
This one's blurry.
Yeah.
May,
I wish you could see Mook's face that day
at the shoot with Mr. Thee and Ms. Bella.
I felt so bad for her.
The vibe was like a battlefield.
Everyone was throwing bombs at each other.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Mook already agreed to back off.
She didn't have to go so far.
And what's more,
the knight in shining armor
who came and save Mook was Boss.
Boss probably did that to defend her
from that kind of situation.
You're right.
Poor Mook.
She shouldn't have to face any of this.
Isn't she here yet?
She's wrapping up the project
with Mr. Thee so we can finalize it today.
Poor Mook. And here I thought
she finally found someone good,
yet now she has to face all this.
She probably won't date for a while.
That woman's got nothing to do with me.
Saifah!
If he'll choose a woman like you over me,
who adopted him, then so be it.
But if you're hoping to marry into money,
then dream on.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya