But I'm just not ready to face
the same problems again.
Please just return
to your fiancée and your mom.
Mook.
- Boss!
You told me to compete with you, remember?
…which is that Bell
is the fiancée of Mr. Thee,
an executive at TJ Group.
We're also about to have great news
to share with you all very soon.
MOOK
I've driven Mrs. Anna to her place.
I still can't get ahold of Mook.
She might not want to talk to you for now
because the press conference today
probably got published on social media
by some agencies already.
I want to know where Mook is right now.
Got it.
I'll try to contact her.
Yes, Mr. Chadchai?
Sure.
I'll see you when we sign the contract.
We're here.
Do you think this place
could be turned into a chic studio?
I want to make it my office
for when I design clothes.
It'll also be a spot for emerging
designers to showcase their work.
Would this be a good spot?
But I think this place
would work better as an office.
Why don't you ask Mr. Thee for advice
or ask for a room at The One?
Why should I ask him?
I can make my own decisions.
This has nothing to do with Thee anyway.
Can you come with me?
I'm not good at negotiating prices
or handling the details in the agreements.
I'm busy.
Come on in.
Do you like this?
It looks pretty good. What do you think?
Maybe this one.
Here's the lease agreement.
Thank you.
I may need to review
all the terms on here again.
I may need to make
some adjustments or additions.
Of course.
Would you and your girlfriend
like a short-term or long-term lease?
Can we discuss it first?
We'll let you know soon.
Sure.
Do you like this place, honey?
May, why don't I see that guy?
Will he really show up?
He will.
Ms. Ploy said he's here regularly.
Stay calm, or you'll look panicked.
He really came. What do we do now?
Don't be nervous. Just follow the plan.
Excuse me.
Can I sit with you?
Sure.
Hey, have we met before?
That's an old one.
Why? If we never met,
would you not want to talk?
Of course I would.
Who would let a pretty girl like you
stay so lonely?
Cheers.
KEMTIT
He took the bait. What do we do now?
Mr. Pitak, are you sure Mook came here?
Yes, Mr. Thee. Mr. Suetrong said
the whole team went there.
Top's here now. He's talking to May.
MOOK
How's the situation?
Everything going according to plan?
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Sorry, that's my car key.
Hold on. I can get it for you.
Thank you.
What?
My dear client,
why are you calling me now?
Excuse me. I dropped something here.
You wanna book more?
MS. BANGORN: CALL BACK ASAP
I'D LIKE TO BOOK MORE TOURS
I'm not sure if it's there.
Can you help me find it?
Found it. Thank you.
Here it is.
Hello, Ms. Bangorn?
Yes, Ms. Bangorn.
It's really loud where I'm at.
Can you give me a moment?
I'm outside right now. Please hang on.
Mook, what should we do?
Tell May to try and lure him
into taking her to his usual place.
We'll hurry and follow them there,
so we can get inside and find evidence.
Whan, go with May too, just to be safe.
Sure.
What if Top hurts Ms. May and Whan?
If it goes according to our plan,
he won't be able to touch them.
You're no lightweight, huh?
You've had so many with me.
I'm not as good as you, though.
You had so many drinks,
yet you still look normal.
I'm a little tipsy now.
One more?
Sure.
Are you good?
No! Her phone's here…
Whan, where's May?!
Kemtit! I… I only
went outside to call Mook for a bit,
but now they're gone.
Why haven't those three come out yet?
Let me go find them.
Whan, why are you still inside?
May's gone. And so is that guy.
What? May's gone?
- Top!
- Where?
Hey, look!
Top took Ms. May already!
Whan, hurry and call the cops.
Then follow me right away.
I'll share you my location.
Okay, got it.
FUN PLAZA
It's strange.
Why'd Ms. May agree
to get in his car so easily?
No!
- What?
Why didn't the car in front of us go?!
Why'd it have to turn red now?!
We lost them. What do we do, Mook?
Where should we go to next?
How about my condo?
Let's go to my place instead.
I assure you you'll like it.
I know where
that scumbag's taking Ms. May.
Mook, it's green now. Go!
Who the hell is it?
- What?!
- Your drink, sir.
What the hell?
- Quick, let's go!
- Hey!
Ms. May! Ms. May?
Can you hear me? Wake up, Ms. May!
- Ms. May!
- He really did set up a camera!
Ms. May, get up slowly.
- Ms. May!
- Now you're asking for it!
‪Let go!
- Let go!
- Stop!
- Let go of her!
- Let go!
- No! Mook!
- Mook!
- Get May out of here! Hurry!
- Ms. May!
Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Hurry!
Go! Be careful!
Let's go.
- No!
- You're really asking for it, huh?
Let go!
- Come here.
- Let go! No!
No!
Let go!
Let go…
Mook!
Stop! This is the police!
I didn't do anything!
We got a report that you lured
a woman here to assault her.
- I don't know anything.
- Move!
- I didn't do it!
- Let's go!
Please let me go!
- Come on!
- Let me go. I didn't do it!
- Move.
- Officer!
- Come on.
- Please let me go!
Move!
- May, May!
- Sis!
May!
Are you okay, May? May!
- Kem…
- May!
Kemtit.
Go with May.
I'll stay here and look after Mook.
Okay.
- Take her bag.
- May.
- Watch out.
- Okay.
- Please mind your head.
Stop resisting!
Move it.
Just watch your backs.
I'm coming for you all.
We have solid evidence.
No one can help you now.
Go pay for your crimes in jail.
We'll need you all at the station
for statements.
- Of course.
- Let's go!
Move!
Get in!
You did it, Ploy.
Mook, are you okay?
Mook,
you're bleeding.
It's just a scratch. I'll be fine.
Top's arrested now.
You two won't have to be afraid anymore.
Mook, worry about yourself
instead of others for once, would you?
Let's get her to a hospital.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Yes? Hello, Boss. Mook is injured.
Just fess up.
We've got solid evidence here.
That's just part of it.
There are many other videos, Officer.
What are you on about?
I've never done that stuff!
You caught me with a girl at a hotel
and got jealous,
so you made all this up to accuse me.
Why are you doing this to me?
Stop pretending to be a good person, Top.
Everyone knows your true colors now!
Officer,
there's enough evidence
for him to be locked up now, right?
Don't listen to her! She's lying.
She's just mad I cheated.
You're the one who's lying!
Your evil ends here, Top.
I'd like to file a report against him too.
He filmed me and threatened me.
He assaulted me too.
I'd like to file a report too.
Fine!
File your reports.
I'm not scared.
My family's rich. I'll be fine.
Just watch your backs.
I'll make sure you pay!
Officer, why are you grabbing me?
Let me go!
Just watch yourselves, bitches! Officer!
NURSE - ASSESSMENT ROOM 1
I'm alright now. You should go home.
You know what you did
was really dangerous, right?
What if he hurt you or if he had a gun?
What would you do?
But it's over now, and I'm alright too.
You call this "alright"?
Did he have to hit your vital organs
for you to realize?
Don't do this again, Mook.
If someone's got to be hurt,
it has to be me, not you.
Mook.
- Boss.
- Bell?
Why are you here, Thee?
Are you hurt? Are you wounded?
Mook, are you badly hurt?
It's just a scratch.
Nothing bad. What about Ploy and Khim?
They're at the station,
giving the police more information.
I want to see my friends.
Can you give me a ride, Boss?
Of course.
I'll take care of her, Mr. Thee.
Don't worry.
Mook.
Does it hurt a lot?
Ploy, are you okay?
VISION - BE LOYAL, ENSURE
OUR NATION'S SECURITY, EARN PEOPLE'S TRUST
I did it.
I dealt with the scumbag who hurt us.
I did it, Khim.
Good job. You're the best, Ploy.
Ploy, Khim,
is everything alright?
It's all over. You're all safe now.
- You're okay now.
- Yeah.
ARRESTED FOR VIDEO BLACKMAIL
POLICE HAVE ARRESTED
MR. UDOM MONGKOLPANICH
WHO'S SECRETLY FILMED AND BLACKMAILED
MANY WOMEN. MANY MORE ARE FILING REPORTS
Pa, Ma, I'm sorry.
No.
Why are you apologizing, Ploy?
I'm the one who should be apologizing
for introducing you
to such an evil guy.
That's why you're in this much pain.
I'm sorry, honey.
No, Ma…
It's okay, honey.
Don't blame yourself, Ma.
Let's just forget about it.
It's over now.
Don't cry, Ma.
Move back in with us, honey.
Now that it's all over the news,
what do you plan to do?
If you don't want to see anyone yet,
just ask for some time off,
or you can quit your job too.
Then we'll make plans
on what to do next.
I'm really sorry.
Khim,
I saw the news about you.
Are you okay?
What you saw on the news is true.
I'll make sure he pays for his crimes.
I never thought
you'd also be one of his victims.
People these days are so scary.
They can seem so nice,
but they're hiding their evil side.
It was partly my fault.
I was too reckless and pleasure-seeking.
Otherwise, I never would've got into this.
I heard they're setting up a committee
to look into your case.
I think it'd be really unfair
if you got fired.
Hey.
Bell!
- Hi, Thee.
- You're here so early.
Sit down, Thee.
What's wrong?
I wanted to ask you about something.
You know Mr. Anapat too?
Of course. Mr. Anapat
is the CEO of A Round Trip Travel,
my hotel's partner.
How about you? How'd you two meet?
Just a coincidence.
How come you came with Mr. Pat last night?
It's a long story, Thee.
Yesterday I saw Mr. Anapat and Mook.
They seemed really close.
Does he have a crush on her too?
I don't know. If you want to know,
you should ask him yourself.
Where are you going?
I'm heading out for a meeting.
Is there anything else?
Here it is. I got it from a famous place.
I had to wait in a long line.
They say it's super yummy.
Please eat up, so you'll feel better.
She's smiling!
I got so scared last night.
I'm glad you and Mook are okay.
That jerk!
How dare he hurt May!
I'll kill him with my own hands!
Well, if we let an evil guy like him go,
he'd go on and hurt more people.
Aw, just admit you're worried about her.
You know me too well. Cheers!
- What?!
- Mook!
Why are you here?
Wait till your wound's healed!
It's just a scratch.
I wasn't hurt that badly.
May, how are you?
Why didn't you take some time off?
Mook,
thank you so much.
I'm doing better now.
I'm still a little paranoid and sad.
I've never been drugged before in my life.
It was my very first time.
I got all dazed and dizzy.
I wasn't in control at all.
I'm just glad you're okay. I'm sorry.
And I really appreciate you all
for taking a risk to help catch Top.
I should be thanking you. You too.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Mook.
I've got to go.
See you.
Hello.
How are you holding up?
I…
I'm alright now.
Please excuse me. I've got work to do.
I'm really worried about you, you know?
Don't risk your life like that again.
I wouldn't know what to do
if something were to happen to you.
Is there anything else?
Something work-related?
Yes.
I came to tell you to get ready to go
to Narin Beach Resort with me tomorrow.
Why? It's not nearly time
for the event yet.
I'm signing a contract
with Ms. Narin tomorrow.
That's got nothing to do with me.
Why do I need to go?
I wanted to adjust some of the plans
for the event we're organizing there.
You're in charge of that, no?
Therefore, you have to come
with me tomorrow.
You look so pretty.
- There you are.
- I'm here!
Thank you so much, you guys.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Once again, I'm sorry, Ploy.
Thank you for understanding.
Friends should be there
for each other anyway.
Sometimes we might argue or fight,
but we'd never leave each other.
Oh, Mook,
I saw the news about Mr. Thee's fiancée.
What's that about?
Why'd you never tell us about it?
I just found out not long ago too.
If he can get engaged, then you can too.
Come again?
Mr. Pat, of course!
You and Mr. Pat
are perfect for each other.
Everyone's rooting for you
to be together, so just date for real.
Mr. Pat's my boss, my brother,
and a good friend of mine.
He's also very understanding
and gives great advice,
but I've never had feelings for him.
And I think he sees me in the same way.
Are you okay, Mook?
You got your heart broken again.
I'm worried about you.
I'm okay.
Maybe I'm lucky in games
and unlucky in love.
But either way, I have a mom
and a daughter who love me very much.
And I also have you two, my best friends,
who support me with everything.
Come on. Give me your hand.
From now on,
no matter what we may face,
we'll get through it together.
Okay?
Okay.
Good. I love you two.
As if you haven't seen it before.
- Your dress slayed both of us.
- Can I pull off sexy too?
Here we go.
- Here we go.
- Try it. Embrace it.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
I'm trying to reset myself.
Come on in.
Someone's here to see you, Mr. Pat.
It's you!
What's Mr. Thee's fiancée doing here?
Yeah. Why'd she have to come
all the way here to see our boss?
- Oh, could it be--
- Hey!
Quiet!
Could it be she's here
to end our contract?
She might be mad at Mr. Thee
for liking Mook,
so much so, she's ending our contract.
I hope it's not that bad.
Let's not jump to conclusions here.
Why else would she come
to our office then, Mr. Suetrong?
What?
KOH CHANG - CHIANG MAI - KRABI - KOH LIPE
Mr. Suetrong!
How'd you find this place?
It isn't that hard, really.
I just had to ask Mr. Pitak.
Are you that surprised that I'm here?
You like Ms. Mook, don't you?
I asked Mr. Thee, and he told me
to ask you myself.
Why do you want to know?
Well, I wanted to get closer to you,
but if you like Ms. Mook, then that's it.
What if I told you
I didn't have feelings for Mook?
Then I'll get to know you,
so we can become closer.
Bee, there's something I want you to see.
Isn't this Prao's husband, Pat?
It's him, right? I happened to be
viewing the same building that day,
and I saw Mr. Anapat with Ms. Bella,
who publicly confirmed
her engagement with Mr. Thee recently.
You should let me cover this story.
Mr. Pat's about to enter politics.
If you wrote about it,
you might get into trouble.
Is that so?
Ms. Prao's father is a big shot.
He wouldn't let anyone
discredit his son-in-law so easily.
Who's the girl?
Her name's Bella.
She's Mr. Thee's fiancée.
Mr. Thee's fiancée?
Why was she seen with Pat?
How'd they meet?
I know, right? When I saw
the photo, I was surprised too.
They seem really close too.
Thank God it was my junior reporter
who saw them
because if this photo got out,
it could damage
Mr. Pat's career in politics.
Don't worry, I'll reward you for this.
Thanks for looking out for me.
It'd be great
if you could keep an eye on him.
Of course, Prao.
If you don't want to see anyone yet,
just ask for some time off,
or you can quit your job too.
Then we'll make plans
on what to do next.
ACCOUNTING DEPARTMENT
We're happy for you
for getting through it, Ploy.
We wish you lots of happiness from now on.
Here you go.
What's all this about?
Haven't you been online?
So many pages posted about your story.
Everyone's rooting for you
for standing up to a scumbag
like that guy.
You're really brave, Ploy.
If it happened to me,
I don't know if I'd have your courage.
You did great.
- You did great.
- You rock!
Woman of the year.
Great job.
What's this about?
Why'd our clients cancel on us?
It's a huge group of them too, no?
Who's in charge of this tour group?
It's Ms. Usa.
Go get her in here, then.
She hasn't come in yet.
I tried to contact her,
but she turned off her phone.
And our clients also complained
that our service isn't good like before,
when Ms. Mook was still here.
Go. You can leave now.
I brought you some dim sum.
What's wrong? You look stressed.
Are you crazy? No way!
You can't ask Mook for help!
But it's seriously bad this time, Ma.
We just lost a huge group of clients.
That's a big loss,
and we're already struggling.
No money coming in, just going out.
No, no, no! Don't say that.
Our company's great, and we're prospering.
Keep repeating that.
Prospering downhill, more like.
Our old clients keep leaving,
and we have no new clients.
I don't know what to do, Ma.
Ask Usa to help you find
more clients, then.
Usa, you say?
Our clients don't want her anymore!
She's rude,
and she gives horrible service.
- It was so different when we had Mook.
- Stop it!
Stop praising her already.
I won't allow you to ask
for her help, no matter what.
I'll handle this myself.
I'll find you some clients.
- Really, Ma?
- Yes.
And remember,
we've got this, even without Mook.
- Ms. Mook!
- Hello, Ms. Narin.
Hello.
My staff told me you've arrived,
so I wanted to welcome you myself
in case you needed something.
Thank you.
About that day,
you're feeling better now, right?
Sorry for mentioning it.
I'm just really worried about you.
Thank you, Ms. Narin.
I'm finding the best way out too.
But I can't tell how I really feel either.
Have you ever had something
weighing on you, Ms. Narin?
Of course.
- Hello.
Everything's all set.
Then, if you'll excuse me.
Okay.
Mr. Thee said to invite you too, Ms. Mook.
- Sure.
- Let's go together then, Ms. Mook.
Let's go.
SIGNATURE
MR. THEECHUDA TEERASU - PARTNER
SIGNATURE - MS. NARIN PONGSATORNPITAK
I hope you'll remember our promise.
Yes,
I promise to help make this place better.
Thank you.
Where's my phone?
Everything's handled now.
Not yet. This is just the beginning.
- I want all of this resort's shares.
- Don't worry.
I'm already talking to them.
There shouldn't be a problem.
With the price you offer,
they're all willing to sell.
Good,
if everyone's on board,
I'll leave the rest to you, Mr. Chadchai.
I don't want to waste any time.
Of course, Mr. Thee.
Did Mr. Thee do something
to make you uncomfortable?
Should I go there?
It's okay, Boss.
We mostly just talk about work.
I can handle it.
I'm leaving tomorrow, so don't worry.
Feel free to call me anytime
if something comes up.
Sure, thank you.
What do you want from me?
I just want to be sure
that my decision
won't affect anyone's relationship.
I have very few friends.
Almost none, actually.
And I feel comfortable talking to you,
so I want you to be a friend
who can give me advice.
And I want to be sure you're okay
with having me as a friend too.
So, what do you think? Would you mind it?
Won't it affect
your relationship with Mr. Thee?
Because I don't want to damage
anyone's relationship either.
Thee and I are just fulfilling our duties.
I think I got my answer.
I'll get out of your hair now. Bye-bye.
PRAO
Yes, Prao?
Mr. Thee wanted you to have this.
Thank you.
For our special day,
please come to dinner with me.
I have something important to tell you.
I just wanted to return your stuff.
And don't do this again. It isn't funny.
Calm down, Mook.
I just wanted to clear things up.
I want us to go back to the way we were.
I want you to trust me.
Trust you?
After you just announced your fiancée
and you're pretending
like nothing happened?
Mook,
please listen to me.
I'll show my mom
that we really love each other
and that I'll still be able
to do my job well.
What about your fiancée?
Please don't drag me into that mess again.
I don't want any more trouble
with your mother.
I just need you to believe in me.
I like to stay realistic.
It might hurt sometimes…
but please don't make me go back again.
Mook.
Ms. Mook!
What's wrong? What's wrong, Ms. Mook?
It's okay.
Where have I seen this kid before?
If you have someone else, just admit it.
Is that so hard, Pat?
…because my son's made the same mistake.
That's why I'm worried about Mr. Thee,
since I'm a mother like you.
If you can't make Ms. Mook happy,
you should let her go.
This is my problem.
I can deal with it myself.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya