[Episode 20]
You might've moved on,
but I haven't.
Cao Ping.
Look forward.
Stop living on the past.
From the day I went to prison,
I did try to move on.
For the past two years,
I've been straightening up
to get out and reunite with my sister.
What exactly do you want?
Nothing.
You listen to me:
stay away from my sister.
Otherwise, I'll make life hard
for everyone around you.
I never touched your sister.
Our beef is
between you and me.
If you've got guts, come at me.
Stop fighting!
I'll call the police if you keep going!
Xing Wu!
Xing Wu,
We're not done yet.
Who is he?
An old acquaintance.
Why did you start fighting?
- It's nothing.
- You were about to brawl.
How is that nothing?
Before you came to Zhazhating,
I've got into plenty of
fights and brawls.
Xing Wu.
If anything happens,
you must tell me.
Our beef is
between you and me.
If you've got guts, come at me.
Let my family alone.
That's too good for you.
Xing Wu,
as long as I'm alive,
I'll never let you have peace.
I'm going to drag you
through the mud I'm in.
- Thank you.
- Auntie, I'll take it.
Okay.
Sent you the money.
Let's go buy some meat.
- What else do you want to eat?
- Anything is fine.
Li, here.
Fresh tenderloin. Take it?
Fresh?
- Then I want this one.
- All right.
And two pork trotters.
Sure, no problem.
- Here you go.
- Okay, let me.
Come back if you like it!
Grandma said
that you and Wu have been studying hard lately,
so we need to make sure you eat well.
Ye,
why are you so distracted?
I'm fine.
It's Xing Wu.
I feel like
he's always got something on mind.
Are you having a tiff?
No.
I just don't get him sometimes.
Auntie,
he's like a clam.
You know there's a stone inside,
rubbing against it,
but you just can't pry it open.
Do you ever feel that way?
Yes, of course I do.
When Wu was little,
I had the energy to look after him.
I always wanted to know
what was on his mind.
I was afraid he was bottling everything up
and hurting himself.
When I was young,
I wanted to be a good mom, too.
And then?
Later on, I couldn't even take care of myself.
I had to think of paying off debts
and making ends meet.
I had little time for him,
but he was low-maintenance.
They say the squeaky wheel gets the grease,
but he never cried,
and never asked me for anything.
Over time,
I just acted like nothing was wrong,
like everything was fine.
I got used to it.
Let's not dwell on that.
Come on, let's go get some yams.
Braised pork trotter with yams.
Wu's favorite.
Your recent grades have been
like a roller coaster.
Dropped nearly a hundred points this time.
You need to step it up
on the next exam.
Don't worry, I know what I'm doing.
Cousin. Wu.
Don't you usually bike?
Why take the bus?
Got a flat tire.
It's been so windy lately.
Can't be bothered to ride.
Plus, we can squeeze in
some vocab review on the way.
Nice. Good to see you studying.
Xing Wu, you can't afford to lose.
I won't.
What's that for?
See if its location sharing still works.
Can't you just call me?
What if it's an emergency?
Three taps are always easier.
Let's go.
Wen Hui, have you heard?
Cao Fan's brother did two years,
because he stabbed someone.
Really?
- Don't just repeat rumors.
- That must be fake.
Isn't her family pretty well off?
She's always in the top three.
Think about it.
If it weren't true,
would everyone be talking about it?
So it has to be real.
People are giving all the details.
They're even saying Xing Wu was involved.
What does that mean?
I saw Cao Fan over the weekend.
She was scrubbing shoes in a laundry.
I went up to her and she got all shifty-eyed.
She said her brother
runs a business in Shenzhen.
To me, he's an ex-con.
No wonder her clothes have that laundry smell.
She claimed that her clothes
were sent to the cleaners?
Who is she kidding, acting like a rich girl?
The only reason anyone
hangs out with her is to copy her homework.
Otherwise, who would?
Having a tea party here?
Why are you always showing up?
Did you hear everything?
From which part?
The part about Cao Fan's brother,
or about herself?
You were talking so loud,
Why not just grab a loudspeaker
and let the whole school hear?
So what if you heard us?
She spread the word about your dad before.
I was just getting back at her for you.
Don't bother.
You were right there
spreading those rumors yourself.
Acting like you helped clear my name.
Just a friendly reminder:
You two are tight with her now,
but who knows what'll happen down the road?
You heard all that, didn't you?
Now I'm everyone's target.
That must make you happy.
I don't feel good about it.
It's never right and honorable
to attack someone
over their family.
Every family has its ups and downs.
We're students. We should focus on studying.
No one wants to be put
in the spotlight like that.
Don't you agree?
Mind your own business.
No one asked you to stand up for me.
I'm just speaking up for what's right,
not for you.
Your nose is bleeding.
Here, tissue.
Don't pretend to care about me.
We're not friends.
And,
you'd better not tell anyone
about Xing Wu and my brother.
I don't want to get dragged into
whatever's between them.
I owe you one for now.
Between them?
A boy at the competition
had it out for him,
and slashed him
in the back
with a knife.
Cao Fan's brother did two years,
because he stabbed someone.
If it weren't true,
would everyone be talking about it?
So it has to be real.
They're even saying Xing Wu was involved.
Isn't one camera by the entrance
enough?
There's no need for an extra one inside.
This brand's camera
- isn't cheap.
- Nail.
Wasting money.
Better safe than sorry.
Yang Gang has Cao Ping backing him now.
They are going to
keep coming around, looking for trouble.
Last time, with all those people showing up,
nothing serious happened.
So don't be so tense.
But what if one time I can't get here in time?
And things blow up?
An extra camera means extra protection,
and offers evidence to the police.
I'll be fine.
Cao Ping is after you, anyway.
If you need more hands,
you must tell us.
Hei and I are ready to ride with you anytime.
Ride? Ride for what?
You've watched too many gangster movies.
If your sister knew I got you into a fight,
she'd kill both of us.
That's true.
Sometimes,
fists don't solve anything.
If Cao Ping
keeps messing with you,
what are you going to do?
Don't worry about it.
Hei.
Wu, what's up?
I've got exams coming up,
so I probably
won't have much time to come to Shunyi Repair.
Kind of worried about leaving Canine alone.
If you have some free time,
could you keep an eye on him for me?
Wu, you don't even have to ask. Don't worry.
The guys and I will drop whenever we can.
Just focus on your studies
and do well on the exams.
Thanks.
We're brothers. No need for thanks.
We all really envy you now.
Look at you in that school uniform.
You look so sharp.
People like us might never
leave this little shop,
but you're different, Wu.
You're smart.
You've got a mind for studying.
You fought your way back to school,
so don't let the old garbage
drag you down again.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
Go get them, Wu.
I'm off.
Come on, eat up.
Why the sudden skewers?
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
There's a rumor
going around school lately
that Cao Fan's brother
just got out
after two years in jail.
Have you heard it?
Xing Wu's sworn enemy
is Cao Fan's brother, right?
I have no idea.
Like there's any gossip I don't know?
Must be fake.
Yeah.
The scar on Xing Wu's back.
He got that from a knife two years ago,
and the guy did two years for it.
Just got out.
Am I right?
Not cooked yet.
Xing Wu is afraid he'll come after me,
so he had you two shadow me.
Right?
This is bland. I'll get some dipping sauce.
Feels like we don't have enough skewers.
I'll go get some more.
You two are terrible actors.
I can tell by your faces that I'm right.
Sorry.
The number you have dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
Sorry.
The number you have dialed...
[Lighthouse by the sea]
[Distance: 8.5 km]
Qing Ye found out about your beef
with Cao Ping.
- Qing Ye!
- She didn't let us follow her.
- I'm worried she might go find him.
- Qing Ye!
Qing Ye!
You...
Why are you so out of breath?
Sorry.
Just let me hold you for a minute.
My phone died.
Right before it shut off,
I saw you'd called me,
so I sent you my location.
I didn't realize
it would make you think I was in danger.
I'm just glad you're okay.
Actually,
after I sent the location,
for a split second,
I thought about
faking an emergency,
let you not find me,
so you'd know what it's like
to wait for an answer that never comes.
But then I figured,
forget it.
Either way,
you have the right to keep your secrets.
Then I'll tell you
what happened two years ago.
Two years ago,
Xing Guo Dong mortgaged Xuan Island.
We were buried in debt.
Grandma was in the hospital
and we desperately needed money.
So I decided
to enter the city basketball tournament.
If I won the MVP award,
there'd be a cash prize.
[Lianhai City Future Star High School
Basketball League]
[Attack Team vs. Xuan Island Team]
Xuan Island! Xuan Island! We're the best!
Xuan Island! Xuan Island!
Xing Wu! Xing Wu!
Cao Ping was also
in that tournament.
At that time, he was at a vocational school.
In his third year.
For him,
winning that tournament
was his last shot to be recruited
into a sports academy.
But he had an Achilles tendon injury.
Xuan Island! Xuan Island!
Attack! Attack!
Conquer the world!
Ping, how's your foot?
I'm fine.
We have to give it our all. You hear me?
Given how good you are,
even injured,
MVP title won't be a problem. Right?
It's really down to all of us.
Xuan Island! Xuan Island!
Attack! Attack!
We're the best!
Xuan Island! Xuan Island!
Go for it!
Nice shot! Xuan Island scores again!
That's Xing Wu?
As a rookie, he's unstoppable.
A force to be reckoned with!
What a dark horse!
Attack's Cao Ping
has really met his match this time.
I wonder if his MVP title might slip away.
Go! Go! Go!
Are you okay?
Xing Wu!
Let's congratulate Xing Wu
for winning the title of
Most Valuable Player in this year's league!
Congratulations to Xuan Island!
Xuan Island! Xuan Island! Xuan Island!
Congrats to Wu for getting MVP!
And the prize money!
Xuan Island champs!
Order whatever you want tonight.
It's on me.
Really?
Have I ever lied to you?
Hello!
20 kidney skewers!
And 20 pork fat skewers!
Coming right up!
Neither of you is leaving until you finish.
Hi, 20 meat skewers. Whatever else looks good.
Got it. One sec.
Wu,
Cao Ping is coming over.
Look at that loser face.
Definitely salty about the loss.
Another toast to Wu.
Cheers!
Xing Wu.
Congrats on the win
and on getting MVP today.
I know your leg is injured.
Otherwise,
maybe you would have been the MVP.
I heard not only did you get the prize money,
but a provincial team coach
came to recruit you.
I'm not up for that.
Being a pro athlete is not for me.
I just need the money.
Don't give me that.
Can't you stand up when you talk to Ping?
Do you know how hard
Ping risked for this tournament?
Risked his life for what?
So he hurt his leg. What a big deal!
He's standing here with all his limbs.
You want to join the provincial team?
Go talk to the coach yourselves.
Wu has zero interest
in the provincial team at all.
What's your angle? Looking for a fight?
I'm not looking for a fight.
I'm just telling the truth. What's wrong?
The truth is not allowed?
A leg injury doesn't make him a cripple.
- Don't start something, okay?
- Hey, you...
All you've got is hitting?
What's your problem?
Don't make me do it.
That's enough, both of you.
My buddy's got a big mouth.
Sorry about that.
I'll toast you.
Hold on.
Use this instead.
Exactly. Who do you think you are?
This is how you toast Ping?
Am I being too easy on you?
- What's your problem?
- Don't push me!
- What do you mean?
- Nothing.
Try me. Make my day.
Lay a hand on me and I'll drop to the ground.
My parents will be getting a new car out of it.
Try me!
By the way, Cao Ping.
Provincial teams don't take gimps, do they?
You asked for it!
Come on!
Fuzz!
Cao Ping.
I have no intention of
joining the provincial team.
Xing Wu!
Wu!
Call 120, quick!
Anyone!
Call an ambulance!
Cao Ping lost it
and slashed me in the back.
He got two years.
If
that hadn't happened,
you would've become a pilot, right?
Maybe it's fate.
I thought
I was so close to my dream.
Take off your shirt.
Turn around.
Xing Wu.
You can go now.
I once heard someone say
that the days crushed by pain
are like
the mud after the tide goes out.
It looks messy,
but
when the sun rises,
the shell fragments
hidden within it shimmer.
That shimmer
becomes the mark
of your life.
We all have
our own path to follow.
Take me,
I thought I'd be
studying abroad by now.
Look at me instead.
Still, I'm not bitter.
Fate brought me here,
to live a different life
in Zhazhating.
In fact, I'm grateful.
Because every second here
has made my youth burn brighter.
Anyway...
it's getting late.
Let's head back.
Good luck
on your test tomorrow.
Don't worry.
I've got this.
Come on.
- Over there.
- Okay.
She has been on her own a lot lately.
Studying while eating?
Look at her showing off.
Such a prig.
If she can't even get selected after all that,
I'd be embarrassed for her.
She's hitting the books.
Keep it up.
Keep grinding and she still can't beat Qing Ye.
You go ahead. I'll be right back.
Let's just watch.
She's so insufferable.
Why are you staring at us?
What's up?
Eat.
Your food is getting cold.
None of your business.
You don't look well.
Are you okay?
Mind your own business.
All right, begin.
Teacher! Teacher!
Cao Fan fainted!
Cao Fan! What's wrong?
Cao Fan! Cao Fan!
Can you hear me?
[Emergency]
Hello? What's up?
Ping, bad news.
You told me to keep an eye on your sister.
She's unconscious at the county hospital.
Doesn't look good.
Xing Wu and his cousin
brought her in.
I bet they have something to do with it.
Doctor,
how is she?
38.9 degrees.
That's a high fever.
We ran a blood test.
She has low blood sugar,
some malnutrition,
and her nosebleed is from dry nasal membranes.
Clearly, she's been staying up late
and not getting enough rest.
Doctor, when will she wake up?
Given her condition, she's still very weak.
But nothing too serious.
Let her rest.
- Page me if anything comes up.
- Okay.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Zhu,
how about you head back to school?
We'll stay with her.
All right.
I'll come to relieve you
after evening self-study.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Xing Wu.
I could tell something
was off with her before the exam.
I should've told the teacher sooner.
Don't overthink it.
The doctor just said
it's nothing serious.
Don't worry.
I'll go get you something to eat.
You're awake.
How are you feeling? Any better?
Here's a thermos.
Weren't you looking for one earlier?
Take it for now.
Thank you.
The water room is over there.
- I can go by myself.
- Okay.
I know you blame me.
I haven't been a good brother.
You have every reason to ignore me.
If anyone bullies you at school,
remember to tell me.
And then what?
Are you going to start a fight
like you did before?
Plenty of people have bullied me.
Can you fight them all?
Just leave.
I can't sleep with you here.
Take care of yourself.
Xing Wu and his cousin brought her in.
I guarantee they're involved.
Plenty of people have bullied me.
Can you fight them all?
Where do you think you're going?
You're Cao Fan's brother, Cao Ping, right?
I think you've got it wrong.
Cao Fan and I aren't enemies.
Save your excuses.
My sister ended up like this
because of you and your brother.
You've got it wrong.
This is a hospital.
People will come by any minute.
You'd better calm down.
You think I care about that?
Your sister didn't faint because of me.
We were taking an exam.
She suddenly started sweating a lot,
and then she collapsed.
[Anzi County First People's Hospital]
[Distance: 500m]
Young man, your fried rice!
Let go of me!
- Let go!
- Who are you trying to call?
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
You go back first.
I'll talk to him.
No way. But...
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
Go back.
Okay.
I'll go back.
If you aren't back in ten minutes,
I'm calling the police.
Just go back.
I told you not to touch my family.
Got some fight in you.
What if I insist on messing with them?
What do you want?
Simple.
I want you to lose
everyone as I did.
Then I'll be satisfied.
Then come at me.
Three days,
we'll settle this once and for all.
Fine.
Sit here.
Hello,
two more orders of fried rice.
- No green onions, mild spice.
- Got it.
And add that last order to my tab, too.
- Sure.
- Add an egg to one of them.
Alright, no problem.
Are you hurt?
No.
You got scared, didn't you?
It's my fault for dragging you into this.
I didn't lose anything.
How did it go with him?
Nothing. It's fine.
Don't worry.
I'll handle it.
What brings you here?
Brought your meal.
What'd you make me?
Dumplings, red braised pork belly,
and some other dishes.
All your favorites.
Wait for me a moment.
- Brother...
- Why are you staring at me like that?
I'm eyeing a watch.
It looks really cool.
A watch?
What do you need a watch for?
- Well...
- Alright, let me see.
Let me see the page.
This one.
It does look nice.
Fine. After I win the tournament,
I'll buy it with the prize money.
Are you being discharged?
Don't act as if you know me.
I owe you one for yesterday.
I'll find a way to pay you back.
How about you owe me another favor,
and make it a big one next time?
What do you mean?
Go to the Winter Camp.
Are you giving me your spot?
But I have one condition:
Help your brother and Xing Wu make peace.