Abrasions on the hand…
…rib fracture… from CPR…
Darn! This will never end.
You scared me.
Too many reports. Someone take over.
I'm busy organizing files.
Same, I got inspection reports.
I can't either.
The MEJ is different from what I imagined.
Tell me about it.
Makes me want to go back
to university research labs ASAP.
Dr. Honda, you're finished?
-With ease.
-I still have some, if you're free.
I have plans tonight.
Oh, a date.
No.
Going for drinks with an old colleague.
Lucky.
See you later.
Shall we get to it then?
Okay.
…the coronary artery tissue of…
Dr. Matsubara.
-Can you put yourself on mute?
-What?
Sorry.
Welcome.
Hello.
Hey!
Hirono.
Here's your oden.
Hey, do you remember?
That massive pile-up on the highway.
Of course, I remember.
That was brutal.
We saw 30 patients in one night.
Pretty much just the two of us.
Once you've survived a scene like that,
nothing scares you anymore.
True.
And then, we had a toast
in that empty lobby afterward.
That canned beer
was the best in the world at that moment.
Spoken like a guy
who was drinking non-alcoholic.
More importantly, how's the new workplace?
MEJ, is it?
Yes.
It's the worst.
Really?
The police and everyone else
find us annoying.
I have no idea what my boss is thinking.
He's a weirdo.
I'm worked to the bone for low pay, too.
I see.
You've got it good.
Settled in nicely as a surgeon
at Meiwa University.
I should never have gone
into forensic medicine.
Honda, you know--
Don't start with the comforting words.
-Sorry, it's work.
-Top doctors have it tough.
Sorry, it's work I really can't miss.
Sure.
I'll make it up to you next time.
You know, I--
Just go.
You're busy, right?
Let's talk properly next time.
Good luck.
My head hurts.
A hangover?
Coming into work after partying?
That's just wrong.
You stink.
I went home after
my friend got called into work.
-An emergency patient?
-Yes.
He's a surgeon at Meiwa University.
He's moving up in the world. Unlike you.
Dr. Honda, the toxicology report…
I turned it in yesterday.
There's an error in the diagnosis
of the poison, please fix it.
No way, I was certain
everything was correct.
No, the lethal dose of Olanzapine
was overlooked.
Oh.
This is Medical Examiner Japan.
Someone please also
cross-reference it with past cases?
Okay.
There's so much to do
even without any autopsies.
I wish we got paid extra.
Yes.
Yes, goodbye.
Dr. Honda.
Yeah?
Where did your friend work?
Meiwa University Hospital?
What was that call?
There's a body of a person
who died an unnatural death.
What?
This can't be real.
He knows the victim?
It seems he was his friend.
They went drinking together last night.
Ms. Dojima! We haven't been able
to find his smartphone.
There are no surveillance cameras nearby.
We don't know what happened.
The cause of death
was a cerebral contusion
from a strong blow to the head.
Or perhaps internal organ damage
from multiple fractures.
This is a condition seen
when there is a violent collision.
Like a traffic accident?
In that case,
there would usually be secondary injuries
from being thrown onto the hood
or windshield,
and tertiary ones
from hitting the road's surface.
It doesn't add up.
Rather than that,
it looks as though he fell
from several meters above.
Are you saying he fell from the sky?
An example, going by the evidence I see.
-Supervisor.
-Yes?
Maybe the crime scene was elsewhere,
and he was moved here? Or something?
There are blood droplets
directly beneath the body.
It doesn't add up.
In any case,
he must have fallen somewhere
not too far from here.
Well, even if you say it's not too far…
-He really fell from the sky?
-Idiot!
Don't say stupid stuff, it's annoying.
Sorry.
These bloodstains…
What is it?
Possibly from when he fell,
but in that case
the amount of blood is far too small.
It doesn't add up.
Could we ask you a few questions?
Sure.
Okay. First, what was your relationship
with the victim?
We were colleagues when we worked
as ER doctors.
And you were with him last night?
We had dinner.
What time?
Dr. Honda.
You don't have to do the autopsy.
You can take--
Bureaucrats
are soft, aren't they?
Let's begin.
As a result of the autopsy,
the direct cause of death was indeed
a cerebral contusion from a strong
impact to the back of the head.
However, before that,
Mr. Hirono took a heavy blow
to his lower back.
I believe there is no doubt
that he fell from a height
of about ten meters, landing on his back.
At the moment, we have no reports
of people falling out of airplanes.
Of course not.
Furthermore, there were abrasions
on his right arm and left leg,
as if something had rubbed
against the skin.
They look like burns.
I wonder. Doesn't look like
the skin is peeling either.
What do you mean, they look like burns?
So he did not actually fall?
These injuries were not fatal,
and no doubt it was a death from falling.
Something bothering me is
that there is absolutely
no gas in his intestines.
His rectus abdominis muscle
is expanded out.
Temporary post-mortem expansion?
Probably.
Expansion?
Is there a connection to the fall?
That is also unknown.
Also,
in the back of his throat,
his lungs, and his hair
a small amount
of a powdery substance was found.
Detailed tests
are currently being carried out.
So in the end, we don't know anything.
That's right.
Not at this point.
Contact me if you find out anything.
Okay.
Same to you, Ms. Dojima.
I will if we find a witness who saw
a guy flying in the sky.
It's ridiculous.
First, we'll do questioning.
Yes, ma'am!
Could this powder-like stuff
be wood dust from these trees?
He climbed a tree and fell?
Could be, if we found
alcohol intoxication.
Then,
from the roof of this stadium?
But the distance from where he was found
is eight meters.
If he fell from there…
He would have to do a long jump.
Did he even fall on his own?
Maybe he was pushed?
Someone with a grudge against him?
That's not possible.
What?
There's no way someone
would hold a grudge against Hirono.
Dr. Honda, let's go.
Until the appraisal results are out,
I'm going to look into Hirono's work.
At the hospital?
Hirono cut the drinking session short,
saying he suddenly had work,
and then died.
He might have been meeting someone.
Come on…
When looking into
the victim's surroundings,
it's convenient to have someone
who knew him well with me.
I'd like to ask about
an incident at Miyagawa park…
Thank you for your cooperation.
Sir!
Are you a resident of that apartment?
Yes.
Could I speak with you for a moment?
A collision sound?
There was a terrible noise.
I rushed to open the window,
but I couldn't see anything.
Your daughter must have been startled too.
Yes.
I thought maybe
there had been an accident,
but then I heard the sound
of a car driving away,
so it was probably nothing.
A car driving away…
So good.
We'll re-examine if there were
any suspicious vehicles.
I'll re-examine.
There's no way a human
would fall from the sky.
No way at all.
I've talked to the surgery department.
Thank you.
Just a moment.
Okay.
I really am glad
you came along, Dr. Honda.
It's Hirono.
I had to come.
I…
think I should just be doing autopsies.
I am a forensic pathologist.
What kind of person was Hirono?
As a friend. It's just for reference.
He was a good guy.
Kind.
Passionate.
Not the kind of person
anyone would hold a grudge against.
Definitely not.
However, Hirono has passed away.
Perhaps there were aspects of his life
that you didn't know about, Dr. Honda.
Don't you think?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
He was still so young, it's such a shame.
What kind of person was Dr. Hirono?
Who knows?
We never talked about personal things.
I only remember scolding him.
What?
You were his supervising doctor,
right, Dr. Imabayashi?
Back when he was an intern.
He did nothing but make mistakes.
I don't want to speak ill of him,
now that he's no more.
Were things not going well at work?
Yes.
Or rather…
What is it?
Please tell us.
Look at this.
RESIGNATION LETTER
I got the day before he died.
He said he intended
to quit being a doctor.
Well, I suppose he wasn't suited for it.
Have you heard
from Dr. Honda?
No.
Oh, okay.
Do you know where you are?
-Please.
-Bandages.
I'll take this one.
Thanks.
I'll put some bandages on you.
One, two, three, okay.
Hey.
-Ta-da.
-You little…
-Here, cheers.
-Cheers.
That hits the spot.
You really are something.
What?
Your suturing is so fast.
I guess.
I think I'm better suited
for doing research after all.
I want to be a good doctor.
I listen to the voices of the living.
You listen to the voices of the dead.
Let's both do our best.
Of course.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
I'm Maki,
I'm getting my car repaired here.
-Police.
-What?
We're investigating an incident
that happened at Miyagawa Park.
Can we talk to you?
Why me?
We're investigating cars that were
in the area that night
and have been brought in for repairs.
GPS records from your company car
show you parked there for 30 minutes.
No, that was--
Your bumper was badly dented, wasn't it?
Let's see.
What did you hit?
I forgot.
One more thing.
So what did you hit?
It turns out
Hirono submitted his resignation
the day before the incident.
It seems he was losing confidence because
his clinical work wasn't going well.
He didn't tell you anything, Dr. Honda?
Well, there are things you can't say
even to friends.
That's right.
He probably couldn't find
the timing to tell you.
I understand that.
Honda, you know--
Don't start with the comforting words.
Well then,
let's re-verify the cause of death.
What does everyone think?
If he was troubled by work,
maybe suicide is possible?
It doesn't look like a suicide.
Right.
Dr. Honda, what do you think?
Um…
Listen, just as an example,
is it possible he fell from a large truck
or a crane by accident?
That might be possible.
But considering the powder residue,
falling from a tree
is also a possibility, I think.
What could those abrasions be?
Did he get caught in something
while he fell?
Yoshimoto,
when will the test results be ready?
They're at the forensic lab right now.
I think they'll be out by noon.
Understood.
Accident, suicide, homicide.
All possibilities remain.
Dr. Honda,
let's go and re-examine the scene.
Is it fun?
Shamelessly digging up facts
and talking about
someone's death like that?
Look, that's not
what everyone's trying to do…
Performing an autopsy, giving findings,
and diligently writing up tedious reports.
That's about all we can do, isn't it?
Let's go.
I have an autopsy report to write.
Take someone else.
An animal jumped out suddenly.
I thought, "Crap, I hit it!"
I panicked.
At the time of the incident,
you were parked there
for a long time. Why?
That was to wipe the blood off the car.
I can't handle blood.
I got a bit lightheaded,
so I was resting with the window open.
Ms. Dojima.
The traffic police informed us
that no brake marks that would indicate
an accident occurred have been found.
Pop!
What are you doing?
Oh, hey.
I tried to contact you
but couldn't get through.
Sorry, I've been busy.
A doctor says a body fell from the sky,
and the crime scene is in total chaos.
Please don't inform my company.
Yeah, all right.
Is he a person of interest?
He hit an animal near the scene.
Did you hear any sounds
like a collision near the scene?
What?
No, nothing in particular.
The interrogation is over.
Hey! What about the sound?
What?
You didn't hear a sound,
but was there anything else?
No, well…
There was kind of a smell.
What kind of smell?
It was like
something rotten.
Why don't you take a break?
Don't bother with that.
Caring for my colleagues
is part of the job.
A very bureaucratic way of thinking.
But I'm fine.
Take this.
They say you need sugar
to make your brain work.
You're quite the meddler.
I suppose so.
Oh, I get it.
It would be a stain on
a bureaucrat's career if someone quit.
Quit?
I can't do this job anymore.
This case made it clear to me.
I just…
can't handle this job.
I also…
did not intend to do this kind of work.
And I'm always hating
how useless I am.
But maybe everyone feels that way.
I wonder how
Hirono felt.
I never thought…
I would never be able to see him again.
If I had known
it would be the last time…
I would have said so many things.
It's not over yet.
You're a forensic pathologist.
Hello, this is Masumi.
This is Yoshimoto.
The results of the lab test are in.
All right.
I'll head back now--
Doctor?
Are you there?
I'll call you back.
No components
matching the powder found on the body
were detected from the trees
or the stadium roof.
Then, Hirono…
It seems like he at least
didn't throw himself from anywhere.
I'm going back to check the test results.
However, a piece to solve the cause of
Hirono's death is still missing.
I never found out
what he was going to tell me.
I'll find it.
All right…
Sorry, did Hirono tell you anything?
Excuse me, I'm busy right now.
Anything will help.
No, I didn't know him well, sorry.
Did anything seem different?
Sorry, I really have no idea.
Excuse me, may I ask you?
Finally, I'm done!
Me too!
Finally.
Shall we all do it?
-Dr. Honda's work.
-Yes.
I guess we have to.
Okay, thank you.
Sure.
Can anyone talk to me?
I didn't know him well, sorry.
I've got work to do.
But…
-Please!
-I'm sorry.
Are you talking about Dr. Hirono?
Where did Dr. Hirono go?
He hasn't fixed my tummy yet.
Well…
Dr. Hirono has gone somewhere far away.
But he gave me a message for you.
A message?
Yes.
He said he's made all the preparations
to fix your tummy perfectly,
so you can just relax
and focus on getting better.
Really?
Yes.
So,
do your best.
Did Dr. Hirono go away
because he made people angry?
A scary man was really angry with him.
He said, "It's your fault she died."
The detailed results are out.
The powder detected on the body
was sodium bicarbonate
containing hydrogen sulfide.
There was also a testimony
about a strange smell at the scene.
It must be putrefactive gas
generated by this.
Could this be why the body
expanded after death?
The gas escaped,
making the body move
as if it were convulsing.
What?
Corpses can move?
It's a special case of post-mortem change.
It's when the body temporarily moves
due to putrefactive gases or rigor mortis.
This also explains
the surrounding blood spatters.
They must have gotten scattered
when he had a violent convulsion.
What happened?
There may still be a piece
we haven't found yet.
Hello, this is Medical Examiner Japan.
It's Dr. Honda.
Got it.
This is Masumi.
I've found a clue.
I think I might know
what job Hirono was talking about
on the night of the incident.
It was…
What did he say?
Dr. Masumi?
The pieces may just
be coming together.
I would like to talk to you
about the incident that occurred
at Miyagawa Park.
Take a seat.
Mr. Takemura.
On the night of the incident,
you testified that you heard
a collision sound
and the sound of a car driving away.
Since then,
no other information has come up.
Not one other person
heard such sounds.
So what?
There were findings on Hirono's body
that looked as though
he had fallen from the sky.
However…
that actually was not the case.
The key to solving the mystery
was the scars on the body.
There were burn-like abrasions
on the right arm and left leg of the body.
There is one hypothesis
that makes these traces possible.
When a person falls in a narrow space
where movement is restricted,
their limbs will rub against the walls
as they fall.
In this case,
near where the victim was found,
in a manhole.
In other words,
the victim did not fall from the sky.
He fell from the ground into the deep,
and died there.
It's natural that no one heard a sound.
The collision sound
echoed inside the manhole,
and no one could hear it.
In his body we detected both
hydrogen sulfide
and sodium bicarbonate,
which is used to neutralize it.
These matched what could be found
inside this sewer.
You're a sewer worker,
aren't you, Mr. Takemura?
We've obtained a warrant earlier
and seized your work equipment from
the vehicle parked near your home.
It's only a matter of time
before we have clear physical evidence.
The person who died
was a surgeon
at Meiwa University Hospital,
Tomoki Hirono.
You know him, don't you?
Six months ago,
your only family member,
your daughter Yumi was transported
to the ER at Meiwa University Hospital.
Yumi! Stay with me!
Don't worry, we'll help you.
Temperature 37.2, blood pressure--
The one who first examined her
was Hirono,
who was still an intern at the time.
The blood tests
show no particular problems.
She may have mild appendicitis,
so we'll have her stay
at the hospital for observation.
Thank you.
But three days later,
Yumi's condition suddenly worsened,
and sadly, she passed away.
Murderer.
You killed her!
Give me… Give me Yumi back!
-You directed your anger at Hirono.
-Hey! Say something!
For a mistake in his diagnosis.
You killed her!
I'm telling you to bring out that intern!
Hurry up!
-What are you doing? Stop.
-Hey!
You went to the hospital
many times after that.
That's medical malpractice, right?
Continuing to claim
there had been a misdiagnosis.
But…
the hospital forbade Hirono
from handling it.
He lost his daughter!
We should apologize with sincerity.
If we apologize publicly,
it means we're admitting a mistake.
I should have urged more strongly
for a retest of the coagulation function
of her blood after the first test.
But isn't the biggest issue
the mistake made in the hemostatic
procedure during surgery?
You won't be able
to become a surgeon either.
You were the one
who performed the initial treatment.
Go ahead, if you want to
give up your future as a doctor.
But
Hirono didn't run away.
He was…
He was trying to expose the hospital
for covering up the medical malpractice
they had committed.
A statement written by Hirono
that explained all of this
was also found in your room.
Does that not mean you knew all of this?
So…
why did you do it?
Why do that to Hirono?
No.
That's not it.
This is Hirono
from Meiwa University Hospital.
Could I talk to you directly?
So now he decides to contact me?
I thought he'd want to settle this
with money, and wanted to refuse.
After the examination is over…
But then…
Let's go for a walk?
-Yes!
Yay!
Nice.
He's the one who killed Yumi,
and yet he's pretending
to be a good doctor, acting so happy!
-Can I have this?
-Sure.
Really? Thanks.
That's why that night…
COME TO MIYAGAWA PARK AT 11:00 P.M.
Sorry, it's work.
Mr. Takemura,
thank you for your time.
No matter how much
I apologize for Yumi,
I can never make amends.
But that's why
I want to take responsibility--
Don't give me that crap.
You killed her.
You…
killed Yumi…
-You're the one…
-I…
As a doctor, I tried to--
-You killed her!
-Please, listen to me!
You killed her!
REPORT OF INTERNAL MISCONDUCT
1. THE FIRST EXAMINATION
TOMOKI HIRONO
By the time I found his report,
it was too late.
Hey. Hey!
But I'm not in the wrong.
His report is proof.
It was all their fault!
Don't give me that!
Hirono was planning to
expose the medical malpractice
and quit being a doctor!
He was taking responsibility.
Dr. Honda.
He…
He was an incredible doctor.
More than anyone.
Why…
Why did he have to have
such a horrible end?
You could say that it was Hirono
who gave us the final clues
to solve the case.
He wiped away
the bloodstains from the murder,
disposed of Hirono's smartphone,
and then it should have been over,
once he hid the body.
But why couldn't he do that?
Post-mortem change.
He glared at me
as if he had come back to life.
And so,
I left him there.
It was for Yumi.
It was all for Yumi.
It's miraculous.
If he had disposed of the body…
the truth might never
have come out.
He…
To the very end…
he was such an amazing guy.
I heard that the medical malpractice
is going to be made public.
Yeah.
Apparently, Ms. Kiryu negotiated for it
at the Ministry.
Wow, I see.
Not bad, for a bureaucrat.
Here.
What?
You did them for us?
No, I was just paying back the favor
from the other day.
You could just say thank you.
Well, it's fine.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Well,
see you.
-Take care.
-Bye.
Oh, good morning.
Good morning.
Um…
Thank you.
I've come to listen
to what you have to say.
I'm a bit late, though.
TNS NEWS ONLINE
4TH CASE OF WOMAN FOUND STRANGLED
SHIRAMINE SERIAL FEMICIDE CASE
RESEARCH DATA
Subtitle translation by: Maslin F.