Masumi.
Stop that.
Don't touch dead things.
Hello.
This is Medical Examiner Japan.
Thank you for coming. It's this way.
Yasuo Izawa, 52-year-old male.
Found lying face up
on this road around 1:00 a.m. today
after being hit by a truck.
A passerby called emergency services.
When they arrived, they concluded
he had already passed away.
That man over there is the first witness,
Nobuhiko Yamanuki.
His company handles transportation
for Mr. Izawa's factory.
At our company,
we're all part of a family…
It seems they were somewhat
acquainted through work.
What?
Doctor?
Is this car paint?
Paint fragments?
The same paint is on him here.
There are broken glass fragments
over here too.
Does this mean he was hit by a car?
-Probably.
-No.
We can't be sure of that yet
with just this.
This is near Mr. Izawa's home.
It's believed he was in an accident
while on his way back.
Were there no witnesses?
None so far.
However,
Mr. Izawa's smartphone is missing.
The perpetrator likely took it.
To prevent him from calling for help?
Presumably.
With the scene in mind,
this doesn't look like
a simple traffic accident.
Doctor?
What is it?
The estimated point of impact
based on the paint fragments,
and Mr. Izawa's position
are too close together.
What do you mean?
In a collision with a vehicle,
a person would normally
be thrown further away.
No matter how small the car is,
you are hitting a mass of steel
weighing over 300 kilograms.
It doesn't add up.
You can't say for certain
that these fragments fell
at the moment of impact.
But you could also say that they did.
In other words, it's a mystery.
There's one more issue.
Huh? What is it?
Acceleration marks.
These are marks left
when a car accelerates.
The presence of acceleration marks
implies the car hit Mr. Izawa
at a high speed.
In that case,
he should have landed further away.
So what's your point?
For now, it's a mystery.
-So--
-All right, all right.
I get it, I get it.
Let's begin.
There are signs of bruising
on the back of the head and shoulders.
But I don't believe
this was the fatal blow.
There are also marks on the thigh
resembling a bumper impact,
but that is also unlikely
to be the cause of death.
Upon opening the retroperitoneum,
the tissue around the pelvis
was found to be completely blackened.
The pelvis was severely fractured,
causing massive internal bleeding.
So the cause of death
was internal bleeding?
Yes.
I believe Mr. Izawa's cause of death
was hemorrhagic shock
due to a pelvic fracture.
Well, at least it seems certain
it was a traffic accident.
In a traffic accident,
a person reflexively tries
to protect their body with their arms
at the moment of impact.
Naturally, defense wounds
would remain on one of the arms.
However, in Mr. Izawa's case,
there are none.
It doesn't add up.
That is certainly unnatural.
There are not enough injuries
for a collision.
Usually, there are skin tears.
And yet,
there's only one cut
on the back of his hand.
You're right.
The pieces of the puzzle
may be coming together.
If Mr. Izawa's death
was caused by a car collision,
and the pelvic fracture…
Then he must have been hit
by a car moving extremely slowly.
For now, it's a mystery.
-What?
-What do you mean?
Come back…
Yes, excuse me.
Your turn, Dr. Takamori.
Okay.
First,
when hit by a fast car,
you are thrown a significant distance
and suffer various external injuries.
But if hit by a very slow car,
you fall straight backward.
Like a heavy fall on your rear.
In this case, the force is focused
on the center of the body,
which can cause a pelvic fracture.
I see. That would explain
why there are external injuries,
but a severe internal one.
Hang on a second.
How slow is "slow"?
About 20 kilometers per hour?
You can easily avoid a car
moving that slowly, can't you?
At the very least,
it wouldn't be a direct hit.
Then maybe he was hit intentionally?
Don't you think that's a bit of a stretch?
That's right!
Doctor, what do you think?
Well…
If the vehicle was moving fast,
it contradicts the body's distance.
If the vehicle was moving slowly,
there should not be
any acceleration marks.
Several points don't add up,
whether it moved slowly or fast.
And, the lack of defense wounds
remains unexplained.
Considering all of this…
Considering all of that?
For now, it's a mystery.
Yes?
What?
I understand.
Was that Dojima?
Yes.
It seems they found the truck driver.
I would like to hear what he has to say.
Wait, Doctor…
Well, about that…
The deceased is Kazutoshi Tamura,
24 years old.
He was the driver
of the truck in the incident.
A missing person's report
was filed by his transport company.
We confirmed he was using the truck
on the day of the incident.
Anything catch your eye?
Where's the truck?
It was abandoned nearby.
The bumper is dented,
and the paint is chipped.
Mr. Izawa's smartphone
was found in the deceased's pocket.
What?
And on top of that.
This was found in his pocket as well.
The police think
it was a suicide motivated
by remorse over the hit-and-run.
The driver suspected of the hit-and-run
was found dead by hanging.
So he killed my husband
and then just took
the easy way out for himself?
How could this happen?
I understand how you feel.
Do you recognize this man named Tamura?
Anything at all will help.
He has come to our factory a few times.
I think he was in charge
of our deliveries.
Did you notice anything
strange about their relationship?
One time,
I saw the two of them having an argument.
Do you know what it was about?
I couldn't hear any details.
When I asked my husband
if he was all right,
I got no clear answer.
Would you say they were
on bad terms with each other?
No.
I don't think they were.
Did they often meet with each other?
I don't know any details, but…
I think they met a few times every month.
Thank you.
He hits him with his truck,
and then commits suicide over the guilt.
That's the size of it, right?
We don't currently know.
If they had some bad blood
between each other for whatever reason,
then it's a possibility he hit him
with his truck on purpose, isn't it?
We don't currently know that either.
You're right.
Sorry.
However,
there is one thing that caught my eye.
What is it?
The condition of Tamura's body
at the scene.
Normally, when one dies
from asphyxiation from hanging,
their face becomes pale.
However, Tamura's complexion
looked just fine.
He had all the color in his face, right?
Yes.
Therefore…
Let's begin.
It's over here!
YAMANUKI SHIPPING CO., LTD.
Could you tell us about
how Kazutoshi Tamura was at work?
Right…
Tamura…
It honestly pains me
to speak ill of the dead.
Were there any problems?
He was often found sleeping
in the middle of work.
Are you okay?
Sorry.
He was not very bright.
What are you doing?
To be honest,
I wasn't sure what to do about him.
I didn't really want to do this,
but I attached a GPS to his truck
to monitor him.
A GPS…
We also have the shift records over there.
-Please look at them if needed.
-Thank you very much.
Hey.
Yes, sorry!
There was mild pulmonary edema
in his lungs.
This can be a sign of asphyxiation,
but also a sign of heart failure
or death from poisoning.
The CT scan results show
that the decisive blow
wasn't to the heart or brain.
It doesn't seem like heart failure.
Thank you.
Next, on the neck,
there are clear rope marks left.
So, he died by hanging?
We can't draw a conclusion just from that.
Because you can make it look like
someone hanged themselves
after killing them, right?
Yes.
There is one more thing
that caught my eye during the autopsy.
Thank you for your cooperation.
No, I'm happy to help with this.
Well then, goodbye.
By the way…
you wouldn't know about any trouble
Izawa was having, would you?
Trouble?
Trouble…
Well…
Did you think of something?
Well, it's only a rumor.
Only a rumor?
Actually…
Take a look at this.
There are few petechial hemorrhages
behind the eyes.
In cases of asphyxiation,
blood that should flow down
from the neck pools,
and there should be
signs of bleeding behind the eyes.
If it wasn't hanging, then what was it?
We're still missing some pieces.
How was the autopsy for Kazutoshi Tamura?
How was it?
We couldn't conclude
that Tamura's cause of death was hanging.
I see.
What about you?
We learned something interesting.
Izawa had been in debt
for two years to run the factory.
Nearly 100 million yen.
What? 100 million?
That's not all.
A 100 million yen life insurance policy
was taken out on Izawa.
And it's only been three months
since he signed it.
I see it as money to protect the company.
The police are moving forward with
the investigation as a case
of induced suicide by Akemi Izawa.
Wait, what does that mean?
We mean that she induced Izawa
to commit suicide
and make it look like an accident.
To get the 100 million
from the life insurance policy.
No, wait.
If that's true,
then why would the driver,
Tamura, have to die?
If it's discovered he committed suicide,
then she won't get the 100 million.
She killed the driver, Kazutoshi Tamura,
and made it look like a suicide.
Then it would make sense
that he didn't have much hemorrhaging
because he didn't die of asphyxiation.
That may also explain why Izawa
didn't dodge a slow-moving truck.
Because she hesitated
to run over her husband,
Akemi hit Mr. Izawa
at a half-hearted speed.
Does that mean Akemi is the culprit?
We'll go ask the suspect directly.
Yes. We'll check with the insurance
company for--
Don't dawdle!
Yes, ma'am!
I'll get the referral!
Doctor,
what do you think?
The night of the accident?
I was at home.
I see.
I'm under suspicion, aren't I?
Oh, no, it's nothing like that.
A police officer came by earlier, too,
and asked me all sorts of things.
Like about how managing the factory
wasn't going well,
and about my husband's
life insurance money.
I wonder if they think I killed him
for the insurance money.
No, we're not saying that.
Just because we have debts to pay back…
I haven't fallen so low
as to commit murder.
I'm very sorry.
You have a child, huh?
Yes.
Well…
Kazuki…
passed away ten years ago.
It was suicide.
Kazuki
was a serious boy.
But he was clumsy,
and everything he tried
seemed to go nowhere.
His job hunting didn't go well either.
REJECTION NOTICE
Kazuki.
I'm coming in.
Is it not going well?
Dad, actually…
What?
Would it be okay
if I worked for your company?
Even if you join us, you'll only suffer.
Why don't you keep at it
just a little bit longer?
My husband didn't really want
him to join the company,
but to find a better job,
and become happy.
But that day…
Kazuki, I'm coming in.
I've got breakfast--
It was my husband who found Kazuki
after he had hanged himself.
My husband thought that if only
he had noticed Kazuki's
suffering back then, Kazuki would…
My husband always blamed himself for it.
Day…
after day…
I would never do such a thing.
I don't think it's possible after all.
I don't think someone
who cares so much for their family
would commit instigation of suicide.
You cannot conclude
whether a parent is truly
thinking of their child.
The doctor was kind of strange today.
From what I know, he just seems like that.
Well, yes.
He's always calm and collected, right?
He just does sudoku.
Yeah.
Oh.
Maybe it's just not a topic
he's comfortable with.
Not comfortable?
Like parental love?
It's not that uncommon.
I'm very sorry about the other day…
I visited the factory,
but you weren't there.
I've decided to close down the factory.
The management
wasn't going well to begin with.
And my husband is gone now, too.
Ma'am,
if it's all right with you,
could we investigate inside the house?
We might find some kind of clue.
I want to find out exactly
what happened on the day of the incident.
For your husband's sake.
Above all, for your own sake.
He's coming up from the rear!
Go, go, go!
-All right!
-Wow.
You did it.
What?
Right.
Is there anyone here
who used the same truck
as the late Mr. Tamura?
I have.
-Great!
-Me too.
Great!
Have you felt unwell
in the past few weeks?
Just a little dizzy.
I had a cold.
Thank you very much.
There is something I would like to check.
This is the truck
he was driving that night.
Oh, I see.
Oh, may I borrow this?
Hey… Are you okay?
Oh, don't worry.
I'm sorry to be so forward.
No…
If I take anything that seems of interest,
even if I don't understand what it is,
Dr. Masumi might notice something.
Well, in that case,
would you like to check Kazuki's room too?
What?
This is it.
We've left it just as it was
since Kazuki passed.
Neither I nor my husband
could quite accept it.
If you would like,
could you investigate it?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I'll go in then.
I used to have one of these, too.
When I first started working,
I tried to act like an adult.
That fountain pen
is something my husband
gave to Kazuki as a present.
When his job hunting wasn't going well,
he told him that if he used it
to write his resumes,
he would be fine.
I'm back!
Ms. Kiryu, what's all that?
I got permission from Akemi
and borrowed some of his belongings.
This much?
Yes.
Everyone.
Could you help me investigate everything?
How are we going to handle all this?
I'm busy too, you know. I'll pass.
Please.
I'm asking you.
Dr. Masumi, you too, please.
I just can't believe Akemi is the culprit.
So, I thought you might be able
to find some kind of clue.
Please.
Of course.
Thank you very much.
All right.
You too, Dr. Matsubara.
-Ugh.
-Come on.
I've got a show I want to watch!
Just record it, then.
Here, thank you.
All right.
Hey.
This is a gift Izawa gave to Kazuki
when he was job hunting.
-What were Tamura's blood test results?
-Hold on.
Where are they…
Here.
Acetaminophen.
What is that?
It's an ingredient often found
in things like cold medicine.
You can make it look like
someone hanged themselves…
…no defense wounds.
There's only one cut
on the back of his hand.
Just a little dizzy.
I had a cold.
Kazuki passed away ten years ago.
This is a gift Izawa gave to Kazuki
when he was job hunting.
Acetaminophen.
I think they met a few times every month.
The pieces may be
coming together.
MUSASHINODAI POLICE OFFICE
Thank you for coming while you're so busy.
There is something
I would like to ask you about.
I'm sorry, but I'm busy,
so could we finish this
as quickly as possible?
I understand.
Right this way.
Please, have a seat here.
Okay.
These are photos taken
when I visited your company the other day.
You can't just take liberties like that.
I'm terribly sorry.
I just had something
that was bothering me.
This is the truck Tamura
drove on the night of the incident.
Please look at this part.
The pipe is broken.
Also, there are cracks in the welding
several centimeters big.
And there is one more thing
that concerns me.
Tamura had been suffering from symptoms
like dizziness and a cold
for several weeks.
Strangely,
there were several others
suffering from similar symptoms.
It's just a coincidence.
Everyone at our company works hard,
so it wouldn't be strange
for them to fall ill.
I do not believe
that it was a coincidence.
On what grounds?
I believe the workers
were suffering from
carbon monoxide poisoning.
On the day of the incident,
Tamura parked the truck on the street,
and exhausted from working all day,
took a nap.
That day,
it was very humid,
even when the sun went down.
He most likely left the air conditioner on
while inside the vehicle.
If you continue to run it
while parked for a long time,
exhaust gas will begin to accumulate
under the vehicle from that broken pipe.
As a result,
carbon monoxide,
which is lighter than air,
leaked through the crack
in the bottom of the vehicle.
Tamura, who was sleep-deprived,
had fallen into a deep sleep.
And without even realizing it himself,
he was suffering
from carbon monoxide poisoning.
The reason his complexion looked normal
when his body was found
was because of that.
But what was more decisive than anything…
was this.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING LIKE THIS
This note,
found at the scene of the incident.
And that alone
doesn't add up.
What?
Why?
Initially, we thought this note
was a suicide note left by the driver,
Kazutoshi Tamura.
But we were wrong.
What do you mean?
It was written by your late son.
What…
These letters haven't bled
through to the back of the paper.
The ink has not been absorbed
into the paper.
If it were oil-based,
it would bleed through.
If it were water-based,
it should smudge because of the paper.
But it is neither of those.
Pigmented gel ink is what it's called.
Pigmented gel ink?
Can you see the fine cracks in the ink
on the surface of these letters?
A characteristic of pigmented gel ink
is that it cracks
after several years of exposure to air.
In other words, that means
this note was written several years ago.
And this ink
matches the fountain pen
that Izawa's son, Kazuki, used to love.
I believe your husband
kept it with him at all times
as a form of atonement.
Why would something Kazuki wrote
be inside the truck?
I believe…
your husband was trying to help Tamura.
That night, when Izawa was going home…
Hey!
Are you sleeping?
You'll catch a cold!
Hey!
Hey, are you okay? Hey!
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey! Pull yourself together!
Hey!
Hey…
All right…
Izawa inhaled carbon monoxide
from the vehicle.
Is that bastard
seriously slacking off again?
Hey!
What happened?
The truck…
Something's wrong with it.
What?
I'm so dizzy.
Hey.
Are you okay?
If this gets out, my company is ruined.
Hey…
Are you okay?
Can you stand?
I finally climbed my way to the top…
And, after that, Yamanuki…
I'M SORRY FOR BEING LIKE THIS
He was desperately trying
to make it look like an accident.
He put Tamura into the truck,
and fled the scene.
Tamura made it look like
he committed suicide.
Considering the above,
I believe the reason Yasuo Izawa
had no defensive wounds
was that he was trying to protect Tamura,
who was unconscious at the time.
If you had called an ambulance right then,
they would both have survived.
Neither of them…
would have lost their lives.
This is what we believe
to have happened to Yasuo Izawa
on that day.
My husband…
tried to save someone?
Yes.
He tried to save Tamura,
who was about the same age as your son.
He risked his life to do it.
I…
think he was a magnificent person.
Detective! Please listen to me!
This man is--
Overworking employees,
false statements, tampering with evidence…
Plus a whole bunch of further offenses.
Nobuhiko Yamanuki, you are under arrest
for murder and failure to render aid.
It looks like
you're going to spend a lot of time
with us, don't you think?
Let's go.
Move!
Thank you for your cooperation.
You as well.
Thank you,
as always.
From here on,
it's police business, so…
IZAWA
I hope Izawa's feelings reached those two.
Oh. From a forensic science
perspective, the deceased are…
Yes, I get it.
Thank you for today.
Good work.
Wait, Doctor.
That reminds me.
I've actually wanted to ask you…
Why did you want to become
a forensic pathologist?
Well, I wonder why.
For now, it's a mystery.
Good work today.
Masumi.
Stop that.
Don't touch dead things.
Why…
Dad?
KOICHI MIZUSAWA
There is no value
in dead things.
THIRD KILLING BY STRANGULATION THIS YEAR
4TH CASE OF WOMAN FOUND STRANGLED
SHIRAMINE SERIAL FEMICIDE CASE
RESEARCH DATA
AUTOPSY REPORT
SURGEON: MASAHITO KUJO
MARCH 2008
ASSISTANT: MASUMI MIZUSAWA
MASUMI MIZUSAWA
Subtitle translation by: Maslin F.