Ms. Kiryu.
Please sign this.
Okay.
You look like you don't get it at all.
-No, I'll check it.
-Thank you.
This too, please.
April's post-mortem reports.
And here is the summary
of the test results.
Got it.
-Thank you.
Will you really be okay?
Yes, it's no problem at all.
Of course it isn't.
Ms. Kiryu is the head of MEJ, after all.
Right?
Yes.
Here is the summary
of the chemical analysis.
Please sign it.
I'm going to step out for a bit.
My boss at the Ministry of Health
is calling for me.
-She ran away.
-She certainly did.
Regarding that youth poverty support
project you were moving forward with,
it is finally ready to launch.
What?
Really?
However, since you are busy
with the MEJ now,
I have decided to put
another person in charge of it.
What?
Keep up the good work over there.
Is something wrong?
Well…
It seems your hands have stopped moving.
Oh, yes, they have.
I'm just stamping seals. I'll be fine.
I'll finish it after this all-nighter.
I wouldn't recommend that.
Staying up all night
is the same as being drunk.
Drunk?
Cognitive function
after 24 hours without sleep
is reportedly at the same level
as a blood alcohol concentration
of 0.10 percent.
Information cannot be retained
by the brain in that state.
But I won't finish unless I work
all night.
That said, research shows that women
who sleep for less than four hours
have twice the mortality risk
compared to sleeping seven hours.
By pulling an all-nighter,
you think you're increasing your time,
but you might actually be decreasing it.
I will be careful.
As much as I can.
Okay then!
Hello.
Good evening.
It happened in the owner's room.
This way.
The victim is 39-year-old Hayato Kuriyama.
The owner of this club.
A host from a partner club found the body
when he came for a meeting.
Fine white froth is visible
around the nose and mouth.
There is a possibility of drowning.
Drowning?
You mean he drowned inside a closet?
It would be difficult to kill him outside
and move him here.
But drowning inside a room?
It is possible as long as there is enough
water to cover the mouth and nose.
The autopsy shows
that the cause of death was drowning.
Components of the cleaning agent
used in the room's toilet were
detected in the water inside the lungs.
We found pressure marks on the neck
and a slight bruise on the head.
Both occurred while he was alive.
We also found skin fragments
under his fingernails
that don't belong to Mr. Kuriyama.
Testing revealed
that it is female DNA.
Female…
Did the victim
have any trouble with women?
When he took a liking to a girl,
he would try to keep her for himself.
They were too scared to refuse.
Some girls were backed into a corner.
Had he been clashing
with anyone in particular lately?
Well, actually,
one girl was arguing with him
about breaking up.
Excuse me.
Police.
Police?
Could you come with us to the station
to discuss Hayato Kuriyama?
I'm sorry.
I have to go to work now.
Female DNA was detected on the body.
Will you cooperate with a DNA test?
I'm sorry.
The culprit is 24-year-old
Miyuki Yanagihara,
an employee at the club.
She visited the victim's room
on the day of the crime.
Please just let me go.
I'm at my limit.
I'll kill you if you run away.
She put poison in his protein shake
and left the room.
However…
Where's your earring?
What?
One second.
So then, she strangled the victim
after he regained consciousness.
After that,
fearing he would wake up again,
she submerged his face in the toilet.
What?
But no poison was detected
in the autopsy, was it?
The components checked
in the initial screening are limited.
Irregular toxins won't be detected
unless we specifically test for them.
Test for them?
What was the substance used?
She's actually remaining silent
about the poison.
What poison was it?
Where did you get it?
I forgot.
What?
Why?
Maybe she's protecting someone.
In that case, finding the toxin
could be quite difficult.
For now, let's broaden
the scope of the analysis.
-Okay.
We will investigate
the source of procurement as well.
Hello?
Huh? What do you mean?
I'll be right back.
What happened?
A staff member from the club
turned himself in.
He says he was the one
who killed the owner.
I'm the one who did it.
That day, I went
to talk to him about a loan.
Please, I beg you!
Are you stupid?
Bastard!
After that, I got scared
and ran away.
But then I saw on the news
that Miyuki had been arrested.
It was all my fault.
Miyuki is innocent.
Please, arrest me now!
Mr. Murano.
Did you really kill him by strangulation?
Yes.
She has already admitted to the crime.
That's impossible! Please, investigate!
Like I said…
Where is the ashtray you used to hit him?
Hey.
I threw it into the Ooguri River.
Why did you ask about the murder weapon?
The bruise on the top of the victim's head
might have been caused
by Murano hitting him.
If we find the weapon and match it,
we can be certain.
Wasn't that just from bumping into
something when dragging him around?
Besides, the cause of death
was drowning, right?
Murano's statement
that he strangled him doesn't add up.
It's only natural to consider
Miyuki Yanagihara as the culprit.
Murano is just giving a false confession
to protect Miyuki Yanagihara.
Miyuki is innocent.
Please, arrest me now!
However, as long as
no poison has been detected,
we should investigate
assuming every possibility.
Let's investigate their relationship and
search for the murder weapon.
-Supervisor.
-Yes?
The cause of death
has been determined to be drowning.
There's no need for the MEJ
to investigate any further, is there?
Oh, well…
The MEJ has the authority to conduct
all general investigations to--
Do you have anything else
besides "authority"?
How can you call yourself the supervisor?
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am!
We have no choice but to move on our own.
Could you investigate the relationship
between Yanagihara and Murano?
What? Me?
I will proceed
with identifying the poison.
I'm counting on you.
Are we looking for it after all?
We were told the weapon was thrown away,
so we have no choice.
Here I thought I could go home today.
I wanted to finish early too.
Do you have any plans?
I do.
I'm getting snacks,
watch a reality-TV show
while drinking wine, and doze off.
Wait. Ms. Dojima, you watch dating shows?
I do.
Wow, you're actually interested in love
and things like that?
Even I have interests in things
that aren't violent and terrible.
We're taking a break!
We're taking a break.
I mean, how long are we going to do this?
The culprit is Miyuki Yanagihara.
We're not going to find that ash tray!
Something's bothering me.
Nothing came up in the gas chromatography
or liquid chromatography.
Capillary chromatography is also negative.
Damn it!
We'd have no trouble
if she just said what it was.
I wonder why she won't.
Maybe that club staff member
got it for her.
I think she's staying silent
to protect him.
So they're both covering for each other?
Exactly.
Is there a possibility that there was
no poison in the first place?
Kuriyama had pulmonary edema.
While it's a finding seen in drowning,
it can also occur in drug poisoning.
We cannot deny the possibility that
some kind of drug was ingested.
I'm asking again.
How did you get the poison?
Why won't you tell me?
You're protecting someone, aren't you?
A lover…
perhaps?
Were Miyuki and Murano possibly
dating in secret, without telling anyone?
No, I can't imagine they were.
The owner would have them killed.
When did Miyuki start working at the club?
About a year ago, I think.
She had money problems
and was looking for a new job.
What kind of person was Murano?
He was actually a former host.
He was working at an affiliate club
and moved here.
Do you know the name of that host club?
Supervisor!
Why are you here?
To interview involved parties.
Without telling the police?
It was Dr. Masumi's instruction.
You just do whatever
people tell you, don't you?
Excuse me.
A host club?
So that's your hobby?
No! It's Murano's former workplace.
I thought I might learn something.
Are you coming?
What?
You'll just move around secretly
on your own anyway, right?
Murano was a good guy.
He wasn't suited to being a host.
Had you heard anything from Murano?
About trouble with the owner,
or about a hostess
named Miyuki Yanagihara?
I'm not sure.
It's 100,000?
-One of those then.
-What?
Champagne coming up!
Thank you, welcome to the club!
-Welcome!
All right!
Thanks.
What? Aren't the police
supposed to pay this?
You're the supervisor, right?
Figure it out with your budget.
Want to go get food?
I'll at least make that my treat.
Let's go.
NO DRUGS TARGETED FOR SCREENING DETECTED
Getting a hostess job
because of financial trouble, huh?
Many young people can't earn enough
even if they work full-time
due to non-regular employment
and low wages.
So they end up in the nightlife business.
You're surprisingly well-informed.
Originally, I wanted to
work in social welfare
because I wanted to help those people.
Before coming to MEJ,
I was in youth poverty support
for a long time.
Why is someone as noble as you
the MEJ supervisor?
Poverty support and
the cause of death are totally different.
You got transferred.
Yes.
Of course, I intend to work
as hard as I can in any way I can.
But, to be honest,
I still want to return to the MHLW.
That might be perfect, actually.
What?
If you've done that kind of work,
don't you understand how she feels?
You know,
she has stopped talking to the police.
Why don't you try talking to her?
My name is Kiryu from MEJ.
We're an MHLW organization
that specializes in determining
causes of death.
No matter how many times you ask,
I don't remember anything
about the poison.
Are you protecting Murano?
Murano?
What has he got to do with it?
Actually,
Murano turned himself in.
What?
What was your relationship with Murano?
Murano…
was always supporting me.
I started this job
to pay back my student loans.
I've always regretted it.
Student loans?
My family was poor.
I went to a beautician school
on a scholarship.
But the salary
for an assistant was low, so…
I started a part-time job
at a hostess club.
You don't have to worry anymore.
Some girls work only until
they've paid back their scholarships.
Thank you very much.
But in the end,
I was forced to become his mistress.
Before I knew it…
I had nowhere else to go
and no place to return to.
I had no choice
but to rely on that man to live.
And during that time…
I'm here for you.
…Murano encouraged me.
I had to do my best to get out of there…
and started to believe that I could.
But…
How did it end up like this?
So they were dating after all.
Probably.
Also,
it doesn't seem they coordinated
their stories and turned themselves in.
When I told her Murano
had turned himself in,
Miyuki looked genuinely surprised.
It didn't seem like she knew beforehand.
Then Murano really was
protecting Yanagihara?
That might be true.
What's wrong?
My family was poor too,
and I went to university
thanks to a scholarship.
I joined the MHLW
because I wanted to help people
like myself move forward, but…
In my current position,
I can't do anything.
Is that really true?
Even in your current position,
isn't there something you can do?
That's what you worked so hard for
at the Ministry, isn't it?
Also,
there's something bothering me.
When her arm was grabbed by the victim,
he apparently called her "Mari."
Mari?
Mari…
What?
To have to depend on someone
who gets your name wrong…
She felt pathetic
for having to live like that.
She said that before she knew it,
she was strangling him.
Maybe she was just at her limit.
The victim laid hands on many women.
She might be one of them.
It might have something
to do with the case.
I'll look into it.
Let's get married.
It's impossible.
We can't escape.
If only he wasn't here,
I could be with the person I love forever.
Even in your current position,
isn't there something you can do?
I had to do my best to get out of there…
All right.
What…
You were working until morning?
As you can see.
So, did you find any poison?
No.
I've tried a thousand patterns,
but the parameter settings
are still infinite.
Yes?
Ms. Dojima, it's an emergency!
The ashtray believed to be
the murder weapon has been found!
The shape of the discovered ashtray
matches the wound on Kuriyama's head.
Murano's fingerprints
were also detected on the ashtray.
What about
Miyuki Yanagihara's fingerprints?
None of hers.
So the culprit really was
Murano after all?
Yes.
The prosecution has also decided
to indict Murano.
Please wait.
The cause of death was drowning.
Murano's statement says
that he strangled him. It doesn't add up.
We know that.
But evidence backing the crime
has surfaced.
According to the police,
it appears that Murano is the culprit.
The investigation task force
is being disbanded.
Wait!
The mystery has not yet been solved.
What poison did Miyuki administer,
and why does Murano's statement
differ from the cause of death?
I'm going to the scene again.
There might be a piece
we haven't found yet.
Okay!
We're going to
Miyuki Yanagihara's apartment.
What?
We can't just let it end
like this either, can we?
Yes, ma'am!
Cute.
Did it belong to the victim, you think?
Hey, you!
-Wait!
-Stop!
Did you find something?
No, nothing in particular.
Doctor,
that pen is bothering you, right?
Compared to the victim's
other belongings, it's quite different.
I wonder why. It's a mystery.
Dr. Masumi,
no toxins were detected
in the line test either.
Okay.
Let's go back to basics and start over
from the elemental analysis.
Okay.
It's Mari-chan!
Mari-chan?
Magical Detective Mari.
It's a new popular anime.
Oh, okay.
Is this girl called "Mari"?
Yes.
Is something wrong?
When the victim woke up,
he apparently called Miyuki "Mari."
The police couldn't find any Mari
who knew the victim.
But surely, it couldn't be
an anime character, right?
I found out the name of the poison.
What is it?
Aconitine.
Of course, we wouldn't find that.
We don't usually test for that.
I'll cross-reference it with the database.
Wait.
We did not find aconitine in the body.
The pieces might be
coming together.
Regarding the poison
you said you gave to Kuriyama,
no matter how much we investigated,
it could not be detected.
However, that was only natural.
Kuriyama had not ingested poison
in the first place.
What do you mean?
I put poison in his drink.
I heard you were called
"Mari" by the victim.
What about it?
Do you know who Mari is?
I don't know.
Just some other woman, right?
I thought so too at first.
But no matter how much we investigated,
we could not find any woman named Mari.
The only Mari found…
was this girl.
From an anime?
Her name is Mari,
from Magical Detective Mari.
Kuriyama was a die-hard fan
of this character.
You're saying I was mistaken
for an anime character?
Yes.
When we examined the hippocampus,
the part of the brain
which governs memory,
we saw necrosis in the surrounding area.
In other words,
Kuriyama suffered
a consciousness disorder,
and as a result,
he mistook you for his beloved Mari.
That's because of the poison, right?
No.
Because the poison you used
was aconitine.
The person who purchased
the poison for you told us.
What?
Of course,
you know who that person is.
You've been silent all this time
to protect him, haven't you?
The one who bought the poison
was the host…
Kaito Miura.
No! I bought it myself!
Kaito Miura has already
admitted his involvement.
I was worried there was evidence left
of me buying that poison,
so I went and checked Miyuki's place.
Does that mean you also had
a grudge against Kuriyama?
He found out I was trying to
go independent and was interfering.
But I only bought the poison,
Miyuki is the one who did it.
I won't be charged with murder, right?
It's not Kaito's fault.
I just asked him.
He has nothing to do with it!
You put the aconitine purchased
by Mr. Miura into the protein.
However, if aconitine is ingested,
brain function is instantly destroyed,
so one would never regain consciousness.
So, a disturbance of consciousness
and mistaking you for Mari,
is not possible.
That doesn't make sense.
Then why did the owner collapse?
That's because Kuriyama
had people trying to kill him twice.
Twice?
That day, another person had visited
the owner's room
between when you mixed the poison
into the drink
and you returning
to retrieve your earring.
It was Murano.
Murano?
He said that he went
to ask the owner to release you.
He confessed just now.
Please let Miyuki go!
Please, I beg you!
Are you stupid?
But,
at that time, Kuriyama was not dead yet.
He lost consciousness
because he was strangled,
and his breathing and pulse
became extremely weak.
It's a so-called state of apparent death.
Kuriyama regained consciousness
exited the closet,
and lost consciousness again.
And then you came in.
Seeing him like that,
you mistakenly thought Kuriyama
had died from drinking the poison.
However, Kuriyama,
who was still breathing,
regained consciousness once more.
And due to the consciousness disorder
caused by the hypoxic state
from being strangled,
he got your name…
Mari…
…wrong.
That pushed you
to lay your hands on Kuriyama.
You and Murano both tried
to kill Kuriyama,
and both of you failed.
However, in the end,
you were the one who completed it.
Ms. Yanagihara,
I am committing you to trial
on suspicion of murder.
What about Murano?
He will be charged with attempted murder.
You hid the fact that you had entered
a relationship with Kaito Miura,
and tried to get Murano
to kill the victim, didn't you?
If only he wasn't here,
I could be with the person I love forever.
But you got tired of Murano
never following through,
so you finally did it yourself.
Yet coincidentally,
Murano followed through
on the same day.
I have a message from Murano.
Please tell Miyuki this.
This is my fault.
I'm so sorry.
But,
let's both atone for our crimes
and get married.
I'll be waiting for her forever.
You might have just been using him,
but he was serious.
Are you kidding me?
Stupid useless man.
Don't get ahead of yourself!
It's because you failed to kill him
that I'm in this mess!
And here…
And here I thought
I could finally get out.
Did you really…
think that?
You killed someone.
Even if you managed to get out of this,
by doing all this,
did you really think
you could move forward?
Move forward?
Why would you assume that?
I never said anything about "forward."
I just wanted to break away from the owner
and be with Kaito forever.
I don't care about the future.
As long as I'm happy now,
that's all that matters.
Someone who's talented,
has a good job,
and lives without any hardship
wouldn't understand my feelings.
I even defaulted on my scholarship
and used all the money I earned for Kaito.
It was fun, though.
I…
didn't see anything.
There are people
in society waiting for help.
I thought I was working for those people.
But it was all just an ideal.
I didn't see anything.
Isn't it a good thing by itself
that you realized that?
Hey.
Your nose is running.
You look ugly.
Go on, cry.
Ms. Kiryu.
-Stamp this, please.
-Okay.
Mark them all
as "by the end of today," please.
-Okay.
Wait.
Dr. Honda…
What does this LC-MS mean?
What?
Oh, it's the same as always,
so if you could just stamp it for now,
No.
As the supervisor,
I want to really understand it
before I stamp it.
Please tell me.
Can't be helped…
-I'm busy, you know?
-I'm sorry.
Well, simply put,
it means separating components
with LC and analyzing the mass.
Analyzing mass?
Yes.
You mean like on a scale?
No, like I said…
More documents?
For LC-MS,
I recommend this book.
Thank you very much.
LC… Liquid Chromatography?
So what is LC-MS?
It's that instrument over there.
A child suspected of being abused
was in an accident.
What kind of screaming?
Are you okay?
In the middle of the night,
suddenly, like "wahh!"
Subtitle translation by: Maslin F.