This is the fifth case this year
of a girl being found strangled to death.
According to investigators,
they view these repeated cases as linked
and are investigating accordingly.
What? You're going to be a dad?
Yes.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
I had no idea.
You should have told us!
Sorry.
Dr. Takamori,
I bet you'll be a great father.
I wonder.
We have to celebrate.
No, you don't have to.
A pre-celebration drink.
A big one!
-You just want to drink.
-No, I don't!
Dr. Masumi is on vacation, right?
Now is our chance.
Hello, this is Medical Examiner Japan.
How does the mindset
of becoming a father feel?
I'm not sure.
It hasn't really sunk in yet.
When is the due date?
For now, it's next weekend.
Really?
Hey, excuse me.
We got a request
for an examination of a living person.
A child suspected of being abused
was in an accident.
Clinical forensic medicine, right?
Yes.
It's rare, isn't it?
Until now, we've only done
examinations on bodies.
With domestic violence, abuse,
or other special cases, we sometimes
get asked to do an examination.
What should we do?
Unfortunately,
I can't come back yet.
Could you all handle it by yourself?
What? Without you?
Clinical forensic medicine
is Dr. Takamori's specialty.
I'll let him handle it.
I understand.
All right, then. Thank you.
That's unusual.
Dr. Masumi never dumps a job
on someone else.
That's true.
I wonder where he's going.
Sorry we're late.
Huh? That doctor isn't here today?
He couldn't quite make it today.
Well, that helps.
Explain it to them.
Yes, ma'am.
The victim is ten-year-old Kanata Togawa.
A neighbor found him collapsed here,
and he was rushed to the hospital.
He still hasn't regained consciousness
and is receiving treatment.
We don't know yet
if it was an accident or a crime.
What kind of findings suggest abuse?
Bruises all over his body.
On his back, his arms, everywhere.
But there were no reports
to the child consultation center.
Also, I don't think it's relevant,
but just to let you know…
You're okay.
The monster…
The monster is coming.
The black monster…
He said that and then lost consciousness.
Monster?
We found a knife!
Maybe he was attacked with this
by the person who was abusing him,
and then fell from here?
First, we need to find out
if there really was abuse.
Yes, ma'am.
Just imagining it
is painful.
Come in.
Excuse me.
I'm Kiryu from MEJ.
I'm Takamori.
We received a request for an examination
because there's a suspicion of abuse.
He hit his head quite hard,
so please be careful.
Yes, sir.
Kanata…
I'm sorry.
Please.
Okay.
Are you all right?
It's nothing.
Are you Kanata's mother?
I was at my part-time job
when I got the call.
You must have been shocked.
Yes.
I'm sorry, but it seems
there are marks on Kanata's body
that were unrelated to the accident.
Do you have any idea what they might be?
Ms. Togawa?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Was Kanata at home alone today?
I think so.
Sorry for asking,
but you were divorced
five years ago, right?
Are you living alone with Kanata now?
For the most part, yes.
For the most part?
The person I'm dating
also comes over sometimes.
Where is that person now?
I can't get in touch with him right now.
I think he'll be back soon, though.
Could you tell me more about him?
Yes.
Kanata fell down the stairs
for some reason.
He hit his head
on the landing midway down the stairs,
resulting in a cerebral contusion
and an acute subdural hematoma.
There are also…
several other bruises
likely caused by hitting the stairs.
Those are the injuries from the fall.
So the rest are from abuse.
That's awful.
Are these all abuse marks?
I think so.
The bruise marks can be covered up
and are a characteristic of child abuse.
There are many scar patches
and keloids on his back, too.
Those are old wounds.
These wounds on his arm
look fairly new, though.
Coexisting old and new wounds
is also a characteristic of abuse.
Doctor.
This might be irrelevant,
but when Kanata was being transported,
he said, "The black monster is coming."
He seemed afraid.
The black monster?
Maybe the person who abused him
looked that terrifying to him.
But isn't it strange?
If he was beaten by someone
who was abusing him,
he would likely say
"I was beaten by the monster."
Instead he said, "The monster is coming."
-True.
-No.
He hit his head and was confused.
Well, sure, but…
Anyway,
let's first investigate
what Kanata's daily life was like.
-Okay.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Long time no see.
Professor Kujo.
Has it been 15 years already?
A lot of time has passed, hasn't it?
I heard…
I heard you're now working
at a death investigation facility
established by the Ministry.
Yes.
Professor, how is your health?
The cancer has spread all over.
They say I have three months left.
I've lived long enough.
I'll let myself…
relax here for a little while longer.
You mean Ms. Togawa from 401, right?
I've heard screaming and things before.
What kind of screaming?
In the middle of the night,
suddenly, like "wahh!"
I couldn't tell
what they were saying, though.
It didn't use to be like that, though.
The mom started dating
a scary-looking guy.
That's when it started.
I saw Kanata
crying a lot in the park once.
How did Kanata look to you?
He was terrified.
He was screaming.
I felt so bad for him.
I heard from the detective.
I was shocked.
To think that Kanata
would have an accident like that.
Mr. Kamijo, since the divorce,
have you seen Kanata?
I haven't seen him for years.
We divorced
because of my affair.
I didn't feel like I could face him.
Sir…
There's also a suspicion
that Kanata was being abused.
Do you know anything about that?
I've heard rumors.
I was worried.
Rumors?
Saya started dating a bad guy.
If I had taken Kanata in,
this would never…
I should go see him.
I could buy him some kintsuba.
Even though he's a kid,
he loves Japanese sweets.
I'm sure that would make him happy.
But maybe his tastes have changed by now.
I bet he has grown up.
Ryoji Kida, 34 years old.
A construction worker.
He's Saya Togawa's boyfriend.
We haven't been able
to contact Kida since the incident,
and it seems he didn't show up
for work today either.
So the mother's boyfriend is the abuser.
I think so.
However…
What?
Regarding the knife that was found,
it seems only Kanata's fingerprints
were detected on it.
Kanata's? Not Kida's?
Yes.
And one more thing.
What?
Well, it might not be relevant, actually.
Just say it.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, about Kida…
It seems he was abused himself
in the past.
RYOJI KIDA
He was?
Ms. Kiryu said she heard it
from the police.
Apparently, he was quite severely abused
by his stepfather when he was a child.
Even though he was abused himself,
he abuses a child?
Well, don't they say
people who were abused
tend to become abusers themselves
when they grow up?
Maybe because that's
the kind of parent they saw?
A cycle of abuse, so to speak.
Taking the pain you suffered
out on a child…
Right…
I'm glad you took the time to come.
I was only able to get where I am
because of you, Professor.
"Loved One."
How to face a body.
To doubt common sense,
not to be bound by precedent,
and to have free thought.
I was captivated by this field of study
because of your words.
You remember them well.
But…
during that case,
you didn't do any of that, Professor.
The Shiramine serial femicide case.
You remember it, don't you?
I intend to face that case once more.
Fifteen years ago…
SHIRAMINE SERIAL FEMICIDE CASE
RESEARCH DATA
…I ran away from that case.
Even though I had doubts
about your autopsy results.
At that time,
I didn't have the power or the knowledge
to overturn it.
But now,
I might be able
to unravel the contradictions.
Please tell me, Professor.
What really happened
behind the scenes of that case?
Well, isn't this a rare visitor?
Kyoko.
Don't push my father too hard.
I'm sorry for coming
at such a difficult time.
I'll come again.
Okay.
You're back.
How long will you be in Japan?
For a while.
You haven't changed at all.
That's not true.
You've heard about my father, right?
He has little time left.
I want him
to be able to forget everything
and pass away in peace.
The serial murders happening recently…
They're similar
to the Shiramine murder case.
There might be a connection.
Even if there is a connection,
it has nothing to do
with you or my father.
Don't come back.
You should forget it too.
This is the fifth case this year
of a girl being found strangled to death.
They're similar
to the Shiramine murder case.
You should forget it too.
Kanata has apparently
been terrified at school
for about a year,
saying he didn't want to go home.
That matches the time
Ms. Togawa started dating Kida.
It does.
Detective Dojima.
What?
Kida has turned himself in.
Like I said,
Kanata was being annoying.
He never listened to me,
so sometimes I slapped him,
telling him to be quiet.
It was the same that day.
He wouldn't stop crying,
and was bothering others.
So,
I gave him a light push.
I'm sorry for running away.
But I just panicked.
What about the knife we found
at the scene?
No idea.
It's not related to the incident?
Calling it an incident or abuse…
All I did was discipline him a little.
Discipline, you say?
That's right.
That was just a little discipline.
This is just some discipline.
I'm sorry!
Don't cry!
Dr. Takamori?
Are you okay? Dr. Takamori?
Hey, are you okay?
How is Kida?
He's in the holding cell now
and is being quiet.
He said he doesn't need
a lawyer or any visitors.
That's great, right?
The case was solved easily.
I don't think it's solved.
What?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
No, not at all.
Go home for the day and get some rest.
We need you to get well soon.
Since you'll be a dad.
I don't have the confidence.
I was abused, too.
A long time ago.
By my stepfather.
When he got drunk, he would get violent.
I still have the scars.
They're on my back.
They're very similar to Kanata's scars.
I'm sorry for making you remember
something so unpleasant.
I didn't remember it.
It's always in my head.
Kida…
was also abused by his parents.
And now,
he's the one abusing a child.
I'm scared…
that one day…
I might also end up raising
my hand against my own child.
No, you would never.
But maybe…
because you experienced that,
there is something you can do.
I think you're the one who understands
how much Kanata suffers
better than anyone, Dr. Takamori.
I'm sorry…
Kanata.
MY CHECKUP IS DONE
THEY SAID THE BABY IS VERY HEALTHY!
This is Masumi.
This is Takamori.
Sorry for calling while you're on leave.
No, it's fine.
Did something happen?
I'm sorry for leaving
the investigation entirely to you.
I've heard about the situation
from Ms. Kiryu.
I don't know what to do.
The suspect turned himself in,
but I feel like nothing
has been solved yet.
I was wondering what you would do
in a situation like this.
If it were me,
I would re-examine
the remaining contradictions.
Like, the wounds on the arm.
Those wounds were arranged in parallel
with a certain regularity.
In cases of abuse, scars and bruises
would be scattered randomly,
not perfectly parallel.
It doesn't add up.
But, please keep in mind,
this is just how I would do it.
How one faces forensic medicine
is free and different for everyone.
Dr. Takamori,
how will you solve this mystery?
Dr. Takamori is late, isn't he?
There's no point in waiting.
Let's start with what we can do.
Sorry, I'm late.
Dr. Takamori.
I've decided
to try and find the truth one more time.
I've reclassified Kanata's scars
based on their characteristics.
Contusions on the head from the fall.
Bruises and burn marks,
which suggest abuse.
And systematic wounds on the left arm.
Looking at them like this,
they each seem to be wounds
inflicted in different ways.
Right.
That's easy to understand.
So the arm wounds are the only ones
that are strange after all.
I want everyone to analyze
these arm wounds in detail.
Okay.
Understood.
What about you?
I…
A long time ago,
I was abused by my stepfather.
I looked back at my own experience.
Abuse always happens inside the house.
I'm going to look for clues there.
I'm sorry for having you come
all the way out here with us.
It can't be helped,
since the police need to be present.
It's a big help.
I want clues too.
I'm sorry for taking up your time.
Since it is such a serious case, we need
to investigate inside the home as well.
I don't want to leave Kanata alone
for a long time…
We won't stay long.
Is something wrong?
It's not roughed up.
What?
When there's abuse,
there are marks
on the walls and everywhere.
From going on a rampage
and throwing things and stuff.
That's how it was at my place.
Here you go.
Please, don't trouble yourself.
Thank you very much.
Have some of this too.
He likes them, so I bought some.
Those are nice photos.
That was Kida's influence too.
He does martial arts,
so he said he watches his calories
and chooses Japanese
sweets over Western ones,
so Kanata started eating them to copy him.
Forgive me for asking, Saya,
but did you not notice that Kida
was committing abuse?
Or perhaps,
did you not think he was committing abuse?
I don't know.
Well then,
what about the "monster"?
The "black monster" Kanata mentioned
when he was being transported.
Do you have any ideas?
I only vaguely remember…
I might have read him
a picture book about that.
A picture book?
THE BLACK MONSTER
The Black Monster,
a picture book published in the '80s.
One night,
a black monster appears before a child
who does nothing but play pranks.
Eerie hands stretch out from the darkness
and wrap around the child.
He desperately resisted,
and drove it away.
But after that,
every time he did something bad,
the black hands
would wrap around the child again.
In the end,
the black hands wrapped around
the child's arms and wouldn't let go,
and he finally ended up
becoming a black monster himself.
The end.
Why is it such a hopeless story?
A lesson not to do bad things?
If the thing Kanata feared
was the monster from this picture book…
Kanata?
Kanata!
Kanata…
Kanata,
can you talk to us for just a little bit?
Yes.
Thank you.
Do you remember what happened
when you fell down the stairs?
I don't know.
I don't really remember.
I see.
It looks like you have quite
a few injuries besides your head.
Where did you get hurt?
Can I look at your wounds
for just a second?
Yes.
Sorry.
Kanata!
I'm scared, I'm scared!
The monster is coming!
The black monster!
Kanata!
I'm sorry, that's enough for today.
Kanata.
You'll be okay.
Doctor, what's that?
This is Kanata's head MRI.
-Something is bugging me.
-Bugging you?
This.
What is it?
Those wounds were arranged in parallel
with a certain regularity.
In the end,
the black hands wrapped around
the child's arms and wouldn't let go,
and he finally ended up
becoming a black monster himself.
The black monster!
Dr. Takamori?
Now…
the pieces might be coming together.
What else do you want?
I already told you everything.
No, you haven't.
I need you to tell me the truth.
What?
You weren't the one abusing Kanata.
How is Kanata doing?
Are you not going to see him, Mr. Kamijo?
Well, even if I did…
It was you, wasn't it?
You were the one abusing Kanata.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Looking at Kanata's head MRI,
there is slight atrophy
in the temporal and frontal lobes.
Atrophy?
This is a characteristic seen in children
who have been abused in the past.
It is said that
the emotional scars received
manifest in the brain.
Kanata's scars are also unnatural.
The wounds on his back and thighs
have a different color tone
compared to the others.
Those wounds
might date back much further
than a year ago,
to before you even started dating Saya.
In other words,
he was being abused
long before she met you.
Mr. Kamijo,
these are considered
wounds from past abuse
that occurred when he was living with you.
Stop joking around.
Why would I--
You said it the other day, didn't you?
That Kanata likes kintsuba.
Of course I know what my son--
Kanata only started liking kintsuba
after meeting Mr. Kida.
That happened within the past year.
You said you haven't seen him in years,
so how did you know?
You've actually been seeing Kanata
over the past year, haven't you?
The question is,
why are you protecting Kamijo,
when you have nothing to do with him?
I don't know.
I'm not protecting anybody.
The important clue for us
was the parallel wounds
carved into Kanata's left arm.
Normally, if someone
continued to abuse a person,
the wounds would be more random.
But those wounds
were placed systematically,
in the same spot
over and over again in the same way.
They aren't scars
from abuse by another person.
They're scars that Kanata
was inflicting on himself.
to stop the black monster from coming.
The black monster is coming… The monster…
Three months ago,
during a drinking session
with old friends,
you apparently heard
that Saya had a new lover.
You seemed to have become very jealous.
-Coming!
-So then…
You went to Saya's home.
Please leave.
What's the big deal? I'm your ex-husband.
Are you her new boyfriend?
Please leave.
You've grown, Kanata.
Hey.
Daddy's talking to you.
You should answer.
Past memories of being beaten
flashed back to Kanata.
To resist the trauma,
so that the black monster wouldn't come,
Kanata, it's okay.
-The monster…
-Go away, now!
I'm scared! Stop!
Kanata!
What is this?
No, the monster!
-Hey, Kanata!
-The monster…
It's okay now.
You're okay.
All right!
You're doing it. Go!
I'm scared!
-No!
-It's okay.
-Should we do something?
-No! Stop!
-You're okay!
-Kanata's flashbacks kept coming back.
You wanted to help him somehow,
didn't you?
If you're a man,
you've got to become
strong enough to help your mom.
-But…
-You can do it.
Kanata,
you're strong.
I'm… strong?
Yes.
Thanks to Mr. Kida,
Kanata gradually began to recover.
But then the incident happened…
because you came to Kanata's house again.
Probably,
what happened on that day was…
TOGAWA
What?
Saya's not here?
Where's Saya?
Where did she go?
I am…
strong.
But…
Kida's teachings…
backfired.
Don't talk nonsense.
It wasn't me.
Saya's boyfriend has confessed.
Yes.
After being threatened by you.
From my perspective,
I just went to the house
and was almost stabbed to death.
This is a clear case of attempted murder.
You've got to be kidding me.
What about you abusing him?
You can't prove something
from that long ago.
On the other hand,
Kanata has strange delusions
and self-harms,
and tries to stab people to death.
He'll go to a detention center.
Just say that you did it.
If you want to save Kanata,
you know what to do.
Mr. Kida…
You had no choice--
I did it.
That's enough, isn't it?
Actually,
before I came here…
Saya told me everything.
I HAVE TO SAY I DID IT, FOR KANATA'S SAKE
After the incident,
she was told
to match what you were going to say,
and she has been hesitant about it
the entire time.
No matter what the police ask you,
just say you don't know.
What about Ryoji?
Where is he?
He's okay.
It'll be fine.
She wondered
if this was really for the best.
There's no way this is a solution.
After all, Kanata likes Ryoji, too.
He really loves him.
That's what Saya said.
The one you were trying to protect
and keep safe
was Kanata, wasn't it?
Yes?
Do you understand how heartbreaking it is
to be beaten by your own parent?
Scars from being beaten by
someone you want to be loved by most
stay with you for a lifetime.
How…
can you do something
so cruel to your own child?
Protecting your precious child
is what a father does, isn't it?
I will never…
become a parent like you.
Mr. Kida has apparently
retracted his confession.
Mr. Kamijo.
Could you come talk with us
at the station?
Feels nice outside, right?
Yeah.
Hey!
It's Ryoji!
Kanata.
I'm not going anywhere anymore.
From now on, we'll always be together.
I…
will make you and your mom happy.
Got it?
Yeah!
Isn't this great?
The cycle of abuse can be broken.
I will break it.
I will.
Good morning.
Oh, Dr. Masumi.
Sorry for waking you.
It's fine.
It's already this late?
Doctor…
Thank you very much.
I am very glad I relied on you,
Dr. Takamori.
Good morning.
Oh! Dr. Masumi!
It was tough without you here.
For Dr. Takamori, it was.
Sure, but…
We should get him
to treat you to something.
No, that's all right.
What?
Oh, dear…
Is something wrong?
Well…
-My wife is in labor.
-What?
-She's about to give birth.
-What should I do?
-Just go!
Don't worry about things here.
I'm going then!
-Take care!
-Sorry.
-Hey, hey, hey!
-Oh, my bag.
-Be careful!
-Thank you.
-See you!
-Bye!
Bye!
Subtitle translation by: Maslin F.