-Is it around here?
-Yes, we'll be there soon.
Is this it?
All right, let's get our money's worth!
ETHNIC CAFE
This is good stuff.
It's great, isn't it?
Do you not like ethnic food?
Come on, you should have just told me.
Well, every single option
you gave me, Dr. Matsubara,
was ethnic food.
I hate people
who just try and read the room.
Sorry.
But this feeling of the spices
rushing through your whole body
is the absolute best.
Whether a person reads the room or not
won't show up in an autopsy, will it?
If you die, nobody is going to
know your were kind.
I wouldn't want that.
Right…
MOM: YOUR SISTER IS IN TROUBLE
YOUR SISTER IS IN TROUBLE
PARLIAMENT MEMBER TOSHIO AOTA'S
FORBIDDEN AFFAIR: HIS CHIEF SECRETARY!
CONTACTS
SAKI MATSUBARA
OFFICE OF TOSHIO AOTA
Dr. Matsubara?
Yes?
Do you need any help?
No, I'm fine.
Hello, this is Medical Examiner Japan.
What?
The parliament member's office?
Yes.
I understand.
Hello.
The deceased is Toshio Aota,
a lawmaker from the National Party.
When his chief secretary, Saki Matsubara,
visited the office this morning,
he was discovered already hanging.
No suicide note has been found,
but a magazine published an article
about an affair of his.
Furthermore, it was with the person who
first discovered him, Saki Matsubara.
Considering the situation,
the police are viewing it as a suicide.
Wait.
Where's Ms. Dojima?
She was called in by the chief
regarding this case.
Dojima.
Don't look too hard into
the parliament member's death.
You get it, right?
No subcutaneous bleeding.
No facial congestion either.
The stop of circulation
is highly likely due to pressure.
Which means?
There is a possibility
that he was hanged after he died.
I see multiple small,
hole-like wounds on his chest.
The autopsy shows, as expected,
Mr. Aota's cause of death
was not asphyxiation from hanging.
The discoloration on Mr. Aota's
body is concentrated on his back.
If he had died from hanging,
it should have appeared
on his fingers and lower legs.
It doesn't add up.
Does that mean it was murder?
Mr. Aota appears to have suffered
cardiac arrest before he was hanged.
It seems someone used a rope
to hang him several hours after his death.
There are minor scrapes
and bruises on his hands and feet,
but they are all light injuries.
From their location,
they are highly likely
from a fall or a stumble.
Was that fall the cause of death?
There was a mark indicating
a strong impact to the chest.
The shock most likely fractured his ribs,
which punctured his lung.
We also confirmed
bleeding inside the chest,
but nothing that we could say
is the cause of death.
There were also
four small stab wounds on the chest.
Rather than stab wounds from a knife,
it looks more like a mark left by
forcing something sharp into the skin.
There is almost no bleeding
from the wounds, which means
it is highly likely these wounds
were inflicted after death.
Meaning, whoever made those wounds
holds the key to this case?
For now,
it's a mystery.
Apparently, that man Aota,
whom we autopsied today,
was suspected of having an affair.
What? Really?
And it was with his chief secretary
who first found him.
Maybe she killed him over a messy affair.
What do you think, Dr. Matsubara?
That's… my older sister.
-Huh?
-What?
That politician's secretary,
Saki Matsubara.
She's my older sister.
Please let me join the investigation
for this case.
I can't accept this,
so I want to investigate it myself.
Please.
I think
this could be
a piece of a bigger puzzle.
Hello, this is Medical Examiner…
What?
Yes.
That's right.
Yes, goodbye.
Is something wrong?
The MHLW told me not to get involved
in the investigation of this case.
I…
was having an affair with Mr. Aota.
We met at my apartment
during the day of the incident.
I seriously can't believe you.
Do you think I'm stupid?
He told me he would divorce his wife,
but he never actually did it.
Recently, we ended up arguing
every time we met.
But I never imagined
he would commit suicide.
We are investigating with
the possibility of murder in mind as well.
Is that so?
Mr. Aota fell from the exterior staircase
of the apartment where you live?
Yes.
May we investigate that?
Go ahead.
No bloodstains or signs of a fall
were found on the apartment stairs.
Aota did not appear
on any of the security cameras either.
The components found in the wound
did not match the concrete components
of the apartment stairs.
None of it adds up.
But that makes no sense.
Why would she come forward
just to lie to us
and seem more suspicious?
There must be a reason.
Dr. Matsubara,
do you have any insights?
She has always been like that.
She just reads the room
and tries to please everyone.
Her special talent was avoiding conflict.
An affair?
Murder?
That's hilarious.
That's a lot of conflict.
She might actually be…
reading the room right now.
So Saki Matsubara knows the truth
that Aota fell somewhere else,
and she is lying
to try and hide another truth?
It is only a possibility.
Did you find anything out
about the stab wounds?
There is something strange
about the entry paths.
Strange?
Out of the four wounds,
three are very shallow,
but the fourth one goes
all the way into the chest cavity.
Furthermore, all the wounds
were deliberately inflicted
along a path that avoids the ribs.
Any trace substances yet?
We should get results soon. I'll check.
PARLIAMENT MEMBER AOTA (50)
FOUND HANGED IN OFFICE
Thank you.
Sure.
Let's eat.
It's rare to see you working this late.
Apparently, Aota used to work
as a surgeon at Senshu Hospital.
I might find something out,
so I plan to go there tomorrow.
I summarized the policies
Aota was working on.
It looks like he was recently drafting
a bill related to the healthcare system.
Impressive.
This is about all I can do right now.
I really don't like her.
My sister.
She always reads the room
and tries to smooth everything over.
When she’s in trouble,
she takes it all on herself.
She acts tough and says she's fine
even when she isn't.
It's all so annoying.
But…
my sister would never do
anything to hurt another person.
An affair? Murder?
Why would she lie?
That means it's your turn to step in,
Dr. Matsubara.
Living people might tell lies sometimes.
But bodies never do.
The truth is there, I'm sure.
Our food will get cold. Let's eat.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Mom.
Are you okay?
Isn't that Mr. Aota's wife?
Is your mother hospitalized?
Yes.
Her lungs have always been a bit weak.
I'm sorry.
We've been going around
asking questions about Mr. Aota.
Did you find out anything?
No.
Hey.
That's the chairman
of the Senshu Group, isn't it?
A charismatic figure
in the medical world who believes
in saving every life.
My husband originally
started working at this hospital
because he admired Chairman Mukai.
Ten years ago, he suddenly
decided to become a politician.
All of Mr. Aota's policies were wonderful.
Or like, they felt created
by a proper human being.
I'm sorry.
On that day,
he told me he would be late,
but would come home early the next day
so we could go out for dinner somewhere.
But…
that day turned out to be his last.
TOSHIO AOTA
May I have a balloon?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
You're welcome. Bye-bye!
May I have one?
Sure.
Thank you.
Doctor, is that…
The reason balloons float
is because the helium inside it
is lighter than the air around--
It's okay.
Take this one.
Have this one.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
Let's go.
Excuse me.
One more?
One more, please.
Oh, sure.
Thank you, sorry.
Thank you.
Sorry.
When you listen
to the stories of the living,
the truth becomes harder to know.
Dr. Masumi.
Do you ever read the room?
The human brain contains nerve cells
called mirror neurons.
These are brain cells that react
to actions of others
by mirroring what we observe.
Because of this function,
we are naturally wired to empathize
with the words and actions of others.
What is it?
I just read the room.
So you can read it?
It's simply the function of nerve cells.
Is that how it works?
I don't think it's a bad thing.
Reading the room
is an innate ability humans possess.
It is one of our tools for survival.
Take a seat wherever.
You didn't engage in an affair, right?
You read the weekly magazines, didn't you?
They're lying.
They're not.
Why?
Answer my question.
There is no particular reason.
I just fell in love with him, that's all.
But what you said
about the stairs was a lie.
You didn't kill him, right?
Hey.
What are you trying to protect?
Is it really that important to you?
Is it worth more than your own life?
Shut up!
Don't assume everyone
can live their life like you do.
What?
What does that mean?
Suzune, you've always been this way.
You think speaking the truth
makes you entirely right.
I have spent my whole life living
in a world that isn't quite so simple.
A world like that
is completely meaningless.
Just leave.
Fine.
But answer me just one last thing.
What?
Did you truly love Aota?
What kind of question is that?
Did you genuinely intend
to build a life together with Aota?
Yes, I did.
See?
Are we done now?
Leave.
These are the chemical components
from Aota's clothing and nasal cavity.
The amount of volatile sulfur compounds
is exceptionally high.
Yes.
I can't quite figure out this part.
We also recovered traces
of phthalocyanine pigments,
glycerol, emulsifiers, and fragrance
from the stab wounds.
Phthalocyanine is a pigment, isn't it?
The kind used in paints and inks.
Glycerol is commonly used
as a solvent in ink as well.
Emulsifiers and fragrances
point toward cosmetics.
It's a mystery.
I need to look into something.
What?
There might be a piece of the puzzle
we've missed.
CHEMICAL COMPOUNDS
This… might be the secret spice.
The secret spice?
Asafoetida.
Otherwise known as the secret spice.
It is native to South Africa
and has a vey strong odor,
much like garlic or durian.
The chemical composition is a close match.
When heated in oil,
it volatilizes quickly,
which explains how microparticles
could adhere to someone.
Incredible, Dr. Matsubara!
Ethnic maniac!
This feeling of the spices
rushing through your whole body
is the absolute best.
SECRET SPICE CURRY
I need to go verify this.
What?
Don't tell me you're leaving too?
There might be a piece of the puzzle
we've missed.
We are indeed using it
in our current special menu, but…
Did you happen to hear anything heavy
falling nearby on that day?
Oh, I'm not sure…
EMERGENCY LADDER
That day, Aota fell down the stairs
at the Sanyo Hotel.
I believe he took a heavy hit
to his chest after falling.
If that's the case,
then he really did die from a fall, right?
But we still don't understand
the mystery of the stab wound.
Like a mark left by forcing
something sharp into the skin.
I was having an affair with Toshio Aota.
I believe he took a heavy hit
to his chest after falling.
We also recovered traces of phthalocyanine
pigments from the stab wounds.
The kind used in paints and inks.
Her lungs have always been a bit weak.
She just reads the room…
The pieces might be…
coming together.
First,
regarding Aota's cause of death,
a certain hypothesis has been formed.
Traces of a rare spice called asafoetida
have been detected
on the clothing Aota wore
and in his nasal cavity.
On the day Aota died,
a dish using this spice
was being served at the Sanyo Hotel.
And, Aota's fingerprints and bloodstains
were detected
on the hotel's external stairs.
It is likely that,
somehow, Aota fell from
these stairs and hit his chest hard,
fracturing his ribs,
causing a hole to open in his lungs.
When a hole opens in the lung,
air leaks into the chest cavity,
putting pressure on the lung and heart.
This condition is called
a tension pneumothorax.
Judging from
the circumstances of the fall,
it would not be surprising if Aota
had developed tension pneumothorax.
However, during the autopsy,
we found no air to be trapped there.
A tension pneumothorax
is a life-threatening, critical condition.
As an emergency measure,
you must puncture the chest cavity,
before it becomes fatal.
What is it?
Could you stab that into the chest cavity?
The chest cavity?
As a rough guide, it's around here.
To be exact, it's between the ribs.
No, no way I could do that.
Could you do it?
Traces of what is believed to be
ink pigments were detected in the wounds.
And in his office,
parts of a ballpoint pen with ink
components that match were found.
If someone,
as a life-saving measure for Aota,
who was suffering
from a tension pneumothorax,
had stabbed a ballpoint pen into him,
and if that procedure
had relieved the tension pneumothorax,
it would be difficult
to notice it during an autopsy.
Aota's chest wound
was not a trace of an attempt to kill him.
I believe it is a sign of an effort
to save his life.
For Mr. Aota's sake as well,
won't you please
tell us the truth?
I'm sorry.
A long time ago,
when I was walking with my mother…
Mom, what's wrong?
She suddenly clutched her chest
and collapsed.
Are you okay?
Mom, are you okay?
I'm a doctor.
She is experiencing
a tension pneumothorax.
I have performed emergency first aid.
I'm sorry, but please rest assured.
-Thank you so much.
-Call an ambulance.
We had been married
and together for so many years…
and I thought I knew everything about him.
But lately,
he seemed to be hiding something.
That's why, on that day,
I really suspected
he was having an affair.
Mr. Kakei!
Do you have a moment?
Not in here.
Let's go somewhere else.
Please retract that article.
It's because you guys
are sneaking around snooping.
Bribery is a crime.
You're an adult,
so read the room a little bit more.
Besides,
an evil that can bring change
is far better than justice
that can't change anything, isn't it?
Mr. Aota!
Follow him!
Okay!
Dear!
Are you all right?
Kaede?
OFFICE OF TOSHIO AOTA
Explain to me what happened.
I'm sorry.
Let's separate.
What?
It's better if we aren't together.
Kaede, pretend you didn't know anything.
Live a normal life.
What are you saying?
I don't understand!
Dear?
Dear!
Dear! Are you okay? What's wrong?
What?
Dear!
It's not working!
Dear! Don't go!
Dear?
Dear…
Why?
Dear!
I…
killed my husband, didn't I?
Out of the four stab wounds,
one of them successfully punctured
his chest cavity
and allowed air to escape.
However,
by that point,
your husband had already passed.
The traces…
of your attempts to save him…
told us the truth.
I believe your husband
was trying his best
to stay alive as long as he could
for your sake.
I never had an affair with him.
Mr. Aota…
was trying to expose
the bribery between Mr. Kakei
and the Senshu Group.
It was about a month ago
when Mr. Aota realized that Chairman Mukai
of the Senshu Group
was giving bribes to Kakei.
Why would you bribe him?
To expand this hospital
and save as many lives as possible.
I will do whatever it takes
for that cause.
Doing that, the future of
Japanese healthcare will be--
I have seen countless hospitals collapse
because of that kind of idealistic talk.
Saving as many lives
as possible through politics…
That may just be idealistic talk.
I might drag you into this as well.
If you want out, do it now.
I will give it some thought.
The bribes were always in cash.
And that day,
we tracked down their location
and were about to secure the evidence,
but Kakei caught wind of our movements.
Follow him!
Okay!
Mr. Kakei!
What?
I…
I believe the role of politics
is to create a world
where we can call what is right, right.
Aota's bill
is going through
the internal procedures, right?
You want it to pass, don't you?
You were being threatened?
Neither I nor Kakei
knew the truth behind Mr. Aota's death.
So,
when Kakei found out that Mr. Aota
was going to be autopsied,
he panicked…
and he…
You didn't have to…
That bill…
contained all of Mr. Aota's hopes.
I don't understand.
I don't understand why you've kept quiet
this whole time, Kaede.
After all, you weren't the one
who fabricated the evidence, right?
You're still hiding something, aren't you?
A prosecutor came.
A prosecutor?
He told me that if he were transported
to the hospital as he was,
it would be written off
as a disease or sudden death.
He said everything
would be covered up by Kakei.
The corruption my husband tried to expose,
and the hopes he had in politics,
would all be wiped away
as if they never happened.
I absolutely could not allow that.
So, I decided to wager everything on this.
But…
I've been worried this entire time
if it was the right thing to do.
The next day, when the police contacted me
saying they found him hanging,
it completely stopped making sense to me.
Oh, it's very red.
Let's see.
There.
Oh, that was shocking.
Sorry, that's not why I'm here.
I didn't do that on purpose, sorry.
Oh, man.
Mizusawa.
That's you, right?
What was the conclusion
on Aota's cause of death?
It's believed to be tension pneumothorax
resulting from a fall down the stairs.
Is there a possibility that someone
intentionally pushed him down?
None of the wounds
or bruises left on Mr. Aota's body
provides clear proof of homicidal intent.
Furthermore, considering their statements,
it doesn't add up.
It doesn't add up, huh?
Yes.
It doesn't add up.
It doesn't add up, which means
it was bribery after all.
Oops.
Tails, that makes sense.
Excuse me, but who are you?
I'm Ota.
From the Public Prosecutors Office.
A prosecutor?
By the way,
I heard you went to see Dr. Kujo?
How did it go?
Were you able to speak with him?
Well?
You didn't?
Oh, listen.
Bribery paid in cash makes it
quite difficult to secure evidence.
However, it has been confirmed
that Chairman Mukai
was at the hotel that day.
Therefore, if we have
Mr. Aota's autopsy results
and the testimony of both individuals,
it will serve as major leverage
to pursue Kakei.
Your methods are foul.
Our objective is also
to uncover the truth.
An unnatural death
must always be autopsied.
You just used the MEJ system
to bring down a powerful politician.
Used?
Fabricating a suicide by hanging
constitutes the crimes
of damaging and abandoning a corpse.
Is that so?
What?
Please leave.
This is a place
to listen to the voices of the deceased
and uncover the truth.
It is a place to learn
what they loved and who loved them.
It's not for you to bring in
your self-serving narratives!
Didn't you hear her?
Please leave.
Heads or tails? Pick.
What?
See you around.
I think I went a bit too far.
You can just be scolded for it later.
Don't worry about it.
I still want… to live in a world
where I can call what is right, right.
Yeah.
You can't let people
you don't even believe are right
run your life.
Reading the room
is different from
letting yourself be used.
You're right.
So Kakei ended up
not being prosecuted after all, huh?
They say he claims
his secretary did everything.
In the end, nothing changes, huh?
It looks like the bill Mr. Aota drafted
was properly submitted.
The younger politicians
carried on his vision.
It's true!
If you seriously want to change things,
they will change.
I want to believe that.
All right, let's work.
Subtitle translation by: Maslin F.