"Lost To You"
(Episode 6)
We tentatively drew closer,
only to run into a figure
who shouldn't be there.
Jealousy is a silent tsunami,
drowning all our unspoken understanding.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you couldn't swim.
You lied to me.
I didn't realize you were afraid of water.
I thought you just didn't like it much.
Why did you jump?
I just wanted to know...
if you really meant it...
when you said you'd save me.
Now you know.
I know.
Even though you're afraid of water,
you'd still jump in to save me.
Why... are you afraid of water?
Because of my dad.
He died at sea.
The year I was born,
an old fortune teller came to town.
He said I was born under an unlucky star.
But my dad refused to believe it.
He said on the day I was born,
the sky was blue and the sea was calm.
I must have been a gift
sent to him from the heavens.
That's why he named me Xu Yuan
[TN: "Make a wish" in mandarin]]
His wish was...
for me to live a safe and peaceful life.
Then, when I was ten,
he took me out on the boat.
I accidentally fell into the water.
To save me,
he used all his strength to push me ashore.
But he never made it back up.
After that,
everyone in town said...
the curse of the Jinx had come true.
Ever since then,
I've been afraid of water.
That wasn't your fault.
It was never your fault.
I'll tell you one of... my secrets.
Actually, I'm just like my older brother.
I'm also the "monster" my dad talks about.
I like men.
I'm scared...
of becoming like my brother.
So I desperately tried to
convince myself to be normal.
But I know...
how I really feel.
This is something...
I've never told anyone before.
Now you know.
I'm trading my secret...
for your secret.
Now we're even.
Thank you.
For what?
Thank you for telling me...
that the sea swallows people up,
and that what happened to my dad...
was never your fault.
Liking men...
is not your fault either.
So let's both stop blaming ourselves.
I'll be with you.
Do you mind?
What?
Yesterday on the fishing boat...
the secret I told you.
Do you think it's weird?
No.
We're good friends.
Why would I mind?
Pass it here, pass it here!
Here!
Zhan Wang!
Come on, come on!
Thanks.
One more day.
[An unbelievably sad string of unanswered texts
to his dad, ending with "Dad, It's my birthday"]
[He's considering deleting his
WeChat conversation with his dad]
What are you doing here?
There's a problem I can't solve,
so I came to ask you.
Is that not okay?
No problem.
The power must be out.
I'll go check.
It's okay.
I have this.
This is for you.
Next time the power goes out,
you can use this for light.
I have something to give to you too.
Wang-wang.
Happy birthday.
How did you know...
it was my birthday?
I...
of course I knew.
Yuan.
Thank you.
["His fingers ran through his partner's sweaty
hair, the moment their lips drew close..."]
Bro.
You're reading this?
Xu Nuo.
You're the one who put
this on my bookshelf, right?
Well, Mom doesn't go through your stuff.
So? What do you think?
Isn't it super intense?
Let me tell you,
this pool scene...
I dog-eared the page specifically.
It's so perfect for you and Zhan Wang!
Stop talking nonsense.
Oh, stop pretending.
I can totally see it.
You and Zhan Wang have
been inseparable lately.
The way he looks at you...
So...
you guys should go on a proper date.
Find a thrilling environment.
Get your hearts racing.
It's a catalyst for love.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll tell Mom...
that you read novels in class.
And have her cancel your acting classes.
Okay, okay.
I'll stop.
But, bro...
if you really like Zhan Wang,
you should be brave.
I can tell.
Zhan Wang is so good to you.
And you're good to him too.
Xu Yuan.
What is it?
Get on.
Where are we going?
Don't worry about that. Just get in.
Let's go.
What are we doing here so late at night?
Didn't you say you wanted
to learn how to swim?
Where did you get the keys?
I borrowed it from the equipment room.
You stole it, didn't you?
Borrowed, borrowed, borrowed.
Come on.
Xu Yuan.
I don't want to go in.
Why not?
Didn't you say you wanted to learn?
I changed my mind.
Is it because of...
what happened to your dad?
Xu Yuan.
You can't be afraid of
water your whole life.
Running away won't solve anything.
I don't need to solve it.
I just won't get in the water.
What if that person was me?
What if I fell in the water?
Would you just watch?
Like with your dad?
Trust me.
Just this once.
Come on down.
Give me your hand.
You smell like mints.
I can smell it even in the water.
Okay, how about this?
I'll teach you how to hold your breath.
Okay.
How was that?
Breathe. Relax.
When the water reaches
your chin, exhale slowly.
I'll show you first.
Okay.
See?
Got it?
Why don't you do it with me?
Trust me.
Let's try it together.
I'll count to three.
We'll go down together.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
You okay?
Let's hold it longer this time.
If you can't, just tap me.
Okay.
You can do it.
Three.
Two.
One.
Who's there?
The pool is closed at night.
Come out.
I know someone's in there.
Sneaking in for a swim, are we?
Zhan Wang. Xu Yuan.
Get out of there, now!
Well, well. You two.
Getting bold, aren't you?
Stealing the key.
Sneaking into the pool.
Do you have any idea how dangerous this is?
What if something had happened?
I'm sorry, teacher.
We were wrong.
T-Teacher, I'm sorry.
Is just saying sorry going to cut it?
Today, you dare to steal a
key and sneak into the pool.
Tomorrow, will you be
breaking into the science lab?
And the day after that,
you'll be completely lawless?
No respect for rules. No discipline.
When I was underwater just now,
I was saving you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
School property is public property.
Does that key belong to you?
You don't believe me?
If you don't believe me,
next time I'll show you
the underwater rescue manual.
Also, your lung capacity...
You really need to work on it.
Do you know how to train it?
Do you?
If you don't know,
I'll teach you next time.
Did you hear a word I said?
Yes, sir.
Loud and clear.
Get back to your dorms.
And await your punishment.
Go.
Goodbye, teacher.
Beat it.
Are you asleep?
Not yet.
What's up?
Tomorrow, you can help
me with my boxing practice.
And I'll help you with your lung capacity.
Deal?
Deal.
It's a deal then.
Get some sleep. Good night.
Good night.
You smell like mints.
I could even smell it in the water.
Let's check, Teacher Xu.
Class.
I'd like to introduce a new student.
Her name is Lin Xia.
She's an art student from Jingzhou.
She's here in Hong Town to sketch.
She'll be studying with us for a while.
Let's give her a warm welcome.
Find a seat for yourself.
Zhan Wang.
Long time no see.
What are you doing here?
Uncle was worried about you.
So he had me come check on you.
And to check on your second brother.
I knew it.
That's all he cares about.
He wants you to keep an eye on me.
He's afraid I'll get too
close to my brother.
Hi.
I'm Lin Xia.
You must be Zhan Wang's friend.
It seems you two are pretty close.
Zhan Wang is stubborn.
He doesn't have many friends.
For you to be his friend...
is quite impressive.
I'm Zhan Wang's fiancée.
Lin Xia.
What nonsense are you talking about?
What nonsense?
Didn't our families agree on it?
Or...
am I wrong?
Zhan Wang.
It was arranged by our families.
It doesn't mean anything.
What are you all looking at?
Stop it. Don't talk nonsense.
That girl who just went upstairs,
she's the new transfer student.
I saw her by the field earlier.
White dress, long hair.
Carrying a sketchpad.
She looked like a fairy.
I heard she's an art student from Jingzhou.
And that she's won an
international painting award.
No wonder she's so elegant.
Compared to the girls at our school,
she's completely different.
She seems like someone
straight out of a TV drama.
That's what you call an idol.
You guys haven't seen
someone truly impressive.
There's someone at our school
even more eye-catching than Lin Xia.
See?
That guy Zhan Wang from my brother's class.
He's handsome,
a great fighter,
and amazing at sports.
Plus,
he's from a truly wealthy family.
Now that's a real star.
Senior Zhan Wang.
He does seem pretty famous.
Yeah, yeah.
The Jinx's friend.
Those two are practically
joined at the hip these days.
That might not be the case for long.
I heard...
the 'fairy' and senior Zhan
Wang know each other.
Someone saw them earlier,
coming out of the
teachers' office together.
So what if they know each other?
My brother and Brother
Zhan Wang hang out every day.
They're the real deal.
Anyway, I have to bring
them their lunch later.
Then,
I'll get a look at that 'fairy' myself.
And see if she's really all that.
Xu Nuo.
Are you scouting the
enemy for your brother?
Or are you checking her out
for your 'Brother Zhan Wang'?
None of your business.
I'm just bringing them lunch.
Hope you don't get the cold shoulder.
Look, she's mad now.
You.
Your hair, on this side...
Bro! Brother Zhan Wang!
Time to eat.
You must be the new girl.
You're so pretty.
I'm Xu Yuan's little sister,
Xu Nuo.
So you're Xu Nuo.
You're so cute.
Bro.
Brother Zhan Wang.
My brother specifically asked Mom
to make your favorite pork ribs.
You two are really close.
My brother remembers
everything you like to eat.
However,
I don't think Zhan Wang
has ever eaten cilantro.
He can't stand even a hint of it.
And it looks like this dish
is full of chopped cilantro.
I'll remember that for next time.
So picky and so proud of it.