A survival show crowning K-POP's top boy group.
National producers,
pick the best members yourselves.
[Yoon Soo An]
You made it to the final stage.
How does it feel?
It hasn't sunk in.
Thank you for the kind words.
I'll work harder.
Through the rough times,
was there anyone you leaned on?
Hyun Jae and Soo An,
people say you two must be dating.
That rumor's out there.
Is it true?
Come on...
Yeah, it's true.
Huh?
What, am I wrong?
Hey, knock it off.
What's wrong?
Not just for the cameras, right?
Does it look that way?
[AI Alert: Mallangs Swoon Moments]
No way, it looked so real.
Seriously?
Props to AI.
These two keep me going.
I really want them to debut together.
[Soo An out by one rank? No way]
[Splitting them up? Brutal]
[Mirae Times: Final 6 'Wakers' Debut]
- Waker! Hi, we're Wakers.
[One-year contract run ahead]
♪ Happy birthday ♪
['Wakers' Ending, No Renewal]
[Wakers Goodbye Fan Meeting In September]
Wait, a year already?
What about the trainees who got cut?
Right?
Anyone still remember Mallangs?
What's Soo An up to?
Alright, eyes on Hyun Jae.
[Hyun Jae]
Looks good.
That's a wrap for the stand-ins.
[Wakers Goodbye Fan Meeting]
When the members arrive in an hour,
we'll jump right into rehearsal.
Mark your spots now,
and recheck the rest of the setup.
[Se Beom]
Okay, come on down.
Hurry down and clear the gear.
Honestly, Soo An,
the stage suits you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Huh?
Oh, I didn't mention it?
Thought I had.
My head's everywhere lately.
You're stuck at home too much. I worry.
Get out, meet people, breathe a little.
I know Hyun Jae makes you uneasy,
but Yoon Soo An, you've worked sets. You know.
Can you recall a single crew face?
Has anyone ever spoken to you?
You won't run into Hyun Jae.
Don't worry.
Wakers just pulled up. Move fast, please.
Don't hang around. Go haul boxes from the lot.
We're late, Hyun Jae. Get out.
Do you need help?
I'm good.
Public opinion shaped by mass media
shapes everything.
- Who's Shin Jae Min?
- That's why the press
- He's never come to class, right?
- is a double-edged sword.
Does anyone know him?
He's in the group chat.
A year ago,
on the audition show Next Stage,
we found
- one such case.
- Team 4?
Some contestants rode scandals into favor
and gained popularity,
but it went the other way too.
[Next Stage Contestant Lee Jae Min
Stalking Scandal]
- No way.
- What?
This contestant Lee Jae Min
was a front-runner for the debut lineup,
riding high on popularity,
when news broke
that he stalked a famous idol...
Presenter, wrap it up.
Right.
So, as you see...
Mass media's power is huge.
That's why fact-checking must be airtight,
so innocent people don't get hurt.
Any questions?
In the case, it's Shin Jae Min, not Lee.
[Contestant Lee Jae Min Stalking Scandal]
Fact-checking matters.
What, who is he?
- Who?
- Isn't he the stalker?
- Stalker?
- Really? Shin Jae Min?
Where?
I think it's really him.
Shin Jae Min goes here?
- I'm sorry.
- Why is he here?
This is insane.
Any more questions?
If not, let's wrap up today.
Nice work.
I already asked to switch groups.
It's too uncomfortable.
Stalking is a crime.
I won't team up with a criminal.
This is the group chat.
I'll drop the class.
You don't need to switch.
Wakers, camera rehearsal starts.
The green room's empty, toss the trash
and restock the snacks.
I'll do it.
I'll debut too,
so let's meet again.
Yeah, we will.
Let's stop here.
We'll skip the next song
and move to segment three.
It's the fan meeting game,
so check the members' props,
and we'll roll once you're set.
Crew, move quickly, please.
Hyun Jae, hurry back.
Okay, one sec.
[Cast Green Room: Wakers]
Where's that scarf?
Hyun Jae, we're starting.
Coming!
That's chili paste.
What?
Oh, you're foreign.
That's not ketchup.
This is ketchup.
Thanks.
Shake it.
Your number,
please.
That was bold.
You won't pick up.
Hey, where are you?
I'm home.
I saw him.
What?
Well, look who it is.
Don't slack off just because the group's done.
Plenty of eyes are on you.
You're a contestant, and he's an active idol...
His agency
released a statement.
Did something really happen?
With that idol.