[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Love Upon a Time Series]
Grant me your forgiveness,
I beg of you, Klao.
So...
Which temple is it?
It is Wat Sema Muang.
My father brought me to that temple as a child.
Is it true that the meeting place
lies in the woods behind it,
Pim?
Indeed, on the second period of
the fifteenth night of the waning moon,
the opium trade shall occur
at the hut by the river every month.
Klao, are you certain that
you shall not inform the patrolmen?
I must witness it with my own eyes.
To report it to them without certainty
may serve only to tarnish
both Phop's name and my own.
Are you courting death?
Where the devil is he?!
Klao!
Show yourself!
Find him,
or you shall not live to see the dawn!
Everyone...
Move!
Goodness!
Whither do you think to escape me?!!
You are far more stubborn than your father.
I seek no quarrel with you.
But you!
You refuse to let us be.
Your meddling has at last
exhausted his patience.
He has ordered me
to send you to hell to join your father.
If this is my end,
then I shall drag you all,
you scum of the earth,
down into hell with me.
Go and mark me a place
in the depths of hell, then!!
Klao!!
Unless...
you change your mind and join us.
The opium trade flows with gold.
One may make a fortune overnight.
If you serve as our informer,
feeding us news,
the words of your superiors,
and every move your brother
Lord Phop makes,
you may be handsomely rewarded.
What say you, Klao?
If you are wise, accept the offer,
and I shall spare your life.
Not in this life.
You are just as stubborn as ever.
Pim,
why must you do this to me?
For a mere handful of coins,
you chose to stoop this low?
I only wish to redeem myself
and live a life far from the capital.
What more could a woman
such as I ever hope for?
Back then,
I truly hoped you would capture Cherd,
so that he would no longer be in my life.
When you failed,
I was truly devastated,
and that remains so.
But now
you have uncovered too much,
and I fear I am the one in danger.
Cease this, Pim.
Kla,
leave at once before anyone finds you.
What of the promise
- to grant me the title of lord?
- Begone, I say!!
He shall see to it
once you reach Pak Nam Pho.
I have the vessel ready behind the hut.
Begone at once.
As you wish.
Grant me your forgiveness, Master Klao.
Wait!
Pim!
There is no way out to the river!
It is but a pond. It leads nowhere!
What? What are you doing?!
Such is the nature of this world, Klao.
[Love Upon a Time Series]
When I returned,
I prayed that you had lost
your memory forever, as the rumors had it.
Yet you remain as stubborn as a mule,
digging into the past
until you have recalled everything.
Klao, I truly wish to know
how on earth you managed to return
from the brink of death.
I saw my men
throw you into the pond with my own eyes.
And I shall do the very same
to Pim and Kla.
Klao,
are you some kind of spirit?
What unholy power do you possess? Huh?!
Answer me!
Finish me off once again at this instant,
before Phop comes to save me.
Your foolishness remains unchanged.
I never took your life, Klao.
What did he say?
He refused.
You have left me no choice in this, Klao.
You claim this meddling
is for your father's sake,
but I too do this for my father.
Bid the world farewell, Klao.
Cherd.
Yes, my Lord...
Send him to his grave.
Yes, my Lord.
Lord Harn was the one who dealt the blow.
I merely cleaned up his mess.
But tonight, I shall send you
to your watery grave by my own hand.
How does that sound, Klao?
Agonizing, is it not?
Fear not
that you will be alone in hell,
for your good brother
shall soon join you.
No...
You two shall be in hell together tonight.
Splendid, is it not?
Wonderful, is it not?
Is this not wonderful?!
Make haste!!
At once!!
Lay down your sword.
Lay down your sword, I say!
Patrolmen...
You were so near to escaping your fate, Phop.
Had you wed Lady Varna,
we would have been part of the same family,
allowing me to keep a closer eye on you.
We would not have come to this.
When did I give you away?
Was it the absence of a pond here?
I saw right through you long ago.
Every time we close in
on those opium traffickers,
they still manage to slip through our fingers.
And when it comes time for interrogation,
none are willing to confess.
The soldiers have captured the smugglers
who carried opium
from the capital to sell in Sam Khok.
My father conducted the interrogation himself,
yet none of them would confess.
Who would dare to implicate their own master,
and do so to his face?
But what clearly gave you away
was the poisoning of the patrolmen.
To make them lower their guard
and become intoxicated
would require an insider.
It smells of burnt beans.
Are they castor beans?
These people have been poisoned.
And there is also Kla.
Unless it was someone of
equal rank to mine or higher,
there was no way he could have been bought
as an informant.
Every trail leads back to you and your father.
You are far too clever for your own good.
But if you are truly so bright,
why did you follow me here?
Merely to buy time.
By now, your father
has surely been captured by my father's men.
High Lord Pichayabhakdi.
By what means did you find out...
that it was I?
The document.
It bears Lord Preechapiban's name,
with a smear of ink
running from left to right.
The handwriting is indeed identical
in every respect.
Yet my father never smudged ink
upon his writings.
Why, then, is there an ink blot here
and nowhere else?
Hence, the forger
must be...
left-handed.
High Lord.
We are officials of the state,
entrusted with the duty
of safeguarding the welfare of the people.
Having been granted a life
far more bountiful
than that of the common folk,
we cannot commit such an act.
Pray, accept it.
I merely need you to act as my intermediary
with the Farangi and the Chinese.
Nothing will ever be traced back to you.
You have my assurance.
I shall accept only your kindness.
As for all else,
I must most respectfully decline.
Should any word of opium smuggling
reach me from the capital,
I fear...
you shall be the first...
I suspect.
Be that as it may,
remain here
and wallow in your misery in Phichit.
Lord Preechapiban
was a man of many talents,
yet he was a fool.
The moment...
I summoned him to the capital in your name,
he recklessly came,
believing he could lend you his aid.
That trickery
presented me with the perfect opportunity
to steal his personal seal
and forge the document.
High Lord.
High Lord...
How pitiful.
It is a shame
that you are
just as foolish as your dearest friend.
You shall never know,
not even in the slightest,
that Meng and I
conspired to poison your tea.
With this settled,
Lord Preechapiban's secret
shall go to the grave with you.
Your Excellency,
an opium shipment list
has been discovered
concealed beneath his manor.
Huh...
So, you lured me out to lead me into a trap,
High Lord?!
Precisely.
Now then,
who is the fool
at this hour, High Lord?!
So, Meng
has chosen to turn against me?
Meng
simply chose to stand
only on the side of justice.
Phop visits this teahouse frequently.
Meng...
would never dare poison me.
It is not over.
Though you may have eluded my poison,
my men are already upon you.
Soldiers!
Lay waste to High Lord Pichayabhakdi at once!
Soldiers!!
Accept your fate, High Lord.
To resist or flee
would only bring you further disgrace.
This way.
Any news of Lord Phop?
He has yet to arrive and join us.
However, we have already
dispatched reinforcements to assist him.
Surrender now, Phop!!
You shall not escape this night!!
You have been defeated, Lord Harn.
The cell awaits.
Then you shall fall with me!!
By now, Klao...
has certainly been slaughtered by Cherd.
You did inquire about Klao's
whereabouts this evening, did you not?
Then hear me well!
Cherd conspired with Pim,
the lady of the House of Pleasure.
He was hiding in the Pavilion of Affection
to ensnare Klao.
He must surely be in Cherd's hands by now.
At last,
Klao had once again been slain,
despite my having already killed him
with my own hands.
Seize that Harn at once!
I shall make my way to save Klao!
Yes, my Lord!
♫Wat Bot, oh, the temple of old,♫
♫Where seven toddy palms stand tall as told♫
♫Khun Thong went forth on the raid♫
♫Still, he has yet to return
for the sweet embrace♫
♫Wrapping food in a bundle,♫
♫I rowed out to look for my angel♫
♫Yet the rumors had already spread♫
♫That Khun Thong had met♫
♫His fate♫
It is time.
Let us enjoy sending Klao
to his watery grave.
Still here, are you not, Cherd?
My Lord. Oh, my Lord.
I shall depart at once.
This time, he shall certainly meet his end.
Hey! Unhand me!
Unhand me at once!
You scoundrel!
Cherd.
Cherd, Cherd!
Cherd!
Klao...
Klao.
My deepest thanks to you,
Kaew
and Jom.
You are in good hands now, Klao.
And...
Cherd's men...
They...
cast
Pim and Kla into the pond.
Jom!
Blood...
It is Cherd's.
You have my heartfelt thanks,
my dearest Kaew.
Rise.
I am guiltless!
I am innocent!!
Have you gone mad?!
I am merely protecting my master!
It was he who meddled with us!
You!!
Damn you, Klao! You are the cause of this!
I shall drag you into the depths of hell!!
Cease this blaming at once, Cherd!
You are a wretched opium smoker
and a peddler.
You attempted to murder Klao
to bury the truth.
You took Pim's life
solely to save your own skin.
Your stupidity matches your malice.
No one is to blame for your actions.
I ended Pim's life...
I killed her.
Pim, forgive me.
I killed her...
I murdered her!
I am sorry, Pim. Forgive me.
Take him away.
Yes, my Lord.
Pim, I am sorry.
Are you injured at all?
Toast!
My deepest thanks to you all.
Without you,
I would not have survived.
By the way...
Jom and Kaew,
how did you find me there?
We owe our sincere thanks...
to that young man.
That spacing was a crime in itself.
I told Physician Jom that
I saw a patrolman named Kla
linger outside the tavern every night,
speaking with Cherd in secret
once it was closed.
They were acquainted.
That was why they helped Cherd
conceal the truth about his wound.
Furthermore,
I crossed paths with him this evening
on his way to the Pavilion of Affection.
Cherd
harbors deep hatred towards Master Klao.
This means that
Kla was acquainted with Cherd,
and I feared that...
the two might conspire
to ambush you
once you reached the Pavilion of Affection.
Your subordinate
is quite eloquent, is he not?
On this night,
he has spoken more in a single day
than in all his life before it.
What happened next, Jom?
I saw Cherd here
with a certain patrolman.
I seem to recall him being a man
under Lord Phop's command.
This means...
there is a traitor among Phop's men.
Kaew, summon the patrols here at once.
Should anything occur,
they shall aid all of us.
I cannot do this.
I place full trust in you.
Never have I known a soul
so wise and resilient as you.
You are capable of this, Kaew.
We shall not let anything happen to Klao.
Kaew, the patrolmen, and I
kept close watch.
But then Kla
left the establishment with a bag.
He left alongside Pim.
Therefore, we tracked them down to the hut.
Unfortunately,
the route was unknown to us,
and so we were unable to reach
Pim and Kla in time to save them.
I am already more than grateful
for your assistance in this.
Cherd has now been imprisoned.
Lord Harn is being hunted by my men.
He will not get far.
The truth has come to light,
yet one thing remains unclear.
By what means
did you triumph over the High Lord's men?
Master.
A-Chai, step back.
Retreat for but a moment.
Calm yourselves, fellow soldiers.
No need for such haste.
Would you like some tea?
We have a kettle full here.
After taking a sip,
you are free to cut off my head,
should that be your wish.
Behold, in this kettle is Da Hong Pao.
It rejuvenates your soul.
It is the very tea favored by
the current Emperor himself.
It calms your soul
as if a bodhisattva's chant
were echoing within your heart.
!@#$%^&*
Hey!
One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Enjoy!
Form a circle.
Circling
until they lose their senses.
Circling around.
Around and around.
Curse you...
His Excellency
still draws breath tonight
because of my hand.
Before calling the tavern my new home,
I served as a patrolman myself.
Not true.
I shall lie when pigs fly.
Go and smell its arse,
should you not believe me.
Cease this folly, will you?
During my days in China,
I was placed under the tutelage
of a senior kinsman to master the martial arts.
He was my uncle's older brother,
and my uncle was my father's younger brother.
And this man was my father's father.
- I do not believe it in the least.
- He instructed me in the Chinese martial arts...
- Hey! What I have said is true.
- I could never believe you.
A true story, I say.
A lie, I say.
If it was...
- Now, now, Master.
- What of it?
You pushed me, did you not?
- You pushed me?
- And what of it?
You seek a challenge, do you not?
And what of it, I ask?
- Huh?
- Do you wish to...
- What of it?
- Ah, you have struck me.
Begone.
- Begone, I said.
- Did you lay your hand upon me?
Did I?
They spun a grand tale, did they not?
In truth, they were but cowering in fear,
leaving the men of High Lord Pichayabhakdi
to deal with those of High Lord Horathibodi.
Unhand me.
- Let go. I must...
- Come.
Come here.
- This way.
- Come this way.
- A man like me does not...
- I am not afraid of you.
Let that be known. Come this way.
Do you truly believe their words, Klao?
Not even in the slightest from the beginning.
But if you ask
what I have gained from this mess,
it would be that...
I should never again place
easy trust in the tales of others,
perhaps.
This includes the words spun by
others concerning my past,
the stories of Pim,
of Cherd,
of Lord Harn,
and even those set down in the histories.
Whoever tells their stories
shall ever seek
to paint themselves in a favorable light.
All has come to an end.
If Lord Harn is brought to justice,
then your mission is undoubtedly fulfilled.
If my mission is fulfilled,
it means I must return to the present.
A new day is upon us.
The hill myna in the birdhouse
has begun to whistle.
That is not true.
There is an owl within.
It is still dark outside.
Better, is it not?
You seemed very unwell last night.
Well...
I was thinking about Cherd.
Last night,
when his men bound me,
Cherd sang me a lullaby.
It made me shiver.
The lullaby had some meaning.
Wat Bot.
Toddy palms.
Khun Thong.
♫That Khun Thong had met♫
♫His fate♫
He must be yearning for his father.
My men once told me that
his father owned a toddy palm grove.
It was said that he fell from a height,
leaving him broken.
Cherd loved his father dearly.
After his father was crippled,
Cherd's mother became a drunkard
and began beating his father
out of exhaustion.
In the end, he perished,
and she descended into madness.
That is why Cherd took refuge in opium.
He must have been in deep sorrow.
He was often troubled by nightmares
of his mother murdering his father.
He likely wishes...
to sleep without dreams.
That is why you do not wish me
to have a quarrel with him, is it not?
And that is why
Lord Harn gave Cherd opium,
thereby turning him into an addict.
This would allow Cherd
to be used as his tool.
And Cherd...
loves Lord Harn,
treating him as his new father.
The reason he was charmed by Pim
was...
the lack of love given by a woman
such as his own mother.
Even Cherd
is not a demon from hell as we thought,
but someone has made him so.
My dearest.
You truly have a sympathetic heart,
despite his having hurt you so much.
I understood him,
but I do not stand by his side.
And karma has caught up with him.
At last,
Klao had once again been slain,
despite my having already killed him
with my own hands.
What ails you, Phop?
I have something to inquire of you.
Did he learn something from Lord Harn?
Should I tell him now
that I am from the future?
No one knows
when I'll be brought back either.
The temple holds
a merit-making ceremony tonight.
Would you like to join me?
That said, let us go and wash ourselves.
It's fine.
Focus on the present moment.
Cherd has been arrested.
It is best to enjoy my time with Phop,
one moment at a time.
Cherd's whereabouts remain unknown.
The firearm taken from the Farangi
has also disappeared.
Inform Lord Phop at once!
He and Master Klao are in grave danger!!
Your prayers were rather extensive, Phop.
Will the Buddha take heed of all that?
I call upon the Buddha as my witness:
my heart belongs to you alone,
and ever shall it remain.
I shall approach my parents
to ask for your hand in marriage.
Then I shall cherish
and protect the very heart of my life
until the end of my days.
This is another wish of mine.
Should there be another lifetime,
we shall seek each other out once more.
May our love remain steadfast,
though the tides of time may turn.
But...
After this day,
if I am gone,
promise me you will live well.
No.
I shall seek you out...
until I find you
and love you once more.
Do you remember that shop still?
We should choose new rings together.
This one is my very favorite.
Good heavens!
I must have taken it off
when I bathed.
I forgot to put it back on.
Think no more of it.
We shall procure a finer ring than the last.
Which kind do you prefer?
I shall engrave it upon my heart
for when the time comes
to acquire your wedding ring.
Cherd!
How came he here?!
Run! Now!
Make way! Make way!
We can go no further.
You must hide here.
I shall go and seize him myself.
No, I beg you!
What if we should be parted again?
Countless times have we been parted,
yet ever do I find my way to you.
I promise you,
I shall return.
Nothing shall ever part us again.
Klao!!
You shall never escape my grasp!
Your sins are already
too great to bear, Cherd!
I beg of you, let me go.
Hear me well,
or you shall be sentenced to death.
I care not!!
You must die by my hand alone!
Lower the firearm!
Cease this!
Or else,
you shall be sent to the depths of hell
this very instant!
Should I be sent there,
then I shall drag you down with me!!
I shall seek you out...
until I find you
and love you once more.
Phop!
Phop, where are you?
Phop.
I'm back home?
Nakun!
Nakun, my dear!
Nakun!!
That way.
That way!
Mom...
Is that you?
He has come to.
Hey, can you hear me?
If you do, please blink.
Are you injured in any way?
Nakun.
Sweetie!!
My dear.
Nakun.
Mom.
Is this really you?
Of course, it's me.
Nakun...
What's the matter?
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
Tell me where it hurts.
Please take me to Phop, Mom.
Mom, please take me to Phop.
My dear...
Seeing you healthy is all I could ask for.
The doctor told you to rest a lot.
Get some rest, okay?
Dear.
Is something wrong?
Tell me if anything is bothering you.
Dear...
what were you doing
at the orchard all night?
All night?
Yes, you heard me.
You even got yourself a bottle of alcohol.
Nakun...
You can tell me
what's stressing you out, okay?
How...
long was I out?
I don't really know either.
It was well past 11 P.M.
when I came back from the wedding.
You were already gone when I got home.
And I thought
you went to get something around here.
I waited for so long,
but you still hadn't come back.
You didn't bring your phone with you either.
I thought
things were starting to feel a bit off.
Then I saw you lying there in the orchard...
And you were wearing some very odd clothes.
I tried so hard to wake you up, but...
you wouldn't open your eyes.
I was so horrified...
that I called emergency services.
And...
less than an hour later,
you woke up.
Less than an hour?
Nakun.
It had been less than an hour,
but my heart almost couldn't take it.
I was terrified something bad
had happened to you.
The professor said that
upon completing the mission,
the character
would be able to return to their world.
However...
should the main character
fail their mission,
the portal would be closed forever,
preventing their return to their world.
That's a lie.
Even though we knew who the culprit was,
Cherd managed to escape.
Harn is also still at large.
How can my mission be considered complete?
If you can't manage a full meal,
at least have some fruit.
It is of the finest quality,
brought by traders from across China.
Thanks.
Phop.
I wonder how you're doing.
["Lord Phop"]
[No results were found for
"Lord Phop" and "Patrol Department"]
"Lord Preechapiban"]
[No results were found for
"High Lord Pichayabhakdi"]
There is no information at all.
Phop doesn't even exist in the history books.
Or do I have to wait until the next starfall?
Or do I have to wait until my next birthday?
Phop.
I shall find my way back to you.
♫Where are you right now?♫
♫Can you hear this heart crying out somehow?♫
♫Do you know
there's someone waiting for you still?♫
♫Every night I dream of you,
and always will♫
♫Even time means nothing now♫
♫No matter how long,
I'll wait for you somehow♫
♫Though distance keeps our worlds apart♫
♫It cannot separate our hearts♫
♫Our love still travels through the dark♫
♫If you were born to share my heart♫
♫Like the moon beside the night♫
♫I know someday our souls will reunite♫
♫No matter how far we are apart,♫
♫It will never be too far,
if our hearts stay strong♫
♫Across all lifetimes,
nothing could keep us apart♫
♫As long as our hearts remain as one,
where they belong♫
[Chances of seeing shooting stars in Ayutthaya]
♫As long as our hearts remain as one♫
[Shooting stars can appear
any month, all year round, Nakun]
[In fact, it can be seen
one to three times a month]
[You can see it
depending on how clear the sky is]
Your mom said
you're feeling a bit dazed, right?
That's why I brought you some vitamins.
Jom!
Jom...
Who the hell is Jom?
You miss me that much, don't you?
I'm touched.
You...
You don't remember it?
Remember what?
You're the one who doesn't remember me.
You...
You have amnesia?
Jom was probably Thee in a past life.
Thee didn't travel through time like I did.
Your mom is really worried about you.
You refuse to leave your room,
and at night,
you stay on the balcony until dawn.
If you can't tell her, tell me instead.
What's wrong?
Alright. It's fine
if you don't want to tell me.
But you've been absent
from your classes for almost a week now.
Wanna go back to university?
Be with Pun
and me.
Maybe we can help you feel better.
Pun is really worried about you, you know?
He's sad because he's worried about you.
That's why I'm sad too.
Just look.
I'm trying to smile,
but I just can't.
See?
Come to the university, please.
Nakun.
Nakun!
Eat up, will you?
We have classes all afternoon.
Sorry.
I was lost in my thoughts
and had too much fun.
But...
it didn't seem like
you were having much fun at all.
Yeah, he's right.
Let us know
if there's something on your mind.
Just tell us.
We listen; we don't judge.
Thee.
This isn't the time.
Nakun,
are you alright?
Do you want to take the afternoon off?
Thee.
Should we take him back to his place?
Mhm.
It's fine.
Seriously?
You've been zoning out all day.
Have your misfortunes been upsetting you?
Did you do what the fortune teller said
when you returned home?
Guys...
Can you take me to see
the fortune teller again?
The fortune teller...
Fortune teller, do you remember me?
Indeed, I do.
You came to see me the other day.
No.
What should we have tomorrow?
- Anything works for me.
- Oh.
Uh...
It's... It's Klao.
Remember?
My hair looks like a cow's?
It looks fine to me.
It's flowing.
Fortune teller.
I'm serious.
I'm Klao,
a resident of Lord Phop's manor.
Lady Prayong is his mother.
She's the lady who...
often gives you money.
Uh...
Uh, I do remember.
Klao.
I remember.
You remember me now, don't you?
If you do,
could you tell me how Phop is doing?
Now that I've returned here,
is he still safe?
I beg you.
Please tell me.
I can't take it anymore.
If you want to know,
I need to read your cards.
Read my cards...
For what?
If you remember our past life,
you must know how Phop is doing right now.
"Loss."
"Separation."
"A deep fear of change."
Phop...
The person you're thinking of
has met his fate.
That's not true!!
Nakun.
Nakun, Nakun.
Nakun...
Let me go!
The stone.
That stone.
So you also...
traveled back in time like I did?
Nakun, enough.
Did you?
Let go!
I told you to let go.
Let go of me.
Let go of me!!
Please, let go of me.
Fortune teller.
I beg you.
Please...
Can you...
try to remember
what happened to Phop? Is he still safe?
If you really don't know,
can you tell me
how I could travel back in time to Ayothaya?
In your past life,
you helped me so much.
You were extraordinary!
Why must you act so clueless in this life?!!
Yes.
I was better in my past life.
To let go of the old is to welcome the new.
A great change is upon us;
an ending that gives birth
to a new beginning.
Lord Phop has met his end,
yet he shall return once more.
Even the fortune teller is no help.
I guess I have to let it go.
Our amuse-bouche
comes in the form of traditional Thai dishes
with a modern twist.
Please enjoy your meal.
Sai!
Yes?
Uh...
I'm really sorry, sir.
We're sorry for the delay
in serving your food.
Uh...
Not what I meant.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
I thought you were someone else.
Right.
Thee.
See?
I told you to just get him a room here.
Yet, you brought him to the rooftop.
I'm sorry.
I thought...
if he could enjoy good food
with a scenic view,
he might feel better.
Hey,
Pun.
Since when did you become close to Thee?
Well...
Since...
you were absent.
After opening up to each other,
I realized that he does have a soft side,
beyond his constant joking.
My actions from my past life
really do affect the present day.
So, would revealing
the truth about Klao's father
have the same effect?
If Sai...
Jom...
Kaew...
The oracle...
If they can reincarnate into this life,
others might be able to as well.
What about Phop?
Did he reincarnate?
Will he be able to remember me?
Nakun.
Are you okay?
I'm not.
I'm sorry, Thee.
Pun, please finish the dishes for me.
Nakun.
Don't force him.
- But...
- But what?
His feelings come first.
[Thee: Almost here, or another day?]
[I'm here]
I shall seek you out...
until I find you
and love you once more.
In just a few weeks,
my life has changed a lot.
Let me help you.
And in this new life
I'm trying to get used to,
I've met familiar faces from my past life.
A-Chai? Who?
You! Are you alright?
When you called me,
I thought you already knew me.
No. I was calling 'you' as a pronoun.
Since Nakun left for Ayutthaya,
I've only been dreaming of these things.
It feels like I once fell for you, Thee.
But you...
You kept rejecting me.
[Can you help me get back to Ayutthaya?]
Let's take in the scenery
from the top of the prang.
Its condition remains
as pristine as it was back then.
You...
Your memories have always been there, right?
♫Though distance keeps our worlds apart♫
♫It cannot separate our hearts♫
♫Our love still travels through the dark♫
♫If you were born to share my heart♫
♫Like the moon beside the night♫
♫I know someday our souls will reunite♫
♫No matter how far we are apart,♫
♫It will never be too far,
if our hearts stay strong♫
♫Across all lifetimes,
nothing could keep us apart♫
♫As long as our hearts remain as one,
where they belong♫
[Love Upon a Time Series]