(One year ago)
The final member to join Wakers is...
Congratulations to trainee Kim Hyunjae.
Idol Audition Show "Next Stage"
Hyunjae, congrats!
Thanks.
I'm definitely going to debut, so...
Let's see each other again for sure.
Okay.
We have to meet again.
So, I'll be in touch...
We can keep in touch, right?
Yeah, of course.
Let's give him another
big round of applause.
Now, let's hear from trainee Kim Hyunjae.
Hyunjae! What are you
doing here all of a sudden?
I skipped practice.
Are you allowed to do that?
Promotions will start tomorrow,
so we might get busier.
That's why I wanted to see you first.
Well, you've seen me now.
Is there anything else?
No, that's all.
You should go back before
your company finds out.
Hyunjae.
Do well on your promotions.
Hwaiting!
That was insane. I almost fell for you.
Oh, come on.
They really don't give us a break.
Looks like they're planning to
run us into the ground this year.
It's brutal.
You're not feeling sick
or anything, are you?
Of course not.
How about you? How have things been?
I've been getting more fans lately,
and the company is really promoting me.
Maybe I'll get to debut soon?
We'll be seeing each other on stage
soon, so watch out. You'd better be ready.
Yes, sir. I'll be waiting.
(Finally done.)
(What are you up to?)
Finally done...
You're done?
Yeah.
Did I wake you at this hour?
No, I was just practicing.
And waiting for you to text back.
You were practicing? You must be tired...
Not at all, it must be harder for you.
You're the one who's working harder.
You must be exhausted. Go get some sleep.
You get some sleep too.
(Have you eaten?)
Hey! Should I audition for a girl group?
Who are you texting right now?
(Want to grab a bite? I haven't eaten yet.)
What are you waiting for? Just send it.
Forget it, I'll send it.
Hey, give it back.
(I miss you, Hyunjae. Don't you miss me?)
Sooan, are you practicing?
I'm sorry...
The debut plan we talked about...
I'm afraid it's been postponed again.
The company isn't
doing so well right now...
The CEO is looking for new investors, so...
Just wait a little longer.
Okay.
I understand.
Also, starting tomorrow...
we're putting practice
on hold for a while.
What?
We couldn't renew the
lease on the practice room.
I'll let you know when we find a new place.
Okay.
Welcome! Hello, everyone! We are Wakers!
(A thoughtful star) / (Happy birthday
to you~ x2) Happy birthday to you~
(The guys keep teasing me.)
Let's get some of the
birthday boy's good luck!
(I miss you, Hyunjae. Don't you miss me?)
(You must be busy lately. I'm also bus...)
Hyunjae, congratulations.
I'll debut too. We'll
definitely see each other again.
I'm sorry, the company
isn't doing so well right now.
We couldn't renew the
lease on the practice room.
(Block Contact)
I'll let you know when there's news.
"Love Class" Season 3
(Episode 3)
(Incoming Call: Mom)
Mom, I did everything you told me to.
I'm working hard, so don't worry.
Yeah... I'll do that.
Okay, I'm hanging up.
It's gotten cold.
Are you a zombie?
You're done practicing?
It's so cold.
Drink it anyway.
Haven't you been saying
you can't wake up lately?
Coffee is meant to be drunk hot.
Then, should I "warm it up" for you?
Hey, wait, someone could walk in.
No one's coming! It's fine.
Ah... I smell like sweat.
No, you don't.
Just for a second...
Let me hold you.
Is it a little warmer now?
(LUXE Hotel)
This doesn't feel right...
Pay off your debt.
With your body.
What on earth is he thinking?
This is awkward. I'm going in first.
What's wrong?
You're the one who wanted to come here.
Don't judge it by its cover.
It's probably nice inside.
Everyone's looking at us strangely.
Hurry up.
Ah...
What the heck?
You already booked a room?
I didn't realize you were in such a hurry.
Ah... Is this right?
Hey, wait for me.
What was I thinking?
Why did you suddenly show up?
If there's nothing else, I'll be going.
This... You didn't leave this for
me to see on purpose, did you?
Why did you ghost me?
Ghost you?
Never mind...
We're not in the type of relationship
that always keeps in touch anyway.
Then what are we?
A business relationship.
We were just using each other, weren't we?
You got to debut. Isn't that enough?
What?
It was all an act.
What else could it have been?
You really don't have any feelings for me?
In Korea...
there's one thing you
have to do after moving.
Cheers!
What's wrong?
Nothing, I just didn't expect
you to be such a good drinker.
Didn't you say that in Korea...
you have to down
the first shot in one go?
What genius taught you that?
This is so good.
Why are you drinking so fast?
Can you really hold your liquor?
I don't know.
You don't usually drink?
Is it because you're
from a Buddhist country?
No... I'm a damn good drinker.
Wow.
Why is that the kind of thing you pick up?
My pronunciation was damn perfect, right?
Yeah, it was damn perfect.
But that word is considered
a bad word in Korea.
But you speak informally to me.
You're actually Korean, aren't you?
Hey... it's bad luck to
pour your own drink.
Your glass isn't even empty...
You really don't have feelings for me?
I was worried I might have
some lingering feelings...
but I'm glad I don't.
"Love Class" Season 3
(Episode 4 Preview)
Why can't I remember anything, for real?!
Did you sleep well?
Um...
I didn't say anything weird, did I?
I don't know.
I can't speak Korean.
Wasn't it enough to use me for clout?
Is there anything else you want from me?
What, do you want me to sleep with you?
Don't ever show up in front of me again.
Fine, if that's what you really want.