(One year ago)
Jaemin, this is no time
to beat around the bush.
Just tell me straight.
Did something... really
happen between you and him?
What are you trying to say?
Don't you know there's a petition
for you to drop out of the show?
That's why I'm asking. Did you really...
catch feelings for that kid?
Huh?
You're a contestant on a survival show.
How could you get involved with an idol?
Forget it.
Does a scandal like this even make sense?
Their agency...
released a statement.
- What did it say?
- Hyung...
They said the dating rumors
are completely fabricated.
"Our artist has been harassed
by Jaemin for a long time."
"He feels more than just bothered.
He's terrified."
That's what they wrote.
Wait.
Terrified...?
If they go public with that...
people will probably
assume you're a stalker.
What do we do now?
Director...
Ugh... Director.
"LOVE CLASS SEASON 3"
(EPISODE 2)
I'm fine.
Your number.
Hold on.
I'm not the type who just
gives his number to anyone.
I don't know what you think of me, but...
Give it.
Please.
You're pretty forward.
Hey... wait!
Hey...?
No, but...
At least clean up before you go.
And is it right to just get
my number and run off?
You should at least
leave me your number too.
Fighting!
(One year ago)
What's this?
It's my good luck bracelet.
I've passed every audition I've worn it to.
That's why I always wear it.
Really?
You want to try it on?
Can I?
It's almost time to go on stage.
Let's go.
Hyunjae, who were you talking to?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Hello?
Um... well...
Just now...
I'm over here.
I didn't realize you were so close.
Yeah.
This is for you.
What is it?
Just take it.
A T-shirt.
A T-shirt?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's really okay.
I really don't mind.
Just take it.
If you're really sorry...
you can just buy me a meal.
Take it.
Hey, wait.
I need to know your name
so I can save you as a contact.
(Ketchup)
Good work.
(More endless "Good work!")
Sorry.
Good work.
(Yeeun calling)
Hey, Yoon Sooan, are
you trying to get killed?
Get over here right now,
while I'm still being nice.
I can't.
Why aren't you answering your phone?
Hey, where are you?
At home.
What?
I met him.
You should start practicing again.
How can I be an idol?
Why not? You didn't do anything wrong.
You never should have
quit in the first place.
You should have cleared things up.
That guy was the one who pursued you.
How could he call you a stalker?
That bastard.
I think I saw Sooan today.
At the broadcast station.
I think he's working
there as a staff member.
What are you talking about?
He was the ace of Unicorn.
There's no way he'd
be working a regular job.
Why don't you try contacting him?
[Banal couple talk above, followed by:]
(Sooan, do you have a minute to talk?)
Is this really okay?
What's wrong? What is it?
Hey, where'd you get that shirt?
Isn't that a designer brand?
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
This is super expensive.
Really?
Did you blow all your money on this?
No.
Then what? Did you steal it?
Of course not.
Then where'd you get it?
How much is this thing anyway?
Crap.
850,000 won?
850,000 won.
Hey, what do I do?
What?
Wait, this won't do.
I can probably return it, right?
(PNJS Entertainment)
You're here.
If it isn't our big star.
I'm back.
You've worked hard.
Thank you.
We're all looking forward to your comeback.
We have a big project starting soon.
Get some rest for now.
Director Park, please take Hyunjae home.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
What, you have plans to meet someone?
No, it's just...
You know that you can't slack off just
because group promotions are over, right?
A lot of people are watching you right now.
Yes, I understand.
Let's go.
The number you have dialed is not available.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Why isn't he picking up?
Hey.
Hey, student.
(Unicorn Entertainment)
(Notice of end of contract)
I've been practicing like crazy
so I could stand on the same stage as you.
Hey!
Hello.
Did I scare you?
That was a big reaction.
You scared me too.
I actually wanted to ask...
Is this T-shirt expensive?
Expensive?
Uh... not really.
Not really?
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
You don't like it?
This shirt is expensive.
It's too expensive, you get it?
It's okay.
I really don't mind about the shirt.
But...
You should return it.
Return it?
Refund, you know?
But...
I barely wore it.
It's practically new.
What?
Crap.
You should eat too.
Damn it.
Kim Hyunjae...
What do I do now?
It's okay.
No...
I hate being indebted to people.
What I can give you right now...
isn't much, I guess.
I have to do something.
With your body.
Sorry?
Then pay me back... with your body.
Stay tuned for LOVE CLASS 3.
(PREVIEW, EPISODE 3)
(LUXE HOTEL)
This isn't right.
What the hell is that guy thinking?
Don't tell me he left this
for me to see on purpose.
Why did you suddenly ghost me?
You just used me as a
stepping stone, didn't you?
You've already debuted.
Isn't that enough for you?
Want me to heat this up for you?
Do you really not feel
anything for me at all?