EPISODE 6
- Wait, that one's not expired yet.
- Oh. Right.
It's not like you to make such a mistake.
Did something happen yesterday
with the CCTV footage?
Yesterday, I met Jeong Ho-myeong.
You met Jeong Ho-myeong?
Right.
But that guy didn't just know me.
He knows a lot about you, too.
Did he?
- He said he knew me?
- Yeah.
And not just our faces.
He even knows why we came
to Yeongseon Island ten years ago.
He knows everything about us.
Okay, look.
- There's something I need to tell you.
- Go on.
So, what's good here?
Best we've got are lunch boxes.
What did you expect? Chinese food?
What do you say?
There's a new one.
Want me to shove it down your throat?
Ah.
I didn't come for a lunch box.
I came to talk.
You threw me to the curb,
and now you want to talk?
It's not like we're carpooling buddies,
is it?
Cut the crap and listen up.
I'm about to make you
an offer you can't refuse.
I've decided to be generous.
I'll take you in.
What?
Do as I say,
and I'll help you get your revenge.
What the hell are you barking about?
Speaking of barking,
you're pretty good at it.
Mr. Jeong!
How did you get that?
Anyway, you must have realized
you can't take on Yoo In-gu alone.
So you sought another way,
trying to meet Prosecutor Gang yesterday.
But that route's a dead end,
so you have no options now, do you?
You think you know everything, don't you?
I'll never work with you!
You'll be working for me, not with me.
Let's just get that straight.
I bet Gong-bok here thinks differently.
He does have a point.
Maybe you should think it over.
Ma Gong-bok.
You can't just show up out of nowhere!
- You should have let me know!
- I just did.
Anyway, I've said my piece.
The rest is up to you two.
The deadline is midnight tonight.
If you're one minute late, the deal's off.
Choose wisely.
- Did you betray me?
- Betray you?
Boss,
is that all the faith you have in me?
Mr. Jeong, huh?
- You looked pretty chummy.
- We're not.
I was going to tell you.
Recently, I got to know Mr. Jeong...
I mean, Jeong Ho-myeong
looking into Yoo In-gu.
Yoo In-gu?
Didn't you promise to move on?
Boss, can you really do that?
The betrayal ten years ago?
And the humiliation we just suffered?
I can't forget a single thing.
I still hear that asshole's voice
in my sleep.
You should have told me. I'm your boss.
And if I had?
Boss, do you have the guts
to give up this store?
See? You can't give this stupid place up.
How can you even talk about revenge?
- Unbelievable.
- So we team up with Jeong Ho-myeong?
And why shouldn't we?
We've been chasing Yoo and Han forever.
We can't waste our whole lives here.
I'd rather take action,
even if it's with Jeong Ho-myeong.
Don't just keep saying no.
Try to be a little more open-minded.
Just the other day,
you went after Yoo In-gu by yourself.
- What happened then?
- What did you say?
You're getting old.
You can't do anything by yourself anymore.
So you're saying I'm washed up now?
That's not what I'm talking about!
Just get out of here, okay?
Go on,
run to your precious Jeong Ho-myeong!
You're getting old.
You can't do anything by yourself anymore.
Watch your back!
- Here.
- Yes.
- Hey, Chow Yunfat.
The entire Bamnabi Sect
has seen your face.
It'll be tough to work as a waiter.
- Do you have somewhere to go?
- Well...
Well, if it's okay with you,
I'd like to work for you.
Work for me?
- Why?
- Well, I...
I want to be like you.
1,000,000 WON
10,000 WON
I appreciate your help today.
But this is where we part ways.
Take this money.
- Be on your way.
- Where would I even go?
You want to be like me?
And for what?
You'd be a thug
who only knows how to fight.
Don't get any crazy ideas. Start fresh.
Chow
After Chow Yun Fat...
You're the first man
I've ever wanted to be like!
It's not that I have some kind of fantasy.
No matter where you go,
I want to follow you!
And I want to be more like you!
Please, take me in!
Prosecutor Gang, you're coming with us.
Those bastards.
Okay, fine.
So you want to take this all the way, huh?
Yes, come in.
So, our members would like to see you.
- Members?
- The people from the shelter.
I know it's late,
but thank you for saving me.
Look, I don't need your gratitude.
But I have a question.
Why were you in the sea water?
- Are you really a prosecutor?
- Hey!
- I'm sorry.
- What? I'm curious.
She had a prosecutor's ID,
but told us not to report anything.
Is this going to be on the news?
We deserve to know.
I was investigating a violent crime.
I had an accident
during the investigation.
And if my location is exposed,
it could be bad.
It could seriously jeopardize
the whole investigation.
I know this is a huge favor to ask.
But could I stay here in secret
just for a short while?
Oh, of course.
So it's like a stakeout.
A sting operation.
That's what it is.
I'm a cop, so I get it.
But are you sure you'll be okay here?
Oh, yes, of course.
Mr. Bong told me what you all do here.
You help victims who lost their property
by Heaven Capital.
You take in people
with nowhere else to go.
You're such wonderful people.
Of course I can trust you.
Oh, please.
We helped out some neighbors.
It's really nothing great.
So, speaking of.
I heard you've collected some materials
related to Heaven Capital here.
May I look through them?
I mean, that bastard Yoo In-gu...
No, that's not what I mean.
This is about Heaven Capital.
I'd like to see what illegal activities
they've been up to.
I believe I can research things like that.
You just woke up.
Aren't you pushing yourself?
What's there to worry about?
You're here for her.
- Excuse me?
- Just stick with her.
Make sure she doesn't
have to lift a finger.
But I'm tired.
No, it's okay.
I'd just like to look over the materials.
No, no. You still have
trouble getting around.
Je-sun can help you out a little longer.
Yeah.
I pulled an all-nighter yesterday.
TEMPORARILY CLOSED. WE'LL BE BACK SOON.
Hey.
Can you handle it?
Sir?
Rebuilding Hwasan after a decade.
Are you confident you can take down
the Ingu Sect and Han Gyeong-wook?
Boss.
I've gotten rusty
after taking ten years off.
So if you're going to whine
about me getting old...
I'll just leave you here right now.
I'd never do that!
I've waited ten years for this day.
I will do my best.
Tell me everything that happened with
Yoo In-gu and Jeong Ho-myeong.
And don't hide anything from me.
And whatever we do,
we see it through together.
- Yes, boss.
- And...
Gong-bok, you were right.
I really have gotten old.
- I don't think that's what I meant.
- No, it's true.
I'm no match for the Ingu Sect on my own.
Contact Jeong Ho-myeong and talk to him.
- Tell him I want to see him now.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, Mr. Yoo.
Oh? You look happy. You're looking good.
- So? Did everything work out?
- I took care of everything.
Wow, for real? So fast, Mr. Yoo.
So, what's your method?
You have to tell me your secret.
It's something you could never pull off.
Don't get cute.
Watch your mouth in front of Chief Han.
Got it?
- Okay, got it.
- Here are the Imcheon mayoral polls.
Between Kim Seon-jung
and Han Gyeong-wook...
- I'm here.
- A two-way race has emerged.
What are you doing?
- A two-point gap.
- I see you're watching TV.
Candidate Kim Seon-jung's strength
lies in his deep roots in Imcheon.
He has established an image
as an incorruptible educator.
He has become a rival to Han Gyeong-wook
in Imcheon's conservative stronghold.
His approval ratings
have recently been soaring...
You're keeping a close eye on the news.
What's the point of watching the news?
It's all a bunch of nonsense.
A bunch of nonsense?
They can run their mouths all day,
but for our Yeongseon Island Project...
You would have to
win this election, right?
Chairman Do, your thoughts?
Well, I have no doubt you will win.
But that kind of bad news...
Oh, I'm sorry. I just think...
It's best to nip
these negative stories in the bud.
Now you're talking, Mr. Do.
Nipping things in the bud
is my specialty, isn't it?
Kidnapping, blackmail...
Just say the word.
Mr. Yoo.
Can't you see I'm talking
to Mr. Do right now?
Why do you keep spouting nonsense?
I'm sorry.
Go on, Mr. Do.
Yes, an election is ultimately
a battle of images, isn't it?
He's cultivated one
as an incorruptible educator.
- So let's turn him into corrupt trash.
- How long will it take?
A week? A week will be more than enough.
Mr. Yoo.
You'll support him.
Make sure it moves quickly.
You want me to wipe his ass?
I'm a busy man.
I thought your company ran itself,
but you're busy?
What? You got a side hustle
I don't know about?
No, sir. I spoke out of turn.
And just so we're clear.
If anything goes wrong with this project
all of you will be held responsible.
- Do I make myself clear?
- Yes, sir. Understood.
There's so much to do.
This is a real headache.
Oh, Mr. Nam.
Did you get
all the files from Secretary Baek?
Yes. I received the files
on Kim Seon-jung.
Give those files to Geum Kang-sik.
Hey, Mr. Yoo, don't worry about this.
We'll take care of it.
Hey, you think I want to work with you?
With me?
Weren't you told to support me?
It's just that
I don't really need your support.
This job doesn't call for
your brutish methods.
What? Brutish? You son of a bitch.
- Hey, Kang-sik.
- Yes, sir.
Tomorrow, take the guys
and look into Kim Seon-jung.
Sir? But Chairman Do just said
there was no need...
Did you just dodge?
Hey, did you take money
from that bastard or something?
Do his words come before mine?
No, sir.
Kidnapping, blackmail, false imprisonment.
Find anything on Kim Seon-jung
we can use as leverage.
Don't come back empty-handed.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Here's my decision.
I'll accept your offer. On one condition.
Don't even think about giving me orders.
We're working together for a short time
to get what we both want.
I have no intention of becoming your pawn.
So you're determined
to hold on to your pride.
Look here, you thug.
What happens if you go rogue
and ruin the whole operation?
- You want a piece of this thug?
- Boss, calm down. Please.
Does he have a solid plan to take down
Yoo In-gu and Han Gyeong-wook?
Or is he just trying to use us?
Do you know what Yoo In-gu's doing,
or what Han Gyeong-wook is up to?
- You don't have a clue, do you?
- Well...
Ten years of scanning barcodes
has dulled your edge.
Just follow my orders,
not question everything.
Well, you spent ten years
working in a Chinese kitchen.
Special agent, my ass.
When did you last wear a suit?
Who's calling who washed up?
You want to be the boss?
Let's settle this!
Once a thug, always a thug.
Think I can't take you? Huh?
Don't you remember ten years ago?
- Come on, this isn't why we met.
- Get out of my way!
No, get out of the way.
Of course I remember ten years ago.
If it hadn't rained that day
- I would've finished you for good!
- Wow, really?
You're even dumber than you look.
Want me to give you a reminder?
- Move!
- Get out of my way!
- Go on, you bastard!
- Boss!
- I said get out of my way!
- Move, you punk!
- Bring it!
- I'll teach him a lesson!
- Mr. Jeong!
- Boss!
- Move!
You're getting a call. Answer it!
Get out of my way!
- I'll teach him a lesson.
- Answer your phone!
You're getting a call!
JO SEONG-WON
- Yeah?
- Hey, Prosecutor Gang's alive.
- Really?
- I don't know where she went yet.
But I think she washed ashore.
How's your end?
Any progress with Gang Beom-ryong?
- What are you looking at?
- I'm working on it. I'll call you back.
- Move!
- Come on!
Gang is alive.
- For real?
- Of course. Damn it.
Boss, that means
we don't have to do this, right?
Mr. Jeong, do you want to
waste your energy fighting him?
All right, fine. Have it your way.
A temporary alliance it is.
We know Gang is alive now.
- We can't waste time.
- Then let's be clear.
We don't work for you.
Jeez, I get it.
Call it whatever you want, I don't care.
But don't question my operation again.
- Or this alliance is over. Got it?
- Fine!
JEONGSEOK SINGLE ROOMS
Most of the victims were people
who gambled at Heaven Casino.
They lured in ordinary residents
and got them into gambling debt.
And then they intentionally confiscated
their homes and land.
But it's strange.
On Yeongseon Island, they only took land
from Nakwon-ri residents.
NAKWON-RI
But why?
Properties in a small village
are a hassle to sell.
Even with development plans,
it'd take a long time to profit.
Yoo In-gu is definitely acting
on Han Gyeong-wook's orders.
So why would Han Gyeong-wook
give such an order?
- They're using Yeongseon Island to...
- Here's your meal.
Oh, thanks.
Come in.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you. Just leave it there.
I'll eat in a bit.
Oh, okay.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Do you think there's a way
for the victims to get their homes back?
Well, I'm not sure yet.
You should eat something first.
Yes, if you just leave it,
I'll eat it. Thank you.
You have to eat before it gets cold.
And take your medicine.
Just a moment. There we go.
Say ah.
- Can I do it myself?
- Of course.
Thank you.
After you finish the porridge,
make sure you take your meds.
If you get seawater in your ear,
you can get a nasty ear infection.
- Are you a nurse, by any chance?
- Huh?
It's just,
you seem to be a natural at this.
I fell into the ocean ten years ago,
just like you.
I'm just doing for you
what the person who saved me did.
- Why did you fall in?
- I have no idea.
What?
Oh, there's no water.
I'll get you some warm water.
Eat up before it gets cold.
So busy today.
Ah, to meet the two men
who once ruled the Hwasan Sect.
- It's an honor to meet you.
- The honor is all mine.
Why are you being so formal
with these thugs?
We may not have started off
on the right foot.
But let's put the past behind us...
- and focus on what's ahead.
- Yes, I'll do my absolute best.
But is Prosecutor Gang really alive?
Yes, we're certain she's alive.
It'll take some time
to pinpoint her location.
But before that,
there's something I need you two to do.
Not Ma Gong-bok.
I need him to keep tabs on Bulgae.
Hey, so about Bulgae.
He was chased by the Heaven Capital guys
and got away.
- So you lost him?
- We're looking. We'll find him.
Are you kidding me?
Hey.
It's not like you weren't distracted
with other things yourself.
You two are a real piece of work.
Relax.
There's something more urgent
than finding this Bulgae.
Remember what Yoo In-gu said
when we bugged him?
- The drug deal.
- What?
That bastard Yoo In-gu is dealing drugs?
He said soon,
they'd be making a huge deal.
One that will decide their fate.
The question is, how do we stop them?
Wait a minute.
Can the four of us stop that?
I mean, I hate to admit it.
But the Ingu Sect is way too big
for just the four of us to take on.
Since we're doing this anyway,
let's just go straight for the top.
Do you think Yoo In-gu or Han Gyeong-wook
will even bat an eye over one deal?
Typical thug mindset.
You only see what's in front of you.
- What?
- You take out the boss, then what?
You just bury him?
And Gang Beom-ryong,
did you forget what happened
when you charged in alone?
Those bastards have built a fortress.
You want to tear it down?
You have to take it down step by step.
Our priority is to stop the drug deal
and land a critical blow.
So you have a plan?
First, Ma Gong-bok.
Put your search for Bulgae on hold,
and start looking into Yoo In-gu.
Don't miss a single thing they do.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey, Ho-myeong.
Tailing, wiretapping...
This isn't child's play.
You sure a civilian can handle it?
He's not just a civilian.
He stalked me, an elite agent,
for ten whole years.
Well, I don't mean to brag.
But I know his anniversary,
Ji-woo's birthday
and how many spoons he owns.
Just let me know if you ever need to
tail someone and gather intel.
Nice.
See? Now you get
how creepy and relentless he is.
And you, with your leg,
don't even think about overdoing it.
Go through the police CCTV footage
he has access to.
- Track Prosecutor Gang.
- Okay, got it.
What? What do you want from me?
- You just get ready.
- I'm already ready. Ready for what?
To run like a dog.
Try not to wreck the car.
I haven't forgotten
about that scratch on the door.
Jeez, I know. I'll be careful.
Thank you.
I saw the dent in the back too!
I told you that wasn't me.
For goodness' sake.
I'll be on my way. See you in the evening.
- Say hi to Seon-jung for me.
- Okay.
- Oh, dear.
- Oh, hey.
- Welcome.
- Hey, O-ran!
- Boss.
- Yeah.
A woman just went into
Kim Seon-jung's house.
Get a picture.
Did you get it?
But boss, seriously,
isn't this a bit much?
We're already swamped with the drug deal.
Plus the Martial Arts Master,
and now Kim Seon-jung, too?
The guys are complaining,
saying it's too much work.
If you don't use your brain,
your body pays the price.
If you and I want to save our own skin,
we better do whatever we can.
We must get new intel
on Kim Seon-jung before Jo does.
- But for how long?
- Suck it up a little longer, you punk!
This will all be over soon.
All right. Look here.
- See? This is rice...
- Yes.
Underneath are beans, barley, potatoes,
and sweet potatoes.
I was going to donate this
to a homeless shelter.
But you all need it more right now,
so take it.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry for always whining.
- How are the victims?
- Is the number still increasing?
- Yes.
We're gathering all the evidence,
but Heaven Capital must've pulled strings.
Police and lawyers keep saying
nothing illegal occurred.
Even reporters don't care,
saying it's not newsworthy.
- I don't know what I should do now.
- Damn it. Just hold on a little longer.
Wait until I get elected.
The first thing I'll do is
create a relief plan for the victims.
- How ambitious.
- I'm number one in the polls, kid.
I know.
That's why you need to get elected soon.
At this rate, everyone on
Yeongseon Island will be ruined.
Let's just hang in there
a little longer, huh?
Okay.
- Hand me that one.
- Here.
- We'll put this to good use, sir.
- Let me know if you need more.
- Thank you.
- You should get going.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay then.
Huh?
She's driving away.
- What do we do?
- Obviously, we follow her.
Wait, who's that?
I feel like I've seen her before.
Switch.
Damn it. She's onto us.
I told you to keep some distance.
- Perfect. Now get right on her tail.
- Yes, sir.
It's a dead end.
- Right.
- Hey, get ready.
- Kill the engine.
IMCHEON 30 BA 8690
ORAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
Cuckoo!
- Ji-woo.
- Daddy! It's Daddy!
- Ji-woo. Hey there. Have you been well?
- Uh-huh.
- Have you eaten today?
- Daddy, I missed you.
I missed you too.
What's with the dramatic family reunion?
Hey, Jeong.
Whoa, you scared me.
What brings you out so early?
Where have you been?
Do you know how worried we've been?
Ever since you left
the two of us have had it so rough,
you have no idea.
O-ran is always out and about
with her K-pop obsession.
At this rate,
we're going to work ourselves to death.
You're back for good, right?
You're not leaving again, are you?
Daddy? Are you back for good?
I just stopped by for a bit today
to see Ji-woo.
When on earth are you going to
make up with O-ran, huh?
She blocked my number,
so there's nothing I can do.
- A letter. You could write her a letter.
- She'd just tear it up.
So you're just going to do nothing?
You're not going to come back?
To make up with Ji-woo's mom,
there's something I need to take care of.
I'll come back after I've finished it.
Daddy, when are you coming home?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Hey. so...
Since you're here,
can you peel some onions before you go?
Do you have any incense left at home?
STORE CLOSING
CLEARANCE SALE
Boss.
We got this new sour chicken lunch box.
Can I try one?
Go ahead.
There's no one else to eat it anyway.
Were you saving it
for that police officer?
- In that case, I won't have it.
- No, go ahead and eat.
She won't be coming by anyway.
Huh?
What do you mean, she won't be coming?
Did you end things with her?
There was nothing to end.
We were never anything to begin with.
Just eat it so I don't have to see it.
Yes, sir. I'll get it out of your sight.
Mr. Gang!
- You're early.
- I came as soon as you called.
What's this about?
Why are you quitting all of a sudden?
Let's talk inside.
- Stay and eat.
- Yes, sir.
Hold it.
What is it?
There's a store called 25 O'Clock
about 300 meters from here.
- From now on, please go there instead.
- Excuse me?
Is that what your boss said?
That I shouldn't come?
I hate to say this, but...
My boss lives
in a different world from you.
He has big things ahead of him,
so don't be a distraction.
- You should just back off now.
- Big things?
What?
Is he opening a supermarket or something?
And what gives you the right
to say something like that?
I know my boss better than anyone.
Anyone in the world.
Do you have any idea
how much of a nuisance you've been to him?
Is that what he said?
- That I was a nuisance?
- Yes, he said it himself.
He said you were driving him crazy
when you're not even together.
Another Friendly Convenience Store award,
and you'll get even more perks from HQ.
- Please, think it over.
- It's just that something's come up.
- Sorry this is so sudden.
- I don't know how to tell you this.
But you can't close right away.
- It'll take at least three months.
- Please do it as quickly as you can.
Just a moment.
I'll be taking inventory.
- Did the headquarters...
- Jesus! Don't creep up on me!
I've been right here the whole time.
- No, but just now...
- Oh, the cop? She's crazy.
- I sent her away.
- Crazy?
You sent her away?
Didn't you say you two were nothing?
She keeps coming to the store,
so she's a distraction.
So I just took care of her myself.
What do you mean, you took care of her?
Have you really not noticed
the way she looks at you?
- She's into you.
- Really?
- How would you know that?
- Hey, what do you mean, how?
Do you have any idea how many girls
come here just to give me drinks?
That officer had the exact same look
when she was looking at you.
It's a good thing I nipped it in the bud.
What would've happened
if you two had hit it off? Huh?
Next thing you know,
you would have ended up on TV.
The headline would read
"Collusion Between Ex-Gangster and Cop."
Just the thought of it gives me chills.
I did good, right?
You're right about everything.
Let's go with that.
That could've been a disaster.
I really saved the day.
HANMAEUM K-POP
The number you have dialed
is unavailable...
I was too harsh.
Just tell me where you are.
The number you are trying to reach...
UNCLE: I WAS TOO HARSH.
JUST TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE.
Who is it? Your uncle?
Yeah.
Just swallow your pride, apologize,
and go home.
Damn it, are you crazy? I've got my pride.
How can I just go back now?
You're out of money for the PC cafe.
Go home and get some money at least.
Do you really think
I'm that much of a scumbag?
Hey, that man is practically
living like a slave because of me.
You want me to take his money?
When will you grow up?
I'll go back when I can pay him back,
plus extra, and free him.
That's when I'll go back. In style.
You're broke.
You think you can pull that off?
That's why I'm trying to earn money.
I'm scouring the part-time job sites now.
NIGHT SHIFT, SERVERS, ENGLISH TUTOR WANTED
Man, why is the pay so crappy
for all of these?
Ah, damn it.
Hey, Nam-il, I saw Jin-su yesterday.
He said there's a gig that pays well.
But they can't find anyone for it.
If you're interested,
should I ask him about it for you?
- It's not a scam, is it?
- Can't be a proper job.
It pays a million won a day.
What? One million won? For real?
HEAVEN CAPITAL VICTIMS RECORD
BONG JE-SUN / HEO NAM-IL
Bong Je-sun.
Yes.
Oh, dear.
I've prepared a nourishing meal
for you today.
Here you go. There.
This isn't just any regular chicken.
It's made with a free-range chicken.
Looks delicious, right?
Wow.
Je-sun.
- Yes?
- Mind if I eat with my own hands?
- Of course.
- Okay.
Sorry.
Thank you.
I'll get the bones out for you.
Je-sun, why are you always hanging around?
Don't you have a job?
This is my job.
- Huh?
- Well...
i used to have an office job,
but I got fired.
Those thugs from Heaven Capital
came to my workplace and caused a scene.
I see your name, Bong Je-sun,
on the victim list here.
- Did you gamble?
- Not me. My nephew did.
It wasn't even a large amount.
He got scammed.
He's not even your own son.
Who takes on their nephew's debt?
Wait.
- Did you cosign for him?
- No, not exactly.
It's just...
I couldn't just turn my back on him.
Remember when I told you
I fell in the sea ten years back?
These people came and rescued me,
and I had no memory or a place to go.
They took me in as their son and uncle.
So that's why you said you don't know
how you ended up in the water.
Incredible.
It's like something out of a movie.
- So you don't remember anything?
- It's a funny thing, right?
I even tried hypnotherapy,
but it was no use.
It only had me dreaming something
like a scene out of an action movie.
-An action movie?
-Yes.
Come in.
Hi, Prosecutor Gang.
I've something I need to discuss with you.
Do you have a moment?
With me?
You said two men followed you
when you left Seon-jung's house yesterday?
Yes. But I'm not entirely sure.
I'm pretty sure they were tailing me,
you know?
So I couldn't let them follow me here.
So I hid in an alley.
It was either me or them.
I grabbed a wooden plank
and waited for them.
But they just suddenly vanished.
From the glimpse I got,
they didn't seem like regular guys.
They looked just like the thugs
that work for Heaven Capital.
What if they found out
we're helping the collection victims?
What if that's why they followed me?
But why didn't you call the police
right on the spot?
Well, you see...
If they're from the loan company,
it's useless to report them.
I mean, how do you think they get away
with locking people up and beating them?
Who do you think is backing them?
It's no use to call the cops.
They'd have gotten off with a warning.
- Is it that bad?
- You don't have to look far.
My superior, Sergeant Kim,
is a stooge for those loan sharks.
What do we do
if it's really the Heaven Capital guys?
I think we need to come up with a plan.
We face them head-on. How about it?
- Face them head-on?
- Yes. Okay.
Could you tell me more
about this Detective Kim?
Code One. 34 Nakwon 2-ro.
Assault reported.
Yeah, I'm nearby. I'll take it.
DETECTIVE KIM: DISPATCH IN 3
Hey, stop it.
- Let's go.
- Yes, boss.
Everyone on Yeongseon Island knows him.
He's supposed to be a cop.
But instead of stopping debt collectors,
he covers for them.
- There must be cameras around there.
- There were none.
Are the police allowed to do this?
How can a regular citizen
get the CCTV footage?
As if taking bribes wasn't bad enough,
he's been corrupting his colleagues.
There are countless loan company cases
that Detective Kim has covered up.
At this point, he's not much of a cop.
He's more of a goon for Heaven Capital.
Mi-kyung, this Detective Kim.
Remember the traffic accident
on the riverside road?
Can you find out
if he was dispatched for it?
How do you know about that?
He's usually always slacking off.
I thought it was strange
when he said he wanted to go.
Ah, this might be easier than I thought.
I'll go meet with Detective Kim tomorrow.
You will?
Recognize this place?
Yeah, isn't this where Yoo In-gu held me?
That's right. Yeongseon Food.
This is their base of operations.
They package it to look like preservatives
and put it in their beef jerky.
Then they distribute it nationwide
from Yeongseon Island.
The day after tomorrow,
a huge drug shipment from China
is coming into Yeongseon Island
through Yeongseon Port.
So they're bringing it in
disguised as cargo?
Word on the street is that the Ingu Sect
poured all their funds into this.
We haven't confirmed that the drug money
is to go into Han Gyeong-wook's pocket.
But still, if we stop this...
- We can finish Yoo In-gu for good.
- Exactly.
- You're tracking their movements, right?
- Oh, I was about to bring that up.
Those bastards tried to go after
someone named Kim Seon-jung.
Kim Seon-jung?
Yes, he's Han Gyeong-wook's rival
in the mayoral election.
He seems to have
nothing to do with the deal.
So I'm not sure of their plan.
Yesterday, they were even tailing a woman
who visited Kim Seon-jung's house.
I chased them because I thought
they were about to do something.
And I took them down.
Did you see her face?
Well, she got away
while I was dealing with those goons.
But I did get her license plate.
The Kim Seon-jung situation
doesn't seem to be related to this deal.
So take the plate number and
look into it later.
Okay.
You keep tracking Yoo In-gu's movements
related to the deal.
Got it.
What about Prosecutor Gang?
I know a man carried her
and he entered the redevelopment area.
But they've disappeared since then.
There's no CCTV there, either.
Damn. If only we had Prosecutor Gang,
this would be so much easier.
- Anyway, keep looking into it.
- Okay.
Oh, and you.
Gang Beom-ryong.
Gang Beom-ryong!
- Hey.
- What? Why?
- What?
- What do you think?
About what?
Don't you have any idea
what Yoo In-gu's next move will be?
He used to work for you.
You must know him better than anyone.
Right.
Why do you need my opinion?
Gong-bok already did all the research.
Were you even listening?
Give me a break.
I only missed a bit
because I was thinking.
Come on, I got the gist of it.
We're on the verge of drugs flooding
Yeongseon Island, and you're zoning out?
I wouldn't expect any less
from an ex-thug.
No sense of responsibility, no passion.
This guy, I swear.
It's always about me being a gangster.
Hey, you think gangsters
don't have feelings?
Ever think about a gangster's feelings?
What? Why the hell are you getting mad?
- Don't stop me.
- Hands off!
I wasn't touching you.
Hey, what's gotten into you?
Look, I got the gist of it.
So if you need anything from me,
just tell Gong-bok.
I've got things to do at the store,
so I'm off.
- Beom-ryong!
- What was that about?
Beom-ryong.
Get home safe.
- I'm sorry. I got a little carried away.
- Nothing to be sorry about.
Still...
You seem really stressed out.
So that's why he's acting like this?
Because of that cop he had a crush on?
Yes, he said nothing's
going on between them.
But ever since her visit,
he's been like that.
That's not good.
- Why's that?
- We're moving in tomorrow.
He could sabotage the whole thing.
Come on, Beom-ryong was a legend
in the Hwasan Sect.
You think he'd mess up a job
over some trouble with a girl?
So you're sure Gang Beom-ryong
will be over that woman by tomorrow?
Do you think your boss is
that rational and level-headed?
No, not at all.
Tell me everything you know
about Gang Beom-ryong.
Hey, Mi-kyung. Get over here.
Hurry up and get over here.
Why do you keep sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong?
You think all cops are the same?
There are ranks, you know.
You barely got that ID around your neck
at your age.
You should learn to stay in your lane.
Ugh, this is so frustrating.
How'd you even get in?
Get your shit together.
- Turning yourself in?
- Jesus!
Hey, what's your deal?
How did you know I'd be here?
You look right at home.
- What?
- Yeah.
Turning yourself in wouldn't be
that terrible of an idea.
It's one way to repent
for all that you've done.
But that's not it, is it?
Why are you staring at the station
so wistfully?
It's because of that cop from earlier,
isn't it?
- Who?
- She's way out of your league.
Don't you think
you're in two different films?
She's romance, you're crime thriller.
You don't match at all.
If you ask me,
a store owner and a regular.
Thta's the best you can hope for.
- Did Gong-bok talk again?
- Yep.
Leave me alone.
It's not what you
and Gong-bok are worried about.
- I didn't come this way over Mi-kyung.
- Then what?
Why are you here at such a critical time?
Gang Beom-ryong.
- Don't you know what's important?
- I know.
What do you know?
- I want to end this so badly!
- I packed a bag and left my home!
Tomorrow's operation will be hard
even if we're at our 100%.
If you juggle everything at once,
you'll end up dropping it all.
Whether it's Yoo In-gu or Han Gyeong-wook
we gotta finish this so you can go back
to the life you want, right?
So stop getting distracted
and focus on the task.
Asking her out and getting turned down
can wait until the job is done.
I know that.
Don't act like you know everything.
Once this is all over,
I'll go and talk to her for real!
But the way I see it,
I don't think you have a shot.
That's ridiculous.
Gong-bok said Mi-kyung is into me too.
You believe that?
I bet he was just being nice.
Does he look like he cares about me?
But still.
What will you do if she turns you down?
What, is this it? There's nothing.
Sir, Kkot-nim and I have been
watching him like a hawk.
But not a single soul came near the place.
He's very meticulous.
- Did you tail him?
- Just his office and his regular diner.
- He meets no one privately.
- Screw it.
We'd never find any dirt on him
even if we looked for months.
If a guy is this clean,
even Chairman Do won't find anything.
It is a shame
I couldn't outdo him this time, though.
I'll settle for sitting back
and watching him get an earful.
Let's drop this and focus on our deal.
You know what I mean?
Yes, sir.
Besides that woman, no one else has been
in or out of Kim Seon-jung's house.
- Did you ID this woman?
- She's definitely no ordinary woman.
Just as we were about to grab her,
some guy appeared.
He totally ambushed us.
It's obvious she has someone
watching her back.
- Watching her back?
- But take a look here.
- Right.
- Yes, right there.
I got a picture of the plate.
And you're sure Yoo knows
nothing about this woman?
Oh, yes. I haven't told him a thing.
So for now, he's going to
stop worrying about Kim Seon-jung
and focus on the deal.
Okay, okay.
Let's make sure we keep it that way.
Don't let him get distracted
by pointless things. Okay?
Yes, sir.
You can go.
You must be busy with the upcoming deal.
Yes, sir.
Kim Seon-jung...
Seems like there's a new variable.
Should we revise the Kim Seon-jung plan?
No, no.
For now, let's stick with our plan.
No point in flipping a table
that's already set.
Then I'll proceed as planned.
Wait. It can't hurt to be cautious.
Run this woman's plate
and find out who she is.
You said she's no ordinary woman.
We need to see if she'll affect our plan.
- We should at least check.
- Yes, understood.
Man, the flame is too low.
Why is this so tough?
This's cheap beef.
Are you passing it off as prime grade?
Please, just go.
You're disturbing my business
when you're eating for free.
Don't go making false accusations.
When did I disturb your business?
I mean, this is just awful.
So tough.
The meat here is tough!
Here's your money, so please.
Please, just go. Okay?
See, was that so hard?
Why'd you have to make things difficult?
You're a cop.
Don't you know this is wrong?
But it's not.
Look, lady.
Don't you see those shops getting
shut down by Heaven Capital?
And who's letting you stay in business?
It's all thanks to me.
What's the point of me working all day?
If you keep taking all my money,
how am I supposed to survive?
Lady.
You should just work harder.
I believe in you!
Stop annoying me
and get me some beef to go.
For my family.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
What the hell?
What are you doing here?
I'm on patrol.
Patrol?
What patrol?
Looking for thugs like you.
What? Park Mi-kyung,
are you out of your mind?
You're the one who's out of your mind.
Not Officer Park.
- What? Who are you?
- I'm so disappointed.
I thought you were
desperately looking for me.
You don't even recognize me?
What are you saying? Who are you?
Me?
Well, Sergeant Kim.
I'm the one you're dying to find
in Yeongseon River.
Prosecutor Gang Yeong-ae.
What? Don't be ridiculous.
You went to great lengths.
To make it look like a simple accident.
Once you've served your time
for destroying evidence, you'll know.
Whether I'm just a ghost...
or Gang Yeong-ae.
- What are you doing here?
- I was just worried.
Are you okay?
MY CASH COW 2
Pick up your damn phone, will you?
Sorry, I was in the middle of something.
What's going on, boss?
What do you think?
The shipment from China is tomorrow.
- Didn't I tell you to prepare?
- Oh, yes. I remember.
Anyway, make sure no cops
are sniffing around Yeongseon Port.
And check for suspicious people
like that Martial Arts Master.
Make sure to make your rounds.
- Yes, of course, sir.
- Okay.
Sergeant Kim.
Looks like we have a lot to talk about.
Mr. Bong.
- Yes?
- Can you get up now?
Yes, I'm good.
Just a...
Jang Yeong-gi,
Nampo Police, Narcotics Unit 2.
Guess who?
Why'd you call here?
You should've just called my cell.
You're no fun.
Never mind. I'll explain later.
Yeong-gi.
- Want to make a big bust?
- Why? What's up?
Something really big just came up.
I'm on Yeongseon Island.
Come over here tomorrow.
It's been a while
since we worked together.
Boss.
You quit being a cop
and worked so hard to get that job.
You should be doing desk work.
Why are you still
running around the field?
Hey, since when have you been so stuck up?
Is that how I taught you?
I'm just worried about you.
Fine, what is it?
-Hey, thanks for lending me your phone.
-Oh, sure.
Did the call go well?
Detectives will be here tomorrow.
- Are you feeling okay?
- I will be.
I'm still a little tingly, though.
I think I have to get back now.
What should I do with him?
Should I just lock him up?
You can't lock me up! I'm innocent!
No. Let's bring him with us for now.
Those Ingu Sect bastards.
I thought it was strange
how quiet they've been.
I think they're using high school kids
from Yeongseon as human shields.
Using high schoolers in a drug deal?
That's insane.
Exactly. Even gangs usually have rules.
Geum Kang-sik alone has met
with 20 to 30 high school students.
They think it's just a high-paying job.
It'll get complicated
with too many people.
And we can't just mess with
these kids who know nothing.
We'll find a way.
This is a guy named Baek.
A specialist in smuggling
and illegal immigration.
He bribed officials at Yeongseon Port
and set up an office for his smuggling op.
No one smuggles anything into
or out of Yeongseon without him.
Same with Yoo In-gu's drugs tomorrow.
Baek is the one accommodating it.
We just have to secure the location
and set it up perfectly.
we definitely have a fighting chance.
Is that even possible?
What's our objective?
Even if we report the drugs,
Yoo and Han will obviously find a way out.
And it's not like
we can take down all their men.
But if we're just trying
to screw Yoo In-gu over?
If that's our only objective,
then it's not impossible.
I'm starting to see the picture.
So, what should we do first?
- You and Gong-bok can set up the stage.
- With Gong-bok?
- You think a civilian can pull it off?
- Hey, I can do anything.
Just you watch.
Okay, so what about me?
- Should I be on standby?
- You're with me.
We're securing the location.
- Not confident going alone?
- I could go by myself.
I just thought
I'd give you something to do.
So shut up and follow my lead.
- Fine. When are we going?
- Now.
Hey, Kim.
Geez.
Is this your first day in business?
The goods will be transported safely.
- Don't worry. Just buy me a drink.
- Hey, boys!
Wait, hold on.
- What the hell?
- I don't have much time.
So I'll keep it short.
There's an important shipment coming in
from China tomorrow night, right?
We need to make some adjustments
to those goods.
So, we need to borrow your little shop
for just two days.
Think of it as a location sponsorship.
What the hell?
What are these assholes on about?
Hey, what are you doing? Get 'em!
What are you waiting for? Get out.
- By myself? What about you?
- You scared?
Scared? Hell no.
SPECIAL THANKS TO
KIM SANG-KYUNG AND KWON YUL
Location secured. Now let's get set up.
Now we're real allies.
- Aren't you worried?
- My calculations are never off.
Something was definitely
going on between them.
- All by yourself?
- Want to come with me then?
- I'll do whatever.
- Be honest. Did something happen?
- I'm pregnant.
- Pregnant?
- You believe that crap?
- Shut up.
I know better than anyone
just how evil Han Gyeong-wook is.
The package is delivered.
If we're going to set it off,
it might as well be a good show.
I have to save him.
He could die if he stays there.
- Hey, boss!
- I was wondering when you'd show up.
It was you?