MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Grand Prince Cheongheon is forbidden
from leaving his residence.
Who is there?
I have brought you some porridge.
Please eat it before it gets cold.
Is that you? Why did you come?
Have you no fear? Someone could see you
waiting there.
I fear I am no longer able to
discern what is falsehood and what is
genuine. Tell me, if you please, sir.
What is the truth behind it all?
You are quite naive, indeed. This is
why you are so easily fooled and
used by men.
What?
You mustn't do anything for me.
Focus on your survival, just as you
did when you were interrogated.
Consider this…
my final order to you.
Kang Dan-sim…
never…
come to my private quarters again.
Tell me…
who are you really? Kang Clan, Dan-sim.
Wait, what did you just…
Who is she?
What do you mean, "who am I?" Where did
that name come from? What is all this
nonsense? And here of all places?
I keep seeing a woman in my sleep.
A court lady with no family or friends.
At first, I thought these were just vivid
dreams, but what's strange is that the
Court Lady looks exactly like you.
Maybe I've gone crazy.
Well, at least you know how you sound.
You can't tell the difference between a
-random dream and reality?
-Random?
Yes, random. You must be out of your
mind to come here like this,
talking nonsense about dreams. I'll head
inside now, go get dressed already.
EPISODE 9
THAT'S FIRST LOVE FOR YOU
-What should we do?
-Follow him.
Tell me… who are you really? I keep
seeing a woman in my sleep. She's a
court lady with no family or friends.
In his dreams…
Cha, this launch is a huge success.
If I had known you'd hit a home
run on your first try, I would've
invested in your business from the start.
I was thinking the same thing.
At this rate, you'll be breaking into
the US market and taking over the
whole industry.
No need to be scared of that. I won't
take it over entirely.
Well, at least you know how you sound.
You can't tell a dream from reality?
Yes, I thought so, too. It was
wonderful, a great idea, yeah. Oh,
hello, so nice to see you here.
Why do you keep following me all around
the room like a puppy who's lost? You
should be out there getting
yourself noticed and snagging up
every ad contract you can get your
hands on.
-That's not really my field of work.
-"Field of work?"
What's the point of being signed
to an agency if I have to go around
selling my face like some street peddler?
You're not paid to just stand there.
Why does she always have to have to
last word?
Shin Seo-ri.
I've been looking for you.
Are you okay, Cha Se-gye?
Don't worry about me. They're random,
right? And yet, they were so disturbing.
Even that annoying Choi Mun-do was there.
Even in my dreams, he's an aspiring
tyrant. Maybe that's why they say
dreams are an extension of your
consciousness.
Could it be they're not dreams? Maybe he
can truly see the past?
Yep.
There you are, Se-gye.
Don't you remember our last conversation?
I said there's no communication
until the engagement's official--
No, wait, someone might hear you.
You're right. That was thoughtless of me.
I'll be more careful.
You really shouldn't do this, Se-gye,
especially not at an official event
where I'm still--
Yeah, his fiancée. I've heard that so
often, my ears are bleeding. Cha Se-gye,
you have my permission. Take her
by the hand and go around the room.
We should help the less fortunate.
That's not a big ask. Go on, let her
have this one, okay?
Who do you think you are to give him
permission?
You really are an ungrateful pest.
Oh, perfect! I see you're all here
already.
Grandfather, I didn't expect to see you
here.
Well, why wouldn't I come and see
my grandson's tiny business launch.
Hello and welcome, Grandfather. If you'd
told me you were coming, I would've
accompanied you myself.
You're already supporting him as a wife,
Tae-hee. My dear Se-gye is truly blessed
when it comes to women.
Is that so?
Grandfather, I would like you to meet the
brand ambassador for Dynaestie and the
reason we're sold-out, Shin Seo-ri.
Wait, Shin Seo-ri?
I'm very pleased to meet you,
Grandfather.
Uh…
Enough. Stop that. Stop it! You can't
call him grandfather, yet.
-Oh, I can't?
-Just call him, Mr. Cha.
Oh, I also remember you insisting I
call you Mr. Cha when we first met.
I guess being sensitive about titles
is something that runs in the family.
You're very amusing. So, the model and
the CEO of the company are on informal
terms?
Not really, I mean… it's kind of
complicated.
She's filming a period drama right now,
and she's quite immersed in her role.
It's method acting, don't pay attention
to it. Look, Chairman Jung
is over there. We should go.
Chairman Jung. Yes, this way. Yes.
Chairman Jung's here?
Yes, we should go, Grandfather.
You little wench.
Oh, I was just lucky, I guess.
Don't sell yourself short. It wasn't
luck, it was ability.
Oh, you're too kind. Thank you.
Thank you for coming, it was so
good to see you.
-It was good to see you too.
-You should come by the office.
Yes, of course.
My grandson has just launched a new brand
called Dynaestie. We need to make it a
-success.
-Yes, I see.
I heard about it and had to come
congratulate him.
He's very hardworking boy, you know, so
I'm pretty sure that this thing going to…
Today's launch helps Cha restore
his image in the industry. The media's
response is favorable, and opinion among
Chail employees is positive.
I guess it's the result of the chairman's
halo effect, and all the hope people
have for him as heir of the Chail Group.
What's the update on the nurse? Is she
still in the hospital and unconscious?
Yes, I've already bribed the staff
there, so they'll contact us if there's
any change.
No mistakes can be made with her
this time.
You were a court lady in Cha's dream?
If he's starting to see past events, then
they can't be prophetic dreams.
Maybe it is reincarnation.
I know you're a shaman, but your thinking
needs to keep up with the times. In
this world of flying palanquins, do you
really think that makes any sense?
Why wouldn't there be reincarnation
when we can transcend time and space?
But, if it's really a form
of reincarnation, do you know
who he could have been?
You said this Choi Mun-do guy
is the king, then wouldn't Mr. Cha be
someone who's close to the King?
Your dreams are telling you a story?
Would you say you've been stressed
lately?
Obviously… I'm surrounded by landmines.
Never mind, just prescribe me some
sleeping pills. Strong ones that won't
let me dream.
Well, dreams can't really be suppressed
at will. You need to relax and let
yourself go with the flow. Who knows?
They could be prophetic dreams.
Prophetic? Are you even paying attention?
What kind of doctor are you? I'm not
seeing the future, but the past.
That doesn't really matter. They're
equally connected to the present.
You know, you can't think of time as a
straight line. Things can exist
simultaneously.
Are you serious?
Who'd have thought the chairman would be
there in person? I think it's a positive
sign, yeah?
A sign? Yeah, it's a sign that your
imagination is playing tricks on you.
I mean, we've been desperately
waiting for him to ask you to return to
headquarters, to work with him again, and
finally…
I've been so desperately waiting,
I'm even having dreams about it.
Of course, it'll be a slightly longer
commute, but hey! Sleep's overrated,
right?
Yeah, I haven't been sleeping well
at all.
I guess this could be a symptom of sleep
deprivation. Mr. Son, you really
do have a keen sense of observation.
Yeah. Well, could I go on vacation before
we return to HQ?
Oh, I'll tell you what, you can go
on vacation the same time I go
-on vacation.
-Oh, what, really? When would that be?
Just after I die.
Oh, no, what's wrong?
My teeth have been sensitive since
yesterday, and my gums are sore.
You may not be going on vacation, but you
better go see a dentist. Teeth are
the one thing you can lose quickly if
you wait too long.
A dentist?
Mr. Cha, how are you? These documents
need your approval, and here's
the script.
"Kingdom of Women?"
Oh, the one Shin Seo-ri's in?
Their marketing team asked about product
placement, but these days, TV dramas
don't have much advertising impact, so
I turned them down. You can ignore it.
"In bed?"
PALACE, GWIIN'S QUARTERS
SHARING A BED ON A RAINY NIGHT
Stay still.
THE KING AND THE GWIIN SIT SIDE BY SIDE
IN THEIR UNDERGARMENTS
-I am shy, Your Majesty.
-Oh, would you come here.
Wait, Your Majesty. Why are you in such
haste, sire?
Why are you being so shy? One would
think you are a newlywed bride on her
wedding night. Now, come here.
Oh, Your Majesty. Can you put out
the candle?
I will not put out the candle light,
as I wish to see all this laid
bare to my eyes.
Your Majesty. Your Majesty!
Idiots!
-Watch out.
-I'm sorry, sir!
I took a sip because I was
feeling sleepy.
-Argh! Damn, seriously?
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry about the coffee.
Mr. Son, contact the product placement
manager… right now.
You're the Assistant Director,
help us out. You can't just cut an
entire scene without notice! What are we
supposed to do now?
Hey, look, we had a last minute
request from a placement partner.
They offered so much money, even the
director couldn't say no.
Well, why should we let it go just
because you guys decided it was alright?
Here, just learn the new scene.
You know, you should've done it right the
first time around.
What's with this last minute scene
change? What has it been replaced with?
A Royal Sericulture Ceremony.
A… ceremony?
So a ceremony's the problem?
COURTYARD OF THE SEOHYANG PAVILION, DAY
THE SOUND OF TRADITIONAL JOSEON MUSIC
FILLS THE YARD
ROYAL SERICULTURE CEREMONY IN PROGRESS
CONCUBINES, COURT LADIES STAND IN TWO ROWS
The Naemyeongbu is in utter chaos.
The Royal Sericulture Ceremony is
the Queen's prerogative, so why is
she here?
Her Majesty has suddenly taken ill with
indigestion. We have no choice, we
cannot postpone it.
Oh, my, look at that. It's a butterfly.
I was wondering where this lovely scent
was coming from. It must be coming
from Gwiin Jang.
Her complexion is as clear as white jade.
As they say, the one with the most
beautiful skin rules the palace.
When the stormy sea grows calm, and the
winds have died, will you come forth to
me today from over that yonder hill? As
the sunlight sparkles upon the ever-so
JE
Biojei.
Cut! Oh, that was so good! That was
really great.
Good job, everyone. Well done!
Oh, my shoulders. My goodness.
Have the writer and director both
lost their minds? How can they spring
a script change on us?
Yeah, I know honey, but the product
placement deal was for a massive
amount of money. You know how
things work, these shows are always
short on cash, so when they get a
chance to fill the hole, well,
they take it.
And why did they have to fill the
hole with my only solo scene? That's so
unfair.
Then, you should've agreed to do product
placement in the first place.
What on earth are you talking about?
I can't do free advertising for a brand
Shin Seo-ri represents!
Why do you always get so worked up
every time Shin Seo-ri's name comes up?
Do you have an inferiority complex?
Why the hell would I have an inferiority
complex? Damn it!
Cut! Okay, that was great!
Alright, that's a wrap!
Great job, Seo-ri!
Everyone, go to wardrobe.
They say she's an acting prodigy.
Her diction's incredible. What a
great gift for the director.
She's really good.
Thanks again. Good work.
She's the one with the complex.
Even if it's school break, you
need to eat well. You have to eat a lot
because you're small for your age, okay?
Dad, I was thinking about it, can't I
just fly over there?
I've been telling my nanny everyday…
that I really wanna go see you.
Seo-jun, you know I'm a very busy person.
Even if you come to Korea, I won't
have time to hang out with you. Hey,
Seo-jun…
Book me a flight to the US for this
weekend. Just book the… the Friday
red-eye.
Okay…
Mr. Choi, the people at the
hospital called.
How could they just lose a patient? An
unconscious woman.
They said she was still unconcious
when they did their last rounds.
Security cameras? Do we have any idea
where she went?
It seems she took a taxi in front of
the main entrance. We're looking into
where she could have gone.
You need to find her as soon as possible.
She better not start talking to
anyone about what happened…
and especially not the chairman or
Se-gye.
I can't believe how witty you are.
That poem ad-lib was really impressive.
I thought best to do it right. They even
planned to have a white butterfly
land on my shoulder.
-You want one?
-Hard candy?
A sweet reward after hard work.
Seo-ri. Seo-ri!
Director.
That was really phenomenal! Especially
since actors these days hate to do
the product placement.
Well, what can I do? Since everyone
hates it, it falls to a supporting
actress.
Oh, no, no! You don't understand,
It's the product placement CEO who asked
that it be you, specifically, who does
the ad.
They wanted me to do it?
Yes, that's what I'm saying. You,
personally. Way to go!
I guess this is what I have to do to
see her.
I hope they got rid of that bed-sharing
scene.
Hey! You there! Stop where you are.
Who are you?
Me? I'm someone who's poured a lot of
money into this TV drama. I need to
know, has Shin Seo-ri's bed sharing
scene been cut?
Hey, look, you can't just barge onto
this set, okay? What are you, some
kind of fan? Hey, manager!
There won't be any bed-sharing
scenes going forward either. No
unnecessary physical contact with her.
Who do you think you are?
Me?
I'm Shin Seo-ri's stalker.
Okay…
You can't keep barging on set like
this without notifying me. We have to
be discreet, right?
I don't want to. I've been too concerned
about everything that I've stressed
myself out. That's why I'm having
these weird dreams. So I'm gonna cut
myself some slack and do what I want to.
You already do what you want!
Someone changed the script today.
Yeah… that little script change
was thanks to me.
Little?
Well, it was because I heard some
nasty rumors about the male lead.
Apparently, he's known for messing up his
kissing scenes and contacting
the actresses. I heard he's a real jerk,
so, of course, I wanted to protect my
investment. And why do I have to justify
myself? You know, you should be thanking
me!
You're right, thank you, sir. Thanks to
you, I completely stole the scene.
Is that all I get?
I can give you this.
-I really don't like hard candy, you know.
-Too bad.
Wait!
How incredibly sweet.
Gross. Your saliva.
I want you to create a position for
Se-gye at the firm. We can't
keep him shut out of the family business
forever.
We should ask him how he feels about
it first. His startup isn't small
enough to be run on its own.
He can always leave it in the hands of a
professional CEO. Everything's
possible if you really want it.
Is there somewhere you want to go
with me?
Somewhere with you?
We haven't even been on a proper
date yet. Let's see… Where could
we go at this time of day?
Why do you always have to be such
a scoundrel looking at me like that?
I think I just hurt my tooth.
You should have sucked on that candy.
If you crunch it, of course you're gonna
-end up hurting your teeth.
-Why would I do that, it takes too long.
Nice things should always be savored.
Rich people don't know how to appreciate
things.
That's not true.
I know how to savor you. I'm gonna
make this feeling last.
You're bleeding! Quick!
What? I'm bleeding?
Oh…
You really did a number on that wisdom
tooth.
Don't worry, your gums are pink so
you weren't poisoned. The bleeding
TOOTH OF WISDOM: THE JOSEON-ERA NAME
FOR WISDOM TOOTH
of musk for the pain.
Burn chicken droppings?
Come on, start burning it already! This
patient is hurting, you should be giving
-him acupuncture!
-It's really not that bad, you know…
Just stop! You're a patient, you
don't know. Stay!
Take it easy, Shin Seo-ri.
It's an impacted wisdom tooth. You need
surgery right away.
What's impacted?
What? Just pull it out! Why would I need
surgery for a wisdom tooth?
Well, it really depends on the case.
You can see the wisdom tooth on the left
needs to be extracted surgically.
So, would you like to go ahead with the
surgery now?
Yes! Please go do whatever you need to
do. Here!
Okay, I'll get ready.
This is why I hate dentists.
Say Ah! Ah!
-Okay.
-Let's see…
OPERATING UNIT
I can't believe I need general anesthesia
for a wisdom tooth?
It was a good idea to come to a
big hospital. Thanks to me,
your precious life is being spared once
more.
Come on, it's just my teeth, it's not
like I was gonna die.
You need to make sure this is
taken care of, once and for all.
And always suck on hard candy.
Are you leaving?
Well, of course I'm leaving, it's already
late!
Exactly, it's too late to leave.
Stay here.
I'll be in pain when I'm out of surgery.
You said it wasn't like you were going
to die.
Even so, I'm still having surgery
because I'm hurt. It wouldn't be very
nice to abandon someone you've just
started seeing.
That's a pretty indirect way
of telling me to look after you.
It's time for you to go into surgery now.
I trust you!
Don't leave, okay?
Promise me.
We're putting you under now.
By heaven,
now that I have met you and come to
know you,
we shall never be torn asunder.
When the mountain peaks wear down and
the rivers have run dry, when thunder
rumbles in winter, and snow falls
in summer,
when the sky and earth become one,
only then shall we finally part.
I couldn't possibly… give this
painting to her.
Mr. Cha, can you hear me?
Where is she?
Don't worry, your gums might feel
a bit sore from the surgery. You should
ice the area for the next 48 hours.
If everything looks good tomorrow
morning, you can go home after you're
discharged.
Excuse me, do you know if she's left?
Who do you mean?
I guess she did. Well, that was
heartless of her.
Is that not lucky wood? You know,
wood from a lightning-struck
jujubee tree? When I was little, my
father was a potions peddler. Sometimes,
women would ask him to bring some to
offer it to the gods to cure their sons.
Who are you praying for? Your father?
Your brother? Oh, you said you had no
family.
What's going on? I thought you'd left.
I thought you told me not to. I went to
get some ice.
Hey! You must be freezing. Why did you
carry this in your hands? You didn't
have to do that.
What else would I have used? My head?
You were hurting so I did something.
I cannot do much for you, except
things like this.
Your hands are so cold…
Enough, stop it! You're sick, you should
just lie still. That would help me a lot.
You look like one of those pufferfish
with your cheek all swollen.
You should leave now. I can tell you're
enjoying this. Jeez… Ever since
we started going out, I feel like
I'm getting more and more pathetic.
You know those random dreams. Do you
still have them sometimes?
Why? You said they were all nonsense,
but they actually got to you, huh?
If you can't tell us apart, then she
must really look like me. I just
wonder what kind of dreams they are?
I would say they're kind of sad. I don't
think they're gonna end well.
They're sad?
I guess I'm falsly accused. I get
locked up, and stuff like that. Seems to
be heading towards a sad ending. I think
I'll be exiled soon.
What do you mean exiled?
And who do you seem to be in those
dreams?
Me?
Everyone calls me "Your Royal Highness."
"His Royal Highness the Grand Prince."
Even in my dreams, I'm some kind of
Prince or something…
I guess I was right. Bad feelings
are never wrong.
This Grand Prince, he has strong
feelings for a court lady named Kang
Dan-sim.
He must resent me.
He truly loves…
He truly yearns… for her.
By heaven, now that I have met you
and come to know you, we shall never be
torn asunder. When the mountains wear
down and the rivers have run dry, when
thunder rumbles in winter and
snow falls in summer, when the sky and
earth become one, only then shall we
finally part.
This is so beautiful. You can tell
he's in love with her… like the fool
he is.
JOINING HANDS WITH MOCHANG,
IS THE SUCCESSION BATTLE TAKING SHAPE?
Why in the world would you wear
that dress? It makes you look short. I
told you, you need to raise the waistline
to make you look taller. How can someone
who runs her own company have
such terrible fashion taste?
Wow, it's been a while, Mom. I see you
still have your beautiful looks and
wicked tongue.
That's no way to greet your mother after
such a long time. You come back to Korea
and instead of coming home, you decide to
chase after a man you're not even
married to.
I guess I like being with him more than
with you. When I'm over there, no one is
constantly nagging me.
Really?
Either way, I'm glad you're here,
I need to accelerate things. I want you
to invite us over, Se-gye and I.
MOCHANG HEIR'S ATTENDANCE AT CHA SE-GYE'S
BRAND LAUNCH DRAWS STOCK MARKET ATTENTION
They're really shouting it from the
rooftops, aren't they?
MS. SHIN, LET'S MEET SOON
Ms. Shin, let's meet soon.
Could it be him?
GRANDMA
Hey, why did you put me here? It
has to be costing a fortune. Just make
them take me back.
Why would you want to be in an
overcrowded room?
So you can fight all day?
I don't fight! What do you mean?
No, those old ladies are just bored and
running their mouths off, that's all.
You said you didn't wanna stay
there long. You'll recover faster in
that room. It's a nice, bright
room, right? With clean air?
You're not wrong…
And what do you mean, I can't afford it?
Haven't you seen me on TV? I have
lots of money, so don't worry. Focus on
eating well and getting better quickly,
okay?
To think, I'm living a life of luxury at
my age, and all thanks to my little
angel.
But, you know, Seo-ri, I kind of
prefer having those ladies around.
I don't like being here, like this, by
myself. When people are around,
I feel more alive, you know? No matter
how incredible someone is, they can't
live by themselves. What kind of a person
goes in alone? Then you're not really
living, are you? You're withering
away until the end.
So there, that young lady with whom I
shared a table with the other day, does
she come here often?
She does, she comes here two or
three times a week. Why do you
wanna know?
Oh, for no reason. I was just impressed
with her. It's unusual for a young
person to come here and eat alone.
Well, maybe she doesn't have any friends,
many youngsters come here alone.
Maybe she doesn't… have friends.
Tell me, what's her character like?
What do you think of her?
Why do you care what her character
is like? Are you planning on
marrying her?
What are you talking about, old hag? Have
you gone insane? Really!
She's not very nice, she's never
polite and when she talks to
other clients, she talks as if they
were beneath her.
I see.
No matter how incredible someone is,
they can't live by themselves.
Kang Dan-sim, never come to my private
quarters again.
What kind of a person goes in alone?
Then you're not really living, are you?
You're withering away until the end.
Everyone calls me "Your Royal Highness."
"His Royal Highness the Grand Prince."
You're back late.
Have you eaten?
Enjoy your meal.
Tell me, how's your tooth? Is it all
better now?
Yeah, it was just a wisdom tooth,
it's no big deal.
Still, you bled a lot because of it.
You should at least take some herbal
medicine. It will be good for you.
Nah, that's not necessary. I don't
like that kind of medicine. So,
forget it.
I wanted to have a nice meal with you.
Why are we in the middle of the street?
I like the hustle and bustle.
But what if someone recognizes us?
You don't seem to realize that you're a
celebrity now. You have to be careful.
And you shouldn't stay out so late
at night. It's dangerous.
Are you telling me what to do? I'm no
child.
Of course I'm gonna do that. We're
seeing each other. Shouldn't that give
me at least some right?
It's not like it's a big deal. You expect
a lot when it's only a trial period.
Okay, I'll take care of my grandfather,
so you don't have to think about him.
And then… Tae-hee…
that contract thing with her. I'll
settle that quickly… so don't worry.
You're ending it already? Why? You need
to profit from it. It's already in
place, so you might as well make the
most of it.
The newspapers are saying that it's
a good move for both of you. You should
go all out while you're still in this.
You don't have to walk on eggshells
around me.
Tell me, when have I ever walked
on eggshells around you? I've never
been that way with anyone.
You act so proud, but I've seen you
around your grandfather.
No, that's just…
because I really want him to like you.
What?
I want my grandfather… to have a
good impression of you.
Well, it looks like your grandfather
prefers the schemer. I don't blame him.
She has a powerful family behind her.
Schemer? You've given her a nickname
already? She is a bit of a schemer,
I'll give you that.
Don't worry about it. As for family
backing? I don't care about that at all.
I'm a very capable person. Look at
me right now. I'm doing just fine.
Do you know what tall poppy syndrome is?
If you stand out too much, you're the
first they'll cut down. If you're
above everyone, you'll end up withering
away, alone at the top. I've seen
it happen too many times.
You know…
be careful of Choi Mun-do.
And don't trust anyone.
I know how to take care of myself.
Like I said, you don't need to
worry about me.
I wonder…
is the world easy for you? You never
know when someone will attack you
with a knife. Do you think it's the right
time to be fooling around with me, or
whatever this is?
Yes, the world is easy for me. It's
already crazy enough as it is, why
complicate things further?
It doesn't matter how I approach
things, if there's no hesitation,
I have no regrets.
What's difficult, is understanding you.
Strangely, the more I know you,
the harder it gets.
Is it because I'm so into you?
Stop saying that. It's embarrassing.
No one cares if it's embarrassing.
Stop appearing in my dreams, then.
But, what if…
they're not really dreams?
What?
What if these aren't dreams? What would
you say to that?
What do you mean?
The court lady with no family or friends.
The hopelessly naive girl who gets
constantly hazed by her peers. Kang
Dan-sim. What if I were really her?
What would you do then? If I were
the woman who threw everything away to
survive?
You…
COURT LADY KANG DAN-SIM
THERE ARE NO SEARCH RESULTS
FOR COURT LADY KANG DAN-SIM
What the hell am I doing?
MS. SHIN, LET'S MEET SOON
This Grand Prince… he has strong
feelings for a court lady named Kang
Dan-sim. He truly loves…
he truly yearns…
he yearns for her. You can tell he's
in love with her… like the fool he is.
There is no way of knowing for
sure… if he truly yearned for me.
And even if he did, what does it matter
now?
SEOUL MUSEUM OF HISTORY
500 YEARS OF THE JOSEON DYNASTY
TIME TRAVEL HISTORY EXHIBITION 1392-2026
Why do you stare with such interest?
Do you find it strange to see… plum
blossoms in the summer?
I remember, when I was painting this,
I had already buried him in my heart.
You're the lady who was here before! Hi,
Huibin Kang! I'm glad to see you. I'm
currently writing a thesis on a
reinterpretation of the evilist woman
in history, Huibin Kang, so I was glad to
hear it.
I see you're still digging into the story
of Huibin Kang.
Kang Dan-sim. What if I were really
her? What would you do then?
Mr. Cha, I thought you were leaving.
What are you thinking about in here?
Do you believe we live past lives?
What a random question. Yes, I do.
My family has been Buddhist for
generations.
So you think past lives, reincarnation,
all that's possible for you?
There's no reason why not. We're living
our current life, so the one before this
is our past life, and the one after is
our next life. Why do you ask?
I was wondering…
hypothetically, let's say… that someone
is here from the past. What would
that mean?
When in the past?
The Joseon era…
The Joseon era?
Wait, has someone told you they're from
the Joseon era? Did they say you've
made your ancestors angry and they
want money? This is a classic scam
tactic used by cultists.
That's not at all what I meant.
Say you don't care if they're mad and you
don't need a rites ceremony, and if they
say they'll harm you, then they're not
ancestors, but demons. Let's go.
Wow, I never should've asked him.
I just made it super awkward now.
You're an actress, right? In "Kingdom
of Women Two?"
I knew you had a certain presence
about you. Ever since I started
interning here, I've come across some
really interesting pieces like,
well… there's a piece that isn't fully
preserved, and therefore isn't
very popular with our visitors, but
all of us here call it, 'The Portrait
of a Beauty." Let me show you.
It really looks like you. You can only
partially see her face, but the
resemblance to you is truly uncanny.
I guess it's true, doppelgangers
really do exist.
But what's even more amazing about this
portrait is that it's some sort of love
letter. Did you notice the poem on
the right of her? "By heaven."
And it's not just any kind of paper,
this is extremely valuable pure hanji.
For someone to paint this portrait
on such precious paper, and write a love
letter, it must've been an extraordinary
love. Or the end of a love that could
not be expressed.
Isn't that romantic?
My gift to you, my companion.
-Oh, the Grand Prince is coming.
-Clear the way! Away with you! Make way!
Why is the Grand Prince here? Quick, move
to the side.
What are they doing? He's the
Crown Prince's full brother.
Oh, my goodness, he's so handsome!
But what has he done?
-He wears a mask.
-I hear he's a real philanderer.
He seems to take great care of his
appearance.
What would you achieve by following him?
Would you run away together?
As I thought. You shall remain silent.
Bury it in your heart so you may
survive here.
Take this.
I am the one giving this to you,
not the Grand Prince. You can
survive here without needing help from
anybody.
I don't know…
How can anyone call that love?
To love in silence and never express it
to your beloved…
just makes your heart rot and turn to
stone.
How can that be considered love by
anyone?
SEOUL MUSEUM OF HISTORY
HISTORY EXHIBITION 1392-2026
Love… what a joke.
You never even once showed a sliver of
your heart.
Yet, you foolishly play with stones, and
clench your fists in silence.
Tell me, do you truly yearn for my
affection?
I do yearn for you. Screw the world and
everybody else. Let's let our hearts
flutter.
I wanna be your only one.
I will cease this. I refuse to continue
living… so foolishly.
GEONGUK HERBAL MEDICINE
Owner! I need you to give me medicinal
herbs. I need the rarest and most
expensive ones! Hurry up, please,
I need to go!
So, now, have you found a position for
Se-gye?
I have. Creating a position is
not the issue, I'm worried
about internal opposition. I'm sure
Se-gye would prefer to return to a
firm that welcomes him back. It would be
good optics.
Exactly what kind of plan do you have in
mind?
I have a position that needs the
right person.
I was thinking that you could put him in
charge of the US office. If he proves
his abilities and becomes an asset to
the firm, this will surely stop
any opposition.
I see.
Okay, I'll give it some thought.
-There's nothing in here. Look, there is
-What?
Only water. I don't see a single herb
inside this little bag.
It's not water, it's a herbal decoction.
If you want raw herbs in individual
portions like the old days, we don't sell
them like that anymore. It would be
a lot of trouble for you to decoct
them yourself.
Do you mean to say you have already
sorted the herbs into these bags? Wow! I
was wondering how my knees would
survive all that crouching to infuse
the herbs, portion by portion. The
world really has become more simple.
Thank you, sir!
Cha Se-gye, come straight over
after work. I have something to say.
Why be stingy with your heart?
If you save it, it turns to stone.
Yes. My plans have changed, so I won't
be able to make it this weekend.
Don't tell Seo-jun, I don't want
to let him down. Let me see how it goes,
and I'll let you know.
SECRETARY SEO
Mr. Choi, there's a new announcement
on the intranet…
I can't believe this!
Did you know about this?
There was a rumor, but no one knew.
This changes a lot of things.
I didn't know they were even talking
about this.
Mr. Choi needs to read this.
CHAIL PERSONNEL APPOINTMENT ANNOUNCEMENT
EFFECTIVE DATE: 01. 01. 2027
APPOINTMENT: (TRANSFER) BRANCH MANAGER, US
APPOINTEE: CHOI MUN-DO
IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE RESOLUTION
OF THE CHAIL BOARD OF DIRECTORS
WE HEREBY NOTIFY YOU
OF THE ABOVE CHANGE IN POSITION
OCTOBER 19, 2026
CHAIL CHAIRMAN, CHA DAL-SU
Mr. Cha, the nurse who was hospitalized
contacted us. She says she has something
important to tell you.
I might be late, but I'll definitely
be there.
What are you doing here at this hour?
You're such an idiot, I'm out of here.
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE OPENING
OF YOUR CLINIC, CHAIL E&amp;C CHOI MUN-DO
Now I realize just how desperately
you want the chairman position since you
have no issues stalking me like this.
Still… you shouldn't have used illegal
methods.
I'm so sorry, I shouldn't have done
what they asked me no matter how much
money they offered. I promise to pay for
what I've done, but please, you have to
help me.
So what? You think you've got me by the
throat now?
I know you sacrificed everything
for this, and I know how desperate
you are, but… didn't you think of
Seo-jun?
You're right. I had to put everything
on the line to get in this position.
And you? What have you sacrificed?
You screw up everything you touch,
and bully others with your status.
Do you think you deserve this?
Forget it. I'm done here.
-What are you doing?
-I have something to show you too.
What is this?
Why don't you ask her yourself? What sort
of things are there for a man
and a woman to do when they're alone
together?
Don't be ridiculous. What kind
of business could someone like you
have with her? You probably thought you
could blackmail me with these photos.
You seem to really trust her. Do you
know what kind of deal she and I made?
You seem to have made a miscalculation.
That's too bad. You think I'd get
involved with her? Really?
You think Uncle's gonna believe that?
He's not an idiot. He's still
heartbroken that his only son, who was
on top of the world, flushed his
life down the drain by getting involved
with the wrong woman. Can you imagine…
what he'd say about this girl?
I mean, you know better than anyone after
how Uncle treated your mother.
You little bastard, I should…
That's right. Never give someone
something they can use against you.
The more things you care about,
the weaker you become.
You drop out of the firm and I'll
forget about everything.
And of course, I'll make sure Uncle knows
nothing about this.
What a surprise. He said he'd be late.
Cha Se-gye. You're already here.
What were you doing out so late?
I had something to do.
GIFTING HEALTH
THROUGH CARE AFFECTION
I've had a headache all day from the
bomb you dropped on me, but you don't
seem to have a care in the world. How
depressing.
No, Cha Se-gye, that's not at all…
You just throw things out carelessly…
and treat me like a doormat, but
here I am, once again.
Crawling towards you.
I never did that. That is not why--
Is it because you don't have faith in me?
I hoped you wouldn't keep secrets
from me, but I hear you met with Choi
Mun-do. Why didn't you tell me?
Oh, I was going to--
He tells me he made a deal with you.
You should've told me.
Whatever it was, I could've done more
for you.
I thought I had proven myself and finally
earned your trust…
but I guess I was wrong. What more
do I have to do? What proof do you need
now to believe in me, and open
your heart.
If you truly don't feel the same way
about me, then just use me.
For you, I'll happily let myself be used.
Okay… Now, you're acting like
yourself again.
You said you'd be able to throw
everything away. If that's true, then
stop trying to be nice to me, or
pretending to worry about me. You need
to think about yourself. If you wanna be
cold with me, then do it right!
Stop playing around with my feelings.
Let go of me. Let go! Let go! Stop!
Let go! Let go! No!
Because of you, I'm losing my mind.
Whoever you are…
wherever you came from…
I believe you.
What?
Whatever you're gonna say, I believe you.
You have to trust me.
Forget all the assholes out there,
and just focus on me!
Please.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
We're done with our trial period?
Let's go on a date, Cha Se-gye.
Why now?
I'm going to give myself freely from
now on.
So, you're my sweet Seo-ri's new
boyfriend?
Please forgive me.
It looks like we're on the brink
of a regime change.
Mr. Cha has just entered HQ.
Do you think I'll back down without a
fight?
Have you seen the patient in Room 12?
Are you sure… you can handle this?
You lured and threatened a helpless old
lady?
Ms. Shin, you have nothing to lose.
I hate you being involved with Choi
Mun-do in any way!
Well, you're worse than him. You hurt me
more!
What I want is for Se-gye's wife to
have a lot to give.
Shin Seo-ri. Answer your damn phone!