[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] According to
an anonymous philosopher,
love can be best explained
through Science.
You see,
science has many branches.
It has many things to discover,
to analyze,
to solve,
just like love.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DAPHNE] Marla!
This is so bad!
Have you seen it?
What’s happening?
[NYX] No!
No!
[NYX CRYING]
No...
- No!
- [MARLA] Nyx?!
Nyx, what happened?
What’s wrong?
No... no!
Why?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] In science
there's a lot of uncertainties,
a lot of possible answers,
possible results.
And sometimes,
these results are
not what you wanted
or what you expect.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Even if you follow
the right procedure,
or right equation,
or formula...
it doesn’t guarantee you
the right conclusion.
[SCREAMS] Aah!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MURMURING]
[NYX] No!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MURMURING]
[MARLA] What’s worse is that
one failure can lead
to different scenarios,
different theories that make
science more complicated
than it already is.
[WARREN] Excuse me.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Marla, are you okay?
- Stop looking--
- No! Get away!
[SOBBING]
[WARREN] Turn off the screens!
Get out of my way!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA] But here’s the thing
about love...
Sure, we can compare it
to science.
But can we explain it
in its simplest form?
I highly doubt that.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
When an experiment fails
you have to review the steps
and figure out what went wrong.
At this point, that’s all
I can think about.
Where did I go wrong?
Let’s go back to the
beginning of the end.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Is this what turns you on?
Blindfolds, really?
Here I come...
You're really one of a kind.
Where are you?
Coming...
Make sure I'll be surprised.
[CHUCKLES]
Ta-da!
Wow...
You're so beautiful, Marla.
I want you to know...
I’m the luckiest man
in the world.
I've been waiting for this,
Marla.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Oh... Wow!
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Touch me gently...
Oh, are you okay?
Yeah...
For real?
Of course!
- Really?
- Yes! I’m so sure!
See, I'm so ready!
How can you be ready when you’re
several feet away from me?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Marla, we're so far apart.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Ah...
this is just...
you know, inertia.
I’m just...
really nervous.
Marla, if you're not ready,
it's okay.
No!
I’m ready!
I’m ready, I promise!
I just need to...
I just need to warm up.
Whoo! Okay!
I’m alive!
I’m alert!
I’m enthusiastic!
Okay.
Give it to me.
You're so adorable.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIGGLES]
I’m ticklish.
That tickles!
[GASPS]
[RAPID HEARTBEAT]
That tickled...
I'm not forcing you, am I?
If you're not ready,
you shouldn’t have gotten
my hopes up.
I'm sorry...
It’s not you...
it’s me?
Did the top of our batch
just use
“it’s not you, it’s me” on me?
It’s just...
I really imagined my
first time would be like...
how I would whip up
a synthesis of aspirin.
Huh?
Really? Synthesis of aspirin?
I was just hoping
that it would be...
special.
Magical.
You know...
I get you, Marla.
- Okay?
- Really?
I love you.
There are certain equations
that are hard to crack.
Do you know...
the Collatz Conjecture?
[WHIRRING]
Yes.
While deceptively
simple to state,
the Collatz Conjecture
hasn’t been solved
in over half a century.
Exactly.
That's why I'm trying
to solve it,
even if it takes me
another half a century.
[DREAMY MUSIC RESUMES]
That’s how much I love you.
I'm willing to wait for you.
Aww!
You know, that’s
the most beautiful thing
you’ve ever said to me.
[KISSES]
What do you want to do now?
I need to...
- [LAUGHS]
- [SCREAMS]
Stop!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS]
Can we be groupmates
for the science fair?
Um, that depends
on our ranks, right?
Marla,
where's your confidence in us?
We'll certainly be groupmates
because we’re the smartest
in our batch.
But again, that depends.
Although Cole and I are
talking about it.
Speaking of Cole...
So what happened last weekend?
Um...
Nothing much...
We just researched about JWST.
JWST?
Daphne?
JWST.
James Webb Space Telescope.
My goodness.
[SCOFFS]
Girl...
I know what the
James Webb Space Telescope is.
What I’m pointing at is...
what happened between
you and Cole last weekend?
I wanna know the details!
- [STALL DOOR OPENS]
- [TOILET FLUSHES]
[STALL DOOR SLAMS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WATER TURNS ON]
Sorry, Isobel, we didn't know
you were in there.
Yeah. You're peeing so quietly.
Are you on silent mode?
Funny.
Just take your time, and make
sure your hands are clean.
Do you need some hand alcohol?
I have some.
Your hands must be so dirty,
right?
Hm! Daphne...
You know what, Dessalyn
[SCOFFS]
It's Daphne.
Dessalyn.
That's your real name, right?
Because you're so fake
and pretentious.
[CHUCKLES]
Daphne is a far cry
from Dessalyn.
Maybe it's you who needs
to clean your name.
It stinks!
What if I beat your face in?!
Daphne!
We're in school, Daphne.
I'd like to see you try.
Would you like a black eye?
[CLAPS] Huh?
- Daphne! Stop.
- Let's square up.
- Daphne! Stop!
- What?!
Watch whose toes you step on.
Okay, let's calm down.
We're not trying
to pick a fight.
Just go.
We're lovers, not fighters.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[DOOR OPENS]
[SCOFFS]
I'd love to poke her eyes out!
She's so annoying!
Oh my god, yes, but...
Just-- you know...
Just don't mind her.
Isobel's just like that.
She's just...
really weird.
[MUSIC FADES]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- [ANT] What's up?
- Yo!
What's that?
The one you sent us.
Wow.
You're enjoying it
way too much, bro!
You fool.
Who wouldn't be surprised
by what you've just sent?
Just in case you're forgetting,
that's still my girlfriend.
- I know!
- Huh?
- Like I always tell you...
- What?
I think you can do better.
- Bro! Loosen up!
- What?!
It's too tight! It's too tight!
You're annoying!
I've told you a million times,
Nyx is one of a kind.
I'm not like you who
always ogles at other women!
Hey!
Let me tell you something, okay?
Number one,
I am loyal to Daphne.
- Loyal?
- Loyal.
Number two,
there is nothing wrong
with looking.
You're looking at
my girlfriend too, right?
- Of course!
- See?
But I'm just saying,
I have the best girlfriend, bro!
- [CHUCKLES]
- Besides...
what can I do
if my girlfriend's obsessed
with my muscles, right?
- See this?
- Stop.
Yo! Stop flexing your muscles
Do you see these, though?
Feel it. Come on!
Six years.
Come on, feel it.
Homie to homie.
Six years of hard work.
Well, that's nothing.
- Mine's harder.
- You need more protein.
So...
Did you follow the
tips I gave you?
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Mm... Not really.
What do you mean?
Ugh... We didn't do it, okay?
I wasn't ready.
How did Cole take it?
Well, I thought he was gonna be
really disappointed at first,
but he took it really well.
Girl, you're always
changing your mind.
- I thought you were ready?
- I thought so, too.
My God! I mean...
it's just so scary.
Like, imagine, I have
to be naked, completely naked,
in front of...
in front of somebody else.
Then he's gonna see everything.
Everything.
Every part of my body,
every inch of my body.
He's gonna see all
the ugly parts...
Everything. All my insecurities.
I just...
I just feel like
I'm being judged.
Marla, nobody's perfect.
I know we all have insecurities.
But look at you.
You're so beautiful,
just like me.
That's why we're best friends,
right?
But, oh well...
- good luck, then.
- Hm? Why?
- Why good luck?
- Huh? Nothing.
- Why?
- It's not important.
Come on, spit it out.
- Just spit it out.
- Okay, since you insist.
This is just hypothetical,
Marla.
Cole's been waiting for it,
right?
To be intimate with you.
I'm just...
worried for you, that's all.
Why the need to worry?
Marla, Cole is 18.
His testosterone is probably
on hyperdrive right now.
If he's not getting it from you,
he might get it elsewhere.
At least try to spice up
the relationship
if you're not yet ready.
There are so many ways!
Just be imaginative!
Oh!
Something like this.
Um, excuse me?
What are you doing?
Just wait.
Daphne, I swear to God.
Are you doing what
I think you're doing?
- Yes!
- So-- Someone might come in!
Daphne!
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh my god.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Daphne!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Are you seriously telling me
to send nudes to Cole?
[CMAERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Speaking of the devil...
I have the best girlfriend
in the world!
Makes me wild! Whoo!
- Dude, look at that.
- [ANT] Let me see.
- You see that? You see that?
- Mm.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Cole!
- Brother!
- My man!
What's up?
Why so serious?!
Are you okay?
I'm just looking at the
photos you sent.
Oh.
What's up, bro?
Ah...
Let me guess.
She wasn't ready again?
Sorry,
what are we talking about?
His girlfriend
isn't giving him what he wants.
Such a bummer, dude.
I understand you.
Well
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
Don't worry, bro,
Even I wasn't ready.
But I became ready
when I saw that Nyx was.
It's all about timing, bro.
How about this?
Think of her like a flower.
Marla's just waiting to bloom!
[LAUGHS]
Okay, Shakespeare.
[LAUGHING]
How's that, Cole?
Such a weakling!
I mean, it's unfair, dude!
You've seen my girlfriend naked,
but I haven't seen yours...
- neither has Ant.
It'll happen... soon.
[PHONES CHIME]
Who's the weakling now?
Yo!
[GIGGLES]
Is this who I think it is?
Obviously, that's not Marla.
Holy smokes!
Oh!
Bro, bro, bro.
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry!
I take that back!
You're my idol!
- Idol!
- She's so hot!
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
Okay, let's go to class.
Let's go to class!
Let's go.
Whoo!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Bloody-- !
- Oh! Harry Potter, is that you?
- Baby nugget!
Why are you so shocked?
It's just me, baby nugget.
- Hello, baby nugget.
- It's just me.
Where's my
good morning kisses...
- ...baby nug-nug?
- Good morning kiss?
Yes! Good morning kiss!
- Nug-nug!
- Okay.
[SMOOCHES] Good morning, baby.
How wholesome.
Are you my auntie?
- Do it like--
- Babe, my friends are here.
[ANT] We can't do it here.
If we do it right here,
right now,
I won't be able to stop.
[GUSHES] That's the goal!
- I can barely hold it in!
- [LESTER WHISTLES] Psst!
[LESTER] Lovebirds!
Get a room!
Hey, that is a good idea.
- Room? Baby nugget!
- I know a nice room. [CHUCKLES]
Let's just go to class.
I'm just kidding.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Ah, right. Let's go.
[NYX GIGGLES]
- Oh!
- Hey!
Are you blind?!
- I'm sorry.
- [APRIL HUFFS]
Well, since you're already here,
I was actually looking for you.
Me? Why?
[PLASTIC BAG RUSTLES]
What's this?
You are so predictable, Marla.
You see, everyone in school
thinks so highly of you
as if you're an angel.
Sweet Marla.
Most behaved.
Top of the batch!
[SCOFFS]
But I can see you
for who you truly are.
April, because you're
Cole's twin sister,
I will continue to respect you.
Aww!
Thank you.
But since I don't give a damn
about you,
then I will not continue
to respect you.
What have I ever done to you?
Genuinely.
I'd never done anything
to offend you.
As a matter of fact,
you're the one who did something
offensive to our batch.
Remember that?
You and your
main character syndrome...
Please!
If you're gonna hook up
in our house,
make sure to clean up after.
Pick up your own trash! You have
traces all over the crime scene.
Next time, make sure to
not leave any evidence.
I mean, you should know that.
You're the top student, right?
Okay?
Are you okay?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah.
Did you hear the conversation
I just had?
Well, I didn't mean to overhear.
Well, I guess you know
what they say.
Everybody hates you
when you're on top.
Hate is such a strong word.
You're Marla Briones.
How can we hate you?
You're a good role model.
Top student.
Most behaved.
And gold in conduct.
People keep saying that.
"Marla Briones,
most behaved,
gold in conduct,
blah blah blah."
Believe me,
it's a lot of pressure.
And you'd be surprised
by how many people hate me.
Well, I don't.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you for helping me.
- Hey, you dropped your...
- [MARLA GASPS IN HORROR]
- Sorry! I didn't know it's yo--
- No, no, no! It's okay!
It's clean! I promise!
[CHUCKLES] G-Good to know!
Looks like it smells good--
- N-Not that I smelled it...
- No, no, no. It's okay.
- Sorry again.
- Sorry, no. My bad. My fault.
Hi, babe. What's up?
[MARLA CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Is there a problem here?
No.
[MARLA] No, no.
No problem here.
Why are you talking to
my girlfriend, huh?
- Hey...
- Is it wrong to talk to her?
It is.
When we say it's wrong,
it's wrong.
- Hey, Les...
- [SCOFFS]
Relax.
I'm sure Warren here
was just about to go.
Right, Warren?
You're gonna go now?
- Sure!
- Okay.
- I'm gonna go now.
- [DAPHNE CHUCKLES]
- Okay, go.
- Sorry.
Bye!
- [NYX] Hey!
- [ANT] What a cocky jerk.
- [NYX] Shush.
- Let's go.
Come on, baby. Let's go.
[LESTER] Rock and roll!
Babe.
Is he bugging you?
No.
I don't want to see you
talking to him.
It makes me jealous.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe later. Um...
Let's go to class?
We're gonna be late.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I... Isobel.
For you.
I know that popcorn's
your favorite snack.
I also got you
this matcha latte.
It's from your favorite cafe
at the Commune.
Can you hear me?
Ah...
You're wearing earphones.
Let me try again. [SNIFFS]
Do you... want to...
study with me?
Group study?
Because I'm... having...
a hard time... in...
[LESTER] Larry!
My man!
- Hey.
- What's up, man? Hey?
- You look good.
- It's Earl.
Huh? Who's Earl?
Me. My name is Earl.
Since when? [CHUCKLES]
Anyway...
Where's the homework
I asked you to do?
Come on, let's go.
Alright!
If you keep this up, Pearl...
- we might just get along.
- It's Earl, without a P--
[LESTER] What?! Huh?!
Let me make it clear
to you, Pearl.
I can call you whatever I want.
Les...
- Les--
- Am I clear?!
- Lester.
- [DAPHNE] Les!
Dumbass!
[MOCKS A STAMMER]
[LAUGHS]
Good morning, class.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Chin up. Smile.
[LESTER SCOFFS,
CLEARS THROAT]
- [LESTER GROANS]
- [TEACHER] Alright.
First things first.
Your grades
for the first quarter
will be released today,
as well as the results
of your quarterly exams.
Now, obviously,
we're still in the top 20.
So, give yourselves
a round of applause.
[APPLAUSE]
[TEACHER] Yes, that is one hell
of an achievement,
especially for our school.
However, while we are
still in the Top 20,
there are some...
changes in the rankings.
Ms. Briones, you have
nothing to worry about,
because you are still top one.
[APPLAUSE]
[TEACHER]
Now, if you keep that up,
we may already have
our valedictorian.
But it's still
too early to tell.
Well, I guess, we shall see.
Projected on the screen
are your grades
for this quarter.
Coming in at second place
is Ms. Calaquian.
[APPLAUSE]
She is followed by Ms. Baldemor.
- Fourth, Ms. Rodriguez.
- [SQUEALS]
Nug-nug, I'm number four!
Are you proud of me?
Of course, you're proud of me.
I'm number four, nug-nug!
Congrats, nug-nug.
Okay.
And finishing with
top 5 is Mr. Javier.
[APPLAUSE]
- [STUDENT 1] Cole!
- [STUDENT 2] Congrats!
Now the rest of you can check
your grades
on your personal
online bulletins.
Alright?
Now...
Uh... Sir.
May I speak?
Um...
Sure, but make it quick.
- We have a class.
- Yes, sir. Thank you.
I just wanted to say...
that ranks are just
numbers, right?
What matters is that
we did our best.
And, hello? We're still
the cream of the crop!
And that's something that
should be celebrated.
Which is why I would like
to give a shout out
to someone very special...
Cole.
Thank you so much for always
believing in me,
for empowering me,
and for helping me be the best
version of myself.
Everyone, please give him
a round of applause.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Cole?
[INDISTINCT OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[MUSIC BECOMES DARK]
[THUD]
[ISOBEL EXHALES SHARPLY]
You like it rough.
Just the way I like it.
Isobel, please,
I'm not in the mood.
Because?
Do I need to give a reason?
I'm just not in the mood.
[SLAMS LOCKER]
I'm insulted by your rejection.
Do you want me
to remind you
how you begged for me
to give you a chance?
Do you want to beg again?
What's wrong?
Tell me.
Now!
I was surprised you
ranked second.
Me too!
Finally...
Finally someone agrees
with me.
I thought I was going to be
number one this time,
but that girlfriend of yours
is just lucky
that she has
a photographic memory.
But did she actually understand
what she was reading?
But wait...
What does my rank
have to do with this?
Are you jealous?
[SCOFFS]
Then you should've
studied harder.
Or you should've hired
a tutor.
[THUD]
[COLE BREATHING HEAVILY]
You're angry...
because two of your girlfriends
outsmarted you.
Did I hurt your ego?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Isobel...
I don't owe you
or anyone an explanation.
I don't give a damn
about your ranking.
Because even if you turn
the world upside down...
you'll never be
my number one.
- [COLE GRUNTS]
- [SLAMS LOCKER]
[COLE BREATHING HEAVILY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're never going to break up
with Marla...
won't you?
Maybe I could.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is that what you want?
You want this?
Only if you beat Marla
and rank first.
- Watch me.
- Okay.
Let's see if you can do it.
I can.
Call me when you're
done moping.
This sad boy energy
doesn't suit you.
- You look pathetic!
- [THUD]
[SMOOCHES]
Number five.
- [GRUNTS]
- [THUD]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Hey.
[MARLA] I've been looking
for you.
Can we talk?
Hey, guys.
Leave!
Let's go!
Come on, come on, come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
Thanks, guys. Study well.
- [MARLA] Are you mad?
- What do you think?
I begged you, remember?
Marla, this is the first time
I asked a favor from you, right?
Is it hard to make
a few mistakes on our exams?
It's not as if I asked you
to get a failing grade.
I was just asking for
a little consideration,
so I could be the top in our
class even just this quarter.
Just one quarter! So that my dad
won't get mad at me!
You know how he's like, right?
- But...
- What?
Cole, it's just that...
even if I got some of the
answers wrong,
you still wouldn't be
the top in our class.
So, you're saying
that I'm dumb?
- No. No.
- Is that what you're implying?
- No. It's not that.
- Is that it?
Then what?!
Hey. Hey.
You're a SOSH student.
No one here is dumb.
And no one is calling
you that.
But I admit I was scared
to give up my rank
because I have goals, too.
I want to graduate on top and
get a scholarship in Harvard.
We all have dreams, don't we?
Yes, we have dreams.
But why did you agree
to give way for me, Marla?
Why did you give me
false hopes?
Do you know what
would happen to me
if Daddy finds out that
the top four students
in our batch
are all women?
There's nothing wrong with that.
You don't understand, Marla,
because you already got
what you want.
I thought you loved me.
I do.
But your grades
are more important to you.
No.
Cole, I love you.
But you couldn't give way
for me.
You know I'm applying for
an internship at NASA, right?
My future depends on that!
You know that they'll only get
the top student
from each country and you
made my chances even lower!
What's the point
of this relationship, Marla?
If this is just how it is
for you,
we should rethink
about this relationship,
and if we even have
a future together.
[COLE EXHALES LOUDLY]
Cole, please.
Don't ambush me with a threat
of a breakup, please.
It's not a threat, Marla.
It feels like it.
So, what do you want me
to do?
Should I just blame myself?
Am I the one
at fault here, Marla?
When I get home,
Daddy would kill me.
I don't know how
you could make it up to me,
but please, Marla...
Please leave me alone.
Do you still love me?
Collatz Conjecture.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMAN RETCHES, COUGHS]
[WOMAN GROANS]
[WOMAN RETCHES]
Mommy?
Mommy, what happened?
Why is Mommy throwing up?
She was drinking when I picked
her up from the restaurant.
Mommy...
It's only eight in the evening
and you're already drunk.
They're all leaving me!
Who left you?
Henry!
Henry?
Ah Your boyfriend?
He just left me,
just like what your father
did to me.
Just like Blake...
Just like Anthony...
They're all the same.
People always abandon me!
Mom, that's not true.
I'm here for you.
I'm still here.
But you hate me.
[LAUGHS]
- No, of course not.
- Yes, you do.
You blame me for why
your father left us.
You just blame me
for everything.
It's not your fault that Dad
chose to go with his mistress.
And I never blamed you
for that.
Also, Mommy, why are you
doing this to yourself?
It's not even a month since
you've been dating...
What's his name again? Henry?
It's not even a month.
You weren't that devastated
when Dad left.
[SCOFFS]
It's not about how
long a relationship lasted.
You see...
You don't know anything
about relationships.
Do you even know how to
make a relationship work?
Are you even willing to...
sacrifice for love?
Do you have it in you to forgive
your cheating husband?
Do you even know what to give up
or to compromise
just to show how much
you love that person?
And Cole...
Do you think
he's the one?
Well, he may be cute,
but you know,
he's not all that.
[GROANS]
But he's my first love.
Huh?
Did you say something?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mommy, I promise
I won't leave you.
Okay?
Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Please open the door.
Okay.
Careful.
Head, head, head.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
And Cole...
Do you think
he's the one?
He may be cute,
but you know,
he's not all that.
If you're going
to hook up in our house,
make sure to clean up after!
If he's not getting it
with you,
he might be
getting it elsewhere.
I love you.
I'm willing to wait for you.
I'm ready to sacrifice
everything for you.
What's the point of
this relationship, Marla?
Please leave me alone.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[TRIPOD CLACKING, THUDS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[MARLA SCREAMS] Aah!
[MARLA SOBS]
Marla, are you okay?
- Stop looking!
- No! Get away!
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] So, we’re back
from where we started...
but why does it feel
like it’s ending?
[SOBS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
No, no, no...
- No...
- [DOOR SLAMS]
No! No! No!
Daphne, why would you
attack them?
Marla, if I attacked them,
they would be in the hospital
now! [HUFFS]
Didn't you hear what
those fools were saying?
What they were calling us?
Also, how were they able
to get tomatoes?
Tomatoes?
No one threw tomatoes.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Huh?
There were no tomatoes?
Uh... Um... [BREATHES HEAVILY]
I... I must be going crazy.
What happened?
Am I... am I dreaming?
Is this a bad dream?
Please wake me up...
Please wake me up!
[GROANING]
[PHONES RINGING]
[GASPING]
Nug-nug?
Nug-nug, what happened?
Weren't you the only one
I sent those pics to?
What happened? Why--
- Drop that damn phone!
- Hey!
Hey!
- Nug-nug!
- Hey!
Isobel!
Nug-nug! Nug-nug!
Hey! Give me that!
I need to talk to my Nug-nug!
Nug-nug!
It’s over.
It’s over...
This is crazy.
I’m going crazy...
I’m going crazy!
I won’t be able to face
my parents if they find out.
This is crazy.
This is crazy!
[GROANS] Argh! Damn it!
How did our photos get leaked?
And of all the students in SOSH,
why us?!
Why us?! [SOBS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wait
Our boyfriends
are the kings of SOSH.
Cole, Ant, and Lester.
That’s one thing
we have in common.
But why were you targeted too?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But Marla, how did our photos
get uploaded?
Did the...
the boys leak it?
[NYX] No
No.
Why would they do that?
Why would they leak them?
What would they gain from that?
And
my Nug-nug won’t do that.
[ISOBEL]
Say Nug-nug one more time,
and I’m gonna smack you!
Nug-nug! Nug-nug!
Give me that!
Nug-nug!
He’s gone?
[MARLA] You don’t have
a boyfriend, right?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Unless
[TENSE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Isobel, you bitch!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]