You patched things up
with him yet?
Sounds like he's cut you
out of his life.
Forget it.
You told me things can't go back
to the way they were.
"Guys, 'Between Us in
the Deep Forest' is blowing up."
"Y for Life: Review"
I completely lost my mind.
"Men on an untamed forest trek,"
"sparse steamy scenes,"
"just friendship
taking full center stage."
"I'm seven chapters in now"
"and the leads haven't kissed once."
But just one look between them
and I'm already gone.
The writing style is
full-on old school.
Like vintage novels
from the classic era.
Some words had me
doing double takes.
I looked them up
and got completely floored.
So deep. Actual tears.
Need that pleasure hit?
This book has it.
"Between Us in the Deep Forest"
is still free. Why wait?
Dive in before you have to
pay to read it.
Do it today.
Mabel, don't scroll yet.
I can't keep up.
Okay, okay.
What's "gaw-pon" (comprise) anyway?
Did Grandpa misspell it?
No, not "gaw-pon."
It reads "gop."
He didn't misspell it.
It's short for "prakob." (comprise)
Get it?
- Hmm?...Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Never heard that before.
Sure you have. It's in
the wai kru (teacher homage) chant.
(Sings in saraphanya melody)
Phu gop gerd bpra-yote suk-sa
Wow, old school.
Ahem.
Did you just call me old?
You lot live as long as I have,
then we'll talk.
You know these words
all come from my era?
Grandpa, everyone online is
hunting down Honey Cheese Pie now.
What on earth is Honey Cheese Pie?
Your pen name, Grandpa.
Ugh, that gives me a toothache.
Since when did I end up
with such a sugary name?
Since I posted your novel online.
What?
Honey Cheese Pie,
that's the pen name I gave you.
What?
It's a riff on Harn Chanprai.
Works, right?
Works for you maybe.
Next time ask first.
Come on, Grandpa.
You said anything was fine.
Heh...anything's fine?
How about from now on
you're Dog not Save?
Haha.
- Awoo.
Honey Cheese Pie is my name.
Awoo.
Celebrating 600,000 views.
- Cheers...
Here, want some snacks, kids?
This is amazing, Dad.
Truly befitting a great author.
You're like a dinosaur that
actually made it to the modern age.
- Wow.
- Is that a compliment?
It is. Absolutely.
Who'd bad-mouth my Dad, right?
Younger generations are
circling back to old things.
Like film cameras or flip phones.
Hmm?
Coming back into style.
Right, they call it
the nostalgia trend.
- Oh?
- Right, Save?
Something like that.
Eat a lot, everyone.
- Enjoy, enjoy.
- Yes.
Go on, kids.
Hey, this money comes from do...
what again?
- Donations.
- Right.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
Readers' support for the author.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
Wow, Dad, does that add up to much?
Not a lot, but...
not bad, right?
Enough for this party.
So what about
that paywall thing, Save?
Oh, it's too soon.
- The readership could drop.
- Hmm...
Maybe after 10 chapters.
Heh...Smart.
Sharp business mind.
He's got that from me.
Mm-hmm.
Grandpa, readers are already
asking to buy the book.
If you want a lump sum
to clear the debt fast,
just wrap the story up sooner.
Then you'll have to
work a bit harder.
Keep feeding me the details,
alright?
Of course.
Heh.
No time to waste.
- Cheers...
I'll join in.
- Thank you.
Can I join the toast too?
- Hurry, hurry.
- Come, come.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Together now.
- Let's toast, everyone.
- Quickly.
Ready. 1, 2, 3, cheers...
- Yay.
- Woo.
Ugh.
Why did I say that?
So you don't want my apology
or to be friends.
Mm-hmm.
"Where are you? Pheem said
you're heading to America."
Phi Save.
Hmm?
- Look here.
- What?
- Looks just like you.
- I'm not playing. Get out.
- Hey.
- Go. Out. Now.
Huh.
- "Messages Read."
- Hey.
Ugh.
"Golden Pen Award"
"Principal and interest:
12,508,649.75 baht."
"You're such a talented writer."
"I'll love this novel forever."
"It makes me
want to get up every morning."
"8"
"Sorry, wrong send."
Ugh.
"Email Inbox: Honey Cheese Pie"
Hey.
Grandpa.
Who is it?
- Grandpa.
- Oh.
- Hmm?
You're going viral with Gen Z.
Someone wants to interview you.
Who?
The Y for Life channel.
They're huge
with 200,000 followers.
Is that a good thing?
Very much so. Wow.
If people see a retired grandpa
writing BL novels,
- it'll go viral for sure.
- Heh.
Viral?
Because they find it funny
that some old guy is selling BL?
I'm sure it's not like that.
They'll admire you.
Well...
Do you think my longtime readers
can handle me
writing this kind of story now?
Oh-ho. Those old readers
must have dipped by now.
I mean...left this world.
Though my writer friends...
quite a few of them
are still kicking.
- Your men-only literary circle?
- Mm-hmm.
Don't worry about them.
I think, at their age,
they've probably moved on.
Seriously though, Grandpa,
do the interview.
They'll help promote the novel.
Alright, give it a shot.
Really, Grandpa?
Okay, I'll confirm right away.
- Is that okay?
- Go ahead.
Yeah, come in.
Wow.
Looking sharp, Grandpa.
Here, let me do that.
Back in the day,
I looked every bit the leading man
of a BL series today.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
Alright, done.
Grandpa, no need for that.
Not exactly a lot of hair.
Wait till you're old.
Then you'll know
this is a full head of hair.
Here, hold on.
Okay.
Hey.
Grandpa, the interviewer's
almost here.
Hey, Mart, do I look good?
Wow...my heart races
like when we first got together.
- Hmm. You look good too.
- Do I?
Whoo...look at you all dressed up.
- How do I look?
- Oh, wow.
- Wow, Mom.
- Heh.
Well, it's not every day
we have guests over.
Got to make them feel welcome.
Right. And Grandpa?
Getting ready upstairs.
Apparently, his last interview
was twenty years ago.
He's steadying himself.
- Oh.
- Heh.
Quite handsome.
Ho...ha...hoo...wha...
My inspiration, you ask?
I'd say it came from
my time in the military.
"Worachai,
Thailand Writers' Association"
Worachai, how have you been?
It's been a while.
I'm well, Sak. And you?
Can't complain.
Calling about the association,
I presume?
No. I'm calling to let you know
there's a new writer
who's been lifting your work.
Lifting my work?
What do you mean?
I'll send you the thread.
"People are drawing comparisons."
"Some passages in the novel
read suspiciously similar."
"But the most glaring case is..."
"Attention: Harn Chanprai,
someone has copied your work."
"There's a hunter character
named Sin."
"Same name, same personality traits"
"as the hunter Sin"
"in your novel
'Braving the Invincible.'"
"Several phrases are clearly lifted
straight from your book."
"The only difference is
it's more transgressive"
"than typical teen romance."
"Can this go to court?"
"Quality literature is dragged down
into something trashy."
This way, please. Right this way.
Welcome, welcome.
Come in, come in.
My grandmother.
Hello.
Come on in, welcome.
Here he is, Honey Cheese Pie,
author of "Between Us
and the Deep Forest."
Hello...
Uh...
Wow.
So this is the author?
From your writing, I didn't expect
you to be this young.
Well...
Yes. He's my grandson.
I trained him myself.
Oh, shall we start the interview?
Uh...
Could I use the bathroom first?
I'm a bit nervous.
Please, take your time.
I'll set up the equipment.
- Sure.
- Everyone, come on in.
Grandpa, come with me.
I'll go get some water.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Hmm?
Grandpa, why did you tell him
I wrote it?
Shh. Keep it down, he'll hear you.
- Dad.
- Shh.
Why did you say he wrote it?
Read this.
"...more transgressive than
typical teen romance."
If word got out that I wrote this,
my peers who look up to me
in the industry
would lose respect for me.
That's their problem.
You don't owe them that.
Easy for you to say, Save.
Over 40 years of writing,
everything I've achieved,
it was built on their support.
I can't stomach the thought
of being boycotted by people
I've been tied to all this time.
Save.
Help me out.
Okay, ready whenever you are.
Great.
Okay, get the camera set up.
Just a second on the camera...
- it'll keep the drama down.
- Excuse me.
I'm nervous.
Could my grandpa sit with me?
Oh, of course.
We're keeping it casual today.
Sure.
Come on in.
Let me just clip on your mic.
Sure.
Everyone, we're here today
with the hottest BL novelist
right now.
A fresh voice
with a truly unique style,
"Between Us in the Deep Forest."
Join us now, Honey Cheese Pie.
- Hello.
Tell us about yourself.
Sure. I'm Supawit Prasitphithaya,
or Save.
Pen name Honey Cheese Pie.
First question then.
How many novels have you penned?
Uh...
My first.
First? That's wild.
It reads like a masterpiece
honed over decades.
Uh...thanks.
Okay, next question.
Inspiration?
Why adventure in the jungle?
- Well...
- I used to be a soldier, you see.
Hard life. Day and night.
Dirt for a bed. Dust for a table.
Plenty of stories to tell.
See...
Ahem.
Anyway, what I mean is...
I told him stories
from my time in the service;
he must've liked them enough
to put them in the novel.
Oh, so you adapted his stories.
That's right.
He's actually a writer himself.
Pen name Harn Chanprai.
- Harn what, sorry?
- Chanprai.
Harn Chanprai.
Aw...Harn Chanprai, rings a bell.
So, Save, you are truly
a chip off the old block.
Very much so.
Um...that really is admirable
how a young man like you takes after
your grandpa's prose.
The sky's the limit for you.
Was it a good idea telling him
I'm the grandfather?
He'd just search the surname anyway.
He'd figure it out.
And now that we've lied to him,
won't it cause any damage?
It shouldn't...
- Hopefully.
- Hmm?
Anyway, just ignore
those troll comments.
They're not helping us pay our debt.
Hmm...Save. Those trolls...
They've been my comrades,
fighting alongside me...
from the very beginning
of my writing career.
You couldn't possibly fathom
what I carry as Harn Chanprai.
Okay.
Then Harn's grandson will carry on.
Right.
One interview and that's it.
Save.
Keep it smooth, will you?
Heh...I've got it.
But you, don't slip up again.
"Everyone, we're here today"
"with the hottest BL novelist
right now."
"A fresh voice
with a truly unique style,"
"'Between Us in the Deep Forest.'
Join us now, Honey Cheese Pie."
- "Hello."
- "Tell us about yourself."
"Sure. I'm Supawit Prasitphithaya,
or Save."
"Pen name Honey Cheese Pie."
"First question then."
"How many novels have you penned?"
"My first."
- Heading to the teachers' lounge?
- Since when do you write novels?
What novel?
You saw the interview, huh?
Answer me.
I just started. Just messing around.
Messing around?
You, writing a novel?
Well, I'm the grandson of a writer.
Must be DNA, right?
I read it.
There's no way you wrote that.
Your classwork in
Thai essays was horrendous.
If you can't be honest about this,
what can I trust you with?
Okay. Fine. I didn't write it.
Grandpa did.
He just didn't want to put himself
out there, so he had me do it.
Guy.
Wait up, Guy.
- Guy.
- Whoa. Oops.
Watch where you're going.
Sorry.
Anything hurt?
Khun (honorific) Sak, I had no idea
your grandson wrote it.
No worries, Khun Chai.
So what are people talking about
in that thread now?
The plagiarism talk has died down.
But people still compare
your work to your grandson's.
Don't let your grandson read it.
It'll just bring him down.
The comments are toxic.
Understood, Chai.
Thanks for keeping me in the loop.
Are you Phi Honey Cheese Pie?
Uh...yes.
My, my. More handsome in person
than in the clip.
Thanks, guys.
And now, slow new chapters, huh?
I'm dying to read more.
Uh...
I just...
got stuck a bit.
Hang in there.
Both of us are waiting.
Thank you.
Should be the next few days.
Beautiful.
Heh...So handsome.
Hey, you write novels now?
Yeah. What's wrong with that?
- Why didn't you tell us?
- Why would I?
Hey, I'm still mad at you guys for
lying about Guy going to America.
Oy...I just wanted
you two to make up.
So what's the novel called?
Honey Cheese Pie?
- Hey, you.
- Heh.
- Let me search it.
- Yeah, let's look it up.
Honey Cheese Pie.
- Haha.
- Heh.
Hey, don't tell anyone.
Hey.
Found it, right here.
Hey, don't tell a soul.
I'm outta here.
- Hey.
Grandpa.
Hmm?
- Hello.
- Yeah.
Grandpa, drop the next chapter soon.
The fans are clamoring for it.
Don't rush me.
Writing is a craft.
I don't churn out words
just to fill a quota. Never have.
See, I'm giving you
as much slack as I can.
Honestly, I'd want it
done this week.
This is a novel,
not instant noodles.
Don't ask for the impossible.
Ooy, they say if you sell the book
while it's still trending,
the numbers will
go through the roof.
Heh...normally, each book takes me
a couple of years to finish.
Well, that's not the game now.
It's a race.
Haha. Khun Save,
help me figure out, won't you?
How to finally get these
two characters to make up?
People are complaining
they've been sulking too long.
Well...
Afraid I can't help you.
I still can't get Guy to forgive me.
Then I guess I'm stumped;
the two of them in real life
can't even make up.
Hmm. Fair enough.
But readers are hooked right now.
If they wait too long,
they could go read something else.
Hmm?
Grandpa.
I want to read the next chapter.
Five more days.
Five days?
It's like forever, Grandpa.
You see how many people are asking?
Here are some comments.
Please don't abandon this story.
Come back and finish it.
I'm dying to read more.
It's been dragging on forever.
I give up. Time for something new.
Wait, who's that?
Sounds a little personal.
- It's me, Grandpa.
- Oh.
You'd better post soon.
Heh.
Sure. Posting soon.
Yay. I'll be waiting.
- Good.
- I'm off.
Save.
Save, come help me type.
Okay.
Huh.
You see this?
"Nunan: New chapter, a trainwreck.
Promotes male chauvinism now?"
"Young writer with this ideology?
So disappointed."
"Rakpleple: Real man wrote it."
"aomaom: Forget this.
No gender oppression."
Wow.
Huh.
Grandpa, I say it has to be fixed.
Partly my fault too.
Yesterday, I used a doc scanner app
to convert everything to text.
I fixed the typos
and didn't read it carefully.
How bad could it be?
Hmm. See. People are ranting
to Mom and Dad
and dragging you into it too.
Wait, can we take screenshots
and report them?
Easy, Phi Sorn.
What is wrong with people?
Trashing complete strangers.
How rude.
Back in my day,
someone with real expertise
would critique the work properly,
then publish it in
a reputable newspaper or magazine.
Fair and square.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
The internet gives everyone
a voice now.
But if you strip away the language,
the point they're making
isn't entirely wrong.
Like how? What did I write
that was out of line?
Mm-hmm.
Confess. Did you steal our supplies?
Ree.
You are quite beautiful, actually.
But you can't keep snarling
like a wild animal.
Raah. Grr.
Try being a little softer.
A little sweeter.
You'd be far more lovely.
Grr.
All that rage
must come from being hurt
by a bad man before.
Truly, it's sad.
Like I always say,
if you want to get to
her softer side,
just treat her right
like a real man should.
We mean you no harm.
You want food? Ask nicely.
We'll give it to you.
Let us take care of you, Mali.
It's a gentleman's duty
toward a woman.
See? What's wrong with that?
I wrote a man protecting a woman
because she is something beautiful
and worth cherishing.
Exactly.
And he didn't write
anything aggressive.
No forced kiss
or anything like that.
See? I knew you wouldn't get it.
It seems perfectly fine,
doesn't it?
But there's some
underlying gender bias here.
A few red flags.
Point one,
women today don't need men
to protect them.
Two, the female feral character
is written as savage and raw,
more beast than person.
Hmm?
And point three,
women don't have to be
girly and sweet all the time.
Hmm. When he puts it that way,
it does hold up.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
Snow, you read it. Any thoughts?
Why does a woman
have to start being nice
only after a man
treats her well?
Can't she be that way on her own?
Or maybe her temper has
nothing to do with the man?
I mean, men should be decent
to women regardless.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
And why must women be gentle
and men be strong?
Can't women be strong
and men be gentle?
Or just have both in one person?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
If I were Mali, Grandpa,
I'd carry a knife for self-defense.
Not get caught so easily.
Mm-hmm.
Snow, I know
there are strong, capable women
like you're describing.
But this character
thinks differently.
And that's exactly
what readers are questioning.
The character's view
or the author's.
Grandpa, it has to be fixed,
or they'll stop reading.
What? Phi Sorn didn't record
ten orders?
Yes, and we don't have
enough ingredients.
Looks like we'll have to
delay the delivery.
Okay, I'll handle it.
But...don't say anything to him.
Of course.
Why the long face?
Oh, nothing, Dad.
Just a small stock issue.
Tell me right now. What's going on?
Nothing at all. Really, nothing.
Don't lie to me. Out with it.
Uh, please don't tell her
I told you.
Khun Sorn failed to
write down ten orders.
Khun Mart is sorting it out
with the customers now.
Him again.
Always making a mess
for her to clean up.
Stop reading.
It'll just drag you down.
Those people don't know you
the way I do.
Don't let it get to you. Okay?
Hey, are you...worried about me?
No. I just saw you taking a beating.
Afraid you couldn't handle the fame.
Thanks.
Whatever's wrong, you fix it.
And tell your grandpa
I'm waiting to read more.
You're always so good to me.
So are we...good again?
Here's the deal.
I'll make it up to you by
being your errand boy for a day.
You said it yourself.
Mm-hmm.
- Get it fixed today.
- On it.
Every day, a new problem.
Typical men.
- True.
- Preach.
So annoying.
Look at this half-baked job.
Jingjai, come give us a hand.
One sec. I'm coming.
Okay, come on.
I'm here.
Alright. You hold that. And freeze.
Oh.
Who wrecked the arch?
Yesterday, Grandpa.
Pipe and his boys kicked
a ball right into it.
Hmm? They should fix it then.
I'll go get them.
No, Grandpa. It's fine.
We already had them
fix it yesterday.
But it wasn't sturdy at all
and fell apart again.
We'll just do it ourselves.
Hmm.
Can you do it?
Better get the boys over.
We've got it. Just watch.
Let's do it.
I'm so sorry, Khun Sai.
Yes.
I've talked to all the customers.
Heh...well done.
That's my Mart.
Be more careful. No more mistakes.
Of course, I owe you an apology
for all this trouble.
Without you around, I'd be lost.
Of course.
- Oh, Father.
- Yes?
I found a diary.
It's Grandma's
from when she was young.
It was in the storage room.
Have you ever seen it?
I have, but I never read it.
Then take a look.
She wrote about you too.
"Two years since Phi Sombat passed."
"What a shame that he never
got to see little Sak grow up."
"Our boy, at two years old,
is such a dear."
"Today my mind drifted back
to my teaching days."
"Even so, being a mother
fills my heart completely."
"The money from my sewing
and selling sweets"
"is just enough to raise my son."
"I grow tired at times.
I miss you."
"But little Sak's smile"
"always gets me back on my feet
to face another day."
Mom, you must be tired
raising me all on your own.
I never told you
while you could still hear me.
You were the strongest.
Hey, so how did it go?
Did people like the revisions?
They loved it, Grandpa.
They liked what you changed,
and appreciated your
listening to their feedback.
Most writers,
when they get criticized,
don't usually budge.
Hmm. That's a relief.
Heh.
Well done, Grandpa.
Where did you get the idea?
Confess. Did you steal our supplies?
I didn't steal anything.
I was going to trade for them.
Then why not just ask?
If you'd asked,
I would have given them freely.
You weren't here.
I needed to get food back home.
To feed my child.
A child. You have a child?
The idea came from
what's in front of me every day.
I just...never thought to look.
Save, I owe you an apology.
For all the heat
you took on my behalf.
Don't worry about it.
Actually, I have an idea to get
the characters back together.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
How?
Something heavy needs to
hit them first.
Mm-hmm.
When the worry runs deep enough,
when the bond is strong enough,
they'll always find their way back.
Ugh.
Ow.
Bear with it.
Sit down.
Ugh.
Just a little longer.
Mali's village is just ahead.
So you're talking to me again?
You're about to die
and you're still bringing this up?
If I go now,
at least I'll go in peace.
You are not dying. I won't allow it.
So are we...good again?
Mm-hmm.
Save.
Word is a major channel
wants to do another interview.
Yeah, the drama from last time
only got more people talking.
What should we do?
Go for it, Grandpa.
It'll push the novel even further.
The last interview alone
bumped the numbers way up.
And we only posted on a niche page.
Imagine what a major outlet
could do.
Alright, let's do it.
But...make this the last one.
I don't want to see you
lie to the press anymore.
Mm-hmm. This time they've sent
sample questions ahead.
Good. This time you rehearse.
Yes.
- They'll definitely ask you.
- Mm-hmm.
Is this novel hard to write?
- Hard.
- Because?
Because the...
relationship between the characters?
Like the way it has to
develop so gradually, right?
Mm-hmm.
The relationship
between Somporn and Anan
is like forest vines.
They cinch as they twine,
harder to let go.
That covers
all the scripted questions.
Mind if I throw in a few extra?
Uh, off-script too?
Is that alright?
Sure, go ahead.
Is the forest, in any shape or form,
a symbol of their relationship?
Uh, yes.
Excuse me. I need to
use the bathroom for a second.
Be back with the answer.
Oh, of course. Go right ahead.
I think the forest reflects
a kind of truth about life.
People get lost
because they can't see the way.
But sometimes it's us
who don't want to see the way.
Beautifully put, Save.
And how do you create
romantic scenes?
Reading them,
I can't stop smiling.
- Uh, excuse me.
- Yes.
Give me a minute to change
Great-grandma's diaper, okay?
Uh, sure.
- I'll be right back.
- Of course, go ahead.
I'm drawn to the small things.
Like sharing
the last bite of something.
Or leaning against each other
when the rain comes down.
Nothing too romantic.
But still makes your heart race.
And before these two characters
entered the forest,
what were their lives like?
Uh, that one
I can't answer just yet.
It might come up in the future.
It'd be a big spoiler
to reveal it now.
Oh, fair enough.
Well then,
let's talk a little about you.
Go right ahead.
"Between Us and the Forest,
Chapter 8"
You just mentioned some parts
came from real experience.
Can I ask a personal question?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Well...not quite at that stage yet.
We're just talking, really.
Right.
"Do you have a boyfriend?"
"Not quite at that stage yet."
"We're just talking, really."
"Could you bring him on?"
"I'll ask him."
"Phuri"
Hello.
Hello, sir. How are you?
How have you been?
Not great, actually.
Been hunched over
writing this novel.
The one you said wouldn't sell.
Well, sir.
I clearly had eyes but no vision.
I've read all the chapters so far.
It's a genuinely
remarkable BL novel.
So I'd like to be
the one to publish it.
Let me think it over first.
See, now. Several publishers have
already reached out,
and I haven't decided
who to go with yet.
- Heh.
- No rush, sir. Take your time.
Just keep me in mind, please.
Your novels have been
with our house for decades,
going back to my father's time.
I hope you'll consider us.
I'll give it some thought.
Is that everything?
Oh, one more thing, sir.
I caught the interview
on the Y for Life page.
Why did you let your grandson
front as the author?
Hey. I'm here, as promised.
Your personal errand boy
for the day. Whatever you need.
What's wrong?
Are you putting me on a show?
You saw the interview?
Using me to boost your fame,
is that it?
No. You've got it wrong.
Trust me, Save.
Bring your guy on together.
He's not my guy, sir.
And he's shy.
Not comfortable on camera.
But if you bring him on my show,
my views go up
and your novel's readership follows.
He wouldn't like to come on.
I already told them no.
You know, ever since I found out
about your novel,
I could piece together
why you kept coming around me.
I've read the novel
to the latest chapter.
That makeup scene,
you gave your grandfather
everything between us.
Guy.
I've been nothing
but decent to you.
Even after all you did to me.
But was any of it ever real?
Anything hurt?
Let me ask you this.
Do you like him?
If you're clear about
your feelings, don't deny them.
Don't hold back.
If I actually like a guy,
are you okay with that?
Mart, someone just called.
Save has been hit by a car.
- What?
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?