Here he is, Honey Cheese Pie,
author of "Between Us
and the Deep Forest."
Even after all you did to me.
But was any of it ever real?
"That sudden surge
through his chest"
"was unlike anything
he had ever known."
"He traced it back in his mind,"
"yet dreaded to feel it again."
"The more he pushed it away,
the more it clung."
"Anan's steady hands held Somporn
by the shoulders."
"Somporn trembled in that embrace,"
"as though a war
were being fought within him."
"Heat rose to his face,
slow as a gathering flame,"
"until Somporn could
no longer remain still."
Here you go.
Who'd you fight with?
Your mom or dad?
Or your grandpa?
No, I didn't fight with anyone.
It's just...
something I want to talk through.
About?
Uh...
Come on, out with it.
You've vented about your parents
to me plenty of times.
Have I judged you once?
It's just...
I kissed a guy.
And it felt... good.
No, wait. Not exactly good.
I mean...
I'm not sure if it means something.
Can you just give me an answer?
Why do you think I'd
have the answer for you?
Why are you asking me?
Come on, Uncle Sun. Seriously.
Because...you're gay, aren't you?
You knew?
Isn't it obvious?
It's not exactly a mystery.
And...people at home.
Do they know?
Hard to say. Probably.
They just don't bring it up.
But hold on.
Today's about me, not you.
I don't know who else to go to.
Can you help me figure this out?
Hmm, talk to me.
You remember my friend
I did the live stream with?
Guy, right?
Yeah.
You see. He liked me.
So I figured
I'd try things out with him.
And get some material
for grandpa's BL novel.
Why didn't you just
come to me for material?
I didn't want to
make you uncomfortable.
Wasn't sure how grandpa
would feel about it either.
So how'd it go?
It's just...strange.
Strange how?
My heart raced
whenever he came close.
When he smiled at me, I felt happy.
But when he didn't,
when he went cold,
my heart just sank.
I wanted to see him every day.
And when I did,
I panicked and wanted to run.
But I didn't want him
to disappear either.
Thought I was losing my mind.
From what I've heard, I think...
you already know how you feel.
Hey, let me ask you something.
Honest answer. Do you like him?
Look.
A man liking another man
isn't wrong,
nor is it something
to be ashamed of.
Centuries ago,
perhaps it was frowned upon,
shaped by the beliefs of their time.
But in any era, it was never wrong.
Save.
Answer yourself honestly.
Do you like him?
Yes.
I like Guy.
Good.
If you're clear about
your feelings, don't deny them.
Don't hold back.
You're young. You've got time
to figure yourself out.
Whatever you feel,
follow your heart.
But I already messed up.
How?
Well, now he thinks
I was using him for Grandpa's novel.
He doesn't trust me anymore.
Then you have to earn it back.
Make it clear.
Prove to him that
what you feel is real.
Go for it.
If he has feelings for you,
it won't be that hard.
By the way, I've been wondering.
Since Grandpa started
writing a BL novel,
has he...become more open
to those relationships?
I think so, yeah.
But it's still not easy
for someone of his generation.
Uncle Sun.
I'm sure Grandpa misses you.
That's just you.
No, I mean it.
If you can find time,
come home for dinner.
- Hi.
- You're back.
Still up, Grandpa?
Mm-hmm.
You got back later than usual.
I got worried.
Came down to wait for you.
- Grandpa.
- Hmm?
- Can I ask you something?
- Go ahead.
If I actually like a guy,
are you okay with that?
Why are you asking me that?
It's just...
I think...
I like Guy.
Don't play with me.
Because all this time,
you've always liked girls.
Can't things change?
Save, ask yourself first.
Are you simply confused?
Maybe it's just a passing feeling.
I thought so, at first.
But I'm sure now.
It's me who roped you into all this.
- So now you're...
- Do you still think...
a man liking another man is wrong?
Well, it's...not wrong.
But...it's not normal.
Not normal how?
Seems pretty normal to me.
I just want you to think it through.
So you don't regret it later.
Not as much as I'd regret
never even trying.
Would you be disappointed in me
if I were...
I would never be.
If anything is weighing
on me right now,
it's that I might not
be able to save Saeng Karun.
So...you don't hate me, do you?
You're my grandson.
How could I ever hate you?
You should've said that
to Uncle Sun too.
Don't bring Sun into this.
That's a different matter.
I went to see him.
How's he been lately?
He seems fine.
He said to tell you
he's thinking of you.
Thanks so much, Phuri.
I'll have my grandson look it over.
Of course. I've compiled the details
from every publisher for you.
Please look through it.
I would be glad to be
among those you consider.
Heh...we'll just see.
Oh, and that other thing.
Don't forget, please.
Of course, sir. I've got you.
We'll consider you
Save's ghost writer.
Completely under wraps.
You have my word.
Thank you. Much obliged.
Well, if there's nothing else,
I should get back to work.
Of course. So long, sir.
Hmm.
Hey, anybody?
This box on the floor.
I almost tripped over it.
- Surprise.
- Heh.
- Hehe.
What's going on?
Dad, this is the money
from selling sweets.
We've saved it up
for your debt, Father.
Oh, I can't take it.
You keep it for household expenses.
That is also taken care of.
This is on top of that.
Dad, we want to
save Saeng Karun too.
We're in this together.
You must take it, Father.
All of the kids helped us
with the live streams.
So everybody wants to help.
You all must've been
working so hard.
Dad, it's nothing. Easy.
Scorching fire or raging storm,
we'll get through it.
For our home.
I'm basically Superman
at this point.
Oh, boy...
Though I admit, I nearly
crashed and burned along the way.
Thank you. Both of you.
Yes, Father.
Count it and see how much is there.
Heh...must I count?
Just tell me.
I see our young man of the house
can't handle the thrill.
Let me show you then.
See, Dad, this stack is 5,000 baht.
5,000 baht.
And this one's another 5,000.
"If you're clear about
your feelings, don't deny them."
"Don't hold back."
"Whatever you feel,
follow your heart."
Hey.
We need to talk.
I admit
when I first came to you,
it was to get material
for the novel.
Well,
the orphanage
was about to be taken.
I wanted to help Grandpa
write the novel.
It was our only way.
But I knew...
it wasn't fair to you.
And it's no excuse for
using you like that.
You knew?
But when I tried things with you...
it felt real, Guy.
How can I be sure
this isn't just another scene
in the novel?
Perhaps it will be.
But I still like you.
These feelings
I have for you are real.
Just saying it doesn't make it true.
I can't bring myself to believe you.
Huh.
Dang it.
Serves you right, Save.
Perhaps it will be.
But I still like you.
Hey, Save.
- We watched your interview.
- Yeah.
So who is it you've been talking to?
Guys.
I want to make up with Guy.
Help me out.
Done. Say no more.
Thanks.
I want us to perform a short scene
from classic literature.
Form your own groups of five to six.
Then send a representative up
to draw your assignment.
Let's form your groups.
- You and me. Together, okay?
- Come on.
Like this, right?
- What?
- Okay, let's...
- Yeah.
You do it.
- This scene.
- Wow.
- No idea.
- You don't remember?
Not at all.
Alright, there are two lead roles.
Let's vote on who plays them.
Hands up for Guy
in one of the roles.
- Hey, me?
- Come on, you've got the chops.
- Me?
- Yep.
No way. I can't act.
Hey, respect democracy.
We all voted.
You voted without asking
if I want a role.
Too bad, we already picked you.
Alright, next. Hands up for Save
to play the other role.
Okay, so Guy and Save
are the leads. Done.
Did you all plan this?
No, man. You two are
the obvious choice.
- Yeah.
- Don't make it a thing.
- Sit down.
- Yeah.
So what's the story?
The story of Phra Aphai Mani.
The scene where
the hermit teaches Sut Sakorn.
- What?
So who plays who?
Hi, grandpa.
Mm-hmm.
What's wrong, stuck again?
Yeah. Good timing you're here.
You said you'd take me
to see the novel earnings.
Right, let's go.
We've the three latest chapters
behind a paywall.
Let's see how much we've made.
This...
- Whoa.
- What?
Look there, grandpa.
The text is tiny.
Just read it out to me.
Coin income: over 5,000 baht.
Donations...
Total's 15,000 baht.
Fifteen thousand.
How is that possible?
And that's just the first month.
We can actually
start paying off the debt.
At this rate, absolutely.
You're awesome, Grandpa.
Good thing I didn't quit.
Haha.
Told you you could do it.
- Grandpa.
- Mm-hmm.
I need a favor.
Go ahead.
Can you record
a verse chanting for me?
- For the school performance.
- Of course. I'm a master at that.
I won an award for it
back in school.
I remember you bragging about it.
Here.
Let me see.
This part...
Right here.
Starting here.
"Never put your trust in man."
Okay, I got that. I'll record it.
Make it sound good.
Full marks worthy.
Yeah, trust me.
And here...in exchange.
Help me post this.
New chapter.
- Sure thing.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, is this handwriting
or a treasure map?
Getting harder to read
every chapter.
Well, if you can't read,
just ask me.
Hello, sir.
Oh, hello, hello.
It's Guy.
- Hello, Mother.
- Oh, my...
Haven't seen you for so long.
I've missed you.
I missed you too.
Sorry about the live streams.
Oh, not at all.
Don't worry about it.
Save, Guy's here.
How are things?
Where are those guys?
They're coming.
I tagged them in the group.
"Pheem: Dude, I've got
food poisoning. Can't make it."
"Jang: I've got a fever."
"Ron: Guy, Save,
start rehearsing without us."
"I'm taking my mom to the doctor.
I'll get there if I can."
Did you all set this up?
I just wanted a chance
to be with you.
Fine. Rehearse and I'll dash out.
Okay.
So...have you eaten?
Here, eat first then.
You know this is my favorite?
I've been paying attention.
Oh, have you?
Mm-hmm. You even knew what I like.
That was me. You ever did the same?
I did. It's your favorite.
I remember.
Not hungry.
Let's just rehearse.
Can we go somewhere else?
Why?
I don't want to be alone with you.
I'm not gonna do anything.
I feel uneasy.
Alright.
Follow me.
So in this scene, I get pushed off
a cliff by the hermit.
- Who plays the hermit?
- Ron.
So I fall, and you come rescue me.
Do I still have to do
the verse chanting?
Because I'd butcher it.
I had Grandpa record it.
You just lip-sync to his voice.
Here.
Argh.
Help Sut Sakorn...
Ugh.
Heh.
And then, you...
ride a rainbow to save me.
Yours truly.
Is it a rainbow or a bird?
I looked it up.
Some people interpret
the hermit's rainbow
as a rainbow hawk.
Others say it's just a rainbow.
Couldn't decide,
so I combined them.
Ahem.
Then what?
And...
then he carries him up
to the mountaintop.
Argh.
Then you...have to...
Don't touch me.
You must pull me up.
I'm a sorcerer, though.
I'll cast a spell so you float,
rise up, and follow me.
Then the hermit
teaches Sut Sakorn.
Right where it says
"and he teaches."
Then lip-sync to
my grandpa's recording.
Memorize it too.
Move your lips properly.
Is that all?
Mm-hmm.
Pheem got us
a real good story, huh?
'And he teaches,
"Never put your trust in man."'
Sir.
May I have a word?
Of course.
I know you're still angry at Save.
So I wanted to apologize.
I'm the reason you two fought.
It's not your fault at all.
Hmm? How is it not my fault?
I was the one
who played right along with him.
I know you and Save were
trying to save this place.
Honestly, I've let go of
most of the anger already.
We've been friends a long time.
I can tell he genuinely feels bad.
Well, that's something.
But please don't tell him yet, sir.
I'll make him sweat a little
after what he put me through.
Ah! My lips are sealed.
Serves him right.
Thank you.
I'm rooting for your novel,
by the way.
Waiting for the next chapter.
And if you ever need ideas,
hit me up.
Much appreciated.
Oh, and if I do pay off the debt,
just know
you had a hand in that too.
Thanks, sir.
- Grandpa.
- Hmm?
Guy still doesn't forgive me.
You put him through a lot.
I know. But...
- What? Are you giving up?
- No.
- It's just...
- Then keep going.
Stay the course,
and one day, he'll come around.
I'm sure of it.
- Really?
- Of course.
- Heh.
- Sathu.
Keep at it.
Hmph.
Ding-ding.
Heh.
Oops, sorry, Phi Oui.
My hands slipped.
A broken thing
can't be a bad omen, right?
Hmm...it's nothing.
Let's pick it up
before someone gets hurt.
Right, right.
Dad, I'll take the money
to the bank for you.
Yeah, thanks.
(A tokay gecko tolls
like an ill omen.)
Mm...
(A tokay gecko tolls.)
"Account balance: 180,013"
Don't worry anymore, sir.
We'll save this house after all.
Hey, naked hermit.
Hey, hey. Whatchu doing?
Hey, hey. What's this?
Hey.
Oh...argh.
Argh.
Phra Chao Ta (elder sage), help me.
Help me...
Arr...
- Wu-hu.
- Here I come.
Arr.
Hmph.
'A sudden toll rang out,
distant and hollow,'
'Startled, he turned,
and looked around to find.'
'A hermit came, borne
on an arc of a rainbow,'
'And bore him up
toward the mountain height.'
'"Put not your trust in man,"
the hermit said,'
'Man's depths are dark,
beyond all measure.'
'Though vines may twist
in tangled turns and wind,'
'They are not so serpentine
as the human mind.'
'Of those who love,
but two are truly true:'
'A father's care,
a mother's love for you.'
'One refuge more remains
for you to keep:'
'Yourself, your faith,
your hands to see you through.'
'Keep friends close by,
and keep your foes at bay.'
'Choose well who stays
beside you, child, I say.'
'True wisdom stands above
all lesser knowledge,'
'And keeps you safe
from harm in every place.'
'Remember this well,
and go claim the staff.'
'It will serve you well
and guard your path.'
'When all was said, made clear
for him to see,'
'Gone was the hermit,
lost to mortal sight.'
- Wu-hu...
- Yay.
Fantastic.
Absolutely incredible.
Ahem.
Missed your cue out there, huh?
What cue?
You...held my hand for
a really long time.
Yeah, well. First time in a play.
Things get a little off, I guess.
Heh.
Okay.
Quit grinning.
I'm still mad at you.
Go ahead, stay mad.
I'm gonna win you back.
And I...
will not stop until you soften.
Like when you said
you'd keep chasing me.
So...
I've arranged a meeting
with the bank next week.
To sort out the debt
once and for all.
Oh, where are your glasses, Father?
Oh, that's why your face
looked strange. No glasses.
Too much trouble.
They get in the way.
But can you even see?
I'm not blind.
- The bank meeting's all set then.
- Sure.
Ah, teenagers. What can you do?
The hormones are in full chaos.
Hello?
Hi, this is
Thepnakhon Hospital calling.
Your nephew has been
in a car accident.
What?
Your nephew has been
in a car accident.
He needs emergency surgery
right away.
Uh, hello?
Please hold just a moment.
- Sorn.
- Hmm?
Mart, someone just called.
Save has been hit by a car.
- What?
Who? Who's calling, Father?
Hello? Hello?
They hung up.
Let me call Save.
He's not picking up.
Stay calm.
Could this be
one of those scam calls?
You know, that's a good point.
If Save actually got hit,
wouldn't he call me?
Hmm.
Here. Check it out.
Okay, Dad.
Save showed me an app
to check scam callers.
He installed it for Mart.
Enter this number.
Okay.
It's not flagged as a scam call.
Keep trying Save's number
until someone picks up.
Okay.
- Or maybe...
- Got it?
Not yet.
Hello?
Hello, this is the hospital calling.
Your nephew needs to be taken
into surgery immediately.
Tell me first. What's his name?
Grandpa, it's me, Save.
Help me, Grandpa. Ow.
Save.
- Grandpa, it's me, Save. Help.
- Save.
Sir, you must transfer
the surgery fees to us now.
If you don't, your nephew
won't be taken into surgery.
How much do you need?
The surgery fee is 180,000 baht.
Operating room: 50,000 baht.
Anesthesia: 20,000 baht.
Other medical costs: 50,000 baht.
Total: 300,000 baht.
Oh-ho. I don't have that much.
Then the surgery fee first.
So the doctor can operate in time.
Hold on...just a moment.
Stay on the line.
- Grandpa, it's me, Save. Help.
- Save.
- Ow, Grandpa.
- Help me, Grandpa.
- He has lost consciousness.
"Fund transferred: 180,000"
I sent it.
Which hospital is he at?
We're sorry. The number cannot
be reached at this time.
Hello?
Grandpa, Mom said
we got a scam call?
Grandpa.
No wonder. The gecko was chirping
since morning.
Yeah, that really was a bad omen.
It's because of you, Save.
You put that banking app
on his phone.
Dad, quiet down.
Grandpa's already stressed enough.
So what do we do now?
Where should we report this first?
Uh.
Contact the bank first.
Freeze his account,
then file a police report.
"Balance: 13 baht."
Went to the police
just to get lectured.
I know scammers are
all over the news.
But we all make mistakes, don't we?
Exactly. Who would've known
AI can fake voices now?
From now on,
just hang up on unknown callers.
Don't even answer.
If it sounds real,
check with someone else first.
Don't click on any suspicious links.
Okay, Dad?
If they want personal information,
never give it out.
And never transfer money to anyone.
Understood, Dad?
It's alright, Grandpa.
Anyone can make mistakes.
I owe you all an apology too.
I lost the money
you worked so hard for.
It's fine, Father.
Money can be earned back.
It's okay, Grandpa.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
'"Put not your trust in man,"
the hermit said,'
'Man's depths are dark,
beyond all measure.'
His voice was nice,
so I set it as my ringtone.
Grandpa.
Don't overthink it, Grandpa.
You did it quickly because
you were so worried about me.
I am...touched by that.
Next month, there'll be
new money coming in anyway.
You silly old fool.
Everyone, keep a close eye
on Grandpa, okay?
Okay, Phi Sorn.
I'm worried about him too.
He must be crushed.
Mm-hmm.
He just put that money together.
And it vanished just like that.
These scammers are truly rotten.
When will they get rid of them?
Okay, Phi Mart. Keep me posted.
Mm-hmm.
Are you dropping by tomorrow?
If I show up, it'll only
make him feel worse.
Please look after him.
Will do.
"Mom: Missed calls."
Oh?
Sleeping in Grandpa's room?
Mm-hmm. We couldn't leave him
alone tonight.
Oh, Snow.
I want to stay with Grandpa.
He needs some comforting.
Dad, we're coming in.
Sleep tight, Dad.
Save, get some sleep.
Come on, go to sleep.
Where'd you get it from?
My boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
You can't go very far
with grades like that.
I got bad grades just like you.
Snow.
You know, Dad?
I never wanted to stay here
because of you.
If the patient refuses surgery,
there's a real chance of
permanent blindness.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?