No matter how I think about it,
there's only one way.
NO MORE GAMBLING!
The prosecutor.
- Let's take her out.
- But, boss.
Going after a prosecutor
will make things worse.
- Damn, I knew he'd be trouble.
- Get your best men ready.
So they can do the job
when the time is right.
HILLSIDE CAFE
Yes, she's arrived.
She just went into the Hillside Cafe.
Hillside Cafe?
Come on, pick up.
This is driving me crazy.
Taxi!
Wait!
The Passenger Ship Spy Case,
the Kwon Soon-bok Case
and the suicide in March.
Han Gyeong-wook and Yoo In-gu
are definitely linked to these.
That ship that sank ten years ago.
I was on that ship.
And I know everything about the incident
you're so curious about.
Could Gang Beom-ryong
be the one to solve this puzzle?
Get him out of here.
Prosecutor Gang.
About what you asked last time.
I think I have an answer for you.
Is now a good time?
Oh.
I see.
Yes, have a seat.
Actually, it's a bit too loud in here.
Come with me.
Huh?
Hey, grab her!
Hey, open the door! Open up!
How could you let her get away?
- Why are you calling on a regular phone?
- Hey, Ho-myeong.
It's an emergency.
Get over here right now.
What are you talking about? I can't.
- I'm at a show.
- It's Yoo In-gu's crew.
- They're coming to take out Gang.
- What?
- Where are you?
- I'm on Yeongseon Island.
- Prosecutor Gang is on Yeongseon Island?
- Yeah.
Prosecutor Gang
provoked Yoo In-gu,
and now that crazy son of a bitch...
Look, there's no time to explain.
Just get over here, fast!
You must be kidding me.
If you just stay put,
Prosecutor Gang will die, you idiot.
If we lose her now, it's all over.
Damn it.
Ram her!
- I can't.
- Just do it!
Just one more...
Just hit her!
What are you doing, you idiot?
Step on it already!
Why won't it stop?
Where do these bastards
think they're going?
- Why can't you get past her?
- Damn it.
Shit.
Ram her!
Harder!
Hey! What the hell?
YOU CAN LEAVE DEAD, NEVER ALIVE!
Thank you.
LOSE LAND, LOSE HOME, END UP IN DEBT.
YOU CAN LEAVE DEAD, NEVER ALIVE!
Jesus Christ!
It's a ghost.
Hey, wait.
I think I saw a ghost.
The ghost of a young woman.
You get scared so easily.
What kind of job could be
in a place like this?
Look. She's taking us there to be sold.
I can hear you, you know?
This place used to be packed with people.
- But everyone got chased out.
- But why?
Hey, we're here.
- Just get over here.
- Unbelievable.
They barged in and trashed the place
just to catch one woman.
Where did those people go?
I don't know.
They just sped off in their car.
- Which way did they go?
- That way, toward the main road.
Why is Jeong Ho-myeong here?
Gang Beom-ryong.
Why did he show up?
And at a time like this?
Looked like he was looking for
some thugs and a woman.
Is it Prosecutor Gang?
I wonder if Ma Gong-bok
had a different idea.
That means he came to meet
Prosecutor Gang too.
This isn't the time
to worry about Gang Beom-ryong.
My priority is Gang.
Anyway, there's no way that guy knows me.
- For now...
- Play it cool.
Why the hell are you here?
- This isn't a coincidence, is it?
- You.
Do you know who I am?
- What the hell is this?
- Tell me. How did you know?
Are you just playing dumb,
or are you really that clueless?
Anyway, I don't have time to fool around.
Get out of the way.
You were looking for
Prosecutor Gang, right?
Hurry up and tell me what's going on.
She's in danger right now.
What the hell?
You're tailing her, aren't you?
I need to see her too. Let's go together.
What?
Are you crazy? Get out.
Hey, you think I want to be doing this?
If I'd brought my own car...
- Think this is a taxi?
- I'll pay you well.
You don't even know where she went.
Are you saying you know?
Hold on.
Seriously, where did she go?
- Yes, boss.
- Hey, Gong-bok.
Can you pull some CCTV footage now?
Right now?
Hold on, the CCTV footage from where?
The Hillside Cafe in Nakwon-ri.
Pull the footage from 30 minutes ago.
Look for suspicious vehicles leaving.
- Vehicles?
- Trace their route and contact me. Hurry.
- What's going on?
- No time to explain.
- Just text it to me.
- But...
I'm so damn busy as is.
YEONGSEON ISLAND, NAKWON-RO
HANMAEUM SOCIAL DANCE
Come in.
Aren't you coming in?
Come on, get in.
Just a moment.
Come on up.
This first floor used to be a supermarket,
and the second was cheap single rooms.
Why is he staring?
Hey, there.
Jesus.
Hey.
This is either a pyramid scheme or a cult.
- Let's get out of here.
- Hey, come on. Lee would never.
Aren't you coming up?
Hey. Can you just tell us now?
What exactly is this place?
You can think of it as
a temporary shelter.
A temporary shelter?
Everyone in there
is in the same boat as you are.
They lost their homes to Heaven Capital
and were thrown onto the street overnight.
Our Dance Club set this place up
to help people like them.
- It's just temporary.
- Wait, a place like this...
...was set up by a Dance Club?
We used to have a few members
in our Dance Club
who had family problems.
- Come on up.
- Okay.
SEVERAL VEHICLES GOT INTO A CAR CHASE
AND HEADED TOWARDS YEONGSEON RIVER
Make your choice.
Trying to take credit
for what Ma Gong-bok sent?
You know Gong-bok, too?
You think I wouldn't notice
pathetic thugs like you?
- Are you sure he checked properly?
- You don't have time to be doubting me.
You said Prosecutor Gang's in danger.
HILLSIDE CAFE
My family's threatening to disown me
for losing our family burial ground.
- What am I to do?
- Well, why did you sign off on it?
You try dealing with them!
Could you stand up to them
when they threaten you?
Shut it!
Back in my day,
I didn't even blink if I got stabbed.
How dare you?
- Mr. Park, we're here.
- Yeah.
Anyway, you have to keep your promise
about getting the family burial ground.
Where is everyone?
Why do I always get stuck with this?
The others all had plans, you know.
And you're the best at this.
They start all this,
then leave me to clean up the mess...
And who are they?
Why'd you bring these stragglers?
I told you about him.
Manager Bong from my company.
Say hello.
This is Mr. Park Chun-sik.
He's in charge of this shelter.
Ah, the boss.
Pleasure to meet you.
My name is Bong Je-sun.
Ah.
The poor guy who lost his house and job
because of his nephew?
Did they tell you what this place is?
- And what you have to do?
- I was told it's a temporary shelter.
That's a nice way of putting it.
We feed and house people
who lost their homes to those thugs.
You won't find a charity case
bigger than this.
And not a single cent from the government.
I'm working myself to the bone
trying to run this place.
And my joints are killing me.
Well, you're doing a good thing.
Right, a good thing.
But do you think I should be
doing it all by myself?
So while you're staying here,
you can help with cleaning, maintenance,
and a little cooking.
- So, it's a kind of...
- You're asking him to be a slave.
What? A slave?
Don't be ridiculous.
We provide room and board.
We'll even pay you a little.
And we're trying to get people's
illegally seized homes back.
Where else will you find
a perfect job like this?
Can we get our homes back?
Well, the number of victims
keeps increasing,
so we're trying to come up with
a plan ourselves.
Hey, you're not actually buying this,
are you?
They're just trying to use you!
- Seriously!
- Hey, who's this little punk?
Hey, old man.
I get that my uncle looks
like an easy target.
You probably think you can
take advantage of him.
He may be, but I'm no pushover. Got it?
Let's go.
Go where?
You want to stay in a dump like this?
- Have some pride.
- What? A dump?
- A dump? This little punk...
- Stop it. What are you doing?
Okay. All right.
We don't need a punk like you.
As far as I can tell?
You're a lost cause.
You couldn't do the job right anyway.
"Punk?"
Old man.
Do you know me?
Hey, Heo Nam-il.
Why are you being so rude?
Uncle, didn't you hear
that old man insulting me?
You're being insulting.
You called this place a dump.
Apologize right now.
Why should I apologize?
You think that's right?
What about this one?
I'm not going to live like a slave
in a dump like this.
You can stay.
Calm down.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
He's not normally like that.
I don't know what's gotten into him.
I'll go get him.
Man, that hurts.
Hey, Heo Nam-il!
Unbelievable.
They don't look alike at all.
Is he really his uncle?
SEVERAL VEHICLES GOT INTO A CAR CHASE
AND HEADED TOWARDS YEONGSEON RIVER
Earlier, at the cafe.
Those thugs work for Yoo In-gu, right?
Why is that bastard Yoo In-gu after Gang?
You know why, don't you?
Even if I knew,
you think I'd tell a punk like you?
A punk like me?
The enemy who ruined my operation.
The stalker on my tail for a decade.
A Hwasan Sect gangster pretending
to be a convenience store owner.
You...
- You knew all along.
- Stop acting like my buddy.
I could easily toss you off this car.
What did you say?
What happened here?
A car fell into the river.
Could it be Gang?
Hold on.
That bastard.
He's one of Yoo In-gu's men.
What's he doing here now?
Could they have already gotten her?
Hey! Wait!
Hey! Where are you going?
Hey, stop! I'm coming with you!
Nam-il.
- Nam-il!
- What?
You can't just leave like this.
- Let's go back. I'll talk to them.
- Go by yourself.
I'm going to a friend's.
Don't you know thugs are chasing us?
Yeah, and why would that be?
They've already taken our house.
It's because you beat their guys up.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
Whose fault is it that we're in this mess?
This is my fault?
Who else?
You're always getting into trouble.
You've been held back two years!
And you even lost the house.
When are you going to grow up?
Then pretend I don't exist!
After all, we're not even related.
Nam-il! Seriously.
Hey.
- Are you really leaving?
- Think I enjoy calling you Uncle?
I felt sorry you had no memory
and nowhere to go.
So I was playing family with you.
And Grandpa's house?
It's not your house, but mine.
So stop meddling
and promising you'll get it back.
From now on,
let's just go our separate ways.
Okay?
- Hey, did you find him?
- We were one step behind.
Prosecutor Gang's car crashed
into the Yeongseon River.
It looks like she was
being chased by Yoo In-gu.
You're saying she's dead?
Don't know yet.
They're recovering the vehicle.
Where are you? Let's meet.
No, no.
No, Ho-myeong. Then you should just...
You should just go back.
What are you saying?
Didn't you say you were with your family?
Go back to them now.
I can't go back now.
I have to see if Gang is alive.
They're just pulling up the car now.
It'll take all day to know.
I'll tap into the police radio,
so you hurry back.
The show's already over. It's too late.
Hey, man.
The longer you drag out a fight,
the worse it's going to be.
We haven't even found Gang.
You want to lose your wife too?
All right.
- Call me if anything happens.
- Got it.
- Grandpa. There's someone over there.
- Where?
- Over there!
- Oh, dear.
Go on, hurry!
What on earth?
Miss, wake up.
Can you hear me?
Grandpa, that's not a woman.
He's a man. Look!
Je-sun?
I...
don't remember.
You really don't remember anything?
Your age, your name, your parents.
Nothing?
No. I don't know.
- You don't have a mom and dad either?
- I don't know.
- I don't know if I do.
- If you really don't...
- do you want to be part of our family?
- Family?
I don't just let anyone in,
but I'll make an exception for you.
You can't be my grandpa or dad.
What about my uncle?
Uncle?
An uncle.
- What would an uncle do?
- You have to play with me.
All the time.
You're my uncle now, okay?
Uncle, play with me.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
BONG JE-SUN, 215 DOYANG-RO, CHUNCHEON
Uncle, are you bored?
If you're so bored,
you can help me with this.
Don't let go.
- First time on a two-wheeler?
- Yeah.
I won't let go.
Where are you right now?
Huh?
Hey!
Are you okay? Hey!
Oh, no.
Hey!
Can you hear me?
You're okay now. You're alive.
- I'll call 911 for you.
- Don't call anyone.
Hey!
Oh, gosh.
Jeez.
Don't go out of your way to get yelled at.
Give up on him.
With a nephew like that,
would he be any different?
I'm telling you, he's not like that.
He's not picking up.
Mi-kyung.
Didn't you say you had a date today?
I don't know. Don't ask.
Looks to me like you got rejected.
I thought the guy was totally into you.
I don't know, okay?
I may have been rejected in person,
but I've never been ghosted.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Damn it.
O-ran.
Weren't you seeing a show
with your family?
We already saw the show.
I was just dropping Ji-woo off at home.
Already?
Weren't you going somewhere nice after?
Don't ask.
Jeez, things are pretty tense
over here too.
Oh, by the way, Ye-ji,
did the person you were bringing show up?
Is he going to work here?
About that.
He's not answering his phone right now.
She looks pretty hurt.
Shouldn't we take her to a hospital?
Oh, no. No hospital.
No police, no 911.
She kept saying that the whole way here.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Usually, only people trying
to evade the law
go around saying you can't call the cops.
Oh, my! So she's a criminal?
No.
- I think she's a prosecutor.
- What?
- She's a prosecutor.
- Oh, my!
She said not to call anyone.
This wasn't a simple accident.
In that case,
let's just wait until she wakes up.
If she's weird when she wakes up,
Mi-kyung can take care of her.
Yeah, let's do that.
Hey.
- Bong Je-sun, right?
- Yes.
I see you left your nephew.
I guess you decided to work
in this dump, huh?
Well, it's not like I abandoned him.
As for the job...
- I'd like to give it a shot.
- All right.
Let's start right away.
Don't think about getting any sleep.
You'll stay here and keep an eye on her.
When she wakes up,
you contact us all immediately.
Got it?
Uh, by myself?
Of course!
You brought her,
so you're responsible for her.
She better not end up a corpse
in my building.
Is that clear?
Grandpa surrenders!
Please just spare my life!
Oh, no!
Hey, it's Daddy.
- Daddy!
- Ji-woo!
I'm sorry I came so late!
- It's okay.
- Did you like the show?
- Yes.
- Hey.
- Just getting home?
- Yes.
Daddy, check out my new mask.
- Isn't it cool?
- Wow, it's so cool.
- Daddy.
- Yeah?
Did you beat the bad guys?
Yes.
- But where's Mom?
- She dropped off Ji-woo and went out.
- Where to?
- I don't know. She was furious.
She said she needed to
blow off some steam.
It's okay. Mom will understand.
I'm sorry. I have no excuse, really.
No, I'm sure you do.
Go on.
I'll decide if I'll forgive you
after I hear it.
One of my army buddies
is a guy named Tae-sik.
He came to visit Yeongseon Island
and got into a car accident.
He was panicking and thinking
if he knew anyone on Yeongseon Island.
And I came to mind.
So what could I do?
I couldn't just ignore a friend.
So I helped him sort out the accident.
And before I knew it,
it had gotten this late.
I see.
So your friend just happened to be here.
- And he got into an accident.
- Yeah.
Well, I guess you had no choice.
- Right? You understand, right?
- Yeah, of course.
But I didn't know you had army buddies.
I mean, I didn't see a single one
of your friends at our wedding.
So I thought you had none.
Of course I have friends.
He was just too busy back then.
He called me.
He said sorry he couldn't come.
Uh-huh.
But remember when I asked you before?
You told me you were exempt
from military service.
- I did?
- Yes.
What's with you?
You keep leaving the shop,
you forget to pick up Ji-woo.
It's like your mind is somewhere else.
Even today.
Lying to me about what you were up to.
What are you hiding from me?
- Are you seeing someone else?
- No.
Then what is it? Tell me.
Stop lying and just be honest.
It's not like that.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
It's always the same with you.
If you want to live like that,
just get out.
Yeah. You should just get out.
Let's take some time apart.
What did you say?
So, what...
Are you saying I should move out?
What about the shop?
And what about Ji-woo?
The shop will be fine without you,
and I can take care of Ji-woo.
It's your choice.
Either be honest with me...
or get kicked out right now.
- Why are you here so early?
- Gong-bok.
Why were you asking about the CCTV?
Is something up?
Tell me something.
Have you been keeping tabs
on Jeong Ho-myeong?
Jeong... Oh, yeah. Jeong Ho-myeong.
Did you notice anything suspicious?
For instance,
did he seem to know who we were?
Not at all.
The guy has never even seen my face.
I told you.
That I would forget everything.
I had completely forgotten about it.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Well, that's a relief.
It's just...
I thought I saw him out there.
Oh, is that right?
Well, he lives in the neighborhood,
so maybe you just bumped into him.
I'm gonna head in.
Okay.
What's gotten into him?
When did he get so smart?
NO CALLER ID
- Yes, sir.
- Right. So how'd it go?
With Prosecutor Gang.
- The meeting went well.
- She say anything?
She said she'd look into your case.
That's it? There was nothing else?
Anything at all?
I'm sorry, boss.
No, it's fine. Rome wasn't built in a day.
What matters is what comes next.
I'm counting on you.
You know what I mean, right?
Yes. I'll do my best, no matter what.
Is something wrong?
You should've told me
if you couldn't make it.
Hey, is everything okay?
So...
I'm still at the cafe
in front of the theater.
Please call me when you get this.
I'll be waiting.
OFFICER PARK MI-KYUNG
Here's the thing about love.
It always comes without warning.
On a day you least expect,
in an ordinary, passing moment...
It quietly sits down right beside you.
And because it always begins like that...
you may even discover a side of yourself
you never knew existed.
Here's our first song.
"Rebirth" by Yoon Jong-shin.
- Good night.
- You too.
See you.
This is no time to fool around.
- Hey, did you know?
- What?
A police precinct moved in nearby.
Lately, the cops on the night shift
have been coming to the store a lot.
Damn, why did those bastards
have to move here?
What do we do?
At this rate,
we might not find our merchandise.
Damn, it's not like I can put up
a sign that says "No Cops."
Just wait. Every cop I see,
I'm just gonna...
Beat them up?
I'm gonna be a total asshole to them.
I'll make them never want
to come near the store.
Aren't you going to ring me up?
Damn it.
Can you check me out?
Excuse me, where is the microwave?
Over there.
Thank you.
That'll be 1,600 won.
One's for you.
It's just a little something
to say thank you.
I'll be here often.
How am I supposed to take this?
I got kicked out.
Why?
I've been watching
the scene of Gang's accident.
The Yeongseon River's current
is very strong.
It'll take a while to pull the car out
and to recover the body.
Think she's dead?
No clue.
We'll just have to keep searching
and hope for the best.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, man.
This is nothing.
Take it easy.
You're not getting any younger.
And maybe tone down
the street vendor disguise.
Hey.
It's not like I can just sit
in an office in a suit.
Intel doesn't find itself.
Besides, what's wrong with this?
I gather intel and make a living.
It's the best.
Nothing beats it.
You really never change.
Don't you ever get tired?
What, are you tired?
I've been in Yeongseon for a while.
It's been ten years already.
Time flies, doesn't it?
When I first came here ten years ago?
I thought...
I'd be done with the operation in no time.
But that damn Bulgae.
I searched and searched,
but there was no sign of him.
And the receiver was dead silent.
He has a strange accent,
and he's just a bit shorter than me.
His face...
Do you know
how many tourists like that we get?
Seriously.
May I take a look inside?
Mind your own business.
Get out or I'll call the police.
ORAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
DELIVERY RIDER WANTED
- Delivery!
- Hey.
- Hi.
- The room at the end.
Okay.
Delivery!
ORAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
The whole idea...
...was that I could investigate
more freely...
...as a delivery guy.
You're not quite what we're looking for.
I'm afraid we can't hire you.
Who is that?
He's here for the interview, but he's...
- Well, he's a little on the older side.
- Hired!
- But...
- He's hired.
You're hired.
I'm back.
- Oh, well done.
- You must be freezing.
Not really.
- Here you go. Enjoy your meal.
- Oh my, were you cold?
No, not really.
Hey, stop what you're doing
and make the deliveries.
We agreed I wouldn't.
You're starting today.
And Ho-myeong, you can wait tables.
- No, I'm fine.
- I can't have you catching a cold.
But I have a cold too.
Be safe out there.
But the operation...
...kept taking turns I didn't expect.
This is tough, isn't it? Let me help.
I was hired to be a delivery driver,
wasn't I?
- Why do you have me doing work inside?
- Oh, about that.
It's because you're so good at your job.
You've been promoted.
Promoted.
- Promoted?
- Yes.
Promoted.
- Are you crying?
- No, it's...
It's the onions.
Ugh, my eyes are stinging.
No, don't rub them with your hands.
Hold still. Let me...
Hold on. Oh, goodness.
Ho-myeong.
Your eyes are beautiful.
I guess I should peel some more onions.
These onions, huh?
Ah, wait. I can't.
This isn't right. Hold on.
No, we can't do this.
Life, operations...
You never know what'll happen next.
Who would've thought
ten years would fly by?
That's why I told you not to get married,
but you went and did it anyway.
- You regret it now?
- Who says I regret it?
I have never once regretted
marrying O-ran.
Then what's the problem?
It's just...
I've been a little...
worried.
About what?
I'm worried that the next ten years
might just fly by in a flash too.
What with menopause and all that,
she's getting weaker by the day.
Ji-woo is still just in kindergarten.
Our income isn't stable.
When I first had a family,
I was just so happy.
I felt like I could do anything.
But these days,
seeing how fast time is going by...
It's terrifying.
I wonder if I'll be able to
take care of my family properly.
I'm losing my confidence.
Watching you mope like this,
I know exactly what's wrong.
It's because you're getting old.
Hey, who isn't anxious
about the future at our age?
- You feel that way too?
- Of course.
I'm no exception.
You just live with it.
Just think that you've only lived
half your life.
And just keep dealing with
what's in front of you.
You'll get through it.
And another thing.
Don't try to shoulder the burden yourself.
This operation isn't going well.
And with what happened to O-ran,
you're struggling mentally, too.
That's why as we get older,
we have to rely on each other
to get through life together.
Honestly, have you learned nothing?
Which brings me to my point.
Why don't we stop
doing this operation as a duo?
What do you say we recruit a new member?
Who?
Do you still have contacts at the agency?
No, why look so far?
He's right under our noses.
He wants to take down
Han Gyeong-wook and Yoo In-gu.
He wants it just as badly as we do.
Your rival from ten years ago.
Someone who can take a hell of a beating.
What about Gang Beom-ryong?
- That's ridiculous. Are you drunk?
- I'm not drunk, man.
What I said went in one ear
and out the other, huh?
Listen, man.
I'm a National Intelligence Service agent,
for God's sake.
How can I team up with a thug?
Hey, Ho-myeong.
Let's just face facts.
You're about to turn 50.
You're getting old.
Remember the other day?
When you went to see
Yoo In-gu by yourself?
Back in the day,
think you would've failed against them?
You can't just charge in alone
like you used to.
It won't work anymore.
Listen, that time...
I mean...
I feel bad enough as it is.
Why'd you have to bring up my age?
- Welcome back, boss!
- Yeah.
- Any word from Detective Kim?
- Still recovering the vehicle.
Once the body's found,
it'll be ruled an accidental death.
That damn Detective Kim is so slow.
- Kang-sik.
- Yes, sir.
You need to see that bloated corpse
with your own two eyes.
Understood.
Kang-sik, we're almost there.
Find Martial Arts Master,
and it's smooth sailing.
Wait, boss.
About that Martial Arts Master.
I can't find him anywhere.
I can only track his phone to cell towers,
so it's not helping.
- So you're giving up?
- No, I have to find him. It's just...
We should prepare for the possibility
we don't find him in time.
- See? Now you're using your brain.
- Huh?
You're right. We need a backup plan.
Double our men on the day of the deal.
There's strength in numbers.
What's he going to do when we swarm him?
But a large group will tip off Chief Han.
- That's why you said to keep it small.
- Then we'll just use new faces.
- New faces?
- There's up-and-comers in Yeongseon.
You must know some.
Get them ready for the job.
Our own guys got their asses kicked.
What good will they be?
They can serve as kindling
for the Ingu Sect's fire, can't they?
It must be hard to get things done
when it's freezing out.
Thank you.
But it looks like
there hasn't been much progress.
- Right?
- Progress? Are you kidding?
- It's a fool's errand.
- A fool's errand? Why's that?
The current in the Yeongseon River
is really strong.
Anyone who falls in gets swept away.
They don't just stay there.
They didn't find a body in the car.
Probably got washed up
somewhere around Nakwon Beach.
- Nakwon Beach?
- I'm telling you.
If she washed up over there,
she might've even survived.
I've seen people fall from here
and walk away without a scratch.
But they won't listen to me
no matter what I say.
That's how public officials are.
So frustrating.
Keep pulling!
Nakwon Beach.
Jesus Christ!
-You're awake.
-Who are you?
- Wait!
Wait, it's me, prosecutor lady.
- How do you know my job?
- You don't remember?
- It's me.
- Who are you?
I'm the one who saved you
on the beach yesterday.
- I carried you here on my back.
- Yesterday?
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Hey.
Wait, you shouldn't get up yet.
Just a moment.
There we go.
Hold on.
Just a moment.
Let me check your temperature. Hold on.
You're at 37.8 degrees.
It's gone down a bit.
Just a moment.
Since you fell into the sea yesterday,
you need to keep warm.
Hold on.
Okay. There you go.
You might feel fine,
but your fever could suddenly spike.
But, wait.
- Hold on, let me get you some water.
- No. Wait a minute.
- Yes?
- I remember you saving me.
But where am I?
- This doesn't seem like a hospital.
- Oh, here?
A temporary...
- ...shelter.
- Shelter?
Man, that Martial Arts Master
or whatever must be pretty scary.
But don't you think you're overdoing it?
He had a crazed look in his eyes.
I think he'll cause trouble again.
The prosecutor was taken care of, right?
Yes, once we recover the body,
it'll be ruled as an accidental death.
If it weren't for this.
It even has In-gu's voice on it.
It's foolproof.
Okay, good job. Good work.
Listen.
If this gets to the police,
I'll be arrested too.
- Mr. Geum.
- Yes?
I want President Yoo
to complete the drug deal safely.
Don't worry, man.
I won't turn this over to the police.
Never, not at all.
Wait.
What do you need this for then?
I'll have to figure that out as we go.
You sure are curious.
Listen, Mr. Geum.
You just focus on one thing.
Rebuilding the Ingu Sect
to be the Kang-sik Sect.
Let's get the ball rolling. Okay?
Yes. I'll make the preparations.
- Okay.
- Oh, one more thing.
Mr. Geum is one ambitious man.
All right then.
He'll make it big in no time.
- Wait, that one's not expired yet.
- Oh. Right.
It's not like you to make such a mistake.
Did something happen yesterday
with the CCTV footage?
Yesterday, I met Jeong Ho-myeong.
You met Jeong Ho-myeong?
Right.
But that guy didn't just know me.
He knows a lot about you, too.
Did he?
- He said he knew me?
- Yeah.
And not just our faces.
He even knows why we came
to Yeongseon Island ten years ago.
He knew about us, inside and out.
Okay, look.
- There's something I need to tell you.
- Go on.
SPECIAL THANKS TO KWON YUL
Listen up, I'm about to make you
an offer you can't refuse.
You're getting old.
You can't do anything by yourself anymore.
I accept your offer.
-Move.
-Out of my way!
That bastard Yoo In-gu is dealing drugs?
- Let's focus on our deal.
- You don't remember anything?
- I have no idea.
- Did you find out who she is?
Mi-kyung is interested in me too.
Should I just lock him up?
- She'll probably just tear it.
- We don't work for you.
- It's over.
- We face them head-on.
- Are you sure you can take them down?
- I'll find a way.