MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
I checked everywhere,
but no CCTV cameras
cover the rooftop at all.
But one from the next-door building
might capture a small part of it.
Can you explain and show me?
Of course.
The quality is terrible though.
-You can barely make anything out.
-Okay.
-Let's see.
-Yes, sir.
This is it.
-Can you zoom in?
-Yes.
What if someone was here?
What if someone pushed him off?
What brings you here?
Isn't it chaotic at the ERPB?
It's more chaotic in my mind.
I'm wondering
why you came back to this school,
reported bullying as soon as you arrived,
and are doing this now.
Have you done your homework?
Oh, sorry.
I sounded like a salesperson.
If you know what's going on,
I can tell you everything.
I know you want the ERPB gone.
And why would that be?
Probably because of this.
Heart Pills most recently.
Butterfly Pills two years ago.
What are they now?
Diamond.
I guess you don't have any proof.
Otherwise, you'd have called the police
or arrested me.
But here you are, chatting away with me.
You and Ms. Choi
were made for each other.
You're so alike, sticking your nose
in other people's business.
I wonder if you'll share the same fate.
Hey.
Why are you here?
I said I'm not coming to school.
You punk.
Did you expect me to just say,
"Okay, sure, take care"?
That wouldn't do.
Hey, wait. Come here.
Every time you skip school,
you're injured like this.
Oh, that looks pretty bad.
-Let me put some cream on it.
-I'm fine.
Just stay still.
Let's see this side.
I don't know what you've been up to,
but do it at school.
It's the safest place, okay?
The safest place? Since when?
It's not just me.
Lots of teachers
are trying to make it safe.
We'll make school a safe place. I promise.
Here, promise.
That's how you break a finger.
You little punk.
Fine, don't come. I won't either.
I'll follow you around forever.
You think I'm bluffing?
You know what my boyfriend calls me?
Flypaper.
Once I catch you, I never let go.
I'm coming to pick you up
tomorrow morning. Got it?
Hey, Gyu-cheol. Good morning.
Hey, come on. Breakfast…
Gyu-cheol.
Wait. Oh, come on.
-Cho Gyu-cheol.
-Yes?
I'm his homeroom teacher.
You're students, right?
-Put that out.
-Fucking hell.
Gyu-cheol, come on.
-Let's go.
-See you.
-Don't look.
-We'll call you.
Hey, what the hell are you thinking?
The Samgeori guys who came at you
are now after your ass.
Are you seeing that bitch, Choi Ga-yun?
Do you know what Ms. Choi made me realize?
The school is full of people.
So? What about it?
Imagine they were all customers.
-Get inside.
-Nice.
It'd be easy to dodge the cops
and move the product back and forth.
Best of all,
we'd get hundreds of new customers
every year.
Oh man, it's cold.
Ms. Choi.
Gyu-cheol.
You're in uniform.
I figured I'd come to school properly now.
Hey, that's a great decision.
That's a good boy.
I won't touch your hair
since you have your own style.
You haven't eaten, have you?
Want to grab some gimbap?
I BELIEVE IN YOU, GYU-CHEOL!
If she'd just turned a blind eye
back then,
you two would be married by now.
Right?
What's that for?
You're not gonna hit me, are you?
You shouldn't do that.
There's already a stir
about excessive punishment.
If you hit me now,
it'd be a real personal vendetta.
So don't make a move.
If you don't do anything,
nothing will happen--
I'm sorry, Inspector.
I was wrong.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry, Inspector.
Please spare me.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Please spare me just this once.
Please. I'm sorry!
TEACH YOU A LESSON
I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry, Inspector.
Please spare me.
This is exactly
what I was concerned about.
Only a few days ago,
excessive punishment
drove Lee Chi-ho to attempt suicide.
Now, Cho Gyu-cheol, doing well at school,
has been assaulted.
Why do you think this happened?
The ERPB went to Jinwon High,
targeting Cho Gyu-cheol from the start.
They went there for personal revenge,
looking for an excuse to harass him.
In the end,
it was Lee Chi-ho who was sacrificed.
I won't stand by and allow such cruelty.
I will see to it that the ERPB,
fueled by personal revenge, is dismantled.
With opinion polls
showing that more than 50% of the public
support disbanding the ERPB,
the president
is under considerable pressure
during the lame-duck period of his term.
Despite strong resistance
from the opposition party,
the president
has so far kept the ERPB in place.
-But his approval rating is at 20%.
-Hello?
To navigate this
and bring his term to a steady close…
I'll come see you now.
It's the ERPB!
What are you doing here?
The ERPB shouldn't come
to schools anymore.
We're neither potential criminals
nor targets of personal revenge.
I'm here to investigate Lee Chi-ho's case.
Why would the ERPB investigate
when they caused
Chi-ho to end up like that?
Do you really think
you can conduct a fair investigation?
The ERPB's duties will be suspended
until the investigation
into the student's suicide attempt
at Jinwon High School
is concluded.
Accordingly,
the duties of the ERPB inspectors
will be suspended.
DEPUTY DIRECTOR BONG GEUN-DAE
ERPB
Hey.
Everything is set.
When do we start selling?
Now that the ERPB's out of the way,
we can get started.
First, send samples
to each school's main dealer.
Have them drum up business with those.
Tell them
once a school hits over 100 customers,
we'll start the drop for real.
We'll need a shitload of runners.
Just us isn't enough.
Schools aren't just full of customers.
They've got runners too.
And they're all minors.
No one suspects students.
And even if they get caught,
they'll get out right away.
Best of all,
they're disposable.
I flip sneakers with this guy
for some pocket money.
But there are so many scams
that people want to check them out
in person.
All you have to do is deliver them.
Okay.
Hey.
Oh, hello.
SOYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
They're the right ones.
Yeah, it checks out.
Here.
How was it? Easy, right?
Wanna do it again?
Can I?
If you do, that would be great.
-Hello.
-You're here.
-Gyu-cheol.
-Hey.
You're here.
Go on.
Thanks. Can't wait to wear them.
It's called biodiversity.
There's genetic diversity,
species diversity,
ecosystem diversity…
Jin-hyeok and Ju-won, focus.
Traits within the same species
are determined by genetic information.
So what do we call the part of DNA
that stores this information?
We call it genes.
We're in the middle of class.
What's with everyone today?
Let's all focus.
-Looks good.
-Right?
Hey, is this art class or what?
You're going all out with the brushes.
You don't need this, do you?
You're so pretty with a petite face.
So jealous.
Thanks, but I used to have a big face
like you two.
-Sorry. I actually just lost some weight.
-Really?
What kind of diet was it?
I took pills.
They're hard to get.
Try them, and if they work, let me know.
-Thanks.
-You sure I can have these?
-Yeah.
-This is crazy.
Pitch done.
I need more samples. Please send them.
Oh, ma'am. I--
Oh, Seong-gu.
Seong-jun was in a motorcycle accident.
I have to go to the hospital,
so tell the class to self-study.
Seong-jun got badly hurt
in a motorcycle accident.
Our teacher's gone to the hospital.
Holy shit!
Seong-jun's been delivering like crazy
and actually bought a bike.
Fuck, really? Let me see.
-Let me see.
-What is it? Show me too.
-Get lost.
-Hey, wait.
-I'm a fucking genius.
-Why?
We can just take over
that punk Seong-jun's routes. Right?
Right?
-True.
-We're pros.
Doesn't it feel off in school lately?
More kids are absent or leaving early,
and everyone seems kind of distracted.
I'm so scared of kids these days.
When the ERPB was around,
I didn't exactly feel respected,
but I did feel protected.
It feels like we're back
to how things used to be.
LOOKING FOR ADHD MEDS
OK, CAN DO
NEED BEAUTY PILLS
Wow, fucking hell.
We have about 17 schools in Seoul alone,
with roughly 100 orders from each.
Looks like
all that sample-pushing paid off.
Let's start selling for real today.
Then should I blast it out
on Telegram right now?
CHO GYU-CHEOL
DROP IT ONCE PAID
Can I go to the nurse's office?
Ma'am, I've got a terrible headache too.
Ma'am, I'm really sorry,
but my stomach hurts so much. Excuse me.
Ma'am.
Well, my grandma is really sick,
so I've got to rush home now.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Damn it.
Hey, I'm coming too.
Hey, Seong-gu.
I saved one for you.
Here.
Inspector Na Hwa-jin,
please call me when you see this.
I'll be at the convenience store
by my school.
Hi, Seong-gu.
I'm at the convenience store now.
I'm sorry, Inspector.
Something urgent came up at home.
I just remembered
and came home straight away.
Oh, really?
Is everything okay?
Yes, everything's fine.
Yes.
You fucking asshole.
Tell them to drop the product
and send a photo to the customers.
As for him…
He's a good kid.
It's a shame.
SOYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
You must've been very surprised.
Inspector Na Hwa-jin set up
this operation in secret.
So beating up Cho Gyu-cheol
was also part of your plan?
To get conclusive evidence,
Cho Gyu-cheol had to make a move himself.
The ERPB had to be gone
for that to happen, like he wanted.
Of course, I'll take full responsibility
for my actions
once this is all over.
I'll take responsibility too.
My father runs a small training center.
I can work there. Don't worry.
Oh, Minister.
Thank you for all your hard work
on the ERPB over the past two years.
Save it.
I'll also take--
I said save it.
You move like one team, don't you?
I'll be the one taking responsibility.
So you guys
just go ahead as planned.
Take care, sir.
Well…
Then should we request backup first?
How about asking the police
for their cooperation?
It'd be tough for the police
without evidence.
Besides, they'd be reluctant
to enter the school.
It's fine.
If it doesn't work, we'll make it work.
The three of us are enough.
We'll just work nonstop.
Im Han-rim.
What makes you think it's just us three?
I'm Choi Gang-seok from the ERPB.
I know better than anyone
how hard you work
to care for your students every day,
in place of their parents.
So it is with much regret
that I must share such difficult news
once again.
We have confirmed
that a new type of designer drug
is being distributed
among middle and high school students
in Seoul.
If this drug continues to spread
among students,
schools… will suffer irreversible damage,
and the students
will bear
the full weight of the consequences.
I sincerely ask the teachers
who are watching this video.
Please cooperate with the ERPB
one more time
for the sake of our children.
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
Time and again,
we have relied on your sacrifices.
For that, I am sorry
and ashamed.
I WILL NOT FORGET
YOUR KINDNESS
SAVE CLASSROOMS
SAVE TEACHERS
SCHOOL IS STILL A STRUGGLE
MS. CHOI! I MISS YOU
I MISS YOUR SMILE SO MUCH
YOUR WISHES WILL NOT BE FORGOTTEN
WE WILL HONOR THEM
I agree with the ERPB
that school must be the safest place.
I would like to cooperate
with their request.
Here.
By the way,
what about other teachers?
No one else has contacted us yet.
I see.
We collected these
from each of our schools.
I know it couldn't have been easy.
Thank you for coming.
But this drug…
What if it's already circulating
in schools?
Please don't worry about that.
That will never happen.
Right?
Yes.
-Oh, there.
-He's out.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Oh, hold on.
Here it is.
Come here.
All good?
-Good luck.
-Okay.
It's a vitamin and a diet pill.
A double win for us.
-Does this mean we'll be like Yu-ri?
-Of course.
We'll lose at least 5 kg.
-It's them.
-Oh, they're out.
Get ready.
What should we do?
When they come out this way,
hit me on the head.
-Okay, a slap.
-No.
-What? A slap?
-Hey.
-No, on the head.
Hey.
-I'm sorry.
-You little shit.
Going somewhere?
-Come here.
-Go. Run.
If you don't have any cash…
Yes.
-Give me something valuable, like a phone.
-Yes.
Or a watch!
Or at least some vitamin C.
I have some.
-You do?
-Yes, I've got some here.
Vitamin C!
-Here.
-Here you go.
This is all we have.
I'll tail that student at the front,
over there.
I'll take the one with the brown backpack.
What about the rest?
Don't worry.
I've called in backup
from kids who used to be experts
at shaking people down.
Huh?
Yes, we've collected all the samples.
We'll move on to the next step.
-I'll send them the orders on Telegram.
-Okay.
LOOKING FOR ADHD MEDS
HOW MUCH?
LOOKING FOR HEADACHE SUPPLEMENTS
Recently classified
as a temporary controlled substance,
this new designer drug
has been circulating among students
in place of Heart Pills.
These pills were discovered
on school grounds by teachers
and handed over to the ERPB.
As a result
of tracing the distribution route,
the suspect has been identified
as Cho Gyu-cheol of Jinwon High School.
Accordingly, as of this moment,
the suspension of ERPB's duties
has been lifted,
and inspectors
will also resume active duty.
-Hey, put this on me.
-Oh, come on.
Okay.
The suspect has been identified
as Cho Gyu-cheol of Jinwon High School.
Hey, it's the ERPB.
For God's sake. Give it here.
Hey, be careful.
Inspector, this is the only one
that's closed.
Don't open it!
Hold your breath!
Are you okay?
Hey, looks like they actually opened it.
Hey, did you get a good taste?
Fucking good, right?
Tell me if you need more!
-Hey!
-You fucking asshole!
-What, dumbass?
-Idiot, you can't catch us.
I'll go catch them.
Fucking idiots. Come on, let's go.
You know what?
I can fly.
What?
Im Han-rim, ready for high-rise descent.
-Jump!
-Hey, Im Han-rim.
What the fuck?
-Fuck.
-Goddamn it.
My back.
Damn it.
Fucking hell.
Damn, my back.
Im Han-rim, are you okay?
Hey, Im Han-rim!
I've got this. You go ahead, sir.
Okay.
-Oh man, my head.
-Fuck.
For God's sake.
I'll take care of Inspector Im.
You go ahead.
Go on, hurry.
-Okay, good.
-Thought I was a fucking goner.
This bitch is goddamn crazy.
Are you okay?
Damn it.
Depending on your attitude,
I can be an angel or a devil.
Now I'm going to be
a devil.
You fucking…
-It's a real knife!
-Fuck off.
Fucking hell!
-Whoa.
-Move.
What the hell is that?
-She's fucking out of it.
-Damn.
Hey, hit me. Come on.
-Damn it.
-My bad.
Take this, you fucking bitch.
-It hurts.
-Fucking bitch.
-Die, fucker.
-Hands off her!
It hurts.
You asshole. You fucker.
You son of a bitch. Come here, fucker!
-Fucking asshole!
-You bastard!
You fucker!
Inspector Im Han-rim!
Are you okay?
You're so fucking hot.
What?
Hey!
Hey, come here. This way.
Over here, asshole.
Me?
I don't have time, so let's be quick.
You get a punch each.
Damn it.
Goddamn it.
You punk, this is dangerous, you know.
-Let's take a break on the steps.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
-Sorry.
-Sorry, wait.
-Careful.
No, I can go. I can make it there.
Sit down here.
Slowly.
Do you feel dizzy? What should I do?
Whoa, are you okay?
Fucking hell.
It's just like that day.
Can you explain?
Why didn't you call the police?
I wanted to give you a chance.
Turn yourself in.
So you haven't told anyone yet.
I'll make sure not to waste the chance
you gave me.
Gyu-cheol.
You really don't know anything, do you?
Why would I turn myself in?
I'll be able to get out soon
because I'm a minor.
And if it's ruled
involuntary manslaughter,
two years in prison should be enough.
I come from a broken home,
and I had no motive to kill you.
Most of all…
I was in love with you.
Gyu-cheol, you--
I can just sell this again in two years.
Thanks to you, I came back to school.
And I realized this is the best market.
But it's too bad.
You won't be getting married.
You shouldn't
do this.
I guess I can't beat an ERPB inspector.
I'm sorry for everything.
All right.
Then you're getting
one painful punch.
Don't move,
or someone else might die at this school.
Stop resisting,
you fucking son of a bitch.
No!
Inspector.
No, wait. Hold on.
Are you okay?
What is it?
I'll spare Seong-gu.
When you see Ms. Choi,
please tell her
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Look.
Stop it!
Please stop!
Oh, what do I do now?
Help me sober up.
-What?
-Do something.
This won't pass
as involuntary manslaughter.
Or self-defense.
I can't live here anymore, can I?
Well, there are schools
in other countries too.
Fuck!
Who the fuck are you?
Who do you think?
I'm ERPB Inspector Im Han-rim.
You fucking bitch!
Let go.
Let go, you fucking…
You punk. You sure talk a lot, don't you?
Now it's my turn.
Go ahead.
You weren't supposed to grab it.
You just missed another chance.
Listen carefully.
All Koreans have an equal right to receive
an education suited to their abilities.
And through that,
they have the right to be happy.
That means we come to school to be happy.
So,
any bastard who gets in the way of that…
no matter who they are…
will be taught a lesson.
I'm sorry.
Please spare me.
I have no intention of doing so.
Please.
Please give me another chance.
Chances aren't something you're given.
They come to those who want them.
I wanted to give you a chance.
But Gyu-cheol,
the thing is,
chances aren't given to you.
Chances only come to those who want them.
Wow.
You really were made for each other.
Do you know
what Choi Ga-yun's last words were?
"Gyu-cheol,
you shouldn't do this."
Why the fuck shouldn't I?
Don't bullshit me.
Don't pretend you care.
I don't need a stupid chance.
Just kill me instead.
Go on. Kill me.
I said kill me.
Gyu-cheol, you shouldn't do this.
It's okay.
Let's start over.
This is the last chance
Ms. Choi is giving you.
Fuck!
Who do you think you all are?
You think you're Jesus?
A damn Buddha, or what?
Fuck!
We're adults, you punk. Adults.
I did you proud, right?
Shall I get you a stapler?
Oh man.
Don't make me laugh.
For fuck's sake!
I'm going! Damn it.
-You'll be okay.
-Thank you.
-Let go of me.
-Let go, damn it.
Fucking hell.
I'm going, man!
You
are being charged
with violations of the ERPB Act,
the Narcotics Control Act…
and…
the Punishment of Violence Act,
as well as attempted murder.
Therefore, as of this moment,
you're expelled from Jinwon High…
and you'll never set foot here again.
Take him away.
-The ERPB will also follow protocol.
-Yes, sir.
Hey, what happened to you?
Were you stabbed?
-Well, yeah. I'm fine.
-Are you okay?
-That bastard!
-Hey, stop him!
Hey, you punk!
-That's my son-in-law, you punk!
-Stop.
Get out here! You punk, come here!
-Come here!
-Go.
-Minister, please.
-Please go!
Come here, bastard!
-Hold on, Minister.
-Come back! Hey!
-Hey!
-Minister, wait.
-Are you okay?
-Are you all right?
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
Fellow citizens,
do you know the definition of education?
"The teaching of knowledge and skills
and the cultivation of character."
This is what education is.
Yes, good universities and good jobs
are important.
But what's more important
is nurturing a person's dignity
and moral integrity.
This is putting the true meaning
of education into practice.
However, the current education system
of our country has strayed too far
from this purpose and is deeply broken.
Nonetheless, in the midst of this reality,
most teachers in this country
continue to fulfill their calling,
teaching children and trying to guide them
toward the right path.
How long must we continue to see
students and teachers
never making it back home
from school?
The ERPB will uphold
the value of education
and protect victims…
until schools are no longer places
of fear and anxiety
and become truly safe.
We will continue to exist
until our education system is restored…
to its intended state.
I MISS YOUR SMILE SO MUCH
Ga-yun, it must be nice.
So many people still remember you.
THE LATE CHOI GA-YUN
Are you crying?
Hey, who's crying, punk?
I shed no tears.
Well, I heard
you're a man who cries easily.
Who said that?
Ga-yun did.
My goodness.
She said you cried
on the day the stray cat
you were looking after was adopted.
You cried for a month.
-No, that's…
-Oh.
That's actually kind of cute.
He's very cute. He's also very loving.
-And very tearful.
-You're adorable, sir.
Seriously, you punks.
Hey, did you…
finish the report on Jinwon High?
-Come on.
-Send it over now.
He switched back into boss mode.
Can he do this?
This is workplace bullying.
Bullying, my ass.
If you don't want to work, say so.
Got a problem?
We'll settle it under Yatcha rules.
I'll check and get back to you. Bye.
Let's head down now.
We have a lot of work to do, but no time.
I can't be the only one working here.
Minister, fists down, please.
Let's go.
-Come on, Inspector Im Han-rim.
-Okay.
-He scares me the most these days.
-Same.
Whenever he catches my eye,
he asks for a report. It's tiring.
He acts like he's the boss.
Haven't you sent the report?
I can send it today, can't I?
What are you waiting for? Come on.
-Okay, we're coming.
-Yeah, coming.
And Minister, you can't ever mention
the Yatcha rules anywhere.
-Okay?
-Yeah, okay.
-Careful.
-Yeah.
What's wrong?
-Why would you hold my hand?
-Well…
I thought you might trip over a stone.
It was dangerous.
Still, why hold my hand?
Didn't you hold mine first?
No, I didn't.
I let you hold my hand,
and I get told off?
-You "let" me?
-What?
You "let" me?
-What's with them?
-What's with the "let"?
They have feelings for each other,
but they don't seem to know it.
I see.
Do something.
-What do I do?
-Help me sober up.
-What should I do?
-Just do anything.
Do something.
-Do anything.
-What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Why hold my hand?
-I let you hold my hand, and you…
-You "let" me?
Could you guys hurry? You should run.
-All right, punk.
-Yeah, okay.
Should we hold hands?
What? No.
Why are you flustered?
You must be lonely these days.
-Guys, stop chatting and hurry up!
-We're on our way!
KANGJU HIGH SCHOOL SEO TAE-HUN WINS GOLD
Next.
Next!
Hurry up, you bastard.
Seriously, these fucking assholes.
You guys get all these perks thanks to me.
And Yeong-cheol, you fucker.
Yeah.
You're all going to Hanguk University
because I got scouted.
Like a fucking two-for-one deal, idiot.
But you don't even fucking pay me back?
You should make up for the money
I missed out on by not going pro.
Whatever.
You fucking assholes.
Poor fuckers can pay the hard way.
Hey.
You high school punks.
You should be studying, you brats.
Guys, get up.
I said get up.
It's okay. Get up.
Come on, get up.
I'm Deputy Director Bong Geun-dae
from the ERPB.
From this moment on,
the ERPB
will teach you a lesson.
Get up.
I said get up.
You too. Step back.
Get up.
I said get up.
Yes?
-You told me to get up.
-No.
No, I said "get off" me.
You said to get up.
-No, I said, "Get off."
-Oh man.
-You said to get up.
-No, I said, "Get off."
-I said…
-Take your hands off him. Now!
Who's that?
Get up.
Get up!
If they listen to words,
you teach with words.
If they listen only after a beating,
then you teach by beating.
Are you okay?
-Are you okay? Are you hurt?
-I'm fine.
-Why, you little…
-No, stop.
No, stop. You can't.
-This is funny?
-Don't.
-You'll get hurt. Don't.
-Why not?
Man, look at these punks.
You athlete punks
are supposed to be training.
Even with the ERPB here,
you still don't know how to behave.
Do you?
What are you doing?
Students shall have no power of any kind,
even if they represent the country.
You may not know,
but the newly revived ERPB
still has no limits
on how we educate.
So from this moment on…
we will teach you a lesson.
TEACH YOU A LESSON
I'm fine.
You think this is it for me?
Mr. Hwang!
Oh dear.
-Let's get you up.
-Are you okay?
Mark my words.
I'll be back no matter what.
The first thing I'll do is take you down.
When Cho Gyu-cheol gave you the recording,
you knew what happened.
You should've stopped then.
It's adults like you
who turn young students into monsters.
If you can't be a good adult,
at least don't be a bad one.
And what about you? Are you a good adult?
You think I won't find anything on you?
Damn…
I guess
I'm not a good adult either.
Subtitle translation by: Lisa Kim