THIS CRACKED ME UP
CHECK IT OUT
POLITICIAN'S SON'S TRUE NATURE
LOOK AT THEM LOL
HIDING BEHIND MONEY. GROSS.
FORCING DRINKS. IS HE FOR REAL?
SERVES THE BULLY RIGHT
NICE ONE, ERPB
TOO MUCH THOUGH?
HUH? I JUST FIND THEM COOL
THEY'RE SO OVER THE TOP!
I APPROVE OF THE ERPB
Disband the ERPB
that violates student human rights
through corporal punishment!
Disband!
No more student-abusing ERPB!
No more!
They've reacted quicker than I expected.
It's better this way.
It's better to take the hit early.
We expected this anyway.
-Disband!
-The student-abusing…
Even so, don't get caught on tape.
But you said
you'd block all the bullets and missiles--
I can block bullets and missiles,
but not videos.
We have to file in the US
to take them down.
Then I won't do anything.
That's not what I mean…
Disband!
That was on purpose, right?
-Yes.
-"Yes"?
I should've crashed my car
into you back then.
Don't be so childish.
Provide solutions!
You're lucky I'm busy.
Of course. Here you go.
Disband the ERPB
that violates student human rights…
It's packed with reporters outside.
Are you off to take the hit?
One who deserves it should take it.
But that's not us.
Minister, what exactly does the ERPB do?
Did you propose
establishing the ERPB two years ago
because of Jinwon High?
Is allowing corporal punishment
the main focus?
What about the statutory ban on it?
Will it be repealed?
Some say you have reverted to a time
when student human rights
were disregarded.
Please share your view on this, Minister.
Human rights?
Did you say human rights?
The Korean education system has failed.
Children rely more on hagwon
than on schools.
They respect
and listen to their teachers at hagwon
more than their homeroom teachers
at school.
Schools are now merely seen as
somewhere to complete the volunteer hours
and performance assessments
required for college.
Furthermore, aren't we seeing problems
like gambling, drugs,
statutory rape, and even gangs
emerging in schools
we have always claimed to be sacred?
Children no longer respect their teachers,
and teachers are afraid of the children.
How can teachers teach properly
when their authority has been destroyed?
Of course, this may not matter
to children who have access
to hagwon and private tutoring.
But there are also children
who rely solely on school lessons.
Didn't we build our education system
so that those children can learn
without any worry?
Therefore, the ERPB
will use corporal punishment,
and even go further if we must,
in order to protect the right to learn.
To those who disrupt learning,
this is a warning.
Don't get in the way
of compulsory education.
The Educational Rights Protection Bureau
will not put up with it.
"FIRM ACTION" DECLARED
AGAINST DISRUPTION TO EDUCATION
We should give Minister Choi
an appreciation award
on behalf of our party.
Your archrival Ryu Gwang-pil
has been ousted thanks to him.
Things are easier now.
Was the ERPB establishment bill passed
two years ago?
Yes, the ERPB bill was the bargaining chip
they offered at the time
in return for their agreement
to our party's proposal
to increase the prosecution special funds.
So, ultimately, the ERPB
was a joint effort by our party, right?
Choi Gang-seok isn't well-known at all,
and the ERPB
will only be a flash in the pan.
Exactly.
They're saying they'll teach by beating.
The public won't stand for it.
This is the country that grounds flights
during the listening section
of the university entry exam.
With education, people don't care
about politics, ideology, or status.
The Minister of Education
is responsible for such education.
There'll be no repercussions
if we nip problems in the bud early.
GUUN HIGH-TECH HIGH SCHOOL
RANKED IN THE TOP 3 THUG SCHOOLS
TOP SCHOOL FOR NEXT-GEN GANGSTERS
MOST-AVOIDED SCHOOL BY TEACHERS
TEACH YOU A LESSON
Hey, bastard!
-Get out of the way!
-Move!
Get lost, bastard!
It's brand new. Damn.
Hey, got a cig?
What do you even have?
-Hurry up!
-Coming.
I didn't hold it there earlier.
-I saw it, damn it.
-I said it wasn't me, asshole.
-He hit him.
-No, not yet.
Okay.
Try it yourselves, guys.
Hey.
Hey!
You were staring.
No, I wasn't.
Yes, you were.
You want beef?
No, I'm not that kind of student.
Is that so?
Hey, this is brand new.
-You a new kid?
-Yeah.
Did you know it's rough as fuck here?
I did a little research.
Want me to protect you?
I'm not sure if you're the kind of kid
I can count on for that yet.
So many people these days
are just all talk.
So I'll just show you.
Here, protection fee!
What an extremely
well-prepared loser you are.
Wait. Do you think
you could write me a receipt for that?
-No, right?
-Not a chance.
That's what I thought. Sorry.
-Find the other one and put them on.
-Okay.
Hello.
I'm the transfer student. My name is
Bong Geun-dae.
Take the empty desk by the window.
Don't fight, and try to get along.
Books out, everyone.
Let's start the lesson.
-I didn't bring my book.
-Share with your neighbor.
-Don't have one either.
-Same.
-Me too.
-You too.
I'll just read it to you,
and we'll manage.
You go make copies.
"For us, please, sir."
That would take longer.
All the other teachers do it.
Sir.
Fine. I'll go make copies.
Thanks.
Guys, let's go farming.
-Farming?
-Let's go!
Hurry.
Hey, Gwang-kki,
go bring that fucking rat over here.
-Wait. But why?
-Get out here.
-I'm not…
-Come on.
Open.
Guys, our lunch today
is grilled Pikachu!
Let's go!
You teach design.
Draw it in a designer style.
We're in class right now.
No one is paying attention
to class anyway.
-See?
-I'm too sleepy for class.
Damn it. Let go.
I told you to let go. Okay?
Pikachu!
Damn it.
-Fuck.
-What are you all doing?
Miss, we're going to have
a joint class today.
Fucking hell. Those fucking clunkers.
Hey, a joint class sounds fun.
Get out here, you fucking dumbass.
-Hey, Jjik-sae.
-Yeah.
Get some good footage.
Okay. I'll make sure you look great.
You piece of shit! Fuck!
Fucking hell!
I told you to stay on me, asshole.
Damn it.
Fucking bastard!
Go, electrical department!
Are you here for a picnic? Fucking idiot!
New kid! Are you here for a picnic too?
No, I'm not.
Get out here.
Fuck. What the hell?
You promised protection.
You're that moron from earlier. Sorry.
New kid, right?
I'm Kim Hyeong-ju
from the same department.
Hang on.
-What's going on with them?
-They need to get recruited.
What?
That's Park Seong-hwan,
the top dog in the automobile department.
-That guy with short hair?
-Yeah.
Oh, that guy.
Damn it!
Cho In-beom's the top dog
in the electrical department.
-The guy with long hair?
-Yeah.
You need to be a good fighter
to be noticed.
Only winners get recruited.
Fuck you, you son of a bitch.
But who are you being recruited by?
BULLY HIERARCHY CHART
This kid is Jang Gwon-hyeok,
the ultimate third-year top dog.
He only comes to school
when he feels like it.
He beats kids
and takes their money all the time.
He gets into gang fights
with other schools.
He just gives you a real headache.
I shouldn't say this as an educator,
but I just wish
he'd never come to school again.
He's practically half gangster.
He's been recruited even before graduating
and is already living that life.
Here. See this? Take a look.
He's got the expensive motorcycle,
the designer clothes,
the hard liquor, and the tattoos.
The kids say he's earning
tens of millions of won per month.
Who'd want to study, then?
They want Gwon-hyeok to notice them
and get recruited,
so all they do is fight to death.
ULTIMATE TOP DOG JANG GWON-HYEOK
TO WATCH OUT FOR
-Just fucking die, you bastard.
-Fuck.
Listen, you fucker.
That trap of yours is always the problem.
Wait. Shit!
What? Damn it.
-Oh fuck!
-What?
Hey, Gwon-hyeok sent you a DM.
LET'S HAVE AN INTERVIEW
Shit!
Hey! It's fucking Gwon-hyeok!
He wants to interview me, you bastard!
Fucking hell!
Our teaching staff just can't handle them.
That's why we contacted the ERPB.
Anyway,
when will the other inspectors arrive?
-Should we set up a separate space?
-No, it's just me.
You'll be on your own
with these violent kids?
Even the PE teacher,
a former national judo athlete,
has been absent for two months
since breaking up a fight
and fracturing his collarbone.
This goes beyond simple discipline.
You need to wage war on crime.
Is waging war really necessary?
You'll be in big trouble
with that kind of complacent thinking.
-You should consider it a real war and--
-Sir.
If there's a war,
people will actually die.
Don't worry.
The kids will all end up getting along
and enjoying their classes.
Damn it.
What a load of crap, you dumb shit.
You ran away earlier.
Why did you come to our school?
I wanted to study vehicles and get a job.
I'm trying to get a job too.
Gwon-hyeok's like a big company
I want to get into,
and fistfights make up our résumé.
AUTOMOTIVE TECHNICIAN PRACTICAL TEST
Come here.
Hey, new kid.
-Get over here, damn it!
-Come on.
Get the hell out there.
-But why?
-You can beat him, right?
What?
The moron who loses here…
will be the power gauge.
Do you think I could maybe ask
what that is?
Are you curious?
Then try losing.
Fight.
Do you both want to get thrashed?
What? What are you doing?
Hey, push him.
Just hit me.
Why are you doing this?
It's how it is. Just do it.
-Are you kissing?
-How can I?
Or we'll both get it. Hit me.
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Listen carefully, guys.
If we don't get on Gwon-hyeok's radar
this time either,
we're completely done for.
-Okay.
-Hey, gauge.
You'd better gauge properly.
You scored 92 points. Congratulations.
You must be an MMA fighter.
You've improved. Go on the offensive.
What's my score?
Get out of the way.
-Watch.
-You scored 95 points.
Congratulations.
You're currently in the lead.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. No need for that.
Here, hold on to this for now.
Give me your bag.
It's all right.
You helped me too.
Thanks.
Where do you live?
This is my place.
I see. Oh, here.
-Thanks.
-See you tomorrow.
Do you want to come in for some ramyeon?
I don't mean it like that.
I meant actual ramyeon.
Right.
Well…
Sure.
-Come on in.
-Okay.
-Watch your step.
Thanks.
What made you come to our school?
To go to university.
Through the special admissions
for specialized high schools.
Then try a different school.
I'm sure you can
since you've only just transferred.
Ask your parents
to send you to a different school.
Thanks.
What about you?
I'd always thought
this school was my only hope,
but that wasn't the case.
I think it's too late now.
There are options like the GED.
You have to go to hagwon for the GED,
which costs a lot.
Try the kimchi.
My mom works at a restaurant
known for its tasty kimchi.
That's my mom.
Hyeong-ju, are you home?
Hello.
Oh my, Hyeong-ju brought a friend home.
All you're having is ramyeon?
Wait a minute,
and I'll fix you a proper meal.
-No, Mom.
-I'm fine, ma'am.
-It's okay.
-Wait…
-Gosh, I smell bad, don't I?
-No…
I'll wash up quickly.
Just wait a moment.
If you do this,
the newspaper absorbs all the moisture
so it dries out faster.
It's uncomfortable wearing wet shoes
in the morning.
DEPARTMENT OF AUTOMOBILE
I didn't hold it there earlier.
-I saw it.
-One, two.
-Three, four.
-He hit him.
-Five.
-No, not yet.
Try it yourselves, guys.
Those thugs beat you up every day.
Why do you make such an effort
to come to school?
Because it's still school.
Correct answer.
Who are you?
I'm an ERPB inspector.
I did a little research on you.
What? Shall I list some facts
about Kim Hyeong-ju?
How do you know my name?
Hey.
I told you I did my research.
Class is about to start. You should go.
Don't worry.
From now on, you'll get lessons
until you're sick of them.
You've got this, Kim Hyeong-ju.
What receipt?
You're getting mugged, dumbass.
What a crazy bastard.
Comfy, isn't it? Just stay there.
Oh?
-I saw it, damn it.
-It wasn't me, asshole.
One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest.
What's that?
When I say "One flew over the nest,"
you're supposed to go
"flutter, flutter," right?
It's today's code.
"Code"?
Hey!
I messaged it to you
along with a video of the victim.
You must be
Deputy Director Bong?
Yes, sir.
I sure recruited the right person.
RÉSUMÉ
BONG GEUN-DAE
Right.
Look this way.
Deputy Director, are you a good runner?
Why are you taking a…
Hey, you bastards!
Hey, you thugs, hooligans,
dipshit bastards!
Take this!
Look at your hair, you morons!
You're seriously eating? Bastards!
Hey.
Whoever catches that fucker
gets 100,000 won. Get him.
Wait, no!
Oh no. I'm sorry.
No, I mean, take this!
Where did he go?
Get your ass out here, you son of a bitch!
Are you scared, you fucker?
-Where are you, you fucking chicken?
-Fuck.
Where are you? You fucking scared or what?
-What the hell?
-What the…
What's going on?
What the hell?
Who are you?
Me?
The ERPB inspector.
The Educational Rights what?
Protection Bureau.
They apparently beat up
a few nerds from Daehan High.
My goodness, there's hope for Guun High.
Someone here is on top of things.
That's a pass!
Mister.
That's nothing to be proud of around here.
This place is savage.
We don't hold back
for teachers or adults or anyone.
That's good to hear.
You're gaining points nicely.
You think I'm joking.
I'm just worried you'll get hurt
if I take things seriously.
All right, guys.
Take a seat.
You can't be fucking serious.
What are you doing, dumbass?
I'm going to mess him up!
No, I'm going to.
You can't even fight for shit.
What about the heat?
Fuck, all they can do is expel me.
Life is all gas and no brakes anyway.
I'll just go all in on Gwon-hyeok.
You're all dreaming.
Who said we'd let you drop out
on your own terms?
That's up to me.
No, it's not up to you.
How much do you think it costs
to get you this far in schooling?
It's at least 65 million won per person.
Do you think all that precious tax money
was spent just to make thugs like you?
No, of course not!
So as for what you can do
on your terms here,
you have three things.
First.
If you want to leave,
you cough up all that money before you go.
Second.
You knock me down
and proudly walk out of here.
Third.
I know!
The second option. It's quick and easy.
Automobile department!
-Let's go.
-We'll get in on it too!
Goodness me.
Sit down, you punks.
Stay still.
You'll get hurt.
It'll poke your eye. Done!
-I said go!
-Mess him up!
What the… You brat!
Damn it!
Are you in or not?
-Together. Go!
-Fuck!
Has anyone not been hit?
Who wants another go?
Damn it!
Die!
Have you boxed before?
I need to sit down.
Goodness me.
This is why you should listen
to the very end.
Here's the third and final option.
If the first two don't pan out,
then just be grateful
and finish your education.
Come on out now. Okay?
Hey, my foot.
Wake up at 6:00 a.m.
Supplementary class at 7:00 a.m.
After that, you have regular classes,
followed by lunch, specialty classes,
afternoon regular classes,
after-school specialty classes,
and evening supplementary classes.
Why are there so many damn classes, sir?
Because you need to make up
for the classes you've missed.
I'm going to make sure you punks make up
for every single second
of your missed classes.
I'll make sure
you meet your required attendance
so you can graduate.
How does that sound?
Isn't compulsory education just amazing?
That's a wrap for orientation.
I'll bring your teacher over,
so stay seated.
This is the worst.
Goddamn it!
Why are you standing?
Oh man, why the hell
do we have to teach in the gym?
Welcome, sir.
Thank you.
Here you are.
-They're zombies, thirsty for learning.
-Pardon?
Go in. They won't bite.
They're very obedient.
Since this is a joint class
for Electrical and Automobile,
we'll cover electric cars,
which applies to both departments.
Shall we open our books?
I don't have my book,
sir.
-I don't either.
-Me neither.
We can't have class without textbooks.
Who has theirs?
I have a feeling Hyeong-ju might have his.
Should I make copies?
Don't waste paper and power on these guys.
All right, we will make our own textbooks.
The Joseon Dynasty way.
I'm starting the timer now.
Copy down every single word.
Oh no, what should I do?
I have nothing to write with.
Oh no, what should we do?
You need a pen to take notes.
Can you use something else instead?
I wonder.
Oh yeah, your blood.
Oh, wait.
Who else doesn't have a pen?
-Give me that.
-Anyone?
That's mine, you jerk.
Damn it, give that back to me.
What's wrong? Don't you have pens?
What?
-What? Why?
-Fuck this!
I said I was timing you.
If you're not done, come on up!
He yanked it again.
I haven't hit you yet. Keep straight.
Fuck!
Why the hell do I have to take
this damn class?
Just let the kids go already!
The morons who want to take the class can!
Why are you forcing it
when we don't want to?
It won't help us one bit in life!
Yes, that's a very good point.
Then we'll only have classes
helpful to your lives from now on.
When you suspect a brake problem,
you have to check four things.
-First, ask yourself two questions.
-Hey.
Is it an electrical issue,
or is it a mechanical issue?
Electrical students,
examine the electrical circuit.
Automobile students,
inspect the brake pads
and brake fluid levels.
-Yes, sir.
-Okay.
You all heard, didn't you?
Park Seong-hwan and Cho In-beom,
come up and fix the brakes.
-Stop talking shit already.
-You think that's possible?
You can't do it?
No fucking shit.
You said "fucking" again.
-Want a punch?
-No, I'm going.
Why do you keep using violence to…
You should film this.
-What are you doing?
-Damn it.
-Hey, get out.
-Get out.
-What are you doing?
The seatbelt!
The seatbelt. No!
I'm scared!
We're fucked!
What are you doing?
Aren't the brakes faulty?
-Stop!
-You were in class.
And I told you to fix them earlier.
Up ahead!
-What's up ahead?
-We're all going to die!
All right, here we go!
Oh fuck!
Fuck my life.
-How is this possible?
-Yeah, how?
Wow, damn.
It's not for you to decide
whether a class is necessary.
No class is ever unnecessary.
Those fucking bastards.
I looked into that ERPB inspector,
and it's really quite strange.
There is only one word
in the "experience" section.
"Classified."
I formally got this
through the Intelligence Committee.
How can this happen? This isn't a movie.
Since you served as director
of the National Intelligence Service,
I thought there might be a way for you
to find out more information about him.
You need to open the brake fluid tank
and drain the existing fluid.
Then fill it with new fluid
and check the level.
You also have to check
whether there is any air
in the brake system.
Fucking hell.
You think you're a teacher now?
Does nothing scare you,
now that you've climbed the ladder?
Fuck, you little…
You don't ever learn, do you?
Your body will though.
The way I spoke was a bit condescending.
They won't do it again. Right, guys?
-Right.
-Yeah.
Why were you backing them earlier?
If something went wrong, I was worried
we might have to stop our classes.
Every minute, every second matters to me.
You told the inspector, didn't you?
Thanks.
Don't mention it. I'm just doing my job.
We're fucked
if we miss the interview today.
Come on, pull.
Hey, I think it moved.
It's not working.
-Come on.
-Yes, it's working.
Fuck, this isn't working.
Motherfucker.
New kid, you asshole. Come here.
New kid, you little asshole.
You've got cigs, right?
Just let him go.
Hey, he's got some.
Look, this asshole vapes.
Shit.
What a savage asshole.
This is a utility knife.
Hey, give me that and grab him.
What? Why?
Hey, this actually works.
I told you it would.
Last one.
Stop moving.
-Fuck, stay still.
-You're almost there.
I'm done.
-Fucking hell.
-It fucking worked.
-Hey, hold this.
-Okay.
You go first, and then you go.
Why am I going?
Because you'll snitch to the ERPB.
Damn it.
Hey, you came. Good luck.
This is the last time.
Thank you, boss!
Fucking hell.
-He's so damn cool.
-What's with your numbers?
-Dig deep and go all out. Okay?
-Hold on.
Yes, boss.
-He's calling us.
-Hey, loser.
Fucking hurry up.
Two, three.
-Good evening!
I'm Cho In-beom, Electrical!
I'm Park Seong-hwan, 18, from Guun High!
-Your name.
-I'm Bong Geun-dae.
-It's an honor!
I think I only told you to come.
There's a problem at school.
Cheers!
Let's all have a drink together.
Come on!
-Hey, come take a picture.
-Yes, sir.
Hey, he's here.
SELF-STUDY
It's fun
Self-study time
Where did Park Seong-hwan, Cho In-beom,
and Bong Geun-dae go?
We're right here.
-It's not…
-You little punks.
Little rats, I told you to do self-study.
Even you, Bong Geun-dae, little punk!
No, not me.
Sir, you're fucked now.
You can try begging a little now.
"He-he."
What's going on?
Did you bring backup or something?
Back there.
It's Gwon-hyeok.
That's Gwon-hyeok.
This is sick. Seriously!
These little punks.
Good evening!
-Wow.
-Good evening!
-Good to see you!
Goodness me.
Oh my, look at that cigarette.
What shall we do about this?
Didn't you hear?
There's a hella scary guy here,
and he'll destroy anyone disrupting class.
Are you sure about that? I'm quite strong.
Is that right? I see.
A gangster high schooler.
Let's see what you've got.
Can I get my hopes up?
That damn bastard.
Damn it.
You're incredible, boss!
I knew we could count on you, Gwon-hyeok!
Gwon-hyeok!
-I never doubted you.
-Gwon-hyeok!
Listen carefully, you fucking bastards!
From now on,
no one's off the hook
from being beaten up by other schools!
And anyone getting beaten up
by old farts like that bastard
won't be off the hook either!
If it gets bad, drop my name.
If they still come at you even then,
I'll fucking kill them all.
Gwon-hyeok!
-Gwon-hyeok! What the…
-Gwon-hyeok!
Gwon-hyeok!
Why did you stop?
He said he won't let you off the hook.
Jang Gwon-hyeok.
Hey, what will it do?
Jang Gwon-hyeok. What will your name do?
Is it a fast track? A golden ticket?
This is exactly why I said
education is necessary.
You look grown-up,
but your brain is still in diapers.
Jang Gwon-hyeok, do you know
why I made you come all the way here?
You're a learning aid for these guys.
-What?
-Such big words…
You want to call Jang Gwon-hyeok in?
You have to pull the weeds out
by the roots so they don't grow back.
But how will you bring him in?
Well, those who act up,
thinking they've got backup,
are bound to call for backup
if they get beaten.
You damn…
It clearly didn't click for you,
so you get a forehead flick.
Are you all right?
You're screwed now.
My bros said they'd come
to support me.
Oh dear. You still don't get it, do you?
I support you too, you punk.
With this.
Inspector Na Hwa-jin
had an impressive career.
He was a captain in the special forces.
Are you suggesting
a return to military training in schools?
A time when students lived
under the boot of the military?
That's unacceptable.
Our party intends to mobilize
all our resources to disband the ERPB.
The ERPB is an organization
that must disappear.
What exactly is the problem?
Is it because the inspector
is a former soldier?
The intensity of school violence has
long surpassed what is tolerated.
There are students
who are active gang members,
and even gangs formed by students.
In this climate, do you expect teachers
to fight back with nothing but pens?
It's not students the ERPB is up against.
It's monsters.
A monster
should be taken down by another monster.
-Okay, let's go!
-Let's go.
Is it one person?
Hurry up!
-Jump over!
-Stop!
Your bros?
Hey!
You've made a real mess of things.
Enough of that!
Who here is a student? Hands up!
None of you, right? I'm glad.
Now I won't have to go easy on…
What? When did you get there?
Go farther that way.
Even farther. Yeah.
I won't have to go easy on you.
Is that so?
I'm so fucking scared.
This is your first and final warning.
A school is a place
where you have lessons.
-What's going on?
-Be quiet.
No one can enter except students
attending lessons and their teachers.
The moment you take even one step in…
you'll be at war with me.
War?
That's our specialty.
Come here, you bastard!
Please spare me!
I'm sorry.
Sir, I'm sorry.
That's not it.
In that case,
I'll stop coming to school!
I'll drop out.
I said that's not it.
Think about it.
Who should you be apologizing to?
-Hey.
Hyeong-ju!
Hyeong-ju, I'm sorry!
Forgive me. Please?
-Spare me!
-I'm sorry.
-You've got to spare me.
-I'm fucking sorry!
-Forgive us, or we're dead.
-It's okay.
Honestly, it's okay.
Don't do this. It's fine.
No, please spare me. I'm really sorry.
Hyeong-ju.
Are you really okay?
I'm sorry.
If you don't want classes, don't come.
If you don't want to study, then don't.
It's your life.
But…
don't get in someone else's way.
Don't assume your minute
is the same as another person's.
It may feel the same now…
but later, it'll have made
decades of difference.
Understood, you punks?
Yes, sir!
Why are you guys silent? Understood?
I will report
on the results of the ERPB's work.
Through our inspector's efforts
at Guun High-Tech High School,
the ERPB has resolved
violations of the right to learn.
To prevent any recurrence,
we will take the following actions
alongside related departments.
TATTOO REMOVAL CLINIC
From now on,
tattoos will be banned in all schools.
If you move,
your bare skin will get burned.
Motorcycles will be prohibited
on school grounds.
YOU'LL BE A GREAT MECHANIC
YOUR FRIEND, GEUN-DAE
Should a student join or attempt to join
bullying gangs, school gangs,
or any organized crime groups,
they will face adult charges
and penalties under the law
on organized crime groups.
Finally, we will work
with the Ministry of Justice and the MSIT
to continuously take action on
millennial and Gen Z gangs
that recruit members through social media.
We at the ERPB
will do our best to uphold
students' rights to compulsory education.
Turn off the TV!
Yes, sir.
Oh wow!
You walked out of there,
and now you're here.
Minister, don't you think
you're on TV too much lately?
Why? Do you want to be on it?
That's not what I meant.
You just seem to be enjoying it.
Am I not allowed to?
Of course you are.
Did you see that?
"Those who disrupt learning, listen up."
"Don't get in the way
of compulsory education." So cool.
May I interrupt your conversation
for a brief moment?
What is it?
While carrying out my duties recently,
I incurred a few expenses.
Yes, you should claim expenses.
What are they?
I was mugged
about three times in total.
Oh, mugged?
They took 40,000 won in cash
and 500 won for premium coffee
at a vending machine.
And outside the workshop,
a pair of sneakers worth about 125,000 won
called Nike Air Force…
Let's just say white Nike shoes
were taken from me.
And I was microwaving
a 2,200-won Uiseong garlic sausage
at the school snack bar,
and that was taken too.
So I ultimately spent 167,700 won
from my personal funds.
Would I be able to claim those?
Sure.
Was anything else taken?
Well…
MEDICAL BILLS…
No, nothing else.
I see. Go ahead and claim the expenses.
Thank you, sir.
Should I buy you a sausage?
Pardon? No, sir.
-It's fine.
-Have one of those Uiseong garlic things.
-Go on.
-Hey.
He's just a kid.
-But he said he had it taken--
-That's enough.
Subtitle translation by: Lisa Kim