EDUCATIONAL RIGHTS PROTECTION BUREAU
ALL REPORTS
ARE KEPT CONFIDENTIAL AS A RULE
PLEASE HELP OUR SCHOOL
THIS JUST ISN'T RIGHT
THIS IS DAILY LIFE AT OUR SCHOOL
IT'S REALLY MESSED UP
PLEASE COME HELP, ERPB
I FEEL SO BAD FOR OUR TEACHER
EXPOSING THE STUDENT
WHO ASSAULTED A TEACHER
REPORTING A SERIOUS ASSAULT ON A TEACHER
You will remember
the death of a female teacher
that led to the establishment of the ERPB.
The current Minister of Education
and head of the ERPB, Choi Gang-seok,
is the victim's father.
And Inspector Na Hwa-jin was her fiancé.
Is it truly possible
this has nothing to do with
the teacher killed by her student?
These people are not working
for educational rights.
It is cruel revenge
for the death
of their daughter and fiancée.
It is a personal vendetta.
Im Han-rim.
What are you doing?
Have you eaten, sir?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Did you happen to see
the press conference?
Yeah.
Is it all true?
Yes, it's true.
You'll be late to the meeting
if you just stand there.
Come on, hurry.
We have a lot to do.
Where the hell did everyone go?
They're eccentric and…
The members' eccentric,
ignorant, and tyrannical…
I do not see any potential for improvement
in team members' capabilities--
"Therefore, I am requesting
a transfer of assignment."
Gosh, this is…
ASSIGNMENT TRANSFER APPLICATION
Deputy Bong Geun-dae.
Yes, sir.
What is this font?
It's so eye-catching.
Pardon?
Let's use this font
for all official documents from now on.
Oh, yes.
By the way,
that's not a good enough reason.
If you want to be reassigned,
give me a convincing reason.
A reason I can't logically argue against
in any way.
Otherwise, it comes across as whining
to people like us.
Hello, sir.
We're so damn busy right now.
Get a move on!
Look at the time!
Safe…
This report is about
the assault of a teacher by a male student
at Chukmyeong Foreign Language High.
This is the teacher on the screen.
The informant is a colleague
of the assaulted teacher.
They also sent a video of the incident.
-Play the video.
-Yes, sir.
Park Hyeon-ung!
What the hell are you doing?
All that praise
has gone to your head, hasn't it?
Mr. Cheon, are you okay?
-Are you out of your mind?
-Hey, what's wrong?
-What is it?
-Hyeon-ung, what's gotten into you?
Stop it.
TEACH YOU A LESSON
CHUKMYEONG FOREIGN LANGUAGE HIGH SCHOOL
Wow. Is this a school?
What kind of high school looks like this?
I know, right?
I heard they're the best of their kind.
They're very flashy.
You guys go ahead.
I'll catch up with you shortly, all right?
Let's go.
Grades alone don't guarantee
college entry anymore.
-Especially Seoul National Uni.
-Yes.
When I saw his student records,
he had public speaking…
Chukmyeong Foreign Language High School
actually had a lower profile
than other foreign language high schools.
But after that teacher, Mr. Cheon,
started working here,
more students got into elite colleges,
and this became an elite high school.
-It's because they worked so hard.
-But you weren't…
Is that how he became famous?
It was more because of his character.
He's actually really famous
for being a true educator.
A true educator?
Why would a kid hit him?
You're amazing, seriously.
Gosh, sir.
I'd always hoped to meet you one day.
If I ever had the chance to do so,
I wanted to say thank you.
Right.
Allow me
to formally introduce myself, sir.
My name is Na Hwa-jin.
I'm an inspector from the ERPB.
Right, hello.
I got into the Korea Military Academy
after listening
to your EBS online lectures.
That wouldn't be down to me.
You must have worked very hard for it.
The things you said
now and then during your lectures…
The…
Gosh, this is just…
-Are you all right?
-Wow.
What's happening?
What's wrong with Inspector Na?
What you said was really…
Inspector, can't we just
forget this happened?
We have midterm exams soon.
They're important
to Hyeon-ung and the other students.
But still, he was in the wrong
and should be punished.
Sir,
could I perhaps ask a big favor?
Yes, sure.
You know your sign-off
at the end of your online lectures?
Could you say it just one more time?
"I believe in your potential."
Oh my gosh.
There just so happens to be a blackboard
and chalk right here, so…
May I please ask you to do it?
Gosh, Inspector.
I believe in your potential.
Wow!
-You can't just touch it like that.
-What is all this?
I bought it with my most recent paycheck.
Believe it or not, it's dual monitors.
It has a touchscreen,
and the mounting bracket at the back
comes in handy.
Right, it's a computer.
It's not just any computer.
It's a portable monitor.
The display is 16:9, and it's full HD.
It's 15.6 inches, which is great
for watching Netflix and movies.
And it's optimized for gaming
with the ideal aspect ratio and size.
And see this small thing here?
The white USB-C port.
This single device can supply power
and support display output simultaneously.
So it's expensive.
Nice.
PATIENCE
Are you Park Hyeon-ung?
You assaulted your teacher, Mr. Cheon,
a few days ago.
What was the reason?
If I tell you,
will you let me off the hook?
No, you won't!
Expel me or report me to the police
if you want.
Don't pretend you want to know.
If it's hard to decide,
should I make it easy for you?
Do not make me write
the Chinese character for "patience."
The school still hasn't decided
how to punish that kid, Park Hyeon-ung.
I thought the ERPB could really show them,
so I reported the incident.
Mr. Cheon is like a role model
to many other teachers.
He makes you want to become more like him.
Our school didn't attain elite status
simply because he teaches well.
Mr. Cheon is someone
who stays up all night with the students
and gets more excited than they do
when they are accepted into college.
Once the news spread,
students poured in to enroll.
To hit a teacher like him…
I couldn't just stand by and do nothing.
I see.
Damn it!
When do boys usually hit puberty?
Generally, as hormones change,
it spans from middle school
to the second year of high school.
So he's probably at the end of it.
He's all bravado and rage.
He utterly refuses to listen,
and I bet his grades are utterly bad.
Don't make hasty generalizations…
I mean, I think you're mistaken.
About what?
Park Hyeon-ung.
He's ranked first in his grade.
STUDENT REPORT CARD
He really is.
So why would he…
He's ranked first.
Why would he do it?
EXAM MANAGEMENT OFFICE
ENGLISH DEPARTMENT, TERM 1, 2026
MIDTERM EXAM
VIEWING IS PROHIBITED
TO UNAUTHORIZED PERSONNEL
Oh, hello.
Must be the exam papers.
Yes, I'm the Head of Academic Affairs,
so I have to check them.
Wow, the exam papers are all here.
When I didn't want to study for exams
back in the day,
I used to daydream about stealing
exam papers with my friends.
Coming up with ways to steal exam papers
was more fun than studying.
I was like that too.
Really?
Mr. Cheon, it's an honor.
Right, you can't be in here.
Let's head out.
It's like we've led parallel lives.
So why did Park Hyeon-ung assault you?
I'm not sure.
Do you have any idea at all?
I created a special class not long ago.
Right. A special class?
But I don't think the class
met Hyeon-ung's expectations.
That's right. This is ten
plus two over two plus… What is it?
We learned this in our first year.
We already covered that last time.
The line segment A10 is seven,
and the triangle ABC…
Why are we only doing reviews?
How will this help us in the exam?
We've been doing this for days.
You should study with us.
The class wasn't made just for Hyeon-ung.
I had to take the other students' levels
into account too.
But it was ultimately for his sake,
wasn't it?
I'm not sure.
Isn't that just our perspective?
DETAILED SCHOOL LIFE RECORD
What about it?
I just can't make any sense of it at all.
You're a top student,
so why did you do it?
A student as smart as you
must know what happens
if you assault a teacher.
What on earth made you angry enough
to ignore all this?
These grades could earn you a scholarship
at one of the top three universities.
You studied your butt off for 12 years
to get into college
and even became the top student.
So why are you acting
like you don't care about all that?
I had bad grades, and even I find it odd.
Do your parents know?
To tell you the truth,
I made a mistake
I shouldn't have as a teacher.
Once a year, the parents come to school
for college counseling,
but Hyeon-ung's parents live far away
and couldn't come.
So I paid them a visit.
HYEON-UNG'S KOREAN BUFFET
They ran a restaurant,
but they seemed so busy that I just ate,
pretending to be a customer.
What?
I guess your parents don't know.
Then I'll have to ask them.
Damn it!
Let go! Let go of me!
Do you feel wronged?
Angry?
I said let go of me!
Let go!
Then ask for help.
The first step in getting help
is to ask for it.
Excuse me, Hyeon-ung.
This month's tuition hasn't been paid yet.
Hey, son!
Your hagwon tuition
hasn't been paid yet, has it?
The restaurant was really busy,
so I forgot.
I'll pay it soon, so no worries.
Just focus on studying hard, son.
You've got this!
After Mr. Cheon visited, the restaurant
was ordered to suspend operations.
They said someone reported it
as an unauthorized building.
Is that why you assaulted your teacher?
Even in these circumstances,
my parents went to a lot of trouble
and found me a private tutor.
Wow.
You did well in the exam.
The exam questions were hard this time.
Do you have a private tutor?
Yes, sir.
Your tutor must be pretty good.
What are they like?
What? You're going to stop tutoring me?
I'm going to stop tutoring
and focus on my graduate studies.
My tutor suddenly quit
right after Mr. Cheon asked about him,
which was odd.
Sir, why are you picking up these stones?
On their way to and from school,
the kids either read books
or watch online lectures.
I can't exactly tell them not to.
I pick them up just in case
they trip on them and get hurt.
Wow.
No wonder people say you should be next
for Seoul Superintendent of Education.
Please don't say things like that.
Anyway, between Minister of Education
and Seoul Superintendent of Education,
which is the higher position?
Pardon?
Well, our Minister of Education
is great in every way.
On the other hand, he's not great at all.
I was just thinking
I might change allegiances.
-I'm being serious.
-My goodness.
By the way,
Inspector Na.
What will happen to Hyeon-ung?
We'll handle it as per protocol.
When I think about Hyeon-ung,
I feel it's right to punish him firmly
for what he did.
But I'm not so sure.
Please leave it to us at the ERPB,
future Superintendent of Education.
Please don't say things like that.
-Not at all.
-Please stop that.
Superintendent of Education,
let me pick up the stones.
-It's fine.
-I'll pick them up for you.
Please give it to me,
Superintendent of Education.
Your Mimiminu channel
is popular with the students.
So I thought my students might like
seeing me on your show.
That's why I came on.
As someone who is true
to their nickname of "true educator,"
the care you have for your students is…
I've met with Hyeon-ung,
and I think you should hear him out.
The chalk snaps!
TEACHER CHEON SANG-YEOL'S ICONIC FINISH!
-I heard this in real life earlier.
-I believe in your potential!
Back in my day,
everyone used to mimic this.
Even the bottom-scoring students
without any foundation…
Looks like you're here to meet a star.
You don't seem like your usual self,
with no interest
in getting to the bottom of this case.
Mr. Cheon seems to matter more to you
than the cause.
Or did the cause never matter to you
in the first place?
We didn't have college entry results
at this level before.
What's your point?
Your perspective is already skewed.
Aren't you thinking
that everything is the student's fault?
Didn't you come here
having already decided who's at fault?
Is what people are saying true?
Are you really blinded
by your personal vendetta?
If that concerns you,
you may quit now.
Hey, Im Han-rim.
Let's do as we always have.
Seriously!
YEAR 3 STUDENT RANKINGS
2ND - CHOI JI-HUN
TEACHER - MR. CHEON
11TH - JUNG SU-JEONG
NOAVIS INSTITUTE
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
I wanted to register at this institute.
What school are you at?
Chukmyeong Foreign Language High.
I see. Chukmyeong High.
Yes.
Have you heard anything about our hagwon?
That it's a good hagwon.
Sorry.
We're not taking any more students.
Registration is over.
But I had a quick look around,
and the classrooms were all empty, so…
I said registration is over.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
-You said you go to Chukmyeong High?
-Yes.
Which class?
Class four in the English Department.
Then you must know Moon Hyeon-o well.
He's the class president.
Yes. Hyeon-o. I know Moon Hyeon-o.
Oh, that's right.
The class four president isn't Hyeon-o.
It's Bo-hyeon.
That's right. It's Bo-hyeon.
I must have confused myself.
-How did you hear about our hagwon?
-What?
Are you even a student?
Of course I am.
-Who are you?
-What?
-Who are you to come--
-Please stop.
Bong Geun-dae.
Hey, Hyeong-ju.
Why did you transfer without telling me?
I was upset.
Where did you move to?
I moved
to Chukmyeong Foreign Language High.
You got a haircut.
How have you been?
Good for you.
I thought a foreign language high school
would suit you better.
-How are things at school?
-It's the same.
They still fight,
and there's still a pecking order.
They don't bully me though.
-Really?
-Yeah.
That's a relief.
How about you? Are you settling in well?
Hey, pull over!
It's Hyeong-ju.
Hey, Kim Hyeong-ju!
We have exams tomorrow.
Why aren't you studying?
Wait, they're having sundae.
-Damn.
-Hi.
-Take your time eating.
-This is so damn good.
Look at him stuff his face.
He's so damn big now.
Studying for exams
made me gain so much weight.
-It's not from studying, you idiot.
-I guess.
Hey.
Is the cheat sheet I told you about ready?
Open up.
You have to share it with me first.
I told you we have different subjects.
I said only the main subjects
are different.
Eat this.
Fuck. Seriously.
Hey, whoa!
Play rock, paper, scissors for it.
Okay.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
-Scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
You fucker.
Okay, last one.
Rock, paper, scissors.
-I get it first.
-Hey.
REPORT ON CHUKMYEONG HIGH
BY BONG GEUN-DAE, ERPB
Hey! Damn it.
Hey, you fucking bitch!
That crazy bitch.
Where are you going?
Fucking hell. Seriously, stop!
-Stop right there!
-Fuck!
Seriously. Damn it.
Are you done running?
Fucking hell, crazy bitch.
-You fucking nutcase.
-Are you done running?
That must hurt.
It does, doesn't it?
My heart almost exploded,
you fucking bitch.
Han-rim.
How many more beatings
until you get it together?
Are you Joan of Arc?
Why the hell would you butt in,
trying to help an outcast
when you're just a loser yourself?
You sure stick your nose in
when you ain't got shit.
Rip her mouth open for me too.
Should I? All right, Han-rim.
Come here. I missed your lips.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Just a grunt.
Mind your own business and be on your way.
Just be on your way
and "salute" for your country.
I'm a bit busy with my friends right now.
Is that true?
Yes, it is.
"Friends."
Whoa.
-The weather…
-You scared?
-The weather's weird.
-He got scared.
Scared, my ass.
-Are you scared?
-I'm not.
You moron.
Should I help you?
Ask for my help.
The first step in getting help
is to ask for it.
Who is this man? Is he your boyfriend?
Disgusting.
That's so cool.
-He's going.
-Hey, he's leaving.
Please…
Please help me. Please?
I heard you.
What are you going to do?
What? Is a grunt going to hit a civilian?
Yes, I am.
Damn it.
-Let's go, you crazy bitch!
-Damn it!
-Fuck.
-Fuck, take me with you.
Son of a bitch.
Shit, this fucking hurts.
Well done.
-Thanks for this.
-Sure.
All right, let's see.
It's fascinating that the students
ranked 1 to 11 in the grade
are all in your class.
I'm sure you've already discovered
they all come from prominent families.
The other teachers felt a lot of pressure,
so I took them on myself.
-Just as I expected. I believe in you.
-Gosh.
It was nothing.
But they all seem to go to this hagwon.
A hagwon called Noavis Institute.
All the kids but Park Hyeon-ung.
Are you familiar with this hagwon?
I have heard a rumor that they offer
elite courses for a select few.
The hagwon must be in a tight spot.
They push their students so hard,
yet the top student is Park Hyeon-ung,
who doesn't even go to a hagwon.
I heard that hagwons these days
are going all out to get the top students
for marketing purposes.
I heard about that too.
Okay, here's the thing.
Let's say Hyeon-ung can't take the exam
because of the recent assault.
Then who would benefit the most from this?
Is it Noavis Institute
that's in a tight spot?
Is it the kids
who would each move up one rank?
Or…
Is it Jung Su-jeong
who would move up not only in rank
but also in tier?
What are you trying to say right now?
Mr. Cheon, do you know
a student called Han Ye-ri?
I'm not sure.
We were at Soyeon Girls' High School
before here.
She goes there. Don't you know her?
You were her middle school
homeroom teacher.
Her name does ring a bell.
Okay.
Ye-ri did well academically
and had been preparing to enroll here
at Chukmyeong Foreign Language High.
But she never made it
because she missed her final exam.
Is that so?
Yes.
And the student who was able
to come here in her place
was Jung Su-jeong,
the student in your class.
Isn't that right?
Ye-ri had been doing so well in school,
so why did she miss her exam?
Was it because her parents
weren't as privileged as Su-jeong's?
Is that why you created a class
that cut into her study time,
stole her tutor, and pulled strings
to sabotage her parents' store,
pushing her to violence, like Hyeon-ung?
So she would mentally break down
and miss the exam?
What? Do you still have
unfinished business with me?
What do I need to do to end this?
What?
You just need to tell me one thing.
Cheon Sang-yeol.
What Cheon Sang-yeol did to you.
Just tell me that.
You think ranking first in your grade
makes you tier one, don't you?
Each person has a tier
that suits them best.
In your case,
it would be around tier nine.
Your parents are no different.
In fact, your whole family is
tier nine.
Son of a bitch.
She caused a serious problem.
Did you come all the way here
just on her word?
I never said Han Ye-ri
was a problem student.
You barely remembered her a moment ago.
Yet you're well aware of the issues
she caused at Soyeon Girls' High School.
The fact that the ERPB was there
means there was an issue.
But…
what are you playing at here?
I think that's enough.
You know Hyeon-ung…
Park Hyeon-ung,
whom you are so concerned about…
He will definitely take
the upcoming exams.
Will he?
Thank you.
I believe
in the potential of the ERPB.
-Don't you think it's a bit much?
-Yeah.
-It's Hyeon-ung.
-What?
What is he doing here?
What the hell?
How could he even think about showing up?
I know, right?
Wow, so brazen.
If it were me, I'd never come in.
What on earth are you doing?
How come Park Hyeon-ung
is able to take the exams?
For messing up her mock exams,
Su-jeong must now get tier-one marks
in all subjects in the midterms.
I already told you this.
Please have your tea.
If this is how it is, I can't promise you
Superintendent of Education.
Why can't Su-jeong get into tier one
when the others manage to?
I pay you considerably more
than the others do. Is it not enough?
For crying out loud!
It's not my fault
your daughter is a brickhead.
Excuse me?
The others all do it,
so what is it with Su-jeong?
Why set the table
if she can't handle a spoon?
Why are you so brazen?
The Superintendent of Education role?
I can get it without your help.
It's you who has a lot to lose, not me.
Can Su-jeong get into college without me?
So just stay out of it, okay?
I'll handle everything.
And we're in a café. Mind your manners.
Oh, you gave me a fright.
-What are these?
-Hold them up.
What?
Didn't you get over it all
when you ran around the track?
No, I didn't.
It's now past six o'clock,
and I need to add RAM to my computer…
What on earth is the matter with you?
Damn it.
It's Inspector Na Hwa-jin.
-I don't think I recognize him anymore.
-What?
He won't even try
to hear Park Hyeon-ung out!
And he only sides with Mr. Cheon.
For God's sake.
That personal vendetta thing…
It's not like that at all.
Then what is it?
Ever since visiting Han Ye-ri,
Inspector Na Hwa-jin
has been keeping an eye on Mr. Cheon.
He told me to keep looking
into Mr. Cheon's students.
That's why I looked into Noavis Institute
and paid them a visit.
Really?
Yes.
Then why was I the only one
who didn't know?
Why?
Well…
He said you're not very good
at deceiving other people
and that you're a terrible liar.
Damn it.
Gosh.
Whoa.
Deputy Bong.
What's gotten into her?
She says she's acting like this
because she feels guilty.
You call that fast?
Why did you do it?
Why did you pretend
you weren't suspicious of Mr. Cheon?
I didn't pretend.
I hoped otherwise.
I hoped there would be
at least one teacher like that.
I should've known better.
Why didn't you say anything?
I think you could've told me.
Me, of all people.
No, I think you should've told me.
I doubted your intention.
You made me doubt you!
Han-rim.
Yes, sir!
We aren't strangers.
Let's do as we always have.
All right?
Understood, sir!
-That bastard Cheon Sang-yeol did this.
-Damn it.
He's not the type to sit around.
We'll have much more to do.
Where are you going?
I said we'll have more to do.
I was just…
Come here. Just stay here.
Mr. Na Hwa-jin?
We're from the police.
We received reports
that you harmed innocent students
during your time as inspector
at Daehan High and Guun High.
We are enforcing search and seizure
of the ERPB for abuse of power
and violations of recruitment laws.
Following a large-scale search and seizure
of the ERPB,
amid a personal revenge scandal,
the prosecution is investigating
Minister Choi on charges of tax evasion.
They said they would protect
educational rights,
so I had no idea
they would attack our teachers like this.
Especially not someone like Mr. Cheon.
How do you see the ERPB's investigation
into teacher Cheon Sang-yeol?
It feels like the ERPB jumped the gun.
After it was revealed
that the ERPB was borne out
of a personal vendetta
by the victim's father and fiancé
over a two-year-old case,
it seems they tried to muddy the waters
by shifting their targets
from students to teachers.
They likely targeted a well-known figure
like Cheon Sang-yeol
for similar reasons.
It looks like Choi Gang-seok
has screwed up big time.
Should we run some articles?
How about we corner the ERPB
and push to impeach the president?
"We were duped by Minister Choi
when he first proposed the ERPB bill."
Perfect time to shift the blame, isn't it?
Announce we'll hold
a Board of Education meeting.
In the hiring of the inspector,
there was abuse of power
by the Minister of Education.
Do you admit it?
It all played out exactly as you expected.
Impressive connections, don't you think?
The fact that the prosecution,
the police, the press,
and even the tax office
all operated as one is just…
I bet even the president can't match that.
Is this the time to be impressed?
Shouldn't we do something?
We have to stay locked up here
until next week anyway.
Next week? Why?
Chukmyeong High's exams are next week.
They won't let us do anything before then.
Goddamn it.
S sub n equals n squared times a sub n.
Something should come to mind
when you see this.
Right, focus on me.
Okay, here it's n plus one squared
times a sub n plus one…
You're here.
Please take a seat.
I saw you took care of the ERPB
all on your own.
All I have are my connections.
-You were a great help too.
-It was nothing.
Enough about the ERPB.
What about Su-jeong?
Right, ma'am.
What is this?
Tell Su-jeong to memorize it all.
Since she can't handle a spoon,
we should spoon-feed her.
You didn't show the other kids, right?
Please take care of my fundraiser
for the Superintendent of Education.
Don't worry.
We will donate enough
to have your funding overflowing.
If this exam goes well,
you'll be the Superintendent of Education.
My gosh.
When I'm told to provide backup support,
I send necessary materials
to the inspectors and look things up…
You won't get anything
from questioning him.
He's just a public official
who does what his superiors tell him.
Don't waste your energy and let him go.
-Deputy Bong.
-Hey.
They said I'm free to go now.
Bring that thing to me.
Pardon? Bring what…
The assignment transfer application.
I'll sign it off for you,
so bring it to me.
You wanted it.
I thought about it again,
and I've changed my mind a little.
Just bring it, you brat.
But I really thought about it again--
Just bring it to me!
Yes, sir.
-Assignment transfer?
-No, but…
-I really--
-Hurry up!
Yes, sir. I'll go and get it.
I AM REQUESTING A TRANSFER OF…
Please just take a look.
Wait…
The way things are now,
staying at the ERPB won't do you any good.
Inspector Na Hwa-jin,
you sign it too.
I won't think of it as you whining,
so stand tall.
Keep your chin up.
Goodbye.
Oops, sorry.
What? Get back to studying.
Quick, pick it up. It's in the way.
You'll make him cry.
Good morning.
Put your textbooks away,
and shut the other door.
Good luck on the exam.
Take care, sir.
-Goodbye, sir.
-You did well.
What was your real motive
for establishing the ERPB?
Do you seek to avenge your daughter?
Or are you trying
to use your dead daughter
for political gain?
Why did you target the teacher
Cheon Sang-yeol?
As the public turned against you
over revenge allegations,
weren't you deflecting?
EXAM MANAGEMENT OFFICE
RESTRICTED AREA
EXAM MARKING PROGRAM
SELECT TOPIC: CALCULUS
Can you pass that to me?
JUNG SU-JEONG
SUBJECT: CALCULUS
It's correct.
JUNG SU-JEONG, SCORE: 0
Pass me the math exam paper.
Here.
-Pass me the English exam paper.
-Here.
What? What's going on?
Stop the exam immediately.
-What do you mean?
-Stop right now.
Those at the back! Collect all exam papers
and answer sheets. Now!
-The exam isn't over yet, sir.
-This is…
What are you waiting for? Do it now!
The exam paper is…
Wait!
What?
The exam isn't over yet.
Damn it.
-Collect them right now!
-Stop right there.
Guys, sit down.
You have to take your exam.
That's right. Good.
You were so worried
the kids might get distracted.
Is there a particular reason
they shouldn't take their exams?
They're the wrong exam papers.
We'll find out what happened,
void all exams, and retake them.
No. There will be no retakes.
Someone switched the exam…
The ERPB replaced the exam papers.
How…
-How did the ERPB…
-I know, right?
We were all locked up at
the police station, so how did we do it?
Inspector Na Hwa-jin,
you sign it too.
MINISTER OF EDUCATION
REPLACE THE EXAM PAPERS
TEAM LEADER
CHEON SANG-YEOL SON OF A BITCH
CHUKMYEONG HIGH GUIDE.PDF
PS I'M STEALING THEM.
MY HIGH SCHOOL DREAMS HAVE COME TRUE
It's clear you tampered with the exam,
so it stops now.
Give that here. Stop it. Stop working.
Stop working, you punk!
Let go!
Let go, you jerk!
Mr. Cheon!
You must not cause a disturbance
or be disruptive during exams,
even if you are a teacher.
Damn it.
Damn you, ERPB!
Mr. Cheon!
You damn bastard!
ERPB SPECIAL PROJECT
Mic test. One, two.
Hello, this is
the Educational Rights Protection Bureau.
Please stop your exam for a moment
and look at the screen.
A special video will start shortly.
Title.
The Reason the ERPB
Replaced the Exam Papers.
The reason.
THE REASON THE ERPB
REPLACED THE EXAM PAPERS
On Mr. Cheon's original exam paper,
the answer to question one
was "one over two."
Being multiple choice,
the answer was number one.
What about Jung Su-jeong?
Jung Su-jeong's answer to question one is…
number one too.
And the answer
to written-response question one
was "three cosine theta
equals four cosine cubed theta
minus three cosine theta."
What about Jung Su-jeong?
Jung Su-jeong's answer is…
also "cosine three theta
equals four cosine cubed theta
minus three cosine theta."
Today, Jung Su-jeong took the exam
with the exam papers replaced by the ERPB.
Her math score is
zero.
But the thing is…
If you compare the math exam paper
Mr. Cheon had originally set
with Jung Su-jeong's answer card,
the score would be 100.
The exam questions were actually the same.
Only the order of the questions
had changed.
A top student who has always ranked 11th
in her year got a zero.
She may not have felt well today,
or she may have misaligned her answers
by one row.
Even so, it's too much of a coincidence
that all her answers match
the order of the questions
on the exam paper
Mr. Cheon had originally set.
That's right.
Destroying evidence
is a serious criminal offense!
-Were the answers on her hands?
-Is she crazy?
What is this?
Tell Su-jeong to memorize it all.
Since she can't handle a spoon,
we should spoon-feed her.
You didn't show…
No. This is nothing.
Guys, it's nothing.
Tell Su-jeong to memorize it all.
You didn't show the other kids, right?
Please take care of my fundraiser
for the Superintendent of Education.
Don't worry. We will donate enough
to have your funding overflowing.
If this exam goes well,
you'll be the Superintendent of Education.
My gosh.
Guys, it's really nothing!
Mr. Cheon, is this real?
Don't you trust me?
-How could you?
-Everyone, sit down. Okay?
I'll explain. No!
-Da-yeon.
-We studied so damn hard!
We have to go to SNU together, Da-yeon.
Don't you trust me? Seriously?
Will that give you enough energy to study?
Here, have more.
You've turned out well.
Just keep growing like that.
Let me deal
with trash like Cheon Sang-yeol.
I'll kick his butt.
Thanks for the food. I'm off.
Don't stay out too late.
You believe that?
-No, guys.
-Did you tell her?
-I didn't.
-Did you really tell her?
Guys, I really didn't!
I'm Hwang Gi-tae,
the Mirae Daehan Party leader.
As I mentioned
in the last press conference,
the Educational Rights Protection Bureau
was created out of personal vendetta.
But there is a bigger problem.
They cannot be controlled,
no matter what they do,
if they operate under the pretext
of ERPB activity,
simply due to the extralegal Article 8
of the Establishment Act.
"All acts by an inspector
during on-site guidance and investigations
are not subject
to legal and institutional restrictions."
Even if the inspector committed murder,
it would not be in violation of the law.
Right now, you may be satisfied
with their actions.
But in the future,
an irreparable tragedy is bound to occur.
-Watch your mouth.
-Quiet down over there.
-Stop talking nonsense.
-You know we're right!
-Please be quiet.
-Minister of Education.
Do you remember the trial two years ago?
I have met someone
who clearly remembers that day.
Is the prison guard,
Mr. Yoon Sun-yeol, present?
-Yes, sir.
-Please come forward.
Would you tell us what you witnessed
that day as it happened?
As we escorted the accused, Cho Gyu-cheol,
to the transport vehicle after the trial,
a man drove his car at him.
Is this the man you are talking about?
Yes, that's correct.
Although it remained as an attempt,
the inspector was so enraged
that he tried to commit murder.
And the Minister of Education appointed
this person as the ERPB inspector.
Do these people really have any right
to discuss education?
The ERPB must be abolished at all costs.
Mr. Yoon, you may return to your seat.
Minister Choi,
you may make your counterarguments.
Well…
Before I proceed,
I believe
there's a far more important issue
that needs to be addressed first.
Mr. Chairperson, please restrict
the discussion to relevant issues!
Please restrict it!
Please be quiet.
I will proceed as I see fit.
Not long ago, the ERPB conducted
a full-scale investigation
into Chukmyeong Foreign Language High.
As a result,
we uncovered evidence of collusion
among Cheon Sang-yeol, the parents,
and Noavis Institute
to manipulate the grades.
Cheon Sang-yeol
not only leaked exam questions
through Noavis Institute in advance,
but he even leaked the exam papers
for the recent midterms.
No way…
Now I will disclose
the names of parents involved
with Cheon Sang-yeol
in the manipulation of grades.
PH Group Chairman's wife, Kim Yeong-ran.
Oh my God!
Daehan Media owner, Choi Pil-geun.
Former NTS Commissioner, Joo Hyeon-ju.
Former Chief Prosecutor
of Seoul Western District, Kim Jin-cheol.
Doil Semiconductors CEO, Lee Jin-bong.
Former Minister of Environment,
Kim Hui-jin.
Researcher at Seo Bio, Ma Seong-hun.
Dermatologist, Song Eun-yeong.
Former MCST Vice Minister, Kim Jeong-ho.
Ilseong Pharmaceuticals CEO, Ko Tae-hyeon.
Hyeonil Corporation CEO, Kim Sang-i.
Bareun Bank Yeouido Branch Manager,
Kwon Min-ho.
And lastly,
current member of the National Assembly,
Lee Cheol-myeon.
-Lee Cheol-myeon?
-What?
-Really?
-I think it's true.
-Hey, take photos.
What are you trying to do?
This is slander!
-This is slander.
-It's slander!
I'm going to sue you for defamation!
Shut up!
Or your damn child's face
will be all over the news.
Are you not ashamed?
Whenever your child's education
is discussed,
why do you,
regardless of party or profession,
cover your eyes, mouths, and ears,
acting like fools?
A teacher,
who should have been the fairest judge,
pressured a student
from a difficult background
and sabotaged their grades,
holding back their potential.
How can you call him a teacher?
Not everyone who is called a teacher
is truly a teacher.
Did you say the ERPB is an organization
that only goes after children?
Did you say we're now attacking teachers
only to avoid that allegation?
You're wrong.
The ERPB does not stand
with either the teachers or the students.
We stand with the victims.
The ERPB exists
for those who have suffered
when a student or a teacher
could not live up to their role.
If you call this a personal vendetta,
then it is.
Someone needs to step up and take revenge
when the law fails.
Only then can the victims
live their lives with peace of mind.
I will find every person
who got into college unfairly
and the adults who were party to that.
I will find them all
and show them
what real fairness looks like.
I hope good teachers don't get called out
because of a few bad apples.
Please
act accordingly.
Adults should act like adults
and teachers like teachers.
Jung Su-jeong, where are you?
Hurry home already!
And I'm saying this just in case.
Don't even think about
trying to leave the country.
You're all under a travel ban.
Deputy Bong's equipment worked wonders.
-It's a really expensive…
-Hey.
-Should I carry that for you?
-No, I'm fine.
-Teach him how to pack.
-Ma'am!
Thank you.
Just do as you always have.
-I recorded…
-So…
What? Deputy Bong,
did you have something to say?
No, it's nothing.
Why are you crying, dude?
You'd better head back and study.
You've got this, right?
Yes, sir.
All you need to do now is study hard.
Good luck.
Where did you get the list of the people
who manipulated the grades?
I told each of them I'd let them off
if they gave me one name,
and they all told me.
Nice.
All I did was buy him one cup of tea
during the consultation.
We will speak when my attorney gets here!
So what? I'm an assemblyman.
Don't touch me!
Attorney Kang, where are you?
-Why the hell aren't you here already?
-Please sit.
I want to show you
how you ruined a child's life.
Subtitle translation by: Lisa Kim