Inmate 1625!
Hey! Get off him!
Let's get you treated.
The wound is quite deep.
We'll have to keep an eye on him
as he continues his treatment.
How is Min Ji-ung?
He wasn't hurt.
We've separated him from the attacker.
Notify me
once you've questioned the attacker.
Ms. Choi
was the only adult who was good to me.
And to such a teacher, I…
I will live with remorse
for the rest of my life
and repent until I die.
I will not live a single moment
of my life in peace.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
What are you, a saint?
You'd be a psychopath
if you didn't feel anything.
What did I tell you?
That you'd see Cho Gyu-cheol,
and a fire would burn in your heart
and drive you crazy.
It's a fire neither of us
can ever extinguish.
I told you, you would have to decide.
Whether to live as Ga-yun's fiancé
or as an ERPB inspector.
You did well.
Well done.
Is that all you have to say?
Do you want me to pat you on the head
and compliment you?
Yes, please do.
Get lost, you punk!
Gosh.
Let's go out tonight for some soju.
Why aren't you answering?
Living as Choi Gang-seok's son-in-law
wasn't one of the options.
Get out, you punk!
You can walk!
Come on, we're almost there.
You never let anything go, do you? Jesus.
All I'm saying is
that it wasn't one of the choices.
-You're feeling guilty--
-But I admitted it!
-You're here, sir.
-Hello, sir.
Let's cut the greetings.
How's the drug investigation going?
We have officially requested cooperation
from the police,
and we're searching schools
for hidden drugs.
The official urine-test request form
for every school
has been uploaded
for the full-scale investigation.
And the gambling case?
We're tracking
the gambling site's IP address.
We've set it up to track them
through the loan sharks.
This case is also serious.
-Minister!
-Keep on top of it.
-Sir, you can't act like this here.
-Minister!
-I said you can't do this.
Please, Minister.
You need to follow the procedure
to see the minister.
Who cares about the procedure? Minister!
-What's going on?
-Minister!
Minister!
Please just take a look at this.
This is the damage report
from my own investigation.
And
these are
formal complaints.
Just a moment.
One moment, please!
And these are medical records.
And this is… Just a moment.
Where did it go?
Please take a look at it.
Please!
Please have a seat.
-Please have a seat.
-Here.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I have no one to talk to about this,
and no one will listen.
And it's not as if my son is innocent.
You came to the right place.
How can I help you?
My punk of a son…
Our sales for the third quarter increased
by 18% compared to last year.
Our operating profit margin also…
Hello?
You took your fucking time to answer.
You're Lee Jae-yun's father, right?
-Look.
-Fucking answer me.
I said answer me!
Who is this?
You don't need to know who I am.
Just pay off your goddamn son's debt.
I played a game.
A game?
Did you buy in-game items?
How much do you owe exactly?
Is it about 100,000 or 200,000 won?
We're asking you!
How much is the debt?
About 85 million won…
What?
Eighty-five million won?
Oh my God.
Wait.
What on earth did you do?
What kind of game did you play?
TEACH YOU A LESSON
Jae-yun.
Mom and Dad
paid off your debt.
Everyone makes mistakes.
You just can't make the same one again.
I'm sure Jae-yun will do better now.
What matters is that you learn from this…
and never do it again.
Let's eat.
Why are you crying?
Don't cry.
50,000 WON SIGN-UP BONUS
SURPRISE COUPON, CLICK NOW
VIP GAME ROOM
UNLIMITED BONUS EVENT FOR A LIMITED TIME
You little punk!
You punk!
We only just paid off your debt,
and you gamble again? You punk!
-You little punk.
-Honey, please don't…
Just read webtoons on this
when you're bored.
I won't gamble.
I'm going to read just one webtoon.
It's all right.
-Just a moment.
-Look.
-Hold on.
-Your kid is in debt.
That means you gotta pay it back.
It's fine. Just stay seated!
If your damn kid screws up,
you take the beating for them.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I really need…
my severance pay.
You see,
I've tried everything I could.
I put him on impulse-control medication
prescribed by a neuropsychiatrist.
I even went to see a shaman.
I already reported it to the police
a long time ago.
But they say
they can't do anything.
Even if you block
the gambling site's IP address,
all they have to do
is switch to a new one.
There were
so many damn reviews and approvals.
It took me six months
to get this paperwork done.
And all the while,
time just kept slipping by.
Please take a look at this.
My son ran away from home.
I don't even know if he's alive.
I wasn't sure how to deliver this to you.
I'm sorry, Minister!
I'm not sure
how I should give this to you.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to say
anything else to us.
NAKWON HIGH SCHOOL
Everyone, say hello.
This is Bong Geun-dae, a new student
joining our class from today.
Say hi.
Hi, I'm Bong Geun-dae. I'm new here.
Why don't you sit over there
in front of Seong-bin?
Seong-bin,
have you heard from Jae-yun yet?
-No.
-If you do, let me know right away.
Okay.
-Have a great day!
-Yes, ma'am!
I won!
I won again!
How much did you win?
-One million won.
-Bull!
Look. It's for real.
Another jackpot!
-Too bad.
-Damn it.
Fucking hell!
I'm so done.
Yes, 200,000 won!
Fuck, that was close.
My mom would've lost her shit.
-What?
Goddamn it!
What the hell are you staring at, dumbass?
They say online gambling
wouldn't survive without teenagers.
Our recent online gambling busts showed
that over 50% of their users were minors.
There was even a 9-year-old. A 9-year-old!
Loan sharks are always
around kids who gamble.
-There--
-A few million won is nothing.
Those kids owe hundreds of millions!
They owe…
There have also been many cases
where kids, like Jae-yun,
have run away from home.
Gambling is one thing,
but the related crimes
are just as serious.
Most of it is to pay off debts.
We will catch these punks.
But we can't do it alone.
We'll need help from other departments.
They say it takes a village
to raise a child.
The police, prosecutors, the MSIT,
and the Ministry of Justice
must all cooperate.
If they refuse to,
I'll have to drag them in by the collar.
But I think they're all higher up
in the chain than us.
The kids' card wins hands down.
Good day, sir.
Where were you at?
I came straight from home.
Dumbass. Not that. Which school?
Guun High.
I got it! Hell yeah!
-What is it? Did you hit it big?
-Really?
How much?
Fuck, it's a million won.
-A million.
-A million?
-You might actually buy a motorcycle.
-What is that?
I won, so dinner's on me tonight.
Hey! Anyone up for some good food?
Fuck, Seong-bin is buying today!
I hit the jackpot, suckers!
I want octopus jjamppong!
-Seafood for me!
-Beef for me.
-Sure.
-I'll have braised pork belly!
Maybe black bean noodles?
I'm all in on Banker until the run breaks.
Hey, hold on.
Trust me, let's bet on "tie."
The streak's gonna break.
Don't you know not to trust anyone
going for a tie?
You mean full house, not tie, you idiot.
The Banker is drawing.
What is it?
Can you let me in too?
I told you it's just a game.
Isn't it like gambling?
I saw you win money.
Gambling is a scary thing.
This is just a game. A money-making one.
Don't you play with your own money?
Who uses their own money?
You get a free bonus when you join.
Seong-bin here flipped the free bonus
and bought an RTX 5090 Ti graphics card.
-An RTX 5090 Ti? That's super expensive.
-Yeah.
You can do it too.
-Shall I show you?
-Yeah.
If you sign up here
and enter my ID for the referral,
you get an extra 50,000 won.
Just a moment.
Do I really get free money?
For God's sake!
Give me that.
First, sign up.
Create your password.
And for the code…
Hey, see that?
You got 50,000 won.
Since you don't know anything,
start with Odd or Even.
-Odd or Even?
-Hurry.
-Just pick.
-Pick.
I'll go with odd.
-Tap on it.
-Right.
-This guy got it.
-Let's see.
You've got the touch.
Even.
Hey, what the hell?
Here.
This kid, who approached me first,
is the recruiter.
He's Seong-bin,
and he works with a few shills.
At first, they say they've won big,
getting you curious and interested.
Then they exclude you
from the conversation.
And if you don't gamble,
they isolate you like an outcast.
They say "game" instead of "gambling."
It's less off-putting.
Is the next move
for Deputy Director Bong to lose money?
But there's something I don't understand.
Gambling is basically math.
If you know middle school math
and know how to apply statistics,
it's a system where you can't lose money.
I see.
Is that so?
You don't have to lose money on purpose.
Win if you can.
Then what do I do with the money I win?
It's yours as a bonus.
Come on.
You don't believe me.
-Do you?
-Are you serious?
If you win it yourself, what can I say?
All right.
-The 5090 graphics card…
-Is that really allowed?
Yeah, you'll see.
What do I do with the money I win?
It's yours as a bonus.
ODD
EVEN
YOUR BALANCE IS ZERO
RECHARGE
What's up with this guy?
You must have been at it all night.
Did you win?
I lost.
How much?
-A million.
-You crazy bastard.
I told you to only use the bonus cash.
Are you going to do anything? Win it back?
How do I win it back?
You know Martingale's
miraculous betting strategy?
My good friend Martingale
invented a method where you can't lose.
You double your bet every time you lose.
If you lose 100 won, you bet 200 won.
If you lose 200 won? 400 won.
If you lose 400 won?
-800 won?
-That's right.
You're bound to win eventually.
We just need to win once.
You're right.
If you win just once, you break even.
Exactly.
It's an insane, unbeatable method.
You can't lose as long as you have money.
I'm the king of connections around here.
I know a guy who can lend you money.
Do you want some?
What's there to think about, man?
Hello.
I've got a friend who needs some cash.
Yes, about a million won?
He says he'll lend it to you,
but he needs some collateral.
-Collateral?
-Nothing big.
-Just your parents' numbers.
-My parents' numbers?
It's just a formality.
We're not going to lose anyway.
Martingale, remember?
But didn't you say it was a million won?
I only received 800,000 won.
Upfront interest, dumbass.
He takes 20% and gives you the rest.
The interest rate is 3% per day.
For 1,000,000 won, 3% is 30,000 won.
The next day, it's not 3% of 1,000,000 won
but 3% of 1,030,000 won after interest.
It's calculated as compound interest.
After a month,
800,000 won becomes 2,427,243 won.
And after 100 days,
it becomes 19,218,364 won.
After a year,
it becomes 48,482,008,003 won.
You did well. Okay?
Good job. Well done.
Deputy Bong, my man. You lost big time,
so they'll come down on you soon.
Don't cry.
Hello?
Are you Bong Geun-dae's mom?
-What?
-Answer me, damn it!
Watch your mouth.
Why would I be Bong Geun-dae's mom?
Geun-dae's mom, who is it?
-My mom?
-Be quiet! She's on the phone.
Yes, I'm Geun-dae's mom.
You need to pay off your son's debt.
Did my son gamble again?
How much this time?
The kid plays on a fucking grand scale.
20 million.
-Hey, lady. Pay me back fast.
-You did well.
The interest alone
will be 600,000 won tomorrow.
I can't pay it back.
I've paid his debts time and again.
Trying to save this fool
will destroy my family.
I've given up on Geun-dae.
Do as you wish. Kill him or don't.
Damn it.
He's calling me again.
Again! For God's sake.
What do we do now?
These recruiters
are probably just small fry.
Operations like this run on cash.
The guys actually handling the money
know who's at the top.
Our Deputy Bong lost big time, right?
So they'll have the enforcers
come after you.
We catch those guys
and take down… those at the top.
Come on, don't cry.
Okay.
NAKWON HIGH SCHOOL
There's no sign of the enforcers.
You're watching me closely, right?
I'm close by, watching over you.
Damn it.
I picked the wrong spot.
DELICIOUS GIMBAP, TTEOKBOKKI,
TWIGIM, SUNDAE
-Hello!
-Hi, welcome.
-Just one portion, please.
-Order more.
-Come on, here. I'll give you lots.
-Damn.
That's awesome. Thank you.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
-How sweet.
-It looks so good.
-Enjoy.
-We will. Thank you.
Ma'am, can I please get one tteokbokki?
All right.
-Please mix in some twigim.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Sure, please enjoy.
Unlock your phones and hand them over.
Hurry up!
Hurry up and hand them over.
Hurry up.
Just fucking hand them over!
Hey.
I said hand it over.
It's the fingerprint recognition.
-It's not working.
-Give it here.
-Oh no.
-Damn it.
-I'm sorry.
-Fucking hell.
For fuck's sake.
Oh no.
My phone
fell into the sewer.
For fuck's sake.
You're a real piece of work.
I'm sorry.
INSPECTOR IM HAN-RIM
I definitely saw him make it this far.
I watched him from over there,
making eye contact.
-The call cannot be connected.
-He's not answering.
Get that CCTV footage. Let's go.
My money!
Pay me back, or you're all fucking dead.
Your parents won't pay your debts anymore.
You'll have to earn the money
to pay me back.
Take this. Take it.
Go empty the ice cream shop's cash box.
Move it!
Good.
Good job.
Get in.
If you don't do it,
you'll be dead.
You get what I'm saying?
-Why are you--
-Hold it. I said hold it properly.
-No, I can't.
-Get out, moron.
-I can't.
-Get out.
-Get the fuck out.
-I really can't.
-I said get the fuck out.
-No, I really can't do it.
For fuck's sake.
-You little shit.
-What…
Do you know who I am, moron?
-Hey!
-What the…
-I'm scared.
-Hey!
Sir, are you all right? Get it together.
Shit.
Run the plate
and track the vehicle on the CCTV.
I'll go to traffic control
and get their cooperation.
Yes, sir.
We don't have time.
Get your head together.
It's all my fault.
I lost Deputy Director Bong
because of that fucking tteokbokki!
What if something happens to him
because of me?
Sergeant Im Han-rim!
That's right, Sergeant Im Han-rim.
You can make up for mistakes,
but giving up is failure.
Understood?
Yes, sir. Understood!
Get moving.
What the hell?
Where did all the morons go?
Seriously, for fuck's sake.
Fucking hell. Hey!
I told you to close your eyes.
Don't push me.
Wait a moment.
-Wait.
-Hello, boss!
You fucking bastards.
Really? You're eating now?
I'm sorry, bro.
Do I have to deal with kids myself?
-Damn it.
-I'm sorry!
-Get your act together.
-Yes, bro!
Fucking morons.
-Good night.
This moron is a newbie.
Train him and get him started.
Yes, bro!
Fucking follow me.
That's my bag.
-For fuck's sake. Come with me.
-Wait…
-Sit.
-Sorry?
-I said sit.
-Right.
Okay.
Look. This is what you'll be doing, okay?
Now, tonight… See these numbers?
Send out a text to all of them.
Got it?
Yes.
You look dumb as fuck.
Goddamn it.
TEXT RECIPIENT LIST
IT'S BONG, I'VE BEEN TAKEN
You're…
We're all being watched here.
They're watching our monitors too.
Who the fuck is talking?
Fucking hell. Look at me.
You son of a bitch.
When did I say you could open your trap?
You're fucking pissing me off,
you goddamn bastard.
You fucking moron.
Why don't you listen?
You fucking bastard.
Don't fucking act
like you're in pain, all right?
50,000 WON BONUS
MESSAGE HAS BEEN SENT
Get the hell out, goddamn dumbasses.
You fucking morons.
You're fucking useless.
I said get the hell out!
Get back to work, you fuckers.
-Damn it.
-What's the boss flipping over now?
There's a problem
with the Cambodian server.
I hear it's lagging
because of damn traffic spikes.
-Damn complaint calls keep coming in.
-I know, fuck.
-That's not on us.
-Why is he taking it out on us? Damn it.
Are you asleep?
Wow, I already feel like fucking shit,
and you're asleep.
Fine, I'll make sure
you fucking stay asleep.
Please!
I'll put you to sleep forever, you fucker.
Just a moment.
I think I can do it.
-Do what?
-The Cambodian server.
I think you need to set up a reverse proxy
to distribute the traffic.
-Are you good with computers?
-Yes, I love computers.
-Yeah? Come here.
-Okay.
Come on, this way.
I told you
the server keeps fucking crashing.
-Bro.
-Why do you keep…
What?
I think you should talk to this guy.
Since there's lag,
there are a few ways
to reduce the server load.
What I'm doing is setting up
something called a reverse proxy,
which is like a gatekeeper
that sits in front of the server.
Okay, go ahead.
If it doesn't work,
I'm going to gouge your eyes out.
That way, you saw nothing.
Okay?
Yes.
Even a nobody has talent, don't they?
Take it.
You enjoy, all right? Here.
Here, have some water too.
He's asleep again.
Damn it.
-What's wrong with this guy?
-He kept dozing off.
Hey.
You've got to be kidding me. Fucking hell.
Get rid of him.
-Yes, sir.
Hey, get up. For God's sake.
Don't worry about him.
It turned out to be a ghost car.
And it went off CCTV
after Susaek interchange.
We tracked his phone,
but it was broken.
And the kids?
Inspector Im Han-rim is looking for--
Get in, you punk. Sit down.
Sit down.
I'm telling the truth.
All I did was make the kids play the game.
I don't know where the company is.
Find it.
Which banner links
to those bastards' site?
Find it!
For God's sake.
VIP GAME ROOM
I'll head over to the MSIT
and get the information on…
What are you doing?
MUSANGOL
Mansin Aegi. Musangol Mansin Aegi.
Musangol Mansin Aegi?
What do you mean?
One of the banners
is flashing differently.
It's Morse code.
The duration of each flash
represents a letter.
"Bong Geun-dae. My location is…"
I found it.
Musangol Mansin Aegi.
MUSANGOL MANSIN AEGI SHRINE
There's nothing here.
Must've been a coincidence.
-This can't be a coincidence.
-But there's nothing here!
What if he saw the sign
from another building?
Im Han-rim.
Hey, you little asshole.
Go smoke outside.
You're rotting my lungs.
Bong Geun-dae!
Who are you?
-Hey, don't kill--
-Who are you?
What the fuck?
Hey, here.
Share this between you two.
You too.
Shit. What the hell?
Bong Geun-dae!
Has anyone seen Bong Geun-dae?
His eyes are a little small,
but they sparkle.
He gives major geek vibes,
but up close, he's got a cute face.
He's tall and looks like a smart cookie!
What the hell?
Answer me!
A cute face?
It's a girl.
Is she someone's sister?
What a dumbass. She's a girl.
Hey, Han-rim.
Don't get emotional, all right? Don't…
She's doing her hair.
Answer me.
-We're not here to kill them.
-No?
We're here to find
our guy with sparkling eyes.
-Im Han-rim.
-They won't answer me.
What a fucking joke.
Im Han-rim! Hey!
Fuck you!
What the fuck?
Fuck!
What are you doing?
Come here!
Bong Geun-dae!
-You're being too emotional, kid.
-Bong Geun-dae!
Inspector!
Are you all right?
-Are you hurt anywhere?
-No.
Are you grading cattle or something?
But it's not me that's important.
Their leader is upstairs.
And there are…
Im Han-rim, take care of them
and Deputy Bong.
He's tall and has sparkling eyes.
Very cute.
This way.
Hey!
Where's your leader?
Your leader!
Where is he?
Looks like you learned how to fight.
Hey, your…
Just go to sleep.
Hey!
Oh man, that jackass.
What a hassle.
Shit.
Fucking bastard.
You son of a bitch!
Get out.
Man, that was rough. Right?
Please spare me just this once.
Please spare me.
All right, fine.
If you're going to beg like that,
I guess I can spare you.
But not for free though.
Your crimes are countless.
You like games, don't you?
If you win a game, I'll spare you.
How does that sound?
A game?
You've seen Squid Game, right?
If you win, you live.
If you lose, I smack you. How's that?
We'll play rock, paper, scissors, okay?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Right, we go again.
Well…
-Rock, paper, scissors.
-I…
Wait! Wait a minute!
What? What is it?
No matter what I do,
I'll keep losing.
That's what you did to the kids.
Your crimes are countless.
Robbing them of their friends.
Robbing them of their family.
Robbing them
of the joy of their school days.
Breaking
their parents' hearts.
Get it together!
Last one.
Rock,
paper,
scissors.
Rock!
Fuck.
Jae-yun.
Please help me.
You're okay now.
You're okay.
There…
It's okay.
What's up with him?
He's scared.
Imagine what they must've done.
It's all coming back to him.
I'm going to go talk to them.
-Stay with him, okay?
-Okay.
You're his guardian angel.
Where are you…
You did great, Deputy Director Bong.
I saw you in a different light.
You were amazing.
You said you were watching over me.
Do you know how scared I was?
They held a knife up to my eye
and took my bag.
Don't cry. I am really sorry.
I'll never lose you again.
I'll protect you for life.
Just forget it…
For life?
Why would you protect me for life?
Oh, maybe not for life.
Just during work hours?
Oh, yeah.
What was that stuff you said
when you came looking for me?
His eyes are a little small,
but they sparkle.
He gives major geek vibes,
but up close, he's got a cute face.
He's tall and looks like a smart cookie!
Oh, I was just
describing you?
I've never in my life heard
that my eyes are small.
My eyes aren't very big,
but they're not that small either.
Take a good look.
Are they really that small?
Are they?
They're not, right?
Wow, that's…
-Right?
-Have you seen this?
Shall we take a look?
Don't change the subject.
Just say my eyes aren't small.
Have you been here before? It's beautiful.
When would I have come here?
This place… It's really beautiful.
You have very big eyes.
They're not big.
They're just not small either.
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Thanks to you,
Jae-yun's health has improved.
Right.
But I don't think
I deserve to be a father.
I didn't even know
Jae-yun had been dragged off
and suffered all that.
All the while, I was blaming that damn kid
for running away from home.
But because you didn't give up on him
and came to the ERPB for help,
we were able to save Jae-yun
and the other kids.
Minister.
I'm glad Jae-yun is back,
but honestly,
I'm not sure if I've got it in me.
I'm scared he'll start gambling again.
You would've given up already
if you were going to.
Just like you always have,
don't give up this time either.
That's the only way you can change him.
You won't be alone.
The ERPB will help you.
Thank you.
I'VE BEEN MAKING FOOLISH MISTAKES
SINCE I STARTED GAMBLING
TEEN GAMBLING COUNSELING FORM
Will you tell him, or should I?
Jae-yun.
The one who sold you out
to the gambling operators
was me.
I'm the one who got you into gambling
in the first place.
And when you swore off gambling
and switched to a flip phone…
I'm not telling you to gamble.
Just read webtoons on this
when you're bored.
You fucking asshole.
How could you do this to me?
We've been joined at the hip
since elementary school!
We've been such close friends.
I had no choice.
They threatened to call my parents,
so I did as they told me to.
Sit down.
You will be punished accordingly.
At school,
you'll be suspended or expelled.
Outside of school,
you'll be punished under the law.
If you're lucky,
it might end with community service,
or you could go to prison.
This isn't fair.
It's all because of adults.
They used us to make money.
We're victims too!
What did you go through
to call yourself a victim?
Victims?
What about the parents
who lost their life savings and home
and even quit their jobs
because of their kid's gambling?
What about the father who's slapped
in public by someone half his age…
but still has to kneel and beg,
all because of his kid?
What about the mother
who scrubs greasy grills
in the kitchen of a barbecue joint
because the father can't do anything else
but watch their kid?
What about the father
who goes from the police to the ERPB,
even while being looked down on
and treated like some peddler,
begging and crying for his child
to be saved?
Victims?
They're the real victims.
You had countless chances to stop.
And you're the ones
who threw those chances away.
Do you really want to quit gambling
and be forgiven by the people around you?
Then admit you are perpetrators.
Never stop reflecting on yourselves
and never stop asking for forgiveness.
This is your last chance.
Here you go.
It's hot, isn't it?
Oscillate.
You earn money through labor.
There's no such thing
as a get-rich-quick scheme.
Keep scrubbing.
-Scrub your minds clean.
-You need more suds.
Hand it over.
That's it. Good.
That means you now have
98,320,000 won left to pay your parents.
You clean up your own mess.
Oh, and…
To page, press one. To record a message…
Your pagers.
4868253.
Do you remember what this means?
"I love you. Come quickly."
Love you.
Please give our phones back now.
We'll only make calls.
What high schooler
would use this nowadays?
Freedom is only granted
when you take responsibility.
And most importantly,
I don't believe a gambler's word.
I'll page you.
337337.
Oh man.
It's really fine.
After all, I'm the reason
your phone is broken.
It's just the screen that's broken.
It's still usable.
I just feel bad.
I said I'd protect you, but I failed.
So please, okay?
Just pick one.
There are so many phones here.
-Which is the latest?
-It's fine.
Come on, pick one.
-What's the latest--
-Oh?
Then I'll just take a quick look.
-Do you know this one?
-Yes.
They changed the CPU on this model,
so the Internet should be really fast.
-It's so cool.
-I see.
Look.
Right.
Sir, can I please get a flip phone?
-No, we don't need one.
-A flip phone.
I'm not the addictive type.
-Not anymore.
-Hello?
-I'm bringing another addict, sir.
-I'm not an addict.
-Sir, I'm not…
-Yes, sir.
Goodbye.
-Hwang Gi-tae!
-Hello.
One, two.
Hwang Gi-tae!
-Your shop is…
-Life is so tough.
-Here.
-Thank you.
In the latest poll,
Minister Choi Gang-seok
surpassed 50% approval for the first time,
outpacing opposition leader Hwang Gi-tae
by 17%.
Whether Minister Choi Gang-seok
will enter the presidential race…
-Well, then.
-Please look out for us.
Thank you.
This way, please.
-Thank you for treating us, sir.
-Thank you.
All right.
I see you're already out campaigning.
-Choi Gang-seok?
-Why is he here?
-Have a seat.
I'm a regular here. Great food.
Ma'am, can I get another tang here?
Just a moment, please.
Why are you visiting the markets
before even registering as a candidate?
Isn't that something you do
while campaigning?
-This looks delicious.
-Yes, it's good.
Minister Choi Gang-seok, have you heard?
Oh, right.
People don't really hear
the things said about them.
I heard rumors in Yeouido.
You're using your dead daughter
to make a run for president.
They say politics is heartless.
You're all ears when it's about others.
I hear the Mirae Daehan Party
is holding an emergency meeting today.
I guess you weren't told.
I wonder what they need to discuss
that they didn't tell you about.
Could they be planning
to replace their presidential candidate
because your approval ratings
are dropping?
Whose idea was this?
I'll head over
to the conference room right now.
I'm the Mirae Daehan Party leader!
Who's going to stop me?
What is it?
Sir, you have a visitor.
Do I look like I want company right now?
He has something to tell you
about the ERPB.
Subtitle translation by: Lisa Kim