Urine tests were conducted
in schools nationwide
under the ERPB's direction.
The ERPB stated the tests were intended
to detect and treat at an early stage
kidney abnormalities and diabetes-related
conditions among students.
While some are questioning
whether the tests are meant
to detect drug activity in schools,
several schools have refused to take part,
citing final examinations.
This is Seungyeon High School,
known as the most academically competitive
school in Gangnam.
It also sends the most students
to SNU Medical School nationwide.
You must know it well from living there.
My mom wanted me to go to this school,
so my family moved nearby
when I was seven.
Weren't you at a science school?
Seungyeon High School is known
for having very pushy parents.
CLASS S
This is the last exam
that counts for early admission.
If you blow this,
the CSAT is your only option.
Unless you want that, do well today.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's get started.
Is it Class 1, Class 2, and then Class S?
I told you this school sends
the most students to med school in Seoul.
This is a special class
for those aiming for med school.
It's basically a class
of the school's top students.
My boy!
Congratulations
on getting into SNU Medical School!
-My son!
-Congratulations!
This is huge!
Congrats!
Hyeon-min, congrats!
Who are you?
-We're from the ERPB.
-Hey, are you okay?
His nose is bleeding.
-Let's take him to the nurse's office.
-Okay.
-Here.
-Let's get you up.
Sir, where is the nurse's office?
-Turn left, then go down.
-Left? Okay, thank you.
-Here.
-Be careful.
-Hold his head from the back.
-Okay.
URINE TEST CHECKLIST
Class 6…
Stop the exam right now!
My kid can't finish the exam!
Do you want to see
my son and me die here today?
Will you take responsibility
if he doesn't get in?
Hyeon-min will take the exam
no matter what!
-Jung Hyeon-min!
-Ma'am.
He passed out in the middle of the exam.
How much did you get done?
It's okay. There's still time.
I already talked to the teacher,
so just finish the exam.
Can you get up?
Mom, I don't feel so good.
It's from staying up all night studying.
Everyone's the same.
Here.
But Mom,
I keep having weird thoughts.
Weird thoughts while studying
mean you're losing focus.
I've brought your medicine.
You'll feel better soon.
Here.
You're almost there.
You don't want all our hard work
to go to waste, do you?
Hang in there, son. For me?
All right, let's go.
TEACH YOU A LESSON
Attention, students.
There will now be an announcement
of special directives from the ERPB.
All students are to remain on campus
and prepare immediately for urine testing.
SON
Hyeon-min, how did the exam go?
Did you finish?
Why?
What? The ERPB?
They must be crazy.
Okay.
I'll head over to school now.
Call the other moms.
What? The ERPB?
Are they crazy?
The kids have to go to hagwon now.
Where do you think you're going?
Didn't you hear about the test?
We're going to hagwon.
Go after the urine test.
Our moms are coming. You can talk to them.
-What are they doing?
-What's the point of this?
Da-hui, what are you doing?
You'll be late for hagwon. Get going.
-You go ahead.
-What are they doing?
-Go quickly.
-What the hell are they doing?
What do you think you're doing?
-What do you think?
-Hyeon-min's mom, be quiet.
Do you realize
how critical this period is for the kids?
For top students, one point can move them
up or down several university tiers.
There may be no guns, but students
and parents are fighting a war.
So that's why you've put
lives on the line?
You must've heard the rumors.
This test includes a drug screening.
Drugs? Are you suggesting
our kids are on drugs?
Those kids are applying
to SNU Medical School.
-They're not like other kids.
-They all look the same to me.
Have you even thought about what it took
for our kids to get this far?
From birth through preschool,
elementary, middle, and high school,
and now their most crucial year,
they have never wasted a single second.
And what about the moms here?
We sleep an hour less than our kids,
wake up an hour earlier,
send them to hagwon, look for consultants…
If you want them tested,
do it after the CSAT.
Refusing the test will result
in a CSAT penalty. Is that okay?
What do you mean "penalty"?
Are you threatening us
with our kids' lives?
If I were, would you listen?
This is Daechi-dong!
You think you can handle the moms here?
Yes.
The ERPB can handle them.
Then go ahead.
If you want to see people die.
We're doing the test so no one dies.
So we can save even one life
before it's too late.
There's an ERPB-designated hospital.
Take your children there for testing
before school tomorrow.
If you don't,
you won't be able to handle
what comes next.
You're Jung Hyeon-min's mother, right?
Hyeon-min didn't look very well earlier.
Make sure you take him
for the test tomorrow.
By any chance,
do you know who I am?
Well, I've seen you on TV.
You're someone very important.
You hurt your hand
because of the EPRB, right?
Oh, no.
It was my fault.
I'm not trying to blame the ERPB.
I'm trying to help you.
Me? Why?
Providing opportunities
to those who need them
is my job as a politician.
Can I look at your hand again?
It doesn't look like a minor injury.
How about treatment on the outside?
Recently, an armed attack broke out
in a juvenile prison.
A juvenile offender
under the ERPB's supervision
was attacked with a weapon by an inmate.
It could have caused
serious harm or loss of life, but…
-What?
-Oh, nothing.
…the juvenile was unharmed.
However, the inmate who protected him
was the perpetrator of…
-Where is it?
-Well…
That way, sir.
-Lead the way. Hurry up.
-Yes, sir.
They deliberately chose where…
-I wonder where the toilet--
-You're making me more aware of it.
I already saw it all earlier.
Look at you trying so hard.
-Are you okay?
-Of course not.
-That damn photo.
-Come on.
-How did they get it?
-Let's go.
Are the Seungyeon High kids being tested?
Yes, they are.
Need some air?
Let's go outside.
Drink this.
Are you okay? Feeling better?
I'm feeling a bit better.
Good.
REPORT CARDS WERE DISTRIBUTED
TO STUDENTS TODAY
Report cards are out.
-They've also been sent by email. Check.
-Right.
I passed out during the exam
for that subject.
I'm sorry, Mom.
What did I tell you?
Kids like you who can't handle pressure
should at least take your meds properly.
Is it really that hard to take your meds?
Don't you feel sorry for me?
I've had to swallow my pride
in front of the other moms because of you.
Did I ever ask for recognition?
All I'm asking is for you to study.
If you knew how hard I've worked…
For God's sake…
Hyeon-min's goal is SNU Medical School.
I've heard you're a well-known consultant
for medical school admissions.
I'll start by assessing his level.
How advanced is he in his studies?
I've had him study ahead.
He's in first year middle school
but is doing first-year high school math.
He still hasn't finished high school math?
He'll catch up soon.
Our Hyeon-min is top in his grade.
A top student in a provincial school
becomes bottom-tier in Gangnam.
Don't even think about med school.
This isn't exactly the provinces.
We're next to Seoul.
You should meet my son first.
Once you do--
Do you know when moms in Gangnam
start preparing their kids
for SNU's med school?
The moment they're born.
They map out a 20-year plan,
from birth to med school,
and choose preschools, schools, hagwons,
and private tutors accordingly.
These kids have been preparing
for over a decade longer
than those who start in middle school.
By Hyeon-min's age,
he should've already finished studying
the core concepts of the CSAT.
He should be practicing questions
to avoid mistakes on the exam
and working on med school interviews,
essay writing, and English.
Do you understand
just how far behind Hyeon-min is?
Still, he's really…
Kids in Daechi-dong
are tackling questions at this level
right now.
How many of them
do you think Hyeon-min could answer?
DAECHI SKY REAL ESTATE
PRIME LISTING
A HOME THAT SENT KIDS TO SNU MED SCHOOL
GRAND PRIZE IN ENGLISH, JUNG HYEON-MIN
Do you really have to live
in a place like this?
It's within walking distance
of the school and hagwon,
and a bargain for Gangnam.
Besides, the two sons
who grew up here got into SNU.
I even got it with no markup.
I'm not sure about this.
A school is a school.
This area can't be that special.
You have no idea.
Seungyeon High has a med school prep class
just for the top ten students.
If you get into this class,
you're guaranteed SNU med school.
Hyeon-min's goal
is to get into this class.
But still, this place is just…
Aren't you upset?
Didn't your brother go to med school?
Does your family treat you two the same?
But thanks to him, I work at his clinic,
so don't be like that.
That's exactly why
you and I get treated like that
and why Hyeon-min does too.
I'll make sure
Hyeon-min gets into med school
so he's respected.
Who says he's not respected?
That's enough!
Don't be so discouraging.
Just take the door off.
Fine, I will.
I got it.
Okay, hold it.
GOAL
GET INTO SEUNGYEON HIGH!
GET INTO SNU MEDICAL SCHOOL!
Here.
I'm not the only one making a fuss.
All the moms around here are like this.
Okay.
Oh, Mom.
What about tutoring?
All the kids seem to have the same tutor.
I'm looking into it, so don't worry.
Keep studying.
Yeong-jun's mom, do you think
you can invite me to the moms' meetings?
Here.
Enjoy.
Forget about all the other moms.
Just stay on Da-hui's mom's good side.
She's the mama pig.
The mama pig?
You know how a sow
has all her piglets following her?
She has all the moms trailing after her,
so she's called the mama pig.
But it's not something just anyone can do.
Information is power for moms here.
And Da-hui's mom has all the connections
with academic coordinators,
admissions consultants,
and even hagwons
with special programs for SNU med school.
You're not a working mom, are you?
No, I'm not. Why?
Working moms, or parents who both work,
can't join this circle.
They just take information and act busy
when it actually matters.
But doctors and professors
get a free pass no matter what.
How come?
You need a strategic student profile
for early admissions.
Hospital volunteer work
and university lab research
make the ultimate student profile.
With Da-hui's mom, it's a done deal.
I'd better stay on her good side.
It's not bedtime yet.
I'm sorry.
I was just so sleepy.
You must be tired. Eat while you study.
Can I have a little more?
A full stomach makes you sleepy.
Your brain only needs glucose.
Just eat this and focus a bit more.
Okay?
Hi, honey.
We're already here,
and you live by yourself.
You can move to a cheaper studio
or move in with your mother.
It's all for Hyeon-min!
Once he succeeds,
it will all be worth it.
I didn't want to come empty-handed.
I hope you like it.
You didn't have to.
I came to see you because--
Every mom comes to see me
for the same reason.
And I already heard from Yeong-jun's mom.
Just come to a few of our meetings
and see how it goes.
Okay.
Was it? Was it okay?
What would you like?
-I'll have an iced latte.
-A latte.
-Double shot, please.
-Double shot? Okay.
DOUBLE SHOT
-This is already too much.
-This is only the start, okay?
Here you go.
Here's your latte.
-She's a natural.
-Yeah, you're right. It's Da-hui.
That's why she's at that level.
For math, Ms. Jung Da-eun is the best.
She gets kids into SNU med school.
MATH
JUNG DA-EUN
One downside is
that her academic background isn't great.
ENGLISH
OH BO-HYEON
It's easier if you start
by calculating 6 choose 2.
What's 6 choose 2?
Then what's 15 times 6?
-90.
-That's correct.
90 is correct. Try solving this one
and see if you understand.
REPORT CARD
YEAR 1, SEMESTER 1, 2024
Don't worry.
They say grades
depend on how much parents put in.
Go on.
For God's sake.
It turns out these plates come as a set.
If I'd known, I would've brought
the whole set last time.
You didn't have to.
I heard about Hyeon-min.
He didn't get into
the med school prep class again, right?
I got him the tutor you recommended,
and he goes to the same hagwon as Da-hui,
so I don't know what the problem is.
Sitting at a desk for hours
doesn't guarantee good grades.
Even with the same study time,
some kids take in 100%,
while others only take in 50%.
That's the difference in focus.
Is there a tutor for that too?
There are things a teacher can help with
and things they can't.
Hold on.
Here, try giving him this.
His focus will improve dramatically.
Da-hui and her older brother took it,
and their grades went up.
Hyeon-min.
I went through a lot to get this for you
so you can study better.
I know you'd do so well
if you really got your head in the game.
I hear this stuff is amazing.
You'll focus better
and be less nervous during exams.
All the kids around here take it.
Drink this.
This is an illegal drug.
You all look like you already knew.
It's an unapproved ADHD medication
in Korea.
Yet it has already been circulating
discreetly among mothers
because it's effective.
I'm sure you know.
In the urine tests,
the children tested positive
for methylphenidate and atomoxetine.
These two drugs
are only for high-risk patients
and are very rarely prescribed together.
In particular,
methylphenidate is classified
as a controlled psychotropic substance
under the Narcotics Control Act in Korea.
This means taking it
without a prescription is illegal.
It violates the Narcotics Control Act
and the Pharmaceutical Affairs Act,
making it a criminal offense.
It'll be okay.
Everyone here will be subject
to police questioning.
Inspector.
Yes?
The test results for Jung Hyeon-min
are concerning.
Hyeon-min's mom.
Where did Hyeon-min's mother go?
-Hyeon-min's mom? Where did she go?
-I think she went out that way.
Maybe to the bathroom?
I heard Hyeon-min's grades have gone up.
He must have been really determined.
He's completely changed.
He seems to have gotten mentally stronger.
I think he'll make it
into the med school prep class soon.
Still, the competition is really intense.
Do you know of any medicine
that's better than the one you gave me?
Well,
I could find out if I looked into it,
but that one should be enough.
I see.
My child's grades improved
after taking ADHD medication.
I'm looking for something more effective.
If anyone knows, please help.
Could you tell me what medication he took
that improved his grades?
They're no help at all.
I have the meds
last year's top med school entrant took.
Do you want it?
You're from the forum, right?
Yes.
TIER 1
Well done, my son.
Can you get
into the med school prep class now?
Yes, they told me
to join the class tomorrow.
That's great.
Well done.
JUNG HYEON-MIN'S MOTHER
She's still not picking up.
They found another substance
in Hyeon-min's system besides ADHD meds.
It's in the Heart Pills too.
What?
The amount is almost a lethal dose.
If he keeps taking it
or increases the dose,
couldn't it be life-threatening?
-That's right.
-"That's right"? It's not…
Are you crawling or what?
I'm on it, kid!
Hyeon-min.
It's not your fault.
You just got unlucky.
Early admission is out,
but you still have the CSAT.
If you do well,
you can still get into med school.
You can pull yourself together
and do this, right?
I'll get you excused for field study,
so don't go to school.
Just study at home until the CSAT.
Okay?
Mom.
Can you get me the meds?
Yes.
Let's take the meds and study.
Hyeon-min.
Jung Hyeon-min!
Hyeon-min, are you in there?
HIGH SCHOOL SENIOR INSIDE
DO NOT RING!
Oh no.
They won't let me in.
All right, sir.
-What did he say?
-They won't let him in.
However I see it, it seems dangerous.
You're not actually going to jump,
are you?
-The kid might die at this rate.
-What?
Oh my God, why are you up there?
Hold that tight, okay?
Oh my God!
Wait.
Wait, Hyeon-min! The ERPB is here.
Inspector Im Han-rim!
Are you all right?
-What the…
-Hyeon-min!
-Let go.
-No.
-Give me the pills!
-No! Let go!
No!
-Take Hyeon-min to the hospital.
-Okay.
No, you can't!
-Let go. Hyeon-min!
-Come on!
Let me go. Hyeon-min!
Why are you taking Hyeon-min?
Ma'am, do you know
what kind of medication this is?
Some students call it
a pill that keeps them awake,
helps them focus,
treats ADHD, boosts their grades,
and gets them into med school.
But we call it
a pill that kills people.
We call it an illicit drug.
-What do you mean "illicit drug"?
-Didn't you know?
No.
I just gave it to him
because I heard it helps with focus.
Did you really not know?
How could I have?
This is the first time
I'm hearing that it's bad!
Did you really not know?
Did you really not see
the changes in Hyeon-min…
after he started taking it?
Hyeon-min.
Here, I got you. Oh my!
I WANT TO DIE
You knew this drug
was ruining Hyeon-min.
What were you thinking?
As long as he could get into med school,
you thought it was okay
to give him drugs like this?
I was only going to give it to him
until the CSAT.
Something could go wrong
with him before then.
Is med school worth more than your son?
I guess it is.
He's almost there.
Every second counts.
There's no time for this!
Hyeon-min needs to study!
From this moment on,
you are not allowed
to leave this apartment.
Why not?
This is my home!
This is to protect Hyeon-min.
The ERPB will now separate
the child abuser from the victim.
What do you mean "child abuse"?
I'm his mother!
I told you this is the most important time
of his life!
Will you take responsibility
if he misses out on med school?
If you want med school that badly,
go yourself.
Hyeon-min, are you okay?
Oh my God, no!
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Hyeon-min.
Why put your hand there
when you have zero pain tolerance?
It's better my hand gets hurt
than his head.
Do you have a fever?
You're like a different person.
Looking at Hyeon-min
reminds me of my younger self.
My mom tried to send me to med school too.
So why didn't you go?
Because it wasn't fun at all.
CSAT PREP
SAMPLE QUESTIONS
What are you trying to pull here?
I told you.
If you want med school, go yourself.
Do you know why I want Hyeon-min
to go to med school?
I have no connections.
Nothing to leave him either.
When kids have to compete,
they end up resenting their parents.
That's why you should study
and go to med school yourself.
Then you can be his connection.
Why do you want him to be self-made?
He'd prefer well-off parents.
How am I supposed to go to med school
at my age?
I think you could if you stuck to this.
These are
the study and meal plans you made
for Hyeon-min.
You planned it really well.
If you stick to this,
you could easily get into med school.
Study.
Once your mock exam scores
clear the med school cutoff,
I'll let you see Hyeon-min.
For God's sake!
17:30. Instead of going to hagwon,
work through the past CSAT English paper
at least three times.
If you get even one question wrong,
start over.
It's not time to eat yet.
Nutritional support for brain function.
What's this?
It's your dinner.
Being full makes you sleepy.
By the way,
I'm just following the meal plan.
No? I'll take them.
I'll eat them.
After watching online lectures
and completing an error log,
sleep at 1:00 a.m.
It's time to wake up.
Let me sleep a little longer.
Sleep four hours, you pass.
Sleep five, you fail!
Oh man.
So loud.
Oh my goodness!
What are you doing?
I'm getting rid of this mattress
as it's distracting.
Isn't that why you took this door off?
Are you insane?
Insane? Can't you see
that I'm sacrificing myself for you?
More like fooling around.
Does this look like a joke?
Do you think I'd make you suffer the same,
and then one day say,
"That's enough. Let's go see Hyeon-min
since you've learned your lesson"?
That will never
ever happen.
There's only one way
you can leave this place.
By getting into med school.
You're up. Are you feeling okay?
I'm sorry.
You hurt your hand because of me.
It's fine.
What is it?
Hey.
Can you get me those pills?
No.
They're harmful.
Harmful?
It's an illegal drug.
Can I just have one?
-No.
-I swear it's the last.
-No, Hyeon-min.
-I feel like I'll die without it!
No. I said no!
Do you think you can control it?
Everyone says "just one" at first.
Then they say "just one more."
That's how you ruin yourself.
Your body,
your mind,
and even your life.
If you don't want to die,
hold out until the end.
You failed.
Fail.
You improved a little.
STUDY SCHEDULE
JUST ONE MORE YEAR. YOU CAN DO THIS, SON
GOAL
GET INTO SNU MEDICAL SCHOOL!
I WANT TO DIE
I wanted to die.
I felt like the hell I was in
would never end
unless I got into med school.
Every time I felt like I wanted to die,
I took the pills.
Mom.
Can I skip hagwon today?
Why? What's wrong now?
Those who hold out now
will be smiling later.
You can do it, right?
Why did you skip hagwon?
I'm sorry.
When I took the pills Mom got me,
I didn't want to die anymore.
But only for a moment.
Soon after,
I felt like I wanted to die again.
Can you get me stronger pills?
Okay.
I took those pills
because I didn't want to die.
Because I wanted to live.
It's possible to live without them.
Let's quit the pills
and anything that makes you feel suicidal.
If it's studying, then quit studying.
If it's med school,
then quit trying for it.
And if it's your mom,
quit your mom too.
How would I quit my mom?
That was a bit too much, wasn't it?
Sorry.
It's my birthday.
Do you know when it is?
Let me out.
It's too hard. I can't go on.
So when it's too hard,
you just get to quit?
You didn't let Hyeon-min do that.
Do you really think
I was trying to kill my son?
I sold a perfectly good home
and moved into this dump.
I acted like a servant
to the moms just to get information.
I got up early every morning
to make breakfast.
I've never lived a day for myself.
I couldn't even have a hobby
because I had to pay his hagwon fees.
I did all this and sacrificed myself
so Hyeon-min could succeed.
You didn't sacrifice yourself
for Hyeon-min.
Hyeon-min…
sacrificed himself for you.
DRAW YOUR DREAM JOB
NAME: JUNG HYEON-MIN
DREAM: DOCTOR
Mommy would be so happy
if you became a doctor.
-Really?
-Yes, of course.
WHAT WILL YOU BE IN THE FUTURE?
You should become a doctor, of course,
and take care of me whenever I'm sick.
"Doctor."
You're a good boy.
You always listen to me.
Yeah.
Don't you feel bad for me and your dad?
Why do you think we live like this?
We're sacrificing for you.
I'm sacrificing myself for you!
Jung Hyeon-min!
Do you think I enjoy this?
I'm putting up with it for you.
Mom, I'm sorry.
If it weren't for you,
I could live a happy life.
I'm sacrificing myself for you!
Ever since I was little,
Mom has always told me
that I have to become a doctor.
So I naturally thought
I should become one.
Sounds stupid, right?
You said you did well in school, right?
Nah, not really.
Please tell me
what I'm supposed to do first.
First,
think about what you like the most.
I'm happiest
when I do what I enjoy the most.
I can name hundreds of things
my mom likes.
But I can't think
of a single thing I like.
What do I like?
It's not too late to think about it.
Let's figure it out together.
You too, Inspector Im.
Just come on.
Give me a second.
I'm here for the books I asked for.
Oh, yes.
Pediatric center?
Here, read these.
KANG WON-MI THE JUDO GIRL
-You know how old he is, right?
-Yeah.
Here, you can read this.
This is for you.
-Come on.
-This is a children's book.
You want me to read this?
-Yeah.
-Me? It's for me?
HAMSTER YAMMA WHO BECAME A YOUTUBER
CHOI THE FIREFIGHTER CAT
Get ready.
We're going out.
Hyeon-min.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm doing better.
I'm glad to hear that.
How are your studies?
You have been studying, right?
I don't mean to pressure you,
but the CSAT is coming up,
and I'm worried.
You understand, don't you?
Are you comfortable here?
Is the food okay?
Mom.
Yeah?
I have something to tell you.
You do? What is it?
I'm not going to med school.
And I'm not taking the CSAT.
What?
I'll keep studying though.
And I'll take the CSAT next year.
But not this year.
I don't want to live like this,
aimless and doing what I'm told.
I have no idea
what you're talking about right now.
Mom.
Even if I don't take the CSAT
or go to med school…
I'm still your son.
What are you--
No matter what I decide,
please support me, Mom.
No, Hyeon-min.
You have to take the CSAT.
You need to go to med school!
I'm heading to my treatment now.
No, Hyeon-min!
No.
I hope you stop suffering because of me
and live your own life.
In a recent inspection of all elementary,
middle, and high schools,
many students tested positive
for ingredients from overseas ADHD drugs
that are not approved domestically.
In several cases,
we detected a substance known
among parents and students as a study aid.
This drug,
also known as "Heart Pills,"
contains designer drug components.
In the future, the ERPB
will conduct screenings before the CSAT,
and any student who tests positive
for illegal drugs
will be disqualified.
Are there this many types of drugs?
They look different
but have similar ingredients.
These Full Moon Pills
were popular about ten years ago,
and these Snowman Pills
were popular five years ago.
And these letters in the middle
were engraved by the dealers.
They're like a trademark for a product.
-These were popular two years ago--
-Excuse me.
Could I take a quick look at this?
We're fucked, damn it!
What are we going to do now?
Those fucking ERPB assholes
blocked everything.
Isn't it obvious?
The ERPB just needs to disappear,
doesn't it?
WHAT SHOULD I DO… ABOUT GYU-CHEOL?
WILL I EVER BE ABLE TO… FORGIVE GYU-CHEOL?
CRACKDOWN ON GEN Z-TARGETED DESIGNER DRUGS
Gyu-cheol, let's say
your parole hearing goes well
and you're released back into society.
What would you want to do most?
I'm not sure.
I don't even dare hope for it.
But if it were possible…
I'd want to go back to school.
WILL I EVER BE ABLE TO… FORGIVE GYU-CHEOL?
Based on witness statements
that the defendant, Cho Gyu-cheol,
showed ongoing hostility toward Ms. Choi,
we seek ten years' imprisonment
for premeditated retaliatory murder.
It is clear
Cho Gyu-cheol was changing
under Ms. Choi's guidance.
This was nothing more
than a deeply unfortunate accident.
Get on now.
Subtitle translation by: Lisa Kim