Kick the murderer out!
Kick him out!
What did our kids do to deserve this?
What did our kids do?
Isolate the murderer!
Isolate him!
It's Cho Gyu-cheol!
-Bastard! How dare you come here!
-Cho Gyu-cheol!
-Look over here!
-You're not human!
Drop out, you bastard!
-How dare you go in!
-This is outrageous!
Kick him out, for God's sake!
You expect our kids to go to school
with him? Kick him out!
Cho Gyu-cheol has shown
deep remorse for his crimes,
followed the correctional facility rules,
and set an example for others.
Given his minor status and clean record,
the committee finds no risk of recidivism
and hereby grants parole.
What do you think, sir?
I'm talking about Cho Gyu-cheol.
He was paroled
as soon as he completed his minimum term.
When the Educational Rights Committee
signed off,
they approved his readmission
almost instantly.
Everything lining up perfectly,
as if planned, feels off.
It's worth looking into, isn't it?
Readmission
is at the principal's discretion.
Cho Gyu-cheol has already been punished,
and the ERPB has no authority to deny
a student the chance to return to school.
If I stopped him…
that would be revenge.
Where's Inspector Na?
He had to stop by somewhere
before coming in.
Where?
TEACH YOU A LESSON
You look good in your uniform, don't you?
Don't be nervous.
I'm here as an ERPB inspector today.
You're a test case
to see if kids like you
can handle school again,
if rehabilitation is possible,
and if you deserve
another chance.
I will
really do my best.
No, just don't do anything.
Just breathe and live quietly.
Live a normal life.
Live like a student.
I'm sure you know what I mean.
This is Cho Gyu-cheol,
back in school today.
He's older than you, so be nice.
-Say hi.
-Okay.
I'll make sure
I don't get in the way of your studies.
Nice to meet you.
What?
-Jong-su.
-What, dumbass?
How could you… to a teacher…
Seong-gu, call 119, for fuck's sake!
Hey, stab him again.
Damn, you're no fun.
Hey.
I heard you killed someone.
A teacher, no less.
Wow, fucking hell.
Check out the look in his eyes.
You gonna kill me too?
A goddamn murderer, studying?
You feel this is unfair?
You want me to speak politely to you?
No, it's fine. Speak however you want.
Damn, you're chill.
Behave yourself.
If you act up and the ERPB shows up,
you'll be in trouble too.
Get it?
Yeah, I will. Thanks for the advice.
What the hell? Let's go.
Cigs.
-What a loser.
-Hey, are you coming?
Yeah, coming.
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
It's hilarious seeing him act all shy.
Hey, show me the picture.
Shit, I got a text.
Here, look.
That looks good too.
-Holy shit, hold on.
-Why?
I got an S-class.
Screw you.
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
Oh man, this is insane.
What's the matter?
It's a report about a student
assaulting a teacher
after being told not to use their phone.
He challenged the teacher
under Yatcha rules.
Yatcha rules? What's that?
It's a bare-knuckle fight.
No rank, no rules.
We're doing everything we can,
yet things like this keep happening.
What are you doing out there? Come in.
Someone is here to see you.
Bring them in.
Okay.
Right.
What brings you here?
I have something to tell you.
You've got some nerve coming here!
This is the ERPB.
Any student can come here.
Have a seat.
So what brings you here?
I'm here to report bullying at school.
Ms. Choi once told me
that looking out
for others who are struggling
is something students should also learn.
How dare you say her name!
Inspector Im Han-rim.
Aren't any of you angry?
Go outside and get some air.
Okay?
Come on, let's go.
All right.
Finish what you were saying.
I'm sorry for bringing up Ms. Choi's name.
This is the kid getting bullied.
He's definitely up to something.
But the information he gave us
was pretty specific.
He's right.
Cho Gyu-cheol isn't an exception.
We'll do as we always have.
Deputy Director Bong Geun-dae,
this case is yours.
-Yes, sir.
-No, I'll go.
You can't, sir. Instead, I will--
Is there a reason why I can't go?
Stop him, won't you?
Should I stop you?
Stop the traffic instead.
-Oh dear.
-I'm sorry.
Don't even think about
telling any jokes, anywhere.
Get going.
Okay.
-You shouldn't laugh at his jokes.
-I'll see you later.
Deputy Bong.
Oh, come on. Not now.
Don't try to stop me. I'm not traffic.
I laughed. I'm so annoyed.
What's wrong with…
-I'm sorry, Minister.
-Don't laugh.
You shouldn't laugh.
Oh man, I laughed.
JINWON HIGH SCHOOL
Jang Seong-gu from my class?
Seong-gu is being bullied?
He didn't seem to have any problems
from the outside.
He has a lot of friends,
and Seong-gu himself said
he was enjoying school.
We'll sing "Emergency Room" at karaoke.
-No.
-What?
Stop stuffing your face with my chips.
Okay.
That's lit.
-What the…
-Hey, what's going on?
Why is it lagging?
Where did Jang Seong-gu go?
Why are you nervous? Did I scare you?
Well…
You're from the ERPB.
Yeah.
Do you know why I'm here?
No, I don't.
We were tipped off
that someone was being bullied.
That doesn't happen here.
Excuse me.
Let's see.
-Say, "Ah."
-What?
Come on, say, "Ah."
At least you weren't hit.
Oh man, it's not me.
I'll be on my way.
Are you Wi-Fi?
Do you turn your hotspot on so the kids
can use their phones and play games?
Are you a human Wi-Fi?
You're always at the center,
like people gathering around Wi-Fi.
And you're always the first one
to take out your phone.
You probably do that
to turn your hotspot on
so they can connect to Wi-Fi.
Also, you're the only one
carrying around that huge power bank.
You can't let the Wi-Fi go down, can you?
I'm really not a human Wi-Fi.
But seriously, I really have to go.
I'll be going now. Yeah.
Hey, the punk's here.
Hey, Jang Seong-gu.
What are you doing here?
Well, a moment ago…
I was just walking, and the ERPB…
Holy fuck. It's the ERPB.
Watch your language.
What's the ERPB doing at our school?
Fuck, I know.
Is it Cho Gyu-cheol?
No, I'm here because of you.
I heard you're a bully.
-Me?
-Yeah.
Who did I bully?
I told you no!
Please don't accuse innocent people.
It's really not like that!
Why are you upsetting our sweet Seong-gu?
Seong-gu, that's enough, man.
The ERPB can make mistakes too.
Can we go now?
Sure.
-Okay. Goodbye, sir.
-Yeah.
Let's go.
Hey, you scared me there.
I thought you'd vanished.
Were you here all along?
Why are you all sweaty, Seong-gu?
Hey, squad up.
I got a legendary item.
Don't engage now.
-Stay back.
-Okay.
Bong Geun-dae?
Hey, you're Geun-dae, right?
Bong Geun-dae.
-Yeah. Yes.
-It's been ages. How are you?
Yeah, I'm good. What about you?
I heard you're a civil servant.
I think I heard where you worked.
The ERPB? Right?
-The ERPB.
-Wait.
-Hold on.
-Good for you.
I'll call you later.
Sorry.
Wait, Bong Geun-dae.
-One of you, get in here.
-Hold on.
-Hey, we should go.
-Yeah, after this.
-A bit more.
-Group up.
Yeah, okay.
That was fast. Got the audio?
-Wait a minute.
-Why?
-I messed up.
-What?
Put these on.
-Here.
-Why should I?
-What are you doing?
-Hold on.
I failed. Stay still.
Put this in your right ear.
-Isn't this that thing?
-An earpiece.
-Isn't this eyeshadow?
-Yeah.
-What are you…
-Hold still.
It's done.
Just remember one thing.
A loser never makes eye contact.
A loser?
Fucking hell. What?
Let's just go, idiot. Something feels off.
-What the hell, dumbass?
-You're a fucking noob anyway. Let's go.
I said let's go.
Fuck, what are you doing?
Are you freaking blind or what?
Look down.
You're fucking lucky.
Don't let me see you again.
Quit acting dumb and fuck off, damn it.
It's because you flipped out.
Inspector Im Han-rim,
good job holding back.
Damn it, that fucking bastard.
Is it done? Testing.
I'm done cloning Lee Chi-ho's voice.
-Let's check it out.
-Okay.
-It's Chi-ho.
-What's the password?
Nice.
Wow.
-Okay, then. I'll call Jang Seong-gu now.
-I'm a bit nervous.
Don't be nervous. Just act natural.
Hello?
It's me, Chi-ho.
I'd appreciate it
if you could give me the password.
Is this really Chi-ho?
You don't sound like yourself.
-Who is this?
-Let me.
You fucking asshole, who else would I be?
Goddamn idiot.
Give me the password.
It's Wi-Fi. "Wi-Fi" in Korean.
The account belongs to Seong-gu,
but he doesn't have his own profile.
They've been sharing the same account.
I checked Seong-gu's food delivery app,
and he's had deliveries
to several addresses.
There were even orders over 100,000 won.
He's subscribed to more than 20 games.
That's impossible
unless all he does is play games.
He had a lot of charges
for e-scooter rentals too.
It says he's on one right now.
It says the food just got delivered.
He just logged into a game too.
Are you saying
Jang Seong-gu is on a scooter,
eating with one hand
and playing a game with the other?
Do you really need to picture it?
It's obviously impossible.
Money isn't the real problem, is it?
What about the scam cases you looked into?
There's a website
where scam victims share information.
I looked up Seong-gu's user ID,
and it showed reports of undelivered items
and fake sales on resale apps.
They were all scam-related.
The punks used Seong-gu's ID
to post fake items,
then took the money
and ghosted the buyers.
Isn't this way too much
for just one kid to deal with on his own?
The goddamn scammer.
You scammed me over the AirPods,
didn't you?
No, it wasn't me. I really didn't do it.
Some kids stole my account.
-Really, I didn't--
-You son of a bitch.
It really wasn't me.
You fucking asshole, you asked for it.
You bastard.
You goddamn bastard.
You little shit, trying to pull scams?
You wanna die?
You goddamn thief.
Give me my money back, you bastard.
Damn.
You idiot. Why'd you get caught?
He said I'll be sorry
if I don't pay him back.
And?
Chi-ho, I'm really sorry,
but I don't have any money.
-If you could help out a bit--
-That's too bad.
I've run out of allowance too.
You take care of it, okay?
Chi-ho.
Please, I'm asking you.
For God's sake.
I said I'd deal with it later.
Yeah, but when?
Should I break my promise?
No, keep your promise.
Do you know what would happen
if I changed my mind?
Everything is under your account
and your name, okay?
You'll be the one who's fucked.
But I told you
I'd deal with everything later.
Super grateful, right?
My son tells me
your son uses my son's account
to order food and spend money on games.
Take a look.
Hundreds of thousands of won were charged.
That's your side of the story.
I told Chi-ho to come home now,
so let's hear his side too.
There you are.
Hey, Jang Seong-gu.
Go. It's okay.
You sent this crap to my sister?
You DMed her.
Oh my God, what is this?
Seong-gu, did you really send her this?
Mom, I didn't do this.
-It's Chi-ho. He did this too.
-Excuse me?
Are you saying Chi-ho sent this
to his own sister?
Does that make any sense?
Are you crazy?
-I should call the police. Unbelievable.
-Mom.
No, wait.
I'm sorry.
If this offended you,
I apologize on his behalf.
Please forgive him this once.
-Next time…
-This will never happen again.
…I'll send it to every girl in our class
using your account.
-Snitch on me again, dumbass.
-They're only kids.
-Ji-ho, you okay?
-Please forget why I came. I'm so…
Hey, I'm so sorry. All right?
-Go.
-Are you insane?
Mom, it wasn't me.
Be quiet, you fool.
-Mom, it wasn't me.
-I'm sorry.
Are you okay, Ji-ho?
Yeah.
Thanks.
All right.
Chi-ho, do you mind if I take a call?
Can't you see I'm playing a game?
It's going to lag.
It's my mom.
Damn it.
Answer, idiot.
Hello?
What the hell have you been up to?
How much is all this?
FOODMON ORDER HISTORY
When I paid this off for you before,
I said that was the last time.
How many times is this now?
How am I supposed to make sense of this?
Jang Seong-gu. Don't you have
anything to say to me? Well?
Don't tell me it was your friend again.
It really wasn't me.
After all that humiliation last time,
you're lying again?
Why are you growing up like this?
What's suddenly gotten into you?
Seriously…
Seong-gu wants to tell you everything
Lee Chi-ho has done to him.
You'll tell him, right?
Yes.
I'll tell you everything.
He says I can trust the ERPB.
Do you think
the ERPB won't believe you either?
If the ERPB had existed two years ago
and had come
to our school…
I wouldn't have killed anyone…
and no one would've died.
Inspector Na Hwa-jin will be different.
He's just like Ms. Choi.
HE USED MY IDENTITY ON VARIOUS WEBSITES
TO SCAM PEOPLE
Yes.
Inspector.
Well, did you hear about
the School Violence Committee meeting?
Chi-ho reported Seong-gu for bullying.
What?
SCHOOL VIOLENCE DELIBERATION COMMITTEE
VICTIM STUDENT
ACCUSED STUDENT
Just a moment.
An ERPB inspector cannot legally serve
on the committee.
Please have him leave.
We also received a report
and have been monitoring the situation,
so we need to understand what happened.
I'll simply observe.
Speaking is not permitted.
Yes, sir.
All right. We will now begin
the review of the school violence case
at Jinwon High School.
First, we will hear the statement
from the victim's side.
Even before the incident
was fully investigated,
Jang Seong-gu spread false rumors
about Lee Chi-ho
and called in the ERPB,
effectively branding him as the bully.
He is in severe psychological distress.
His psychiatric treatment records
are hereby submitted as evidence.
DEPRESSIVE DISORDER
PANIC DISORDER
Next, we will hear from the accused.
Please make your statement.
Oh, I…
This isn't fair.
I'm the victim here.
They stole my accounts.
They used them to run scams,
play games,
and order food.
Is there any evidence?
Do you have any evidence
that they stole your accounts?
Well, that's--
As you can see, his claim is one-sided
with no evidence.
We cannot rule out
that he might be making false statements.
If so, it could constitute defamation.
You'll see if you look at the records.
I'm online at an Internet café
while on an e-scooter
and having food delivered elsewhere.
If you see the logs--
That's right.
Lee Chi-ho said he borrowed his accounts
a few times for urgent reasons.
It wasn't a few times--
Only answer
what you're asked.
Once or twice, Chi-ho borrowed
his streaming service account
and used his account
to rent a bike a few times.
That's all.
And yet, Chi-ho wanted to help his friend
and sent Jang Seong-gu money.
I never received any money.
Please check your bank account.
SEJIN TRANSACTION ACCOUNT
LEE CHI-HO / REPAYMENT
DEPOSIT 1,000,000 WON
By contrast,
the harm Lee Chi-ho has suffered
is very serious.
Deemed a bully, based on unfounded claims,
he is being shunned
and isolated at school.
But what's more concerning
is that this false narrative
is even threatening Chi-ho's future.
This is not simply defamation.
It is social character assassination.
Of course, we do not intend
to pursue criminal charges.
However, we have submitted
the psychiatric records,
and given his struggles
to keep up with studies,
we believe an appropriate mediation,
compensation, or settlement is needed.
A settlement?
How much…
That said,
since it's a matter between children,
Chi-ho's mother, a truly admirable woman,
wishes to receive an apology
and settle the matter here.
What do you say, Seong-gu's mother?
Chi-ho's mother.
Thank you so much.
I'll make sure this never happens again.
I really appreciate your leniency.
Chi-ho.
I'm sorry, all right?
I'm really sorry.
My goodness, ma'am…
So that's the situation.
Understood, sir.
Can you believe this?
He did wrong,
yet he calls for the meeting.
He even hired an expensive lawyer!
These days, I hear lawyers specializing
in school bullying provide manuals.
"File a complaint first.
That way, you can claim victim status."
"File a counter-report.
That's how it turns into mutual fault."
They say things like this.
But still,
what's the School Violence Committee for?
It should be able to determine the truth!
But it's not that easy in reality.
They have to review the case,
meet the students briefly,
and reach a decision all on the same day.
Since that's difficult,
they just look at the evidence,
but they struggle
to decide who is at fault,
handing down
similar rulings over and over.
What should we do?
Damn it, what are we going to do?
SEONG-GU'S IPHONE
SEONG-GU'S IPHONE, WEAK CONNECTION
SEONG-GU'S IPHONE, STRONG CONNECTION
There you are.
It's okay to cry out loud, Seong-gu.
Why are you holding it in?
If you hold it in,
no one will know you're crying.
If you don't speak up,
no one will know you've been wronged.
And if you're curled up like this,
they'll never know what they did wrong.
Is this how you want to live?
All right, then.
It's not fair!
It's so unfair. It's driving me crazy.
I told the police.
I told my parents and my teachers.
But no one believes me.
I know they were being nice to me
just to use me.
But they were all I had.
They were my friends. They liked me.
Chi-ho said he'd tell everyone everything.
He said he'd come clean
about stealing my accounts.
But he kept putting it off, playing dumb.
And now he's saying I'm the bully.
What if everyone thinks I lied?
What do I do?
Nobody believes me!
Seong-gu, I believe you.
I do believe you.
So you should trust the ERPB too.
Done.
-Wait, what about the keychains?
-Oh!
I have them. They're right here.
Let's see.
Do I have to put them all on?
Just do as you're told, will you?
Done.
Oh, here they come.
Damn it, there's no Wi-Fi.
What do we do now? Our human Wi-Fi's gone.
Don't worry.
We just need to find another Wi-Fi.
You're so pretty!
This was just lying next to you.
I won't hurt your friends.
-Hey, you dork.
-Why…
Remember me?
-Hi.
-Greeting a friend, are you?
You need to act scared.
Hi.
You know you owe me, right?
Oh, I'll pay you back
for your dry cleaning.
No, it's okay. You can pay me back later.
Are you new here?
-Yeah.
-Oh, yeah?
I'll show you around
since it's your first day.
-Really?
-Yeah, let's go.
-Thanks.
-You should lose this though.
-Yeah.
-Why? Isn't it pretty?
Hey.
You're in my class?
Right, yeah.
Let's be friends.
Thanks.
No worries.
-Hey.
-Stop.
What kind of loser walks in front?
Get behind them.
Go ahead.
Thanks.
-Whoa, shit.
-Damn it.
Hey, sorry.
-You're an ass.
-You told me to.
You must be nervous
because it's your first day.
Are you okay there?
You're fine.
Inspector Im Han-rim, calm down.
You're on a mission.
Keep your cool. Hold it together.
I'm okay.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Yeah, sure.
She fucking scared me.
Hey, if you want to thank me,
can I use your Netflix account just once?
These are my accounts
for Netflix, streaming, and games.
I have LoL accounts for each tier.
Use whatever fits.
You're prepared as fuck.
Were you Wi-Fi at your old school?
Oh, that's what you call it here.
It was Hotspot at my old school.
Hotspot?
Also, if the Wi-Fi signal is weak,
let me know.
I'll connect you to the router.
Here's the ID and password.
Oh yeah, and…
-Nice.
-Tell me if your battery's running low.
Here's the charger.
I also have cables
for every type of phone. I'll show you.
There's a reason people prefer
experienced hires.
You don't need to teach them.
Hey, wow.
Phones, please.
I'll fully charge them before class.
Yeah, okay.
Thanks. Here.
Can you unlock these?
Yeah, okay.
-I'll connect them to the hotspot too.
-Okay.
Thanks.
Wow, how did she get to tier 2?
The mithril's mine.
Did she buy the account? It's yours.
I mean, how did she do it? How?
She's better at PUBG than Jong-su.
Damn, this is a bit intense.
I'm taking the mithril.
What the hell?
Is some punk using my account?
Check the login history.
What the fuck? Colombia?
Some ass in Colombia
logged into my account.
You've been hacked.
Fucking hell.
He keeps trying to charge my account.
He's fucked now. What's he gonna do?
Fuck, I'm screwed.
"Stop sending me stupid links, asshole."
"Must be damn bored."
"Spam is so freaking annoying."
Use "hella."
-"Hella" isn't used anymore, is it?
-Isn't it?
What the fuck?
My number is sending spam.
MOM
Mom, I didn't send it.
What are you on about?
Why would I send that to you?
-I'll be ranking up.
-It wasn't me.
Why won't you believe your own son?
I've logged into Lee Chi-ho's account.
This game has a very strict
profanity detection system.
The suspension length depends
on how severe the language is.
Im Han-rim, go all out with swearing
so he gets the longest ban possible.
-Write this down.
-Hold on.
You freaking son of a gun.
Buttfaced jerks.
You Monday-morning assholes.
If that's how your fucking brain works,
rip it out and hang it on a tree instead.
You sons of bitches.
Fuck, you really think you're hot?
You're fucking ugly as hell, bastard.
Keep fucking living like this,
and you're headed straight to hell.
You fucking bastard!
This is good. Keep going.
I'll rip out your hair, eyes, tongue,
cut your head off, and deep-fry them
in shit water, bastard.
It'll taste fucking good, right?
I'll chew you up real good
and pass you around
so everyone gets a fucking bite.
You motherfucker, I'll chew you up.
Sound yummy?
What the fuck?
Why does it say 300 years?
What the actual fuck?
2,500 WON CHARGED
EXTRA 50 MINS
SURCHARGE: 10,000 WON
Damn it.
OUTSIDE SERVICE AREA: 22,000 WON
Fucking hell.
Fucking hell!
This crazy bastard!
Where you going?
I'm going to kill this asshole.
Fucking bastard. Can't be serious.
Fucking hell.
Goddamn it.
For fuck's sake.
Hey, there it is!
-It's really here!
-Damn.
It's really here. Check the plate.
Hey, is it 8729?
-What the hell?
-Yeah.
-It's basically new.
-What?
-Holy fuck!
-Hey!
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing with my bike?
Aren't you giving it away?
Giving it away? What's this bullshit?
Bullshit, my ass.
Didn't you post this?
What the hell? Who used my account to…
That's not my problem.
I'll take good care of it.
Fuck off! "I'll take good care of it"?
My ass. Get the hell out.
-You fucking asshole.
-Wait.
Wait a second. Listen.
Some bastard must've hacked my account.
Then bring that bastard here,
or I'll beat the shit out of you,
fucking asshole.
You fucking bitch. It was you, wasn't it?
You asked me
to unlock my phone to hotspot.
You messed with it, right?
Let go of me and--
Fuck you.
Come clean while I'm still being nice.
Let go while I'm still being nice.
What?
Fucking hell.
Yeah, it was me.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you know how much shit
you've fucking caused me?
How much?
Was it so bad you'd rather die
than come to school?
You're not there yet, are you?
You fucking…
-Fucking hell.
-Wait! Wait a…
Wait a second.
My throat's a bit sore.
Help me! Save me!
-Lee Chi-ho.
-What is it?
-What are you doing?
-I'm sorry.
-What is it?
-Help me.
What are you doing?
Hey.
It's not what you think.
Something about that jerk
always seemed off.
Here comes the School Violence Committee.
I didn't do anything.
She's a nutjob.
I'm telling you, she's a nutjob.
-Help me.
-Seriously?
Help me.
Chi-ho is not the bully.
He's actually the victim.
The transfer student
hacked into his phone,
got his game account banned,
and even committed fraud
by posting fake sales on resale apps.
Do you have any evidence
to support this claim?
Why should I have to prove it
when I'm the victim?
Ask the transfer student.
Excuse me.
We're sorry for being late.
She needed treatment.
VICTIM STUDENT
And I'm here
on behalf of the victim's lawyer
because something came up.
You're not even a lawyer.
What gives you
the right to appear on his behalf?
I have power of attorney.
-Here's the document.
-Okay.
Which lawyer wrote
that ridiculous power of attorney?
-I know most of the lawyers.
-It's this man here.
Do you know him?
-It's Choi Gang-seok.
-Minister Choi also has a law license.
He's a member of the Bar Association
and served
on the Legislation and Judicial Committee.
Even so, the ERPB's intervention
in the School Violence Committee
is an abuse of power.
What you're being handed right now
is an official notice
stating that this committee
will fall under the ERPB's supervision.
Please take a look.
Okay, then. We will begin
the School Violence Committee hearing.
Thank you.
Lee Chi-ho terrorized Im Han-rim so much
that she's in a terrible state.
Oh no, look at you drooling.
She was branded an outcast
as soon as she transferred,
and the happy school life she deserved
became utter hell.
It's okay. Let's try to start over, okay?
She's been left with lifelong trauma
and even mental health issues.
Seriously? Come on!
She's putting on a show!
-I'm the one who got messed with and hit.
-Don't listen.
All right?
Chi-ho.
I'm telling you, she's acting!
What's wrong with you?
Sit down. I'm sorry.
-Chi-ho!
-Oh my! What are you…
-See? Look at him.
-Hey.
I know you're fine. You're not even sick.
-Look at him.
-Tell them.
Tell them it's all a lie, an act.
Like my son says, if it's an act…
Stop it! Oh my goodness.
How does it feel?
Are you finally asking yourself,
"Why did I do that?"
Will it only sink in
if your finger gets broken?
Oh my God, what's wrong with her?
All right, Inspector Im Han-rim.
Oh no, my son.
Inspector Im Han-rim here
is actually an ERPB field investigator
who was assigned
to look into the bullying case
involving Jang Seong-gu.
Right, so that's what's been going on.
So why did we go to such lengths?
It's because of Jang Seong-gu.
Seong-gu!
You see us, right?
Yes.
We are here to clear his name.
How does it feel?
Do you finally realize
what you did to Seong-gu?
This is really not fair.
I never even laid a finger on Seong-gu.
That's right. You never hit him.
There's not a scratch on him.
But do you think it wasn't violence?
You never touched him,
yet he was scared, terrified,
wronged, and frustrated.
No one believed him,
no matter what he said.
Not even his parents. That's right.
He probably thought
it'd be better to be beaten.
Why?
Because if he had marks from it,
his parents might believe him.
Do you know what's worse?
To get out of the situation,
he had no choice but to beg
the very person who put him there.
The victim had no choice
but to bow his head…
and plead with the bully.
This is what you did to Seong-gu.
Without laying a finger on him.
It's been hard for you, hasn't it?
It must've been so hard, all on your own.
Seong-gu, I'm sorry. All right?
I was such a fool.
I should've believed you.
Our investigation found
that Lee Chi-ho's testimony
about suffering harm
because of Jang Seong-gu was false
and that the actual victim
is Jang Seong-gu.
Accordingly, the ERPB will implement
appropriate protective measures
for the victim, Jang Seong-gu, at once.
Additionally, the prior ruling against him
by the School Violence Committee
will be fully nullified
by the authority of the ERPB.
A victim is a victim.
A bully is a bully.
Is that so difficult?
Adults should protect children.
Aren't you ashamed to face them?
Thank you for helping me.
You'll be issued a new resident number.
Do well at school.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you so much.
It's finally over, ma'am.
I'll make sure to raise Seong-gu well.
Go home with your mother.
Okay.
Your friend?
Well.
I'm sorry.
You told me not to do anything.
But still,
something good happened
because I did what I could.
I'm glad.
Welcome.
Get your own glass.
That's for Ga-yun.
Lie down here.
Careful.
Hey.
You should find another woman.
Goodness.
Ga-yun would be mad at me, you know?
Imagine if she heard that.
She'd go on at you
for a couple of hours at least.
You know.
God.
Busted.
No way.
Fine, I won't smoke.
Here.
Cheers!
Why would I toast with this guy?
I don't toast with someone
who doesn't like me either.
Are you really going to be like this?
Yeah, I am.
He leaves me no choice.
Fine, then.
I won't get married.
Where'd that come from?
Good.
Yeah. But I'll never get married.
-Never?
-Yeah.
If I can't marry Hwa-jin,
I'll just live alone
till I get old and die.
Then, Dad, you'll never get to hold
your grandchild
or hear them call you "Grandpa."
You'll just grow old.
If you don't want that,
should you be acting like this or not?
Well, that can't happen.
Then do you think
you two should be toasting or not?
Shall we?
Make it a couples' shot.
That's gross. Why would we do that?
Then I won't get married.
Whatever. I'm recording.
-Ga-yun, that's…
-Wait.
-One…
-Hold on. Hey.
Two…
Three!
For fuck's sake.
Hey.
Damn it.
You said I'd win.
You said if I got a lawyer,
it'd be game over.
File a report first.
Why should I?
What for?
I don't think you can afford
to be this relaxed right now.
The ERPB will do everything they can
to brand you as the bully.
Then you'll at least get suspended.
No,
you may even get expelled.
You need to lay the groundwork first.
The first one to file
becomes the victim in today's world.
If you don't want to be branded
as the bully, act like the victim.
This person will help you.
ATTORNEY YOON TAE-GYEONG
Now what?
-I think everything went as planned.
-Fucking hell.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Hey, my life's over because of the ERPB.
It's over for my family because of me.
I feel like I have to fucking die
to end this.
So how can you say it went as planned?
You bastard.
I reported you to the ERPB
for bullying Jang Seong-gu
so they would come after you.
Do you know what happens next?
This.
MIRAE DAEHAN PARTY
Sir.
Have you seen this?
The ERPB is in serious trouble.
Something happened
while they were at Jinwon High.
Sir, you have a visitor.
Let them in.
Well.
What brings you here at this hour?
Have a seat.
Okay.
Please bring us some tea.
Sure.
Wait, shouldn't you be on your way
to school right now?
I have something to give you.
I'll be on my way after I give you this.
I can't miss school.
My life's over because of the ERPB.
It's over for my family because of me.
I feel like I have to fucking die
to end this.
What is this?
It's what you wanted.
Oh, it's okay.
There were no cameras.
It's not that I don't trust you.
You can decide how you want to use it.
STUDENT FALLS FROM JINWON HIGH ROOFTOP
SUICIDE SUSPECTED
Hey.
What the hell did you do?
You think I got you out
so you could do this?
Oh.
That's not it.
You didn't get me out.
I planned all of this.
What?
You didn't drag me into this.
I dragged you into it.
I sent Officer Kang to you.
PAROLE REVIEW MATERIALS
DEEMED SUITABLE FOR SOCIAL REINTEGRATION
THROUGH PAROLE
It really helped that you pulled strings
with the parole board.
Thank you.
You little shit!
Now, don't swear.
If you want to be president,
you should keep your dignity.
At the end of the day,
you and I are the same.
We both want to bring down the ERPB.
Minister, how is Lee Chi-ho doing
right now?
-Have you seen him?
-It's Hwang Gi-tae.
Are you here to see Lee Chi-ho?
How do you respond to another incident
like this happening at Jinwon High?
What's going on?
Mr. Hwang, what brings you here?
The entire country is in uproar
over this tragedy.
How could I not come?
For now, his treatment is the priority.
You should leave.
I don't think you're in a position
to be saying that.
My life's over because of the ERPB.
It's over for my family because of me.
I feel like I have to fucking die
to end this.
Do you honestly believe
the ERPB played no part
in what happened to Lee Chi-ho?
The release of an audio clip
of a Jinwon High School student
who allegedly attempted suicide
has shocked the public.
The five-second clip
that is going viral on social media
features the student's own voice
expressing resentment toward the ERPB.
The police are focusing
their investigation
on the clip's authenticity,
who recorded it,
and how it was distributed.
The political sphere
is also taking immediate action,
calling for an urgent inquiry to determine
whether there were
any unlawful acts or coercion
during the ERPB's investigation.
JINWON HIGH SCHOOL
Subtitle translation by: Lisa Kim