Talay...
do you know the person in this picture?
Tao Sor has no need for these memories.
You think by doing this, Tao Sor will truly be happy?
We must clear out anything that can destroy his life.
If you really feel bad,
then I beg you.
Quit messing with that family's son!
Your name is Tao Sor.
We're at The Precious Resort, with Mom and Dad.
Why...
can't I remember anything?
It's okay.
I'll be jogging your memory every morning.
About the people who've had direct experience,
would there be anyone still alive?
I know you, right?
And we also have memories together...
right?
Yes!
We love each other very much.
We really love each other.
And..why don't you...
ever come to see me?
Why did you...
leave me in the dark like this..
did I do something wrong?
Not at all!
You didn't do anything wrong, Tao Sor.
I'm sorry.
But from now, I won't ever leave you.
I'll be here as your memory,
your boyfriend,
and everything else for you.
And how will I know that you'll keep your word?
Tomorrow...
I wake up...
and I'll just forget everything.
But this...
will never fade away.
Talay.
What do you have to hide from me?
About if I remember anything?
Becuase Kim's hurt several times already!
Not at all.
He didn't hurt me.
I love him.
He just...
wants me to have memories of every day.
I remind you every day as well!
That you're my younger brother,
that you're a son to your parents,
so why do you have to listen to him?
Why are you angry at me?
You afraid I'll remember something?
Alright.
If you won't tell me,
I'll go ask Mom.
Don't.
I beg you.
Don't ask Mom yet.
Fine.
If you want me to feel like I still love you,
can you please explain?
I really don't know.
It could be something before...
I even met you.
Met me?
What do you mean?
16 years ago...
I found you...
washed up on the beach.
Hey, hey!
Can you hear me?
Wake up!
Kid!
Kid, can you hear me? I'm gonna try to help you.
Stay calm, okay?
It fits you perfectly.
Hungry? Eat something first.
Can I have that?
You have the same taste as my brother.
My name's Talay, what's your name?
I...
don't know.
It's okay, take your time to think.
Do you remember where you came from, and how you ended up on the beach?
It's okay.
Tao Sor!
Tao Sor! Where have you been, son?
I missed you so much!
Don't ever disappear like that, stay with Mom, okay?
Mom?
This isn't him.
I found him washed up on the beach.
Oh...
Are you tired?
Get some food inside you first, okay?
Tomorrow, I'll take you to the police
and we'll find your parents, okay?
Hey, kid!
Kid!
What's the matter?
Kid! Is something wrong?
Kid!
Who are you? And where am I?
Don't you remember? It's me, Talay.
What is this place?
Don't be scared, I'll take care of you.
Tao Sor!
Everything's okay, son. Your mom's here.
My name's Tao Sor?
- Yes.
You're my son, okay? Stay with mommy.
After that,
we tried to find your parents,
but no one ever showed up.
Hello, Tao Sor. My name is Talay.
I am your older brother.
My name's Tao Sor?
That's right. You are my younger brother.
We live with our parents here, at this resort.
That means...
I'm not really Mom and Da's son, right?
That's not it!
You are my brother,
you are Mom and Dad's son,
you are really a member of our family.
Tao Sor...
Listen to me.
Tao Sor, wait!
Tao Sor!
What are you doing?
I am not Tao Sor.
I don't know who I am.
They just took me in...
I don't know...
why I'm even alive.
You're alive so we can love each other.
I don't want to remember anymore.
You're sure about that?
Since you said that...
Because if you need that,
starting tomorrow,
I won't come see you anymore.
You could go back to your old life,
and be Tao Sor as always.
No...
I still want to see you.
Don't leave me like the others.
If that's what you need,
I will be your memory for you.
And no matter how beautiful or hurtful that memory is,
I promise...
that I will always be by your side.
Get over here.
Are you really my friend?
Huh?!
Of course I am!
I've known you for years,
So why the fuck are you helping Kim?!
Talay...
I wasn't helping Kim,
it was for Tao Sor.
I really love you, man.
But I also
love Tao Sor.
The reason I did this, is because...
I can't keep seeing Tao Sor get hurt again.
So you're saying...
I hurt Tao Sor, is that it?
Daiji...
you will never understand how I feel.
I've been looking after Tao Sor for years,
I took good care of him,
Bu today...
you ruined everything!
The one who destroyed everything,
isn't me...
but you!
From now on, you and I are no longer friends!
What are you guys fighting about?
Whatever works for you, then.
Daiji!
Get back to work,
I'll talk to him.
Let go!
Let me go!
- Stop and calm down first.
I said "Let go"
Let go!
I won't let go,
until you stop!
Let go!
Mor!
Let me go!
Tao Sor knows the truth about Kim.
Daiji was the one showed Tao Sor those pictures.
That's not all.
Tao Sor now knows, that he's not my real brother!
I have to do everything to make him forget,
and come back to being the Tao Sor I know!
Or is it finally time?
That you have to let Tao Sor go?
Are you even on my side?
Huh?!
I'm saying this...
not because I'm worried about Tao Sor,
but because I'm worried about you!
How many more times are you gonna torture yourself with this?
If you're not gonna help me, that's fine.
But I'm not gonna lose Tao Sor again.
Normally, what kind of things do you ask for?
I ask for my ship to be safe, and to catch a lot of fish.
And whenever you got out to sea, do you ever see typhoons?
It's a normal thing for sailors.
I see many typhoons, sometimes I don't even know
if I'll survive or not, but usually I do.
But I do think that the Holy Spirits are looking after me.
And normally, do they have any signs or signals for typhoons?
This many questions, will I go on TV?
You won't, but you'll get merits.
Then why am I even here? Wasting my work day.
I got mouths to feed!
What kind of interview is this? I'm outta here!
Sometimes the people here are like that.
That's okay, I've got someone lined up for an interview.
This one's a Shero.
Who?
Remember the list of people you had me contact?
I found one name, but she moved overseas.
But she's in Thailand right now, so I contacted her for an interview.
Which one?
She said she'll be dressed in black.
I've came to ask the Deities here before,
to let me find my lost son, but my wishes have never came true.
Can you tell us what the typhoon was like for you?
That day, our family went out on a ship with Siam Sea.
We were celebrating my boyfriend becoming a Chef.
All of a sudden, the sky changed color.
The typhoon came with no warning, with waves as tall as mountains.
my son who had just turned 5 years old,
was so suprised.
There was a young man on the ship trying to help him,
but the ship rocked over, throwing everyone overboard.
I was holding onto Joe,
but I fell in the water, and the current was too strong.
And I have no idea when I fell in.
And after that, what happened?
I thought I was dead, but I was able to wake up.
Then I found out that I've been Sleeping Beauty for over 3 years.
And your son and boyfriend?
My husband lost his life at sea,
as for my son, he was swallowed by the sea, disappearing without a trace.
Enough?
At first, I couldn't take it.
I tried to find him,
but the officers said it's already been 3 years.
If they could, then they would have already found him.
I couldn't accept it.
Waking up and knowing that there was no one left.
Both my husband and son, so I moved overseas.
We are really sorry for you, and...
me and Siam Sea will have to truly apologize for this tragic loss.
My own family also...
lost our brother from this incident.
I was very young back then,
and no one ever told me this story.
But once I got to hear it from you,
I realize how hurt everyone is.
This should be enough, right?
Thank you so much.
I know that telling this story must be very hard for you.
But I believe that this will benefit so many people.
I also have to thank you.
Being able to let this out has been good.
Ever since I moved,
I haven't told anyone this story.
Then, we'll take you out to dinner.
There's one really good place,
take it as a local bringing you out on a trip!
Shall we get going?
You're so sweet.
- It's true.
Your food is here! This is the chef's signature dish,
please enjoy!
Um, let's start eating.
Delicious as always.
- True! It's so good, it's my favorite.
Is something going on?
Are you okay?
The food doesn't fit you taste, right? I'll tell the chef right away!
Tao Sor! We have a problem!
I apologize, what's wrong with this dish?
You're the one who made this dish?
Yes.
It reminded me of my late husband's cooking,
thank you so much.
It's...no problem.
Tao Sor.
What happened, son?
I'm sorry for startling everyone.
The dish that Chef made, reminded me of my husband
and son, who both passed away.
My condolences.
Thank you for the food.
Your son is talented, and so sweet.
If my son was still here, he'd probably be around this age.
Please enjoy.
Once we're free, we should find a place to go camping with the kids.
So we can have activites together. Where should we go?
- Of course, honey!
That looks nice.
I think it's too far.
We could go to Nok Ped at Phangan.
Not far from Phuket.
The kids can go do acitivites as well. Get some nice photos...
There's tens of places, prices aren't high either
Oh, Tao Sor!
Right on time!
Mom and Dad are finding a place to go camping,
so we can do some activities together.
Oh, I'm...
gonna go draw now.
You haven't drawn us in while! Draw one for us, won't you?
If we do that, then he wouldn't be in the picture with us!
Right, we'll do this.
We have to take a selfie.
Come in.
1, 2, 3. Tao Sor, smile!
Smile a little!
Look over to your mom.
Great, another one!
Alright, Mom? Smile a bit more, Mom!
Okay. Like this, son.
So we'll have you in the picture too, isn't that good?
Yes.
Tao Sor...
You can talk to me if there's something.
I love you very much.
Thank you.
What's wrong, Kim?
Nothing. What are you doing?
Today we went to interview the survivors of the accidents.
It's so sad. She was asleep for 3 years,
and once she woke up, she had lost both her husband and her son.
He's probably not even dead, he might have just been lost at sea.
But 3 years without any signs, doesn't that look like he's gone?
I don't know, but I feel like they'e going to meet.
I don't know who I am.
They just took me in...
I don't know...
why I'm even alive.
Sometimes, it could be true.
What's true?
I think, maybe this woman could be Tao Sor's real mother.
Huh? Is that possible?
What kind of coincidence is that?
Nothing is a coincidence.
Yes, I think we have to bring them together first.
Where is she staying?
She's going back tonight.
We just sent her to the airport.
But if we leave now, we might make it.
Then I'll go ahead. Send me her number and details, okay?
Okay!
Can you send him the details?
Tao Sor.
Why do you have to go this far?
I'm protecting you.
That's not true.
Both you and Mom know well, don't you?
Tao Sor.
Tao Sor!
What's up, Tao Sor?
Kim..
where are you?
Come see me.
Wait, Tao Sor!
Calm down, tell me where you are.
I'm waiting on the bridge.
Okay, alright.
I'll hurry there.
Wait for me, Tao Sor.
Wait for me.
Tao Sor!
Tao Sor, are you asleep?
You can't go to sleep now, Tao Sor!
Tao Sor, wake up!
Wake up, Tao Sor!
Tao Sor!
Who are you?
And...
who am I?
Damn it, not now!
My name's Kim,
and your name's Tao Sor.
You and I are lovers.
Here...
our memories are in here.
It's like this!
Where is it?
Let's take it like this,
if you don't believe me...
we have matching tattoos.
We're lovers, Tao Sor!
Right now, we have to hurry and see your mom!
There's no time left, Tao Sor!
Come with me!
Trust me!
Let's go, Tao Sor!
Trust me.
Tao Sor!
Come with me, come with me!
There's no time left, we have to get to the airport.
Come with me. Trust me, okay?
I'll be the one
that will be your memory for you.
When will you understand?
Every time he finds out the truth, he turns out like this.
You might think I'm selfish for lying to Tao Sor.
But what good comes from him finding out the truth?
I understand everyone's feelings.
How losing someone can hurt so much.
But I've never thought of replacing my brother.
Because in reality,
no one can really replace anyone else.
Please don't! Don't take Tao Sor away from me!
A person like you...
believes in Holy Power too?
I won't ask you for anything.
But there's something I want to ask from you.
In a few days, I'll be going back to Bangkok.
I want Tao Sor's cooking for my last meal here.