MkvDrama.net
It's the Yaji Group, boss.
That’s the mafia group that’s been
trying to take us down for a long time.
Kaizer?
Shan Venice.
You guys really are heaven-sent!
Thanks for helping me out, okay?
Go, go, go!
Pink soldiers!
So does using Aemie still matter
if we want to get back at Ezekiel?
He’s still in
love with Fiona.
We broke up
because I discovered...
that he's part of a mafia group.
What?
Aemie?
You're the guy from the park?
What’s really the truth?
You have to kill three people.
Huh?
Why is Aemie’s mom included?
Dollie, you let me know, okay?
If you've thought of a solution.
Then make it possible.
Hubby!
Wait.
What is it?
You don't want to let
me into my own office?
Huh, woman?
It's because...
Uh, there's a, there's a...
There's a rat!
Yeah.
A huge one.
The rat is really huge.
And it's really angry.
It said if you go in there,
it's gonna bite you.
You want that?
You want a rat to bite you?
Ms. Aemie, is your
meeting done already?
Zeke!
Sir Ken,
are you okay?
I'm okay, I'm okay.
The fuck are you doing here?
Is this why you didn't want
to let me into my office?
Huh?
Because of him?
Sorry, Zeke.
It's just that...
Let me see if it's bleeding.
I'm okay.
No, it's okay.
Come here.
You know what to do.
I'm okay.
We're not yet done, Blood.
Sir Ken, I'm sorry.
It's because Zeke might've
thought you were the
huge rat I was talking
about inside his office.
That's why he
punched you so hard.
A rat?
What?
What's so funny?
Nothing, nothing.
Alright then.
I'll get going first.
Roswell might come
back here again.
And mistake me for a...
Rat.
Okay.
Alright.
Bye-bye.
Alright, alright.
Who gave you permission
to enter my territory?
Blood.
I just heard about what happened
to your company's finances.
I only wanted to help Ms. Aemie.
I have no bad
intention, Roswell.
What's going on
between you and Aemie?
Nothing.
I just find your wife...
very interesting.
And...
You still haven't
changed, Roswell.
Stay the fuck away from my wife.
No.
Mr. Roswell!
Blood, stand up.
Thanks, man.
Don't thank me.
Just leave.
Get him the fuck out of here.
You might lose too much blood.
Move!
Mommy!
Where are you going? Why
are you bringing your things?
Cuz, don't be so dramatic.
We're just going home.
Besides, that Jacob guy said
your husband already got back.
Oh, is that so?
- Mommy!
- Oh, supermarket.
Huh? What supermarket?
We're not at a supermarket,
Mommy. We're at home.
Huh?
Ah...
Sorry, Baby Ae.
Just be good, okay?
Don't give your
husband a headache.
Of course.
I'm even cooking
dinner for him tonight.
Okay.
Okay, bye!
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Take care, okay?
Bye-bye!
Time to cook.
Bye, bye.
Open!
Alyana Heartily?
Wow!
This soda is
amazing, it can talk!
Alyana?
Alyana Heartily Ferrer!
Are you alright?
Who are you?
Don't you recognize me?
Ma'am?
Did you find what you were
looking for, Mrs. Romero?
Romero.
I'm sorry.
Uhm, I thought you
were someone else.
Excuse me.
Let's go, ma'am.
Auntie?
Auntie!
Huh?
Are you okay?
I'm okay, I'm okay.
Come on.
Let's go-go.
Go-go?
To the supermarket?
What happened to her?
I'm hungry.
I wonder if Dodong
is home already.
Zeke probably hasn’t eaten
what I cooked yet, right?
A thief broke in!
Fuck!
That voice sounds familiar.
One more.
What is your problem?
Huh, woman?
Zeke?
You're already home?
Psst, hey!
He finished all the food!
Amazing!
Girl?
Are you okay?
Being sad doesn't suit you.
Why?
How's married life?
Isn't your first wedding monthsary
with your husband coming up, Aemie girl?
When is it again?
Our wedding monthsary?
March 13, I think?
Oh, that's tomorrow.
I think you should buy some
stuff to prepare for your husband.
Is that how it works?
Yeah, of course!
It's your first month as
a married couple, girl.
Do you think Zeke knows that?
I think you should
give him a hint.
So that at least he
could prepare a gift, right?
A gift?
You need a gift?
Of course.
I think you should buy
him something nice.
Maybe like a watch?
A watch?
The thing is...
Zeke already has
a lot of watches.
Then it should be--
It should be something
he doesn't have yet.
Oh dear.
Your husband is rich.
It's like he already
has everything.
Ahh, I got it.
What if I cook something?
What should I make?
Anything will do, girl.
As long as it's made with love.
Love.
Is that a brand?
Where do you buy that?
Oh, God.
Is it some kind of cuisine?
I don't mean it
literally, Aemie girl.
What I mean is, if you're gonna
cook, it should be full of love.
Right.
Hubby, here's your coffee.
Why don't you give
that to your huge rat?
Zeke, about...
about that huge rat.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't actually true.
You saw it yourself, right?
Sir Ken isn't a
rat, he's a person.
And besides,
if he were a rat, then
when you punched him,
he wouldn't have been able to
stand from how hard you hit him.
Are you messing with me again?
Huh, woman?
No, Zeke.
Is that why you wouldn't
let me into my office?
Because Blood was there?
Why would it be
because of Sir Ken?
Ah, unless he thinks Sir Ken was the one
who came up with turning his office pink.
No, Zeke.
You're mistaken.
I...
I was the one who came up
with redecorating your office.
As for your
things-- until now...
You messed with my office?
Huh?
Didn't you notice?
I couldn't even get in
because of you and your rat.
You're so stubborn, I
told you he's not my rat.
Get out of here.
You know, Zeke?
You really need to
see an ophthalmologist.
You have so many issues.
Just recently, you
had LBM, and then--
Get out!
Zeke!
Are you disowning me now?
That's so mean!
Even my mommy!
Even when she bends over
backwards cooking all kinds of things...
she never kicks me out!
To your room!
Idiot!
You keep calling me an idiot.
You're the one who
thought Sir Ken was a rat.
One!
Wait, why are you
kicking me out anyway?
I still have
something to tell you.
I need to give you a hint that--
Two!
Three.
Three...
Four!
You don't know what
comes after three?
I said, go upstairs!
But Dong, don't forget about
our first wedding monthsary, okay?
That should be enough of a hint, right?
What the...
Why the hell are we here?
Well, your monthsary is on March
14, right? You should get her a gift.
I already got her a necklace.
Mr. Roswell, if you're
going to give Aemie a gift,
you should buy something
you know she'll like.
Relax.
It's just a suggestion.
She doesn't really seem
like she's into jewelry.
She seems more...
like that!
Do I really need
to fucking do this?
We don't have a choice.
Fine.
Buy all the dolls here.
I'll wait for you outside.
You're losing
points, Mr. Roswell.
You shouldn't make
someone else buy a gift,
especially if
it's for your wife.
It comes in different colors.
Fuck this goddamn life.
Give them party hats.
Hey, put up the balloons already.
Dong might catch us.
Hurry up!
Oh my God, there it is.
Ma'am Aemie, where
do we put this tarpaulin?
Ah, let's put it here instead.
So Dong sees it right
away when he comes in.
Oh, the design looks great.
Perfect.
Ma'am Aemie...
- the noodles is here.
- Just put it here, just put it here.
Wow, the food looks so good.
Did you cook all this
yourself, Mrs. Roswell?
Yes.
Go on, get some.
What time do you
think he'll arrive?
I'm so excited.
Go on, don't be
shy. Help yourselves.
Good afternoon, Sir.
What are you looking for?
Remote control cars?
No.
We're looking for...
Maybe collectible
action figures, Sir?
Do we look like people who
collect those, Ms. Beautiful?
Then what exactly
are you looking for?
Dollie doll.
Sir?
Dollie doll, Sir?
I need...
the goddamn Dollie now!
It's your fault, you laughed.
Hurry up and open that.
There, take all of those.
Ms. Kate, we're
heading out first.
- Alright, alright.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- I'll get going too.
Take care.
Ma'am Aemie, I'm heading home.
Maybe you shouldn't wait
for Mr. Roswell anymore,
because it doesn't
look like he's coming.
Uhh, Ma'am Aemie.
I'm heading home too.
Thanks for the party.
It's nothing.
Alright, take care.
Let's go.
Jacob, Sebastian,
thanks for the ride.
Why are you only coming now?
What's that in your hand?
You're leaving?
Yes.
It's already late.
And...
don't you remember
anything about today?
Today?
Yeah, today.
As in, nothing at all?
Talk to me tomorrow instead.
I still have a lot to do.
Hey!
Nothing at all.
Nothing.
Come on, join me so I
can at least cheer up.
Hello?
Moo!
Do you have anything to do tomorrow?
A lot.
Wake up, take a bath, eat breakfast,
brush my teeth, get dressed...
a lot. Why?
What I am trying to say is
Moo, maybe I can invite you
to our new resort.
Of course! It's a yes!
Of course I'm coming!
Okay!
I'll pick you up tomorrow, okay?
See you, Moo!
Yes, okay okay. Bye!
We're going to the beach!
Yo, Aemie, I know you're excited already.
How did Kaizer know we
were going to Moo's new resort?
How did you know?
Of course!
I'll pick you up later
after class, alright?
Pick me up?
But I'm not going
to my next class.
And besides, I'm with Moo.
Hi, Moo!
Where are they? Where's cuz?
Ah, they said they'll
just follow later.
Amesyl still has class.
Oh, right.
Come on. Let me carry your bag.
Okay.
Alright, let's go.
So cute!
Let's go!
Very pink.
Where's your car?
Over there.
Wow!
This place is so beautiful.
Too bad Zeke isn't here.
He's actually fun to be around.
Like when, when we had our
honeymoon at the amusement park.
Maybe I should invite him
on another honeymoon.
Moo!
Come on, let's eat.
Okay.
Wow!
Moo is so sweet, right?
Thank you.
You know, I think he'll make
a great husband someday.
Why are you laughing, Moo?
Huh?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
I just thought of something.
I wonder who the lucky
guy Moo will end up marrying.
Honestly, I'm okay with anyone.
As long as...
As long as he doesn't
steal Dodong from me.
Come on, Moo. Let's eat.
Okay.
Aye aye, Captain!
Wow!
There's so much food, right?
I wonder if Zeke
has eaten already.
Why am I even
thinking about that?
Surely, he already ate, right?
I'll just text him.
Oh no.
Oh no, I forgot
to reply to Kaizer!
He said he's going to pick me up.
Why is he going to pick you up?
I don't even know.
He just somehow knew
I was excited earlier.
But I don't know why.
Wait.
But it's true, I really
am excited to be here.
Is Kaizer coming here?
Kaizer?
Yeah.
No.
Oh, it's Louie.
What's up, Louie?
Hello!
Nico,
send me the address.
- Yeah.
- We'll go to you.
Ah, okay, okay.
I'll sent you guys the address,
then let's meet up later.
Okay, okay.
Alright.
- See you, dude.
- Alright, alright.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
Louie and the others
are coming too.
Really?
Yay!
This watermelon is so good.
Moo!
Cheers, Moo!
Cheers!
Kaizer!
Waiting for someone?
Ah...
I'm just waiting for Aemie.
It's her monthsary
with Mr. Roswell, right?
Today?
Hmm.
Are you sure?
I thought it was yesterday.
Yesterday?
March 13 was yesterday.
Yeah, and 13
is their monthsary.
I even helped Aemie
look for ingredients
and a gift.
When you called, remember?
And as far as I know,
she even prepared a surprise party
at her husband's office yesterday.
Ahh.
Hey, twin!
Hi, Amesyl girl.
What?
You guys are going
to the beach too?
- The beach?
Yeah, at Nico's resort.
Actually, they've been
there for a while now.
- They?
Here, Nico just
texted the address.
Look, check it out.
See?
Why?
That's close to the beach
house Mr. Roswell bought.
You sure?
Yeah.
Hey Moo, let's make
a Dollie sandcastle!
You have to kill three people.
Why is Aemie's mom included?
Just because. Meisha and I
couldn't think of anyone else.
Hey, Zeke!
Are you okay? Are you
even listening to me?
Sorry, I just thought
of something.
And I'm not Zeke, okay?
I'm Nico.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry, Moo.
You know what,
let's just take a walk.
Okay, let's go.
You're something else.
Wow!
Hey, Moo, let's go over there!
It's beautiful!
Whoa, we don't own that place.
We can't go there.
We're just going to look.
We're not stealing
it from the owner.
Happy monthsary, wife.
Oh.
Wait.
This is for you.
Is that Zeke?
Zeke!
Come here!
Hurry.
Hubby!
What...
the...
fuck?
Zeke!
Hubby!
What are you doing here?
Get inside.
Huh?
But...
No buts.
But I said "but," not "buts."
Get in!
Wow!
It's beautiful!
A pink house!
What's up, Ezekiel?
Oh, wait.
Dong, can I...
Moo!
Why is there so much
blood on your face?
Oh, it's nothing,
Moo. I just slipped.
Right, Ezekiel?
Huh?
Wait,
I'll get the first aid kit.
Where's the first aid kit?
It's just there.
Inside my luggage.
Okay.
Wait.
Zeke, I can't find
the first aid kit.
Where is it?
It's just in my luggage.
Okay, wait.
Hold on!
Is this it?
Zeke! This one?
No, no, no.
That's my toiletries.
Wrong.
Okay, wait. Hold on!
Wait.
Zeke!
Are you okay?
Moo!
Why did you punch Zeke?
Aemie, I was just...
Let's go, wife.
No.
Wait.
He was still saying something.
We're okay.
Right?
Yeah.
No, uh...
Mr. Roswell and I
were just playing...
rock-paper-scissors.
I think I got a little carried
away and hit him in the face.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hey, Dong.
What?
That's bad for you.
Do you know that every cigarette
takes five minutes off your life?
Yay!
Come on.
Let's treat your wound.
Sit down here.
That's because of you.
Come closer.
Closer.
Ouch!
Careful.
Sorry, sorry.
This Dong of mine.
He just looks cool, right?
But he's terrible at
rock-paper-scissors.
You know, you should
practice rock-paper-scissors.
And of all people, you challenged
Moo. He's really good at it.
Whatever.
Bring your face closer.
Uhh.
Hubby.
Is this house yours?
Why is everything pink?
And why are there
so many Dollie dolls?
You never told me you
also like pink and Dollie dolls.
Come on, tell me the truth.
Are you gay, Dong?
Why do you have a pink house?
This is yours.
It's a gift.
A gift?
For me?
Yes.
Oh my god!
Yay!
Happy birthday to me!
It's beautiful.
So beautiful.
Do you really not know
what date it is today?
Duh, of course I know.
It's March 14 today because
yesterday was March 13!
Does he really not remember?
I'll just go explore
the pink house.
It's beautiful!
Wow!
Beautiful!
Can I take the Dollie doll?
Go ahead.
Oh my god!
Wow, it's beautiful!
It's beautiful!
Do you like it?
So much!
So much, Dong!
It's beautiful!
And...
look!
It must be so nice to eat here!
You get a perfect
view of the ocean!
Beautiful!
Oh, Dong!
Let's make a Dollie sandcastle?
Please?
Right now?
Hmm.
Zeke!
Come on, let's swim!
I'll just stay here.
I'll watch you swim.
You're such a killjoy!
Come here!
What's that?
A Dollie sandcastle!
Ta-da!
Hey!
Why did you destroy it?
I worked hard on that!
That's exactly why I destroyed
it, so you wouldn't have a hard time.
Zeke!
Help! I'm drowning...
I'm drowning...
Zeke.
Help.
Wow, it's beautiful!
Hey, let me join!
Nope!
You've been like
that since yesterday.
Huh?
Let's change the topic.
I don't want to remind him that I
waited yesterday, it's embarrassing.
No, nothing!
Nothing, Zeke.
The ocean is beautiful, right?
But you know,
it would probably be even
prettier if the ocean were pink.
Oh.
Or the swimming pool! Pink too!
Do you want me to make one?
You can do that?
You can make the ocean pink?
Yeah.
It's so beautiful. You're amazing!
Happy
first
month of happiness...
wife.
Yeah.
Oh.
You know.
It feels like
something's missing.
Bela...
ted.
Belated.
Belated?
Late.
It's over, it already happened.
Belated.
Don't you know that?
It's just "belated" and you
don't even know the meaning.
Of course, I know that.
Aemie!
Cuz!
What's this?
Did you make this?
- Of course not.
- Nice!
I knew it.
It's pretty.
Hi, Louie!
- Hi, Cuz!
- Hi, Kaizer!
- Hello!
- Cuz?
Come join us, we're
making a Dollie sandcastle.
Zeke made this one.
Roswell made it.
Oh, really?
It's beautiful.
Right, Zeke, you made it?
It's just too beautiful.
Why aren't you answering?
- You should be proud of it.
- Wow!
It's beautiful!
Aemie, what time did you arrive?
Just a little while ago.
Ah, Aemie.
We'll leave you for a bit.
Mr. Roswell and I need to discuss
something business-related.
Okay.
Fine.
I'll be back.
Hurry!
Let's do this again.
Let me take a look.
Look.
Ah, Mr. Roswell.
Did you know?
Aemie waited for you the
whole day yesterday at the office.
What?
Yeah!
She thought you got
married on February 13.
So that's why there was a celebration
party at your office yesterday.
Stupid girl.
Ohh.
Boss really is a lover boy now!
Are you saying something?
Uhh.
No.
Yes.
Ahh.
It's also about Blood.
Oh, relax.
I just heard that Blood
wanted to help Aemie.
I'm so fucking sure Aemie never
asked for that asshole's help.
Are you jealous of Blood?
I don't see your point in
asking me that, Lamperouge.
I'm just saying.
Blood isn't a threat.
He honestly looks sincere
about wanting to help.
Are you fucking insane?
Why?
If you want to prolong
your meager life,
you better shut your
fucking mouth up.
Mr. Roswell.
We've known Blood
since we were kids.
Wake the fuck up!
He only wants to be
friends with my wife
so he can use her as bait.
Come on.
It's just once.
We'll bury you.
Come on, Louie.
Hubby.
Are you sure you
actually know how to cook?
I'll do it.
I'll do it, there.
Ouch!
Can you please just stay
over there? I'm cooking.
By the way, why were
you holding a gun earlier--
Ah, fuck!
Fuck!
Oh no!
Why are you cutting
your finger too?
Oh, Zeke!
Sorry, sorry.
Are you planning to
cook your finger too?
I don't eat fingers, okay?
Does it hurt?
Oh no.
Thank you.
Let me just check what I'm cooking.
What?
So you mean, you both
are part of a mafia group?
Yeah.
How come?
How did you and
Mr. Roswell join?
Mr. Roswell is the mafia boss.
Is that a trend nowadays?
I mean, why are you
all joining mafia groups?
And, I mean, why
are you telling me this?
You know why I broke
up with Kevin, right?
I know.
And I felt guilty
when you told me that.
Because I'm part
of the Mafia too.
That's why I'm
telling you this...
So I won't be hiding anything
from you as a friend anymore.
So if Ezekiel Roswell
is the mafia boss.
Does that mean
Aemie's life is in danger?
I don't know.
I mean.
The conflict between the mafia groups
right now is on a whole different level.
Okay, how about Nics?
You were opening up
something about him, is he a--
Ezekiel knows that
Young joined the Yaji.
Okay.
What's with you guys
and mafia groups?
Okay, enough
about the mafia thing.
I won't ask any
further questions.
But, does Aemie
girl know about this?
Not yet.
Kai.
She needs to know.
I must tell her.
I have to tell her.
Don't, Venice. Venice, please.
Sit.
Venice.
Promise me this.
No one can know about
this, especially Aemie.
But, Kai...
If Aemie finds out about this.
Would that help her?
Yes, Kaizer.
At least she's aware.
We don't have the
right to interfere.
Besides.
Ezekiel knows what he's doing.
Don't worry.
Ezekiel would never let
anything happen to Aemie.
Yeah, you're
right. I can see that.
He really loves Aemie.
One last thing, Venice.
I'm asking you a favor.
I hope no one else knows yet.
I'm only telling you this because
you're the only friend I trust.
No problem, Kai.
Your secret's safe with me.
I know.
I trust you.
Just stay calm.
Look at me.
That's the secret
of handsome guys.
Always stay calm.
Wow!
Maybe Zeke got me a gift
because it's Christmas!
Wait.
Yesterday was only March 13.
Oh.
Maybe he thought it
was Christmas already.
Zeke.
How did the pool turn pink?
Take a closer look.
Pink lights and glass tiles,
equals, pink swimming pool.
It's beautiful.
That's amazing.
But wait.
I only mentioned that
earlier today, right?
Zeke!
Do you have superpowers?
Well...
I knew you'd ask for this.
So I had it made
a long time ago.
But of course.
Your pink swimming pool
will only be visible at night.
That's why I couldn't
show it to you earlier.
Oh, wow!
Those look delicious.
Where did you order them from?
I cooked those.
I was cooking earlier, remember?
Oh, right. You're amazing!
What did you cook?
You know, I'm hungry. Just eat.
I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
Sit.
Okay, okay, okay.
What is it?
Eat.
What is it, woman?
Huh?
Because, Zeke.
My mommy told me
not to eat food that's
unfamiliar to me.
Because it might not
have been cooked properly
or it could be poisoned.
What the?
Do I look like I'd poison you?
If you don't eat,
I'll have this house demolished.
Hey!
Of course!
Of course I'll eat!
Come on now.
I was just saying.
Zeke acts all grumpy and aloof.
But...
he's actually sweet too.
About yesterday.
I, uhh...
I'm sorry.
Was that about...
our first wedding
monthsary, Zeke?
Then why did you forget?
I didn't forget.
If you didn't forget, then why
did you only remember now?
Look at Dong over here.
He didn't even
answer my question.
And now he's making
me throw away the trash.
Hey, wait.
Where are you going?
To throw it away.
You told me to, right?
Stupid girl.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, I have a gift for you too.
I was supposed to give
this to you yesterday.
Thanks.
Cute, right?
Yeah.
Hubby.
Mmm.
You're rich, right?
Oh?
What else could you
possibly wish for in life?
None.
What else could I wish for?
Nothing at all?
Aemie.
All I want...
is to spend a million
monthsaries with you.
Remarkably beautiful.
We're going to the mall?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Shit.
Huh?
What did you say?
Aemie.
Stay here. Just
keep your head down.
- Huh?
- Stay low.
Why?
Music sounds better
when you're ducking down.
So.
What about the third target?
You have to kill
her as well, Young.
Don't tell me you're
chickening out.
Zeke, what is going on with you?
You don't look okay!
Get inside.
Fiona Stonehurst.
Ezekiel's girlfriend.
I think we need to remove...
all of this trash.
So...
you're Aemie.
Obviously.
Ezekiel
actually mentioned you
while he was in Hawaii,
with me.
Thanks for accompanying
my husband.
My husband.
I love him.
And I always will.
MkvDrama.net