Her name is Song, Sadanun Warakij.
She's one of the company's
top food researchers.
I already told you.
I don’t want a serious relationship.
If you’re catching feelings,
then this ends here.
I like you.
And I'm pretty sure
you feel something for me, too.
So much that
I can already picture our future.
We'll get married
and have twin babies together.
Their names will be Ruean and Rai.
I’m kidding.
Our twins would be named
Nirin and Lila instead.
I searched the names online.
It said they’re very auspicious.
The kids will take great care
of parents like us.
Are you insane or something?
How are you imagining that far ahead?
-I don’t--
-I know you’re not serious about anyone.
I know.
But I’m not in a rush.
You might think that now,
but in the future, who knows?
You’re way too smart.
You know, Ploy getting a stomachache today
was obviously a setup to get us alone.
If you really hated me,
you wouldn’t still be standing here.
I’m only here because I pity you.
You’re the chairwoman’s granddaughter.
If nobody takes care of you,
you'd be like a lost, pricey puppy.
You really have a sharp tongue.
Calling me a dog again.
But it’s okay.
At least I’m an expensive one.
By the way, since you already
brought me food to taste,
would you be interested
in adopting a dog too?
That’s enough.
Stop daydreaming already.
There.
After you finish, leave me a review too.
You’ve already wasted
too much of my work time.
Here.
The food is delicious,
but the chef looks even tastier.
P.S. I’d still love to keep tasting more.
If you're ready for another,
I'm just a call away.
Your hot americano is ready.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to.
Thank you.
Once I'm done, I'll wash it
and return it to you right away.
Mudmee.
You startled me.
Since when did you become so jumpy?
Or are you thinking about someone?
Shut up. Don’t be ridiculous.
Who would I even think about?
So, where did you go?
Did you go bother Song again?
Bother her? I was just flirting with her.
Mudmee.
Song has really put up a wall against me.
It's so high that I’m losing confidence
and wondering what’s wrong with me.
I’m both pretty and rich.
Okay, maybe my boobs are a little small,
but that’s most people’s type these days.
You’re really confident, huh?
Of course.
So, do you think Song
is like ordinary people?
No. She’s a rare item.
Exactly.
I think for Song,
if she’s going to like someone,
there has to be more
of a reason than that.
Not just being pretty, rich,
having small boobs, or big boobs.
That alone isn’t enough.
Then what kind of person does she like?
No idea.
I’ve only seen her work side.
I know nothing about the rest.
She’s hard to read.
Mudmee.
Then let’s turn it into work.
Work?
Bobis Magazine contacted me.
They want to do
a special feature on our company.
The concept is to inspire
the younger generation.
And I'd love to pitch
a piece on researchers.
So how do you want me to help?
Well, by being that researcher.
You want to interview me?
Yes. Who could be more suitable than you?
You’re our company’s
outstanding researcher.
I think I’ll pass.
Song.
I truly believe your story
can inspire readers.
And I also want to use this chance
to promote our company at the same time.
I want people to know
that food researchers are one
of the organization’s driving forces.
If our company has good researchers,
we can guarantee the products
we release will be high quality.
Please help me out.
If it’ll benefit the company,
then I’m happy to do it.
Thank you.
And there’s one more thing.
I know Piang’s been trying
to flirt with you lately.
It’s kind of funny.
In all my life, I’ve never seen
my little sister try this hard before.
She must really like you.
But I also know you’re not playing along.
And that she annoys you.
If it gets too much, you can scold her.
I already did, but she just won’t listen.
Honestly, she does annoy me.
But not that much, Boss.
I think I can handle it.
Who do you want me to interview?
This person right here.
I want to know her life story.
But I want to do it in a more subtle way.
But don’t worry
about your interview flopping.
She’s our company’s leading researcher.
She’s talented and hot.
Wait, this is Song.
You know her?
She’s a freelance model.
I met her a few times
during my internship.
She's a researcher at your company?
You knew her and didn’t tell me?
How the hell was I supposed to know, girl?
Remember the girl I met on the dating app
who used a cat photo as her profile?
That was her.
What a coincidence.
Coincidence my ass.
It’s fate.
Why say you're okay giving
your virginity to a stranger,
when you ended up falling for her?
You’re so weak.
Yeah, yeah. Say whatever you want.
But Song is someone I want to date,
marry, and build a family with.
Even Mudmee volunteered to help me.
So as my best friend,
you have no right to refuse.
I already sent you the script
I want you to ask her.
These are all personal questions.
Of course. I want to know.
As for the work-related questions,
you can handle those yourself.
That’s your job, right, bestie?
Seriously?
All my life, I’ve never seen
my little sister try this hard before.
She must really like you.
THE FOOD IS DELICIOUS
BUT THE CHEF LOOKS EVEN TASTIER
You actually dressed
the way I asked you to.
So, do you like it?
I like it a lot.
You’re really clumsy.
And who told you
to dress like this at the office?
Do you want everyone staring at you?
Yes.
But not everyone.
I only want you to look at me.
I happened to see that this afternoon,
you’re doing an interview for a magazine.
So, I wanted to dress up nicely
in the style you like.
Why? They’re not interviewing you.
Just think of it as me dressing up
to cheer you on instead.
-What should we eat?
-Pizza?
Sure. Then for lunch, we can go eat…
together.
Piang.
What happened?
Nothing.
I was just being clumsy and almost fell.
But Song caught me in time.
-That’s wonderful.
We were about to go eat, Piang.
Would you come with us?
Yeah. We’re heading to the elevator
in the other building.
-Come with us, Piang.
-Can I really?
-Of course.
You’re the company owner.
Nobody would dare complain about you.
-Let’s go.
-Let’s go together.
Let’s go.
Wait.
Where did she go?
Here.
You know, I think Song
is finally starting to waver. Or maybe…
the Arctic wolf is about to fall
for a Holland Lop bunny.
Definitely.
Then hyenas like us
have to support this, right?
Idiot. Gross. What hyenas?
Think of another animal.
Then what about monitor lizards?
What monitor lizards? They're in the park.
-Wait for me.
-Everyone, wait for me.
Wait for me.
-The elevator’s crowded. Wait for me.
-Come on.
What are you eating today? I want noodles.
Then eat noodles.
And what are you eating? Same place?
I’ve never come to the company before,
so I don’t know what’s good here.
You’ll know once we're there.
-But I wanted to know…
-Elevator's here.
-Hurry up. Go.
-Go.
-Let's get in.
-I’m coming too, wait.
Go. Press it already.
It’s me, Piang.
The chairwoman’s granddaughter.
It’s me.
Yes, ma’am. I know who you are.
It’s just that employees like us
have limited break time, Miss Piang.
Besides, our break is almost over too.
-Right?
-Yeah, yeah.
-That's right.
-Yeah.
So if possible, could you let us go first?
-Fine.
-Okay.
Thank you. So kind of you.
-Song, go.
-Song, go ahead.
-Go get her.
-Finally, we get to go.
You guys go ahead.
Hurry.
-Hurry, hurry.
-Bye.
Wait for me.
You didn’t want to leave me alone,
that’s why you got out, right?
Why are you walking away from me now?
Who told you? I only did it
beacuse it was too crowded,
so I walked out.
Then what about this jacket?
If you didn’t care about me,
you wouldn’t have let me wear it, right?
You dressed so revealingly.
Whether it was Namprow or Ploy,
I’d do the same for anyone.
Not true.
You’re falling for me.
You dummy, stop imagining things.
And stop meddling in my life already.
I don’t feel anything for you.
And I never will.
I don’t believe you.
You do feel something.
You just won’t admit it.
Listen.
I’m not a complicated person.
If I really had feelings for someone,
I wouldn’t run away.
I’d even look for chances
to get closer to them.
But you, you’ve never crossed my mind.
Even that night, I don’t remember a thing.
Then let me help refresh your memory.
How about that?
Stop.
That jacket, I spent almost
my entire month’s salary on it.
Pick it up right now. It’ll get dirty.
Song!
Pick it up.
And put it back on properly.
Don’t take it off again
until you get home, understand?
I’m here already. Where are you?
Yeah, I’m coming right now.
These are the questions
for your interview.
Most of them are work-related questions.
There are a few personal ones too.
So if there’s anything
you’re not comfortable answering,
just let me know.
We’re recording this, not live streaming.
We can pause anytime.
Okay.
Do you have any questions, Song?
Just one.
You’re the CEO of Bobis.
Why are you interviewing me yourself?
I was assigned to do it.
-Song, are you ready?
-Ready.
Okay.
Hi.
Hello.
Camera ready?
Ready.
Camera.
Recording.
Action.
My name is Song Sadanun Warakij.
I’m a food researcher at One Two Six Food.
The recipient of the Mega Excellent Award
for Outstanding Researcher
three years in a row.
Could you tell us a little more
about this award?
Sure. The Mega Excellent Award
for Outstanding Researcher
is based on accumulated scores
from each research team
working on various company projects.
Whether it’s OEM projects from clients
or projects we develop ourselves,
the team with the highest score
wins the award for their team leader.
So you’re the team leader?
Yes.
Then you must be really good at cooking.
I can cook a little.
But honestly, the one who’s much
better than me is my grandma.
My grandma is the reason
I became interested in food.
That’s why I decided to study
Food Science and Culinary Arts.
So I wouldn't step on her toes.
So you must be very close to your grandma.
Could you tell us a little about her?
My grandma is very kind.
She’s modern-minded.
She raised me more like a friend
than a guardian.
What about your parents?
Several years ago, something happened.
My mother suddenly became ill.
So my father took her abroad.
Would you tell us
what exactly happened back then?
Song, I’m sorry.
I really can’t stay anymore.
Neung!
Pause the interview.
Cut.
Are you okay, Song?
Are you okay?
Can someone get her some water?
Here's water.
I’m okay.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
But can we skip
the family-related questions?
That's all I'm willing to share.
Of course.
In that case, let’s move on
to another part of the interview.
Okay.
Let’s continue filming.
Song, are you ready?
Ready.
Is the camera ready?
There’s a package delivery for Mudmee.
I’ll be right back.
SENDER: KWANRIN PINIJPHAN
Kwanrin.
One Two Four.
Hello, Mudmee.
-Hello.
-It’s been a while since we talked.
A little while.
The chair I ordered
from One Two Four has been perfect.
Everyone says
it’s beautiful and well-designed.
Thank you so much.
So, is there anything I can help you with?
Well, the other day, I went to a café
and happened to meet a woman
named Kwanrin.
I saw her holding documents
from One Two Four.
Has she started working there?
Oh, Kwanrin.
Yes. We just hired her
as a Project Manager.
She only started working here
a few days ago.
So you know her too?
Oh right.
She lives in the same house
as the chairwoman too.
She’s close
to the chairman’s daughter-in-law.
She even helps take care
of the chairwoman’s fish.
Honestly, she could’ve gotten in
through connections if she wanted.
But Kwanrin…
We’ve gathered almost
all the information we need now.
So I have a few more questions
I’d like to ask you,
on behalf of viewers across the country
including all of your fans
who came to support you today.
You dedicate yourself to work so much,
how do you make time for your partner?
I don’t need to make time
because I don’t have one.
I choose to focus only on work.
I believe work won’t betray us
the way love does.
Then hypothetically,
if you were to fall in love,
what kind of person would be your type?
The one you want to spend your life with.
Someone mature.
Not about age, but their mindset
and behavior must be proper.
From the way they dress
to their personality.
One who understands things right away,
not clingy, not childish,
not chasing after me.
And most importantly,
they must have something of their own.
Not relying on their family’s success
for the rest of their life.
Excuse me.
Did you hear that clearly, bestie?
The type she likes
is the complete opposite of you.
I’m laughing my ass off.
Do you really think
someone like Piangrawin
would be shaken by that?
Dream on.
That’s everything, right?
Yes, all done.
That’s a wrap.
Thank you so much.
-Thank you so much, Song.
-You’re welcome.
-Today went smoothly.
-Piang, how did it go?
Please make yourself comfortable, Song.
Please take care of her.
Okay.
Mon. Did something happen?
Nothing really, Mud.
We just need to give Piang
some time to process things.
Process things?
Come on, Song.
Modeling has always been my dream.
Will you go audition with me?
Please?
At least, if I don’t pass the audition
but you do, I won’t feel so bad about it.
If you don’t pass, how would I?
We look alike.
We only look alike on the outside.
But in every other way,
we’re completely different.
You have this presence.
Some kind of energy
from within that I don’t have.
So dramatic.
I’m serious.
That’s really how I feel.
You’re way stronger than I am.
No thanks.
I don’t like being in front of cameras.
I prefer being in front
of stoves and test tubes.
Fine, I won’t force you.
But can you promise me one thing?
If one day I’m gone
and I still haven’t achieved my dream,
can you do it for me?
Why would you say that?
Just promise me already.
Come on.
Please, Song.
Fine, I promise.
This outfit won’t work.
Is the skirt too short?
So tacky.
But whatever, this is the style she likes.
Nope.
Hello, Song.
No, not this either.
This looks proper.
INCOMING CALL
Hello, Ploy.
Hello, Piang.
Someone told me what Song
said in the interview today.
Don’t overthink it.
I think she was just messing with you.
I think so too,
but I still want to change for her.
Actually, it’s good you called.
I think I already have everything
she’s looking for
except one thing.
I need to find something of my own to do.
But I honestly don’t know
where to even start.
Is there anything
you’re especially interested in?
I'm interested in Song, duh.
That, I know. But I mean,
is there anything you like doing
or especially enjoy eating?
Maybe you could use that as inspiration.
I don’t really have anything
I especially like.
Or try Song's interests?
Her interests?
Mudmee.
You still don’t knock
before entering, Piang.
I want to open a matcha café.
I’m not sick.
You are sick.
So, what made you want to do that?
Don’t tell me this is about Song again.
You know me too well.
Yes. I want to have something of my own.
I want to become
the kind of person she likes.
Please, help me.
Fine.
I’ll handle the location
and the shop decoration too.
Mudmee, you’re the sweetest.
I love you the most.
Piang wants to open a matcha café.
A matcha café?
Yeah. She said she wants to do it.
She said she wants to
have something of her own.
Honestly, I do want to support her idea.
I want her to try working
on something for once.
But I don’t know anything
about this kind of business,
so I came to ask for your advice.
I heard you’ve worked
on matcha-related products before.
Maybe you could give us some advice.
Boss, you really came to the right person.
Not only did Song develop
this product before,
she’s also a huge matcha lover.
She loves it so much
she makes me buy it for her every morning.
Then I guess I’ll have to trouble you…
I mean, Miss Song.
I thought you said
you didn’t like people chasing after you.
Then why are you doing it yourself?
That matcha café thing, don’t you realize
you’re doing way too much?
What do you mean?
I’m not playing around.
I’m serious.
I really want something of my own.
You think I’d believe you?
Believe it or not, that’s up to you.
I mean, Miss Song, we’re adults already.
Shouldn’t one explanation be enough?
Miss Piang.
I still need to discuss the café.
Stop following me.
Stop pestering me,
and stop clinging to me too.
Understood?
That crazy kid.
Excuse me, are you Matika?
Yes.
You’re Kwanrin from One Two Four, right?
What a coincidence.
I should apologize,
for requesting your company
to send you over so urgently.
This project is a bit rushed.
It’s totally fine. It’s my job anyway.
So what do we need to do today?
We need to measure the space,
take your brief and pass it
to the interior designer.
After that, I’ll help oversee everything
until the project is completed.
That’s great.
We’ll get to see each other again.
Then let’s get started.
Come here, I’ll help.
You don’t have to.
You’re the CEO.
I doubt you’re used to this kind of work.
Try me.
This side is 2.5 meters wide.
If we place the counter here,
the morning light should hit just right.
Perfect for customers
who want to make content.
But in the afternoon,
the sunlight will probably be too strong.
We should install
heat-blocking film or sun blinds.
That way the coffee machines
won’t be exposed to direct heat.
As for the materials, I'm not fussy.
As long as it keeps a Zen tone
to match the name Zen Su Garden.
See?
Some CEOs can do more than you think.
You.
Piang.
Did you finish already?
Only the classic menu items.
The signature menu is still left.
It needs a story.
Since you’re the shop owner,
I need to ask you first
before I can come up with it.
Sure.
You can ask me anything you want to know.
Do you have any childhood memories
that are especially meaningful to you?
Not really.
My life was never very exciting.
It felt like everything
had already been decided by my grandma.
I just followed along.
Really?
You seem so strong-willed.
You don’t look like someone
who listens to others,
even if it’s your grandma.
Not about everything.
But if it’s something
I can accept, I will.
After all, Grandma only
has me and Mudmee left.
My parents both died
in an accident when I was little.
Your parents died,
and you can still smile?
It’s been a long time already.
Besides, I believe my parents
wouldn’t want me to stay sad forever.
Same goes for you too.
No matter what you’ve been through,
or how terrible it was,
in the end, you have to
learn to smile through it.
I just remembered
my favorite childhood memory.
My parents once took me to see
the sea of mist on the mountain.
It was beautiful.
There were flowers and little clouds too.
I still remember that feeling so clearly.
Sea of mist, flowers, little clouds.
Little Cloud Matcha.
It’s as beautiful
as the sea of mist I once saw.
Song.
Did you finish creating
the recipe for Piang?
What’s up?
Do you have any plans tonight?
If not,
want to
go grab some drinks together?
I already made plans with my friends.
How about this?
You can come join us.
My friends are friendly.
I promise it’ll be fun.
Okay.
Let me pack up first.
I’ll send you the location.
Ple.
This is Ploy, my junior teammate.
Nice to meet you, Ple.
Nice to meet you too, Ploy.
Did you forget I'm sitting here too?
Are you jealous, babe?
She’s cute, so I accidentally
fell for her a little.
But you know no one
is more important than you, right babe?
You two are really smooth with this act.
If I didn’t already know,
I’d think you two were actually dating.
And you, want to join in too?
That’s enough. You’re scaring her.
Hey Ploy, weren’t you saying
you wanted to use the restroom?
Go ahead.
I’ll order your drink.
Okay. Thanks.
Why were you teasing her?
Hey, I'll get two of the usual.
Two of the usual, coming right up.
What’s wrong with you?
Ple, as someone
who’s been my friend for a long time,
can you do me a favor?
Kiss me.
Make that woman jealous.
Are you sure?
They’re not really together.
They’re just friends.
That’s Piang.
Why is she drinking so much?
I'm sorry.
Song, you’re here already?
That’s enough. You’re really drunk.
Get up.
No.
I really like you.
Even if you kiss another woman,
it won’t make me like you any less.
Enough.
Why did you get this drunk?
What should we do, Song?
We can’t just leave her like this.
Should we call her a ride home?
We can’t.
She’s the granddaughter of the company
owner where Song and I work.
If something happens to her,
we’ll be in huge trouble.
It’s okay. I’ll handle it myself.
You can get home on your own, right?
Yeah.
What about you, Ple?
I’m a little drunk, but my bodyguard
will take me home. Totally chill.
I’ll take her home myself.
Then I’m counting on you.
-Dance with me first.
-That’s enough.
You don’t have to take me home.
I have to.
I already promised Song.
Besides, there’s something
I want to tell you.
What is it?
I know you two
are usually just teasing each other,
but kissing?
I think that’s a bit too much.
It was just a kiss.
You and I have kissed before too.
So you can do that with just anyone?
I’ve done this
with lots of people already.
I’m just having fun.
I’m not serious about anyone.
But if you can’t accept that,
-I understand--
-Why wouldn’t I accept it?
You’re actually really interesting.
Come on. Let’s go home.
Careful.
Get in properly.
Let’s go dancing again.
What dance? How drunk are you?
So where are we going?
To a hotel.
I’ll do anything to win your heart.
And I’ve already started.
I’ve invested this much in you already.
You should agree to date me.
You even let me come up to your room.
Does that make me special yet?
Didn’t I tell you
to take good care of my granddaughter?
Then why did you let her
disappear all night like this?
Hello, Madam Chairwoman.
Stop getting involved
with my granddaughter.
Subtitle translation by: