‎SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
‎ADAPTED FROM XI XING’S NOVEL
‎QUEEN CHU‎ ON QIDIAN.COM
Tie Ying commands an elite squad
of covert warfare.
Night raid on Wuyang Pass,
fire on Panying Pass,
and massacre at Qingshi Stronghold.
They've never failed.
I've heard about this squad.
They always strike on dark, windy nights,
slaying all who stand in their way.
In that case,
I don't think we're likely to win.
Not really.
This squad excels at night raids
because they have superb hearing.
That's why they can move freely
in the darkness.
There's a way.
We can set traps in the bamboo forest
and catch them off guard.
Then we'll shoot them from the shadows.
Then, we might stand a chance.
The whistle is our code.
You can use it
to make our people to set traps for you.
During the fight, use it to communicate.
Thank you.
Tie Ying is mine.
Mere child's play.
Jiu, when you kill, you have steady hands.
But now, they shake.
I failed to protect you.
Don't mind.
It matters to me.
Before, it was an order.
But now,
it's my duty.
And the future?
In the future…
We'll see.
Whatever happens,
I will protect you.
Tie Ying retreated.
Your father is safe now.
Thank you, ma'am.
You helped a lot.
To protect me, you suffered heavy losses.
I don't know
how I can repay you.
Since we promised to protect you,
we will keep our word.
Tie Ying retreated.
But more troops will be sent from Xiaonan.
You'd better leave soon.
Wait.
My father gave this to me.
When this is all over
and I'm back in the Capital,
you people can ask me for rewards
with this jade pendant.
‎WAR ENDS
All right.
What a nice piece of jade.
Come on. Take it.
Eat some of this.
Have you noticed
the way she looks at you is a bit strange?
She means no harm.
But strange, indeed.
I think Tie Ying has fled back to Xiaonan.
Xiao Xun's men will come again.
It's not wise to stay here long.
Right.
We'll leave soon.
Ma'am, in that fight, we had three dead
and seven badly injured.
Three traps east were ruined
and need to be reset.
Have our men properly settled.
Yes. I'm on it.
Let's go.
You're about to leave?
Don't bother to say goodbye.
And you have apologized.
But I have one question.
What exactly happened
during my father's suppression?
I told you, didn't I?
I doubt it.
I want the truth.
This stronghold
is totally my father's style.
I don't believe
it was just a misunderstanding.
In that case, why did Mu Mianhong
jump off a cliff instead of explaining?
If you don't tell me,
I might as well go ask my father.
Do you know your father well?
What kind of man
do you think he is?
My father…
He's the God of War of our state
and an all-powerful frontier hero.
People respect him
and revere him.
Does that include you?
Do you like this kind of father?
No?
Why?
Because he's a hero to others.
He's a hero to people in Yunzhong.
He's a hero to the State of Chu.
But I want him to be an ordinary father.
Carve wooden dolls for me,
watch fireworks with me,
give me pretty braids,
and be there with me
for every important moment.
But actually…
none of this happened.
What about…
your mother?
My mother?
I guess she's a great lady.
According to my father,
she's a perfect woman.
She was well-learned
and versed in all arts.
Sadly, I didn't witness that.
My mother died at a young age.
For as long as I can remember,
I have no memories of her.
Sometimes I wish,
if only my mother were alive.
Then she would have stood up for me
when Father scolded me.
She would do my hair nicely.
When people laughed at me
for failing at everything,
she would still treasure me
and always protect me.
But what a pity.
My mother is gone.
Sometimes, I blame myself.
Why couldn't I remember everything
when I was born?
In that case,
I would know what my mother looked like.
My father claimed he loved my mother.
But throughout our mansion,
in the past 19 years,
there has never been
a single portrait of her.
In your imagination,
what does she look like?
She's a noble lady,
according to my father.
So she must have
delicate eyebrows,
bright eyes,
and porcelain skin.
Girl,
whatever your mother looks like,
your father loves you
more than his own life.
This has never changed.
Zhao.
How could you not know
your letter
would make him let down his guard?
You're right.
And that's enough.
Your mother loves you too.
Sorry, I failed.
Please forgive me.
Where are our men?
The terrain there is eerie.
Too many traps in the forest.
We lost over half of our men.
But I've figured out their defenses.
I request another attack.
Chu Zhao isn't stupid enough
to wait there to die.
She's eager to go back to Yunzhong.
She won't stay long there.
She has to pass through Wangcheng
to get to Yunzhong.
Since Cangmu Stronghold
is tough to invade,
we'll be waiting for her further ahead.
Cangmu Stronghold lies at a key junction.
If Chu Ling incorporates them,
he will be more formidable.
Tie Ying,
send word to the Northern Desert.
Tell them I want another deal
with their king.
Congratulations. You won again.
Do you think
Zhao will be in trouble?
Don't worry. Your Majesty.
Before Her Highness left,
I divined for her.
During the trip,
she'll escape all misfortune.
Your Majesty.
Uncle, did you come so late
because Zhao and Uncle Yanlai
were in some trouble?
Yanlai is skilled in martial arts.
He'll protect Zhao.
Don't worry.
General Chu Ling
killed the envoy without permission.
It might lead to trouble.
His old illness relapsed too.
He might not survive this winter.
In the court, the Grand Mentor said,
if General Chu died, war would break out.
So, our frontier forces
should prepare early.
Exactly.
The 200,000 frontier troops in Yunzhong
safeguard our state.
If Northern Desert foes invade…
Yu,
do you dare to fight in battle?
I will fight.
We people never fear a battle.
Good.
Let me ask you one more thing.
If Chu Ling dies,
who should command
the 200,000 frontier troops?
Uncle Yanlai. He has great martial arts.
Your Majesty,
then get the edict ready.
So we can plan ahead.
Wait, Your Majesty.
Mr. Xie, you're really impatient.
Your Majesty,
military affairs are of vital importance
and need court discussion.
Mr. Xie shouldn't have incited you
in private.
Mr. Deng,
are you trying to delay military action?
I hold the Imperial Seal.
Without the seal on it,
this edict will be invalid.
The Three Departments
approve troop deployment.
It's time for you to end
this practice of nepotism.
‎MILITARY CAMP OF NORTHERN DESERT
Word from Xiao Xun.
Chu Ling is seriously sick.
The Chu court is in chaos.
He wants 3,000 elite soldiers of ours
to bypass Xiaonan and go to Wangcheng
to join the Xiaonan Army
in besieging Yunzhong.
Then, we'll split his state.
He's the most eager of all.
After all these years as a hostage,
he still hasn't become patient.
Come on, Chu Ling.
We've been fighting for two decades.
The state you've guarded with your life
corroded from within a long time ago.
Their ministers scheme against each other.
KING OF NORTHERN DESERT
Even a hostage dares
to collude with enemies for invasion.
Now, it's our time to take over Yunzhong.
But mountain defiles
are perilous in Xiaonan.
Supplies can't get through.
Wangcheng lies to the rear of Yunzhong.
It's weakly guarded.
We'll travel light for a night raid.
Capturing it quickly won't be a problem.
Go. Tell Xiao Xun.
I will wait for him in Wangcheng.
WANGCHENG
Son, we need to think carefully.
The Northern Desert King is treacherous.
To work with him is to play with fire.
He has probed me for years,
but I've never agreed.
If we work with him,
there may be unnecessary trouble.
Can you guarantee
that everything will be under control
once his soldiers come in here?
Without a perfect plan,
we might as well wait.
Father, I understand your concern.
But in some cases,
patience doesn't solve anything.
I don't want to repeat the same mistakes.
Chu Ling is badly ill.
This is the perfect moment.
We'll use our northern foes
to support our own cause.
I get it.
Since you've made up your mind,
go ahead and do it.
Thank you, Father.
I should send a few men to escort you.
I've brought too much trouble to you.
Many innocent people died.
I will keep that in mind.
You helped us at all costs.
Whatever you want, just let me know.
We want nothing from you.
We just hope you won't forget us
when you're back there
and grant us some rewards.
I will.
That jade piece…
Please keep it for me.
Sure.
Cangmu Forest isn't far from Wangcheng.
Xiaonan's killers may pursue you, though.
Every half day, Wangcheng soldiers
patrol the foot of the mountain.
Be more careful out there.
Thank you for reminding me.
We know what to do.
That's good.
Take care.
‎GATEWAY OF CANGMU STRONGHOLD
IN HARMONY WITH YIN AND YANG
You issued the transfer edict, right?
Where did you get this?
Theoretically,
this edict should have left the Capital.
Intercepting an imperial edict
is a grave crime.
I did intercept it.
What does it mean?
It means
without my approval,
it can't be issued.
Do you think I can't hold you accountable
just because of who you are?
You can do that.
But I advise you not to do that.
If we both lose in the end,
our state will be in peril.
Since you know that,
why don't you advise yourself?
You don't fear the peril of the state.
Why would I be scared?
So late at night, you visited
His Majesty and coaxed him.
Why can't I ease his burdens?
Of course, you aren't afraid.
But the way you ease burdens
is a clear overreach of your authority.
How dare you issue an edict
without His Majesty's decision?
Do you also want
to sit on the throne
to ease His Majesty's burdens?
You overestimate me, Mr. Xie.
His Majesty is aware of all this.
As for you…
Do you really think
Chu Ling's defeat of an enemy army
will bring peace?
Once Chu Ling dies a sudden death,
Yunzhong troops will fall into chaos.
Then our state will be in real peril.
Others might not know.
But we both know
what the Lord of Xiaonan will do
when Yunzhong is in chaos.
What will the Lord of Xiaonan do?
You know it perfectly well, don't you?
Back then, you insisted
Xiao Xun return to Xiaonan.
When the hostage left,
you should have foreseen this day.
Xie Yanfang!
Your duty is merely to enforce edicts.
You have no say in military affairs.
This is a real overreach of authority!
WISDOM AND VIRTUES
Here's the Grand Princess Token.
I'm exercising the veto power
on behalf of Her Highness.
GRAND PRINCESS TOKEN
Madam Ge said,
Wangcheng soldiers patrol at this hour.
She's right.
So, what exactly is your great plan?
We'll "surrender".
Are you saying we'll deliberately
let these patrols catch us
and take us to Wangcheng?
So, Mr. Xie, show some mercy in the fight.
Who are you?
I don't think
there'll be a fight.
It's him.
In my past life,
he was a vanguard
under my father's command.
But now, he seems to be
a foot soldier among Wangcheng troops.
Liang Qiang.
How do you know my name?
Mr. Xie, you don't allow me
to dispatch new generals.
And you seem to have decent excuses.
Actually, it's just because
they are not loyal to you.
Then do you think
you can plant your own men
after you stop me?
You don't trust me.
I don't trust you either.
So we should place our trust in Chu Ling.
We must believe he will handle
everything before he dies.
Chaos won't occur.
Northern Desert foes won't invade.
Once our state is in crisis,
we'll be in danger.
So will Chu Ling.
If our state falls,
as the Grand Princess,
her daughter will die too.
Chu Ling won't let her daughter
fall into danger.
Fine.
Since the generals can't go to Yunzhong,
Mr. Xie,
your private troops must not go there too.
I read the files on your father's
connection to the Third Prince.
Who are you?
The Third Prince was executed.
His subordinates were demoted.
Your family collapsed.
You became a patrol soldier then.
Would you really waste your life
in the middle of nowhere?
-Who on earth are you?
-I'm here to help.
We're merely bandits
who have fled from Cangmu Stronghold.
You patrolled here and ran into bandits.
If you take us back,
you'll make great merit.
We just switched allegiance.
Don't be suspicious.
You just need to decide
whether you want that credit.
Back in Wangcheng,
if you dare to play tricks,
I'll kill you immediately.
Since you accept this merit,
we will behave ourselves.
CHARTING THE COSMOS
Mr. Xie,
where is your brother
planning to take the Grand Princess?
My brother has been suspended.
Her Highness is recuperating.
I don't know what you mean.
Then let me remind you.
He who holds the emperor
commands the lords.
But he who holds the Grand Princess
only commands Chu Ling.
It's a bad bargain.
You know that perfectly well.
Then you should also know.
Chu Zhao must not die.
She must stay alive.
Only when she's alive
will the court avoid another rebellion.
Then our game can keep going, right?
In that case,
hope your ninth brother
will protect Her Highness well
as we all expect him to.
Of course.
But you're wrong about one thing.
My brother didn't take away
the Grand Princess.
Instead, the Grand Princess
took away my brother.
CHARTING THE COSMOS
Mr. Deng, you're pretty bold.
You removed the coffin
bestowed by Her Highness.
Her Highness withdrew from the court.
Why can't I move this little thing then?
Impressive.
Let me try.
Hello, Miss Qi. Hello, Lady Tang.
That totally ruined my mood.
What are you talking about?
What did we do?
Is it because we didn't bow
to Miss Chu Tang?
You should be straightforward.
Why do you bother to be so sarcastic?
All right.
Lady Tang, let me ask you.
Do you know if your uncle General Chu Ling
fails to defend the frontier,
people will suffer?
I know.
You speak recklessly
because you worry
about our state and people.
This is good.
Unmarried ladies like us
should pay more attention
to state affairs.
Only then will we know about the hardships
of our state and people.
However, we must not judge by appearances
or take a part for the whole.
We didn't speak recklessly.
What we said is the truth.
What is truth? What you see is truth.
Did you see with your own eyes
that my uncle failed
and our foes gained an advantage?
Don't try to deny it.
Do you know how big Yunzhong is?
Do you know how many soldiers
are involved in a battle?
Do you know how many people
from the Northern Desert
have come to travel
on the trade routes of our state?
When the case is investigated,
my uncle will be convicted or vindicated.
But now,
no one can convict him without proof.
Once war breaks out,
situations are volatile and intricate.
Even the Emperor's orders
aren't always followed.
And you don't even know
what exactly happened in Yunzhong.
How can you parrot what others say?
Let's go.
LOTUS PAVILION
Come on.
Tang.
I…
I'm sorry.
Miss Chu, you seem to be in good spirits.
Your family is in turmoil.
But you're in the mood for tea.
If you're here for some fun, get in there.
More fun with the storyteller.
Tang, how can you be so rude to Mr. Deng?
He wanted to watch the fun,
then I recommended the opera house.
How was that rude?
Has my entire family
already been convicted
that I can't even speak?
You can speak.
Lady Tang, your frankness
is quite admirable.
Even if your uncle ends up guilty,
the Grand Princess will stand by you.
You've got a point there,
Mr. Deng. Farewell.
Tang, wait for me.
Oh no.
What was I even saying?
Yeah.
Scared now, huh?
What happened to all that swagger?
Come on. Don't tease me.
Just now, I lost my temper.
I couldn't remember what I said or did.
Now I've come to my senses.
I'm so terrified.
Anyway, what's gone is gone.
Even if I said that,
who would dare to do anything?
Tang,
you've changed.
You never argued with anyone before.
Not to mention arguing
for General Chu and Chu Zhao.
Oh, my uncle.
Please don't get convicted.
And Zhao…
Come back early.
‎WANGCHENG OUTSKIRTS
Before fully recovering,
you exhausted yourself again.
I know what I'm doing.
Can we trust this man?
Liang Qiang is low-ranking,
but he's a regular soldier.
Xiao Xun's troops
won't provoke or inspect him.
In this way,
we'll be able to avoid Xiao Xun's spies.
Besides, we're taking a carriage now.
No soft cushions or pillows.
But at least, we don't need to trek.
How nice. Two birds, one stone.
WANGCHENG
Get them down.
The ruts are weird.
It seems to be a straw cart
heading for town.
The straw binding is loose.
Usually, a loosely bound cart bears
no more than three to five hundred jin.
But the ruts are deeper
than half a finger.
It carries at least
800 jin.
There's something else in the cart.
Judging from the ruts,
no fewer than ten carts
have entered town today.
Someone's taking so much trouble
to do something to this town.
This is a strategic frontier town.
If it falls, Yunzhong Prefecture
will be attacked from the front and rear.
Xiao Xun sent his men in disguise.
But the gate guards should have inspected
either disguised men or hidden weapons.
By Article ten of the Frontier Code,
a Military Supply Token will exempt
all goods from inspection.
Given Xiao Xun's status,
getting some tokens
would be quite easy.
Follow me in.
You go back now.
Keep up.
Your Highness,
3,000 elite troops of Northern Desert
passed Xinggu Pass
and reached Shalang Col,
less than 100 li from Wangcheng.
Tell them to go along the official road
with the travel permit,
disguised as caravans.
-Make sure they're well provisioned.
-Yes.
We won't dispatch troops
until they take Wangcheng.
Ge. Ge. Bad news.
Our scout spotted
3,000 soldiers headed for Wangcheng
from the official road northwest
toward Xiaonan,
disguised as caravans.
From Xiaonan?
Wangcheng is vital
to the rear of Yunzhong.
Once it falls,
Xiao Xun will block supplies
within half a day.
By then, the Yunzhong troops
will be besieged with no supplies.
Massive soldiers
will be desperately trapped.
Oh no.
At the rate of traveling,
the two of them are just at Wangcheng.
JUSTICE HANGS ON HIGH
General, in Cangmu Forest, I caught
two bandits of Cangmu Stronghold.
Bandits have done countless crimes.
Execute them now.
General, it's easy for you to kill us.
But I wonder if you can remain so decisive
when northern foes break into town.
How dare you!
How could you spread a fallacy here?
If we were real bandits,
why would we come voluntarily?
As we entered town,
we spotted enemy spies in disguise.
The ruts of straw carts
are abnormally deep.
Weapons must be hidden there.
Now, instead of executing me,
you should send men
to close the city gate,
search the city, and increase security.
Shut up!
How dare a bandit
comment on military affairs,
stir up unrest, and shake troop morale?
I'll chop your heads off now
and hang them
on the city wall as a warning!
Kill them!
Brilliant plan.
Xiao Xun didn't kill you.
But someone on your own side will.
You're wrong.
You've been the only one on my own side.
Outrageous. Outrageous!
Seize them immediately and execute them!
Don't you dare!
Zhong Changrong,
deputy of the Guard General,
is here to see the Grand Princess!
Hey, girl.
Girl.
Hey.
It's been years.
Don't you recognize me?
Mr. Zhong.
Did anyone bully you?
You…
You vile creature! Are you blind?
This is General Chu's daughter,
the Grand Princess.
Just now,
who were you going to execute?
Sorry, I misjudged you.
Mercy, Your Highness.
My eyes failed me,
and I offended Your Highness.
Please forgive me.
Not your fault.
Your priority is to close the city gate
and defend deep.
Find out Northern Desert foes and weapons.
I swear to hold the city.
Mr. Zhao,
your official headwear is still yours now.
But if this city falls,
you will lose it and your life.
I swear to stand and fall with the city!
Leave us right now. Get to work.
Mr. Zhong, why are you here?
Your father was worried about you,
so he sent me here
to get you back to Yunzhong.
When I was halfway,
I got this man's message,
saying you would reach Wangcheng.
I traveled hundreds of li for nothing
and rushed back immediately.
You arrived later than I expected.
Zhong, you should work on your speed.
How rude. Nonsense.
Report!
‎THE WAY OF HEAVEN, THE JUSTICE OF ALL
Scouts have spotted
3,000 enemy troops came from the north.
They're within 50 li of this city.