(Previously)
Wait, Gaysorn.
Please listen to me first.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
What do you think of me? A lab rat?
Have you ever even seen
me as a human being?
I already told you that
between me and Gaysorn, it's over!
No! If he wants to know
where his mother is...
he will definitely follow you back!
There are so many documents.
What are you looking for?
Every document related to Pruet.
Your mother was living on the mountain.
Who told her to come down?
Gaysorn, our love is real, Gaysorn.
But right now, I don't love you anymore.
This means someone sent this letter
to trick Bussaba into coming down.
But who?
[Dear Bussaba, I was in a car
accident and I really want to see you.
Please come to Bangkok
as fast as possible.
The person who gave you the letter
will help you get to the city.]
Stop! You can't go.
- Mata.
- Let him go.
If you want to go, then
you can go by yourself.
I won't let you take Gaysorn with you.
I won't let you risk your son's life.
Well…
please take care of him.
Are you going to leave
your son here? Really?
I just went to see Pruek.
He really needs me.
I've been waiting for him
even before Gaysorn was born.
Please, Mata.
Let me go.
I just need to see your dad.
I will be back soon, okay?
Mom, please hurry back.
It's not like I am leaving you.
I am still with you, always.
Please take care of him for me.
Just go. Go!
Bussaba?
Why are you here?
I…
Well, Pruek's condition is so bad
he can barely move.
If it wasn't me, then who would be here?
But…
you…
you make the perfumes.
I understand why
you wouldn't trust me.
It's fine if you don't trust me,
you don't have to go back with me.
Wait.
How…
how is he?
Your husband's condition is very bad.
If you don't come back with me now,
perhaps you wouldn't
be able to see him again.
"Flower Boy"
(Episode 7)
Your uncle called me to
bring Gaysorn's scent project back.
What is going on?
He ordered me to bring Gaysorn back.
What is your plan to get him back?
He said that if Gaysorn heard about
where his mom was,
he would come back.
Huh?
- It means that…
- That's right.
My uncle has known about his mom
since the beginning.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to tell Gaysorn?
I think this is strange.
Let me think about it.
I don't want to hurt him anymore.
Does it smell good?
Is it good?
Your cheek smells better.
So you're going to take Gaysorn
and his Mudan clan back to your place?
Yup.
You're so dedicated,
are you aimimg for something?
Who would do that? He
is looking for his mom.
Right,
I wish your dream comes true.
I gotta go, Gaysorn is here.
Sure.
Mata,
this is Mekin.
He is very nice to me.
This is Mata, she is my aunt.
Hello.
This is my brother, Tawan.
Can we go now?
This way, I've prepared a van for you.
Let's go.
Hello?
I'm waiting in front of your house.
Come out to see me.
Gaysorn?
Gaysorn.
I need to talk to you.
You can come inside.
No need. You can talk here.
How could you ask him to
come inside of the house?
Besides using him,
have you realized what you have done?
Fire! Fire! Hurry up!
How is it?
He ran away with Gaysorn!
He took Gaysorn with him!
I didn't know it'd turn out like that.
I didn't mean to burn down your village.
You need to pay.
It's water under the bridge.
There is nothing we can do.
I'm really sorry.
If you need me to pay in
any way, please let me know.
This is the letter that someone sent to Mom
after Dad had been dead for four years.
It told her to leave
the village to see Dad.
Can you find out who did this?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I can keep this letter for you
and I will search more about it.
You can trust me.
Where are you staying?
You can stay here so we can talk easily.
We're staying at Mekin's place.
You have my phone number
you can call me when there is any progress.
Gaysorn.
I'm glad
that you still trust me.
I just don't have a choice.
Gaysorn,
no matter what.
I'm still glad
that I got to see you.
I missed you.
I really missed you.
Let's get going.
Gaysorn?
Stop hurting him already.
If you need to hold back your feelings
when seeing him,
I don't think you should see him anymore.
Tawan.
Did I say something wrong, Mata?
What are you going to do next?
Are we just going to wait
for him like this?
Is there anybody or anything
that can lead us to what
happened 20 years ago?
Yes, I think so.
Hello?
Mekin,
can you tell your driver
to take us somewhere?
This is Mom and Dad's old house.
It has been abandoned for years.
Why are we here?
You need to talk to me?
I want to ask you
about Bussaba, Gaysorn's mother.
How did you know where she was?
You need to bring Gaysorn to me
and we can talk.
You need to tell me first.
You don't trust me?
Of course, I trust you.
I believe that you know.
You were the one who sent the letter,
tricking Bussaba to leave the mountains.
Am I right?
What are you talking about? What letter?
This letter.
It was sent after Pruek
died four years earlier.
Pruek couldn't send the letter for sure.
Who else could it be?
Didn't you see the letter head?
It could have only come
from the executive level. only.
Is it because of the letter head?
That's why you believed it was me?
Mata,
I remember that back in Mudan village
you can talk to the dead.
I'd like you to talk to Dad.
I want to know where Mom is.
Gaysorn,
if you want Mata to talk to the dead,
we have to use that person's belongings
so Mata can start the ritual.
I have one.
This is his photo.
I found it at home.
Gaysorn.
Normally,
when Mudan people
pass away,
their souls
will protect their children for a while.
That's why I could communicate to them.
But your dad
wasn't from Mudan.
Earlier,
I walked through the house
and I felt nothing.
It's been a while.
I don't think your dad
can come to me.
More importantly,
this is not our place,
I'm not sure if I can communicate to him.
Why are there flowers here?
Watch out!
I'm fine.
I think the ground is uneven here.
There must be something below.
Gaysorn,
Tawan, find something to dig with. Hurry.
Gaysorn.
These are documents from your dad's office.
I wasn't the only one
using the letter head paper.
What do you mean?
Think about it.
Who
was obsessed with Mudan's scent?
Do you mean that
Gaysorn's mom
went to see my dad?
What happened to her? Where is she?
What you want to find out
is right here, in the
basement of this house.
What is in the basement?
You can go and have a look.
What is it?
Your dad
really wanted Mudan's scent so bad.
So he kept Bussaba in here.
[16 Years Ago]
We use the heat to make her sweat
and we will extract the scent from her sweat.
It doesn't smell good.
Why didn't it smell good?
Your dad refused to stop.
He tried every way possible
to extract Bussaba's scent.
He used a cloth to
collect the scent from her skin.
No matter how hard he tried,
he still couldn't get her scent.
Why doesn't the perfume extracted
from your scent smell good?
I already told you.
My scent is gone.
I have a child.
Don't lie to me.
I didn't lie to you.
Women from Mudan
will lose her scent once they have babies.
That's the way it is.
Then you need to stay right here
until we find the way to get your scent.
Damn it! Why can't it be scented?
Tell me.
How can I get the scent out of you?
I've told you
that you won't get it.
Don't lie to me.
Tell me. Tell me now!
What is the secret? Tell me.
- Anurak?
- Tell me.
Hey!
What have you done?
Your dad lost it completely.
And he hurt that woman.
I tried to save her
but I was too late.
Later, I found out
that Bussaba
was already dead.
Dead?
Where was her body?
- Where was her body?
- I destroyed it all.
What the hell did you do?
What did you do?
What did you expect me to do?
Your dad is my brother
and I won't let him go to jail.
I had to do what was
the best for our family.
It's been more than 10 years,
why did you bring up the evidence?
Why did you dig up the past for?
Think about it.
The most guilty person in the situation
was your dad.
You want to put your dad in jail?
Gaysorn,
I won't stop looking for your mom.
I don't care how long
it takes, I will find her.
Thank you.
No matter what, we will find your mom.
Tawan, what is it?
I just need to see your dad.
I will be back soon, okay?
Mom, please hurry back.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
This is a homicide.
Are you okay?
I want them to pay for
what they did to Mom.
I'm sorry for saying this but
it happened aged ago.
It's been 15-16 years already.
Moreover, there are only bones
left in this hole.
We barely have anything
that links back to the criminals.
What about the letter?
The person who wrote the letter to
fool his mom was the bad guy.
Kusuma!
Dad?
I know about Bussaba.
Why did you do that?
I don't know what to tell Gaysorn
that a person who killed his mom
was you.
I don't want you to be in jail.
But I shouldn't be the
one who makes the decision,
Gaysorn should do it.
I love you
and I love him, too.
I don't want to lie to him anymore.
Please tell me.
Tell me what to do.
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Anurak!
Scent,
what did you do to upset your dad?
We'll talk later.
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
I'm taking you to the hospital.
What are you trying to say?
I…
I?
I...
didn't…
do it.
You didn't do it?
You're telling me that you didn't do it?
Dad! Dad!
Smells so nice.
There you go, I'm done.
It's a scented sachet. It's cute.
Do you want one?
You can pick your scent
and I'll draw you for free.
What do you say?
She will draw your face on the sachet.
I want one.
Pick your scent, please.
I'll pick this one.
Sure.
Well,
I need one too.
Alright.
Just a second.
This is more like you.
Can you draw him with
butterflies on his body?
Sure, I can.
Wow! So cute.
I will keep your face with me
and you can keep one with mine.
Smells so nice.
Is it good?
Yes, so nice.
(Next Episode) This means
the person who wrote the
letter must have known
Gaysorn's mother very well.
And back then,
how many people would have known about it?
Scent's father and uncle.
Dad...
Scent asked me to pick up
his things from the house.
Go back to the Mudan tribe.
This place is too cruel.
It's not suitable for you.
And I... am not worthy
of you. I'm sorry.
Scent...