Were you born without a brain or something?
It’s two hundred thousand, do you have it?
If you can't find it, don't come back.
I'll get it for you.
And this is my business card.
In case you change your mind and want to be an actor.
Because back then, I ended up with a stupid partner.
I'm charging you two hundred thousand baht for that cigarette.
If you owe someone, you have to pay them back.
When I regained consciousness,
everyone I knew looked at me with fear.
I don't know what happened to me either.
That really wasn't me.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry.
But I'm scared.
Ugh! You’re not feeling it.
Cut the camera!
Why are you talking like that?
I told you to use a high-pitched voice.
So that you sound like the leading female actress.
No way.
What’s with this script? Why is it so damn hard?
Hey. Why? Are you not going to help me?
You're shy, aren't you?
Are you really?
What is there to be shy about?
Fine, I'll do it myself.
Please don't look at me with those eyes.
It has to be like this. Now you do it.
Higher.
Don't look at me...
No way.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to Angie.
Make a wish first, honey.
Yay!
Do you like it, honey?
Yes, I do!
Daddy didn't come alone today.
Surprise!
Hello! From today on, I'd like to live here too.
Can you name me, please?
Hmm, what should I name you?
How about Candy?
Oh! Candy! What a cute name!
From today on, Candy wants to live with P’Angie and P’Pookie also. Please take care of me.
Sure, you have a little sister now.
Thank you, Dad.
Let's dig in.
Sure.
Come here.
Here's a spoon for you.
Dad will help pull out the candles.
Alright.
There's even a door here.
There are trees and a bear.
Daddy, do you want to join us?
Hmm. I already ate after work.
So this cake is all for Angie.
Is it delicious?
It is.
Am I about to get scammed?
Hello. Who is this?
Hello.
You gave me your business card.
I want to become an actor.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Yes? Is there anything I can help you with?
I'm here to see Khajorn.
Oh, just a moment, please.
P'Khajorn, someone is here to see you.
Hey! I thought you wouldn't be able to find the way here.
I'm so glad you contacted me.
Come inside.
Come on, come in here.
Sky, go get some water for him, quick.
Alright.
What should I call you?
Sun.
Okay. Sun, it is.
Here’s some water.
Actually, we've met once before. But this time, let me formally introduce myself again.
I’m Khajorn.
I’m a talent manager at Dream Entertainment.
And right now, I'm also taking care of Sky.
Why did you scout me that day?
Because my senses told me to do so.
From the first time I saw you, I knew that
you have potential.
Even though you may look a bit ordinary.
But your eyes are interesting.
My eyes?
I mean, you have a character that I can mold.
How about that actor?
Are you talking about P'Sunny?
P'Khajorn also takes care of another actor.
His name is Sunny.
Used to. I mean, I only used to take care of him.
At the moment, Sunny is being taken care of by a new team.
So I have to find some new people on my team as well.
Otherwise, I won't be able to survive here either.
So…
Do you really want to be an actor?
Then take off your hat and let me see.
I agree, very interesting.
Do you think I can be more famous than Sunny?
Whoa, but he’s Sunny, you know.
He's like mega famous right now.
There's almost no one who doesn't know him.
I don't know him.
The person I knew
his name is Bank Thanapat.
So you know Sunny's old name?
Yes.
See ye! See you later.
People who can consider betraying someone,
they’ll do it eventually.
Have you guys had history together before?
I'm here for revenge.
Revenge?
If it's for that reason,
I think…
I'll have to reconsider whether I can work with you or not.
Come in.
Jae Air has confirmed that
she will start being your manager from tomorrow onwards.
Thank you very much, P'Kongkiat.
I feel very honored to have Jae Air as my manager.
Since you're with Jae Air, behave yourself properly.
Everyone in the industry knows Jae Air.
If you embarrass yourself even once, then everyone will know.
Don't worry.
I’ll definitely behave nicely.
By the way, what are you going to do about Khajorn?
Since he scammed so much money out of me.
Aren't you going to fire him?
And do you have any proof that Khajorn has scammed your money?
Well, the money that was transferred didn't match the contract.
Things like this you can't just talk, you know?
If there is no concrete documentary evidence,
or any solid proof at all.
Then I’m afraid I can't help you with anything.
Then I'll go gather it first.
Although if there's no evidence,
but if only Kajorn didn’t have anyone talented under him.
He wouldn’t last here any longer anyway.
I’ll excuse myself.
Oh, and one more thing.
Since I've helped you this much,
don't forget to take care of the sponsor as scheduled tomorrow.
Alright.
Dream Entertainment is holding a trainee audition in three days.
So I want you to understand the script for this casting well.
And memorize the lines accurately.
What happened to your eyebrow?
Anyway, from now on, you are strictly forbidden from having any more scars on your face alright?
100% sweetness Thai tea is ready.
Thank you.
I’m sorry but can you add more syrup?
Hmm, so it's 120% sweetness, right?
Can I get 150%?
Sure thing, N’Sky.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat anything, P'Sun? I'll treat you.
I came here for revenge.
And how about you, what would you like to order?
Is there anything that you like? I can recommend one for you?
P'Sun, do you want to try this?
It's delicious, super sweet and refreshing.
Wow1
Hey, do you want to try it? It's very delicious.
Black coffee, no sugar.
Okay.
Whoa, P'Sun. If you eat like this, you might not have enough energy.
You don't have to call me 'P'.
Just call me Sun is enough.
My mom died three months after starting the second treatment.
The debt I borrowed from Sia Po to treat my mom.
Including interest, it's 1,320,000 baht.
Thank you.
Okay.
How much is it?
Yours is 50 baht.
Is mine almost ready?
Oh, it's almost done.
Please wait a moment.
The shop is closed, right?
Okay, thanks a lot Sun.
Today's wage.
Thank you.
That’s okay.
Good luck to you.
I paid it all back two months ago.
Even if the debt is paid off ิีะ the wrongs people did to me still remain.
And if I wait for karma to work,
It probably won't happen in this lifetime.
It's just me,
i’ll bring karma to them myself.
Have you found the money to pay yet?
Mr. two Baht.
What a bloodsucking leech.
Of course, I am
I take care of the finances of this company.
How could I make myself suffer a loss?
Oh, I know why you came up here.
You want to flatter me.
so that you can become an actor here.
Because you look ordinary.
Nothing outstanding.
Looks like you don’t have much talent either.
The only way you can pass the audition
Is by flattering the person in authority.
Running away? I asuume that you're a coward or anything.
Unless you're afraid of getting a scar on your face.
From now on, you are strictly forbidden from having any more scars on your face alright?
You have good eye contact.
I like them.
What is your name?
And why do you approach me?
That day, I was just asking for a cigarette.
How would I know who you were?
Do you really not know me?
No.
Who scouted you?
I think we need to talk a bit about why you want to be an actor.
If you say you want to be an actor for revenge,
I think with this mindset it will cause problems at work.
Hello?
Get through the audition alright?
And I will reduce the cigarette fee.
And why do I have to do that?
How about this?
I'll be your backer.
So that you can become an actor.
Then you can get your revenge for whatever issues it is.
Don’t stick your nose in.
Oh my god!!!
What happened to your face?
I met a crazy person.
Sky, go get a cold compress.
Okay.
Bro?
Yeah?
Do you happen to know a very tall guy?
He works here in the department related to finance or something?
You mean like the accounting department?
Well, as far as I know, there aren't many men there.
Actually, I don't really mingle with them much.
What’s wrong?
No, it's nothing.
In the meantime, you need to apply the cold compress first.
And rehearse your lines with Sky for now.
If you're having any issue then let Sky help you out, alright.
Most importantly, remember that if you ever forget your lines, don't freeze.
Just be yourself as much as possible.
Do you understand what I said?
I don't understand you at all.
I've been good to you all this time.
Why are you doing this to me?
I never truly loved you.
So I’ve had to put up with you all this time.
P’... I mean Khun Sun
How about you try again?
You need to interpret how the character feels first.
But it's not written in here.
Usually, it doesn’t need to be written down.
Although we are actors,
we have to learn to interpret it ourselves.
That’s hard.
Keep fighting.
You are much better than me.
You call this better?
Well, I get nervous when I'm in front of the camera.
So I can only do stage plays.
I think you can get more jobs.
In the future, you'll probably help P'Khajorn out more.
Shall we go again?
But let's do some relaxation exercises first. It might help you.
Do it like me.
Breathe in and clench your fists.
Then breathe out and open your hands.
How are you going back, Khun Sun?
I’m taking the bus.
Okay, then I'll take a motorcycle taxi.
Wow, he even bought the same car model as P'Penneung?
Penneung?
P'Penneung, you don’t know him.
He’s like the top male lead from Dream’s.
Haven't you heard of his name before?
P'Sunny has always been like this.
He likes to imitate more famous people and replace them with himself.
It means this time, P'Sunny really wants to climb up and replace P'Penneung as the top star.
When I regained my consciousness,
Everyone I knew looked at me with fear.
I don't know what happened to me either.
That really wasn't me.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry.
But I'm scared.
Ugh! You’re not feeling it.
Cut the camera!
Why are you talking like that?
Like I told you, use a high-pitched voice.
So that you sound more like the leading female actress.
No way.
It's funny that you call me a kid, uncle.
That's what you, uncle...
Oh, please come in.
Yes.
It's funny that you call me a kid, uncle.
That's also what I...
Here, I'll put some concealer on your bruise.
It's fine.
No way.
Don't you know that if the judges see your face in this condition,
I guarantee that...
I believe..
I believe that I can do it.
Anyway, I'll have the team contact you back.
Yes.
Good luck to you.
Thank you.
He's quite good.
Agreed.
Very nicely done.
Right?
I like him.
- His character is clear.
- Yeah.
Next in line is Sun, please come in.
I agree. Fully agree.
He's great. With a bit more grooming, he'll be fine.
A little bit to the center, please.
Hello there.
How about you look at the camera and introduce yourself.
I’m Theemekha Rungsubdee.
My nickname is Sun.
I'm 25 years old.
Hold on. Just a second.
Could you tilt your face a bit?
If you can't even take care of your own face,
I think you are not fit to be an actor.
Call in the next person.
Please leave.
Since he's already here, why don't we let him try out a bit?
Go ahead.
What are you standing there for? Start acting.
The script was sent to you to memorize in advance, wasn't it?
What do you want to do?
If you're not ready to be an actor, I think you'd better go back.
Let’s not waste anyone’s time here.
Get out.
Just be yourself as much as possible.
Who said I came here because I want to be an actor?
I came here for my revenge.
Are you threatening me?
You call this a threat?
I’ll show you. What a real threat looks like.
Next time when you get a package at your house,
you better watch yourself.
Because I'll be the one delivering it to you by my very own hand.
Sun!
Let go of me.
Just seconds ago, I felt like it wasn't me at all.
When I get angry,
It's like my soul leaves my body.
Ready to be possessed by anything.
This script is …
I don't know what happened to me either.
That really wasn't me.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry.
Please don't look at me with those eyes again.
It's a dialogue from the drama series "Sap Rak".
The character played by Sunny Thanapat.
Wait, was that acting all along?
Oh, yes. It's like method acting.
I'm not okay with this.
He came to cast but didn't act according to the casting script.
And he improvised out of nowhere.
Without telling us beforehand, is that okay?
Exactly. If we choose this kid, doesn’t it mean that we have lowered our standard.
Is he just going to play whatever he wants?
But the way he acted is hard to come by.
Bringing out his own rawness to use.
He can definitely go far with this.
But do you understand we are casting?
And the actor doesn't follow the script.
The script is there to guide the actors.
Then what script...
How can you talk like this? This is unacceptable, isn't it?
Hello.
Yes.
Alright, I'll take care of it.
Alright, we'll give this kid a three-month probation.
After that, we'll evaluate again whether to sign a contract or not.
Really?
But if within three months,
there is no development whatsoever.
Then there won't be any second chance.
Okay?
Okay.
I’m glad that everything was just an act.
Not everything. Delivering the package part is real.
We prepared this.
You prepared very well.
Awesome right?
Very good.
Welcome Sun Theemekha to the Dream Entertaiment.
Do you know who called the judge?
I don't know, why?
I feel like the reason that I passed the audition,
was because of that person who called.
It doesn't matter at all.
Right now, what you need to focus on is that
you've been given a three-month chance to prove yourself.
So do your best.
Whoa P'Khajorn, don't stress Khun Sun out just yet.
Let's think about what we're going to eat tonight.
Let's go celebrate!
How about Som Tum?
Or Mala?
No more Mala, you eat it all year round.
Let's go.
Oh, I forgot my bag.
I think I'm bored of Som Tum.
Oh, how many times have I taken you to eat Mala?
We eat it only like every week.
- Someday when you have a stable job and make money then you can treat me to Mala. Although today I'm paying and I want to eat Som Tum.
- Let's go, Khun Sun.
Understood?
All you eat is Som Tum.
Oh wow, it's Khajorn.
I’m surprised that you haven't been fired yet.
A scammed manager.
Wait, let me explain more to you first.
The reason I didn't accept that sponsor job you wanted.
Because it's a grey business.
How was I scamming you?
That wasn’t just the reason alright?
I already told you, didn't I?
It’s because you're such a terrible manager.
Now you're left with actors who can't be used.
Soon, the company president won't keep you.
You’re so useless.
But right now, P'Khajorn has got someone new to take care of.
I'm telling you, this guy is godlike.
This was just his first audition.
And he already passed.
Even when P'Boss was watching the new kid, he was shaking nonstop.
Someone like P'Sunny,
get ready to be thrown in the trash.
Hey, that's enough.
Who the hell is he?
Let's go.
If you want to go.
Well, actually no,
You never wanted to go with us anyway.
Suit yourself then.
I need to use the restroom first.
Once you're done, we’ll see you in the car.
Hello.
I have something I want to ask.
That new kid of Khajorn who just passed the audition.
Who the hell is he?
If you don't know, go find out.
Go find a way to get rid of him.
Whatever you do is your business.
Just make it so he can't stay here.
That's all for now.
Who’s there?
I’m asking who?
People are talking all over the building.
About you bringing a knife to the audition.
To both of P'Khajorn's superstars.
Bottoms up.
Calling all photographers to an event, really?
So what do you want?
In this industry, which photographer is the best?
Who are you guys?
How can you be so sure that you’ll survive in this industry?
I have no idea who it's for.