What a dummy.
Oh, Master.
At it again, training so early?
My apologies. Did I wake you?
No.
Don't overdo it.
Your hands are all torn up.
Master.
I'm sorry to impose, but...
I'd be grateful for your instruction.
What are you talking about?
You're plenty strong already.
There's nothing more I can teach you.
You're the only master I'll ever have,
Nagakura Shinpachi.
Cut it out. Spare me the flattery.
It's not flattery.
You accepted your own
lack of natural talent
and overcame it
with nothing but sheer hard work.
The way you became this strong
inspires me, Master.
Lack of talent? You've got some nerve.
I can't tell if you're complimenting me
or insulting me.
My apologies.
Whatever. It's the truth, anyway.
You've gotten good
at that disarming technique.
All thanks to you, Master.
Bring it.
This "talentless" senior
will give you a lesson.
Thank you very much.
"Half past six.
I'll be waiting at Shinkenji Temple."
Guess who?
THE CORPS CODE
Come on, Shimada. What's the matter?
Put more spirit into it.
My apologies, Vice-Commander.
Hijikata doesn't hold back.
Give it your all against every opponent.
It's the only way to show
true respect for your opponent.
But they are all intimidated.
He's just too damn strong.
He's making Shimada look like a child.
Out of the way!
Heisuke, we're practicing.
This is no time for that!
Aijiro... Aijiro has been killed!
Back off.
Back off. Come on.
Hey!
SONG OF THE SAMURAI
Are you sure it was Aijiro?
Yes.
According to the magistrate's office,
the body had countless sword wounds.
They said the fatal wound was a stab
from the back and out through the stomach.
Does Shinpachi know?
No idea.
I haven't seen Nagakura at the dojo today.
Any idea who did it?
No idea.
The magistrate's office thinks
it was probably a thief
since his belongings were taken.
A thief?
There's no way he could've been killed
by a common thief.
I'm coming in.
What do you want, Niimi?
I hear one of your men got himself killed.
I see you get news quickly.
Our faction's full of new blood, you see.
Can't have them losing morale
over something trivial.
Trivial?
The way he died.
Get it right.
His name is Sasaki Aijiro.
There is no one in this corps
named "the guy who got killed."
Killed by a common thief, I hear.
A weakling like that isn't even worth
learning the name of.
You bastard.
How dare you insult a fallen comrade?
"One.
If you fail to kill and take a wound
to your back, it is seppuku."
This Sasaki, whatever his name was,
was cut down while turning his back.
He would have had to commit seppuku
even if he had survived.
That's the Corps Code, isn't it?
Kondo
one of your men has disgraced the name
of the Mibu Roshigumi.
How are you going to answer for this?
Hey, Niimi.
Stop, Toshi.
Shinpachi.
What he's saying is bullshit.
There's no way Aijiro would turn his back
on some common thief.
In that case, who do you claim did it?
I don't know, but I'll find whoever it is.
I'll find the bastard...
and finish them.
THE CORPS CODE
ONE. IF YOU FAIL TO KILL AND TAKE A WOUND
TO YOUR BACK, IT IS SEPPUKU
What's up? Bye.
Couldn't resist causing some trouble, huh?
You think I overdid it?
There's nothing
like picking on the weak, is there?
I just get so into it.
Whatever.
Whoa, damn.
Are you sure I should get this much
for that little thing?
But are you sure about this?
The truth is, I was ordered
to assassinate Kondo Isami
so I went undercover with them.
That's not for you to worry about.
Right.
So, what's next?
You've done enough.
For real?
You think taking out one grunt is enough
to bring down Kondo?
You're a true strategist, Niimi.
Just what I'd expect.
Guess I'll use this cash to celebrate.
Surely...
you didn't mess up, right?
Of course not.
You were listening, weren't you, Yamazaki?
Money... Money!
Keep an eye on him.
Yes.
Move.
Welcome.
Hey.
Skipping patrol to go drinking?
Must be nice.
Crap, I got busted.
And you're not even wearing
your damn coat.
Are you not taking this seriously?
No, of course I am!
Nagakura, you came all the way out here,
so aren't you slacking off too?
Won't you have a drink with me?
Forget that. Saeki...
It's about Aijiro.
Heard he got killed by some thugs, right?
Here.
Thanks.
I saw his body.
The fatal blow was one strike
from the back and out through the stomach.
The style of the sword strike
was Shindo Munen-ryu.
That's your style too, isn't it?
What's more, you're from Choshu.
What a waste!
You're the one who killed Aijiro.
Whoa, what is this all of a sudden?
Why would I go
and kill one of our own comrades?
Besides, there must be a thousand
swordsmen in Kyo who use that style.
Including you, right, Nagakura?
Anyway, I already deserted
the Choshu clan.
What happened to your finger?
A girl bit me over
in the pleasure district.
You would wear a splint
for just a tiny bite on your pinkie?
Aijiro broke it
with his disarming technique, didn't he?
Don't move.
You plan to fight with that hand?
Even you can see
the huge gap between us, right?
You know...
you're going to get crushed,
so why aren't you running?
So, like master,
like student, huh? Hilarious.
Then let me ask you this.
There's one thing I just don't get.
Why did you have to kill Aijiro
in such a brutal way?
A man with your skill...
could have finished him off
in a single blow.
I guess a hack like you wouldn't get it.
Killing someone in a crushing win....
feels better than screwing a woman.
You bastard!
What the hell is this?
Are you trying to kill me with laughter?
Don't you mock me!
And there it is. A decisive victory.
Now this feels good.
Way too easy.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Sorry, but here I come!
You know, Saeki...
the real thrill comes...
when you crush someone
far beyond your own skill!
Wait... Nagakura, please!
Do you have any proof
that I'm the one who killed Aijiro?
Y-You don't have any, do you?
I'm not sloppy with things like that.
If you finish me off now
the truth about me being the killer
will just be swept under the rug.
So... look! I'll cooperate!
I'll go to the magistrate's office.
Anywhere you say!
I'll tell you everything I know, I swear.
Please! Just spare my life!
I see.
Fine.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
I'll be in your debt
for the rest of my life!
Oh?
You're such a transparent piece of shit.
So, Nagakura made his move.
Yes.
Just as I predicted.
The winner is...
Nagakura Shinpachi.
I see.
Saeki was a fool.
For all his talent with a sword,
he let his skill go to his head.
And with this, Kondo Isami is finished.
There are no sword wounds on him.
Unbelievable...
Nagakura, you beat the best dual-wielder
with just brute force.
Hey... Hey, Shinpachi! Hey, why?
Why did you try
to shoulder this all alone?
Toshi, what's the problem?
You guys, that scumbag Saeki
was the one who killed Aijiro!
This was righteous revenge, right?!
Answer me!
If only there were proof of that.
Kondo, any luck?
I searched Saeki's belongings
but found no proof
that he killed Sasaki Aijiro.
Hey! Did you check properly, boss?
Yes.
Nagakura...
why did you pass judgment on Saeki?
If you passed judgment on an assumption
then this was just a private duel fought
for your own selfish reasons.
Don't tell me
you've forgotten the Corps Code.
"One.
Do not engage in personal fights.
Anyone who violates these articles
must commit seppuku."
I am prepared for that.
Hold on a second!
What do you mean, prepared?!
Hey, Shinpachi.
How did you know it was Saeki?
At least answer that much.
Everyone...
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Hey, Shinpachi.
But I have no regrets.
Knock it off!
Farewell.
Shinpachi!
Shinpachi.
You're not meant to fall
in a place like this.
Boss.
Niimi!
I ask that you grant a brief stay
of Shinpachi's seppuku.
Kondo, please stop!
I beg of you!
Hey!
Oh? So, the Commander himself
would bend the Corps Code.
And you expect
to maintain discipline that way?
Shinpachi's failure is my own.
In his place...
I will resign my position as commander.
What are you saying, boss!
As will I.
I shall resign my post as vice-commander.
Yamanami...
What is this farce?!
As if that could ever be a fair trade
for Nagakura's seppuku.
Then Nagakura's life
must be pretty damn cheap.
Then...
what do we need to do?
Commit seppuku.
Hey, you bastard! Cut it out!
Who's being ridiculous here?
Anyone who violates the Corps Code
must commit seppuku!
You're the ones who made that rule!
This is a lively bunch.
Niimi, come on, cut them some slack.
But...
Besides, what's so fun
about making them commit seppuku?
Kondo. Yamanami!
You have Serizawa's mercy
to thank for this.
Hey, Niimi. Watch your mouth.
Why would a vice-commander like me
listen to a rank-and-file soldier?
You rotten country-samurai!
From this moment on,
you're all just common soldiers!
You will all serve under Serizawa.
That is the condition for granting
Nagakura a reprieve from seppuku.
Is that acceptable, Serizawa?
I don't care. Do whatever you want.
What the hell are you doing?
Yamanami, you too!
That was a surprise.
I can't believe you showed them mercy.
Mercy, huh?
It was the best chance
to take out Kondo, wasn't it?
I don't remember showing any mercy.
Niimi...
if you want to kill,
do it with your own hands.
Seppuku is the most boring thing
in this world.
Serizawa!
I heard the news.
I heard you used the Corps Code
to bring the Kondo faction
under our control.
That was all Niimi's doing.
Well, I'm impressed, Vice-Commander.
Watch your mouth!
I'm your superior officer.
What example does that set for our men?
That's ridiculous. We're on the same side.
Well, how about we go out
and celebrate bringing
the Kondo faction under our wing?
No.
I think it's about time
for our little festival.
SEPTEMBER 24, 1863
We are the Mibu Roshigumi!
Hey... Hey! What's all this about?
This is an official inspection.
You've cornered the market on raw silk
and kept all the profits for yourselves.
It's time you learned how much suffering
you've caused the people of this city!
Move out of the way.
This money isn't for you
to line your own pockets with.
It will be used for the people of Kyo.
Got it?
We'll be back.
All right, let's move out.
Yes, sir!
Now, let's begin.
What are you doing, Serizawa?
Isn't it obvious? It's a festival.
Come on, you light one, too.
Do it.
Sir! Bring the fire, you lot!
You need more fire! Go on! Keep going!
Burn it! Burn more!
Serizawa! We're losing
our source of money!
Look, Niimi.
It just burns. That's the beauty of it.
For everything to burn...
and turn to ashes.
Serizawa Kamo. A man I must have.
A moral compass that points somewhere
beyond good and evil, profit and loss.
One who has no interest in money or honor
is a fascinating man indeed.
Whether or not Serizawa Kamo sides with us
rests entirely
on your shoulders, Mr. Niimi.
You needn't worry, Mr. Kusaka.
He's just a simple-minded brute.
He doesn't have a shred
of loyalty to the shogunate.
I'm counting on you.
Our preparations are all set as well.
On this occasion...
The day after your men attack
and burn down the Yamato-ya...
The emperor has announced that he'll lead
the expulsionist faction in seizing power.
So the signal to overthrow the shogunate
has finally been given.
We must use this momentum
to eliminate Matsudaira Katamori!
I'm counting on you, Niimi.
The way you drove Kondo Isami into
a corner that day was truly brilliant.
I'll take care of Lord Katamori.
I have 150 men in the Serizawa faction
under my direct command.
I can mobilize them at a moment's notice.
That's very reassuring.
This is for you, Niimi. Do as you like.
Money... Money!
Do you really love money that much?
I do. It's the one thing
that will never betray me.
I found it.
Good. Things are really coming together!
Oume, how about a song?
Certainly.
Serizawa.
What's this?
You are so loud. Come on! Bring it on!
Hey, Shimada!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't you have
any damn respect for your seniors?!
My apologies. I'll be sure
to go easy on you next time.
Are you mocking me?
Hey, you are getting all worked up.
I mean...
Yeah, I can see why you're pissed.
You two are the only ones even training.
Everyone has been sucked
into the Serizawa faction
and now it's just us left
in the Kondo faction.
And the boss got demoted
to a regular grunt.
This is beyond pathetic!
He's still Kondo,
whether he's the commander or not.
I'm sorry.
Don't get all worked up, Soji.
It's not like you.
Besides, I don't exactly hate
that it's just us now.
It's like being back in the Shieikan dojo.
One more round, please.
No! I don't want to anymore!
You didn't eat again?
Is Shinpachi not eating?
The boss even got
on his hands and knees to save his life.
Does he even understand that?
Now, don't be so hard on him.
If I can save all of you
by bowing my head to the ground
then I'll gladly grovel
in the dirt all day long.
Cut the noble act.
That might be fine for you
but when our commander,
Kondo Isami, bows his head
it's the same as making all of us
grovel on the ground.
I'm sorry, Toshi.
But...
I feel for Shinpachi.
He couldn't protect Aijiro.
I feel like he's punishing himself for it.
But we can't just let this go on!
Hey, Yamanami.
Can't you do something?
I'm at my breaking point.
Hijikata...
I feel the same way.
Kanbei.
I need to have a word with you.
As fired up as ever, I see.
Hijikata, haven't you heard?
An imperial edict is out. The emperor
will personally expel the foreigners.
An imperial edict?
Does that mean that the Imperial Court
is moving to overthrow the shogunate?
That's why you're all on edge.
That would plunge Kyo
into chaos once more.
Now, more than ever,
we need the Mibu Roshigumi.
But for a matter of such importance...
Serizawa is our head commander.
Head commander!
Is this man, Serizawa,
truly up to the task?
He extorts "donations" from everyone
and I hear he even burned down
a silk wholesaler's shop recently.
Kondo! Yamanami! Hijikata!
What's the matter with you!
Pathetic! Utterly pathetic!
You think I don't know?
Don't get cocky with me!
Where has your samurai spirit gone?
If you let him run wild,
you'll bring shame on Lord Katamori.
I don't give a damn about my reputation.
My lord!
Don't you dare hold back!
Sir!
Let's practice!
Kanbei.
Yes, sir!
I couldn't care less about
the Mibu-Roshi's internal squabbles.
However
the edict about the emperor himself
leading the overthrow of the shogunate...
It's a forgery.
A forgery?
Choshu plans to use
a forged edict to win allies
and pick a fight with the shogunate.
Those bastards are playing dirty.
Playing dirty? There's no such thing.
This is war.
Serizawa!
Well, now, sorry to crash the party.
Hey, you're in the lord's presence!
- Stand back!
- Move.
Hey, what the hell is going on?
I'm just saying I have something
to tell the boss.
And you're the ones making
all this damn noise, aren't you?
Huh? What's the deal?
Kamo.
What is it you want to discuss?
Our very own Niimi is connected to Choshu.
You bastard!
What the hell are you saying?!
I found this in Niimi's letterbox.
It's a letter from Kusaka Genzui
of Choshu, addressed to Niimi.
It's all written right there.
Saeki Matasaburo was a Choshu assassin,
hired by Niimi.
- Saeki was an assassin?
- Yes.
Then...
The whole thing with Aijiro...
Niimi and Choshu were behind that, too.
Originally, Kondo...
KONDO
...it seems the plan was
to get rid of you.
Ah, right, and by the way...
Niimi killed Abiru Eisaburo too.
So it was revenge for Abiru.
So?
What are you going to do about Niimi?
Not a damn thing.
I knew all along and didn't do anything.
The man has been far too useful to me.
If that's true,
then you're subject to punishment as well.
I don't care.
My lord
this isn't just an internal squabble
between Mibu factions.
I won't let this man
get away with this, Serizawa!
Yeah, whatever.
I'll cut you down right here and now.
Yes! Finally took the bait.
Hey, Sagawa,
don't chicken out like last time.
If you want to kill me, you had better
come at me with all you've got.
- Hey.
- What do you think you're doing?
Sorry, this is my fight.
Oh? Gotten a little stronger, have we?