Morning.
They're pickled just right.
Damn, this is good.
Sanosuke, you really have a knack
for knowing exactly
when pickles are at their best.
Does it make a difference?
A guy like you will never get it.
Got it.
"Got it."
"Got it." Just kidding. It's a joke.
I said it was a joke.
He's going to kill me! Got it!
SONG OF THE SAMURAI
Kamo, what is it you want to discuss?
Our very own Niimi is connected to Choshu.
Saeki Matasaburo
was a Choshu assassin, hired by Niimi.
Saeki was an assassin?
Right, and by the way...
Niimi killed
Abiru Eisaburo, too.
What are you going to do about Niimi?
Not a damn thing.
I knew all along and didn't do anything.
If that's true,
then you're subject to punishment as well.
I don't care.
I'll cut you down right here and now.
If you want to kill me, you had better
come at me with all you've got.
- Hey.
- What do you think you're doing?
Sorry, this is my fight.
Gotten a little stronger, have we?
Take that!
Great!
Let me go! I said let me go!
You really are as strong as they say.
I like this.
I smell violence on you.
Right now, you might actually
be worth cutting down.
Hey!
Boss!
If we're going to settle this here and now
then it only makes sense
for me to be your opponent!
Don't get in the way!
Right now, you don't do anything for me.
What?
Hey, you heard me.
"Come at me with everything you've got."
When you're ready to get serious,
come back then. Okay?
Aizu, too. I'll take you on anytime.
Thank you.
Hey, Kamo.
You really are
one stubborn son of a bitch.
Takes one to know one, Boss.
I'm leaving now.
That was quite a surprise.
Why would Serizawa choose to go down
with Niimi, knowing everything?
I just don't understand it anymore.
He's simply more honest than anyone else.
Honest?
That man...
All he has ever done
is live his life searching for something
that would set his blood on fire.
In his own way, that man is also...
a pure samurai.
Why did you get in my way?
When you drew your sword
it wasn't to take down Serizawa.
It was to protect me, wasn't it?
Did you think I was going to lose?
Yes.
You must have known that, too, Toshi.
Why did you try to cut Serizawa down?
For the good of the corps, obviously.
Don't play dumb.
You just wanted to fight him
for your own satisfaction, didn't you?
Once you lose your head, it's over.
I've seen a man
go down that path before.
I don't want you
to end up like him.
But I still want that fight.
You'll die.
The weak die.
That's all there is to it, right?
That's who you are, Toshi.
Are you any different, Boss?
There's a strong opponent facing you.
And you want
to risk your life to fight him.
You don't feel that?
Money?
Money... Money!
Lord Katamori is aware
that the imperial edict
is a forgery that the Choshu plotted.
The information came from Satsuma.
Hey, Niimi.
Serizawa.
Looks like things are getting ugly
for the Choshu, huh?
This is all for me, right?
Yes.
But now what?
What?
The truth is,
I already told Katamori everything
that you were connected to Choshu
and that you schemed with Kusaka
to take out Abiru and Aijiro.
By the way,
Kondo and the others were there, too.
I bet they will come at you
with everything they've got.
Serizawa.
Does this mean you've cast me aside?
When did I ever say that?
Then why?
I just want to see you
go head-to-head with them.
I'm expecting some spectacular violence.
So you're really going
to let Niimi handle this alone?
Knowing him
after he defeats them, he'll probably come
for you next, don't you think?
I like that. That's awesome.
You see, when it comes
to violence versus violence
the more you pit it against itself,
the more refined it becomes.
And the most exquisite part...
I'll devour it myself.
Gets my blood boiling.
At the same time
the Aizu clan joined forces
with the Satsuma clan
and completely sealed off
the Imperial Palace.
The Mibu Roshigumi
was also dispatched to guard the palace.
As a result of this coup d'état
on August 18
the seven Sonno Joi nobles
ruling the court
and the Choshu forces
were expelled from Kyo.
Halt!
This is not a rout!
It is a strategic withdrawal.
Justice is on our side!
Mark my words!
The day will come when we return
to the capital in triumph!
But there's one thing we should've taken,
no matter the cost.
The head of Matsudaira Katamori.
After this political upheaval
the Mibu Roshigumi were officially tasked
by Lord Katamori with patrolling the city
and were bestowed a new name.
That name
was the Shinsengumi.
MAKOTO
We'll avenge Aijiro.
You're probably wondering what I mean.
This whole mess started
because you killed Saeki.
Someone was pulling Saeki's strings
from the shadows.
And that same person took Eisaburo's life.
What do you mean?
So...
What's with the formal assembly?
Yes, what gives? This is creepy.
I'm sorry for the wait.
- Nagakura!
Sorry.
Everyone's here now.
We're going to discipline
the Shinsengumi vice-commander,
Niimi Nishiki.
Tell us why.
Niimi Nishiki
is a traitor who was colluding
with the Choshu.
And this letter
is the proof.
Niimi enlisted help
from Kusaka Genzui of Choshu
who sent Saeki Matasaburo, an assassin,
from his clan
and plotted to annihilate
our Kondo faction.
He murdered Sasaki Aijiro.
Furthermore
in order to spy on our movements
and those of the Aizu...
he used Abiru Eisaburo...
and once he was no longer useful...
he murdered him.
How did you get your hands on that letter?
Someone as cautious as Niimi
wouldn't let it be taken so easily.
It was Serizawa.
Serizawa told us everything.
So, Serizawa sold out Niimi?
What for?
He's probably just enjoying it.
He wants to see what happens
if he pits us against Niimi.
He doesn't even care
if it puts his own life on the line.
That's the impression he gave me.
What is wrong with that guy?
That doesn't matter right now.
Vengeance for Eisaburo and Aijiro.
Niimi will be cut.
End of story.
Hajime is right.
However...
To be blunt, our chances of winning
are practically zero.
How come?
If the Shinsengumi splits into two
most of the men will likely
side with them.
And I hear Niimi is using money
to hire unemployed Imperialist ronin
and bandits.
Even a conservative estimate puts them...
at 150.
In contrast...
there are only ten of us here.
One hundred and fifty against ten, huh?
So that's--
Fifteen men each.
Somehow...
I think I'd almost forgotten.
Back...
at our humble dojo...
when everyone looked down on
our "country-bumpkin" swordsmanship...
why did we even come to Kyo
in the first place?
Was it for money? For fame and success?
To play political games
and fight for power?
Of course not.
I came to Kyo to show all of Japan
that we're the strongest there is!
That we of the Shieikan
are the strongest and truest of samurai!
No matter what it takes...
I will avenge Eisaburo...
and Aijiro!
I need every one of you...
I want you with me.
Boss.
You don't have to bow for us anymore.
Hey.
We're up for it, right?
Bring on 20 men or 30.
I'll cut every last one of them down.
You're as reckless as ever.
But this time
it's actually quite...
reassuring.
All right.
And...
do we have a plan?
What a stupid question.
Don't you dare lump me in with you.
Right. That's true.
Here's the plan.
Tomorrow, at dusk.
Lord Katamori and Kondo are set
to meet privately to devise a plan.
The location is Shishigatani.
Katamori will use falconry as a cover
to get himself there.
To avoid being seen, his guard detail
will be kept to a bare minimum.
Money.
I never thought such a perfect opportunity
would fall right into my lap.
That bastard Serizawa.
Just you watch.
I'm not going down like this!
I'll take Katamori's head
to Choshu as a trophy!
Tomorrow! We take the head
of the Lord of Aizu, Matsudaira Katamori!
Take as much as you want!
This energy...
It reminds me of our days as bandits.
With this crew
I can take down Kondo and Serizawa
any time I want.
FRONT GATE,
BACK GATE
This is the rendezvous point.
It's surrounded
by a deep, water-filled moat
and has two entrances, front and back.
Katamori and Kondo both arrived
about 15 minutes ago.
I see.
If we're going to attack
shouldn't we go in
through the back?
The back entrance is down a steep path.
It's sealed shut.
So, you're saying we have
to bust through the front?
That's correct.
Not a problem.
We'll storm them all at once!
Listen.
Don't make a sound.
Got it.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Boss! It's an ambush!
An ambush? Move!
Move!
Katamori!
What is the meaning of this?
Is this your scheme, Yamanami?
We will now begin
the purge of Niimi Nishiki.
You've got a lot of nerve,
taking on all of us.
You damn runts!
Don't flinch! Slaughter them all!
Come at me with everything you've got!
Bring it!
Not fired up enough? You bastard!
Get out of here!
Take that!
- Thanks, Toshi.
- For what?
I cut them down,
and they just keep coming!
"I don't care if there are 20
or 30 of them, I'll cut them all down!"
Who was it that said that again?
That was me!
Move! There's only a handful of them left.
What a pathetic little ploy.
The passage is too narrow,
so we can't attack all at once.
That's why
they deliberately lured us here.
Fools.
Ultimately,
they're still hopelessly outnumbered.
Mushikui!
Attack from the rear.
But isn't that door never used?
That's precisely why you're going!
Hit them from behind.
We'll catch them in a pincer.
All right! My best fighters, on me!
We're going to end this right now!
Look, they're on the move!
Are we going to be all right?
Everyone's starting to get exhausted.
Now's our chance to strike!
Not yet! We stick to the plan!
Your complacency will get us all killed!
I'm heading around back!
Hijikata!
Have faith in Yamanami!
The tide of this battle will turn
in our favor. Isn't that right, Yamanami?
Yes, we have the advantage of the terrain.
Toshi's getting real antsy.
Are you sure we should
be holding back like this?
Yes.
Remember what Yamanami said?
If we move before the signal,
it'll all be for nothing.
- That was a hell of a climb.
- Yes.
So this is
the "door that never opens," huh?
Go on, bust it open.
Coming in.
- It's a Demon Wind!
- What was that?
No, it's far more vicious than that.
That's the Grim Reaper.
It's Harada Sanosuke.
You bastard, get down here!
Idiot! Don't go near him carelessly.
Hey!
Not a single one of you...
is getting past me.
Why are you trembling? It's just one guy!
Surround him and cut him to pieces!
Toshi!
How much longer?
This is endless.
No matter how strong you are
when you're seriously fighting
a whole group
your heart gets heavy, and your body
stops moving the way it should.
Because you're skilled,
you won't get an easy death.
You'll fade out little by little.
This is it, Harada.
Go get him!
Kill Harada Sanosuke!
Are you sure about this, Harada?
They've got
about 20, maybe 30 men.
We need to hold the line at the back gate.
No one gets through.
We should send someone else with you.
No need. They'll just be in the way.
I'm more than enough on my own.
Sanosuke.
You're not planning
on sacrificing yourself, are you?
I'm going to avenge Eisaburo and Aijiro.
That's all this is.
Sanosuke.
I put up another batch
of pickled radishes this morning.
What are you saying at a time like this?
Will you tell me
when they're ready to eat?
If you can't promise me that
I can't let you guard the back gate.
The most important thing
is for all of us to eat together again.
It's not about being ready to die.
You can promise me that, right?
I know.
I made a promise to the boss.
And I'm damn well going to keep it!
What the hell is that?
It's not a sickle?
That's a cheap shot.
There's nothing cheap about it.
I've always been a spear guy.
A monster!
Let's get out of here!
I got it.
Mushikui is down!
Go!
What are you dawdling for? Get a move on!
But...
we can't get through that.
What can they possibly do at this point?
They made a fortress out of corpses?
Everything's playing out your way,
Yamanami!
Go!
MAKOTO
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Don't you dare think you've won!
Enemy! We've got company!
An enemy attack?
Niimi!
Hold it! Hey! Go! Hajime!
Drop dead, Niimi!
Come if you dare, you dumb runts!