♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 7=
This is the Heavenly Yin Cold Marrow.
You.
I...
Why does it not hurt anymore?
Many thanks for saving Xiaonuan.
I...
Grandpa, get up.
Why bow to him?
Get up.
Come on, get up.
Don't keep bowing to me.
Since Xiaonuan is your granddaughter,
it was only natural to save her.
Grandpa, he cured my cold poison,
and we're even now.
After all, I cured his mom's illness.
Xiaonuan!
Ye Xiaonuan is right.
She really cured my mom.
Never expected you two
to have such a fate.
You flatter me. As for fate...
that's a stretch.
Dr. Ye,
your outfit today makes you
a different person.
At the hospital, I'm a doctor.
After work, I'm just myself.
What's wrong?
I will continue treating you.
You still have a long life ahead of you.
Just be yourself.
Is that true?
Of course.
That's good.
I didn't expect you
to have this side.
Are you surprised?
Don't tell me you like me
dressed like this?
Just kidding.
Don't be so serious.
You've got
the same temper Tianmiao had as a kid.
What's your connection with my grandpa?
If you don't want to say it, forget it.
For the future treatment...
will it always be like last night?
I don't understand a pure yin body.
I only know
that this illness can't be cured.
My granddad told me
when my cold poison flares up,
I only have five years left.
That's why you live like this...
Carpe diem,
and enjoy the moment.
Exactly.
So you can fully cure me?
Yes.
Of course I can.
But every treatment
will be just like last night.
You've already seen everything.
So what?
By the way,
if you've made up your mind,
come find me.
What happened last night...
you're not to tell a soul.
Su Wubing,
I owe you a favor.
You don't owe me anything.
You see?
Putting her in charge just doesn't work.
We thought you wouldn't dare come back.
What?
It's rare to see you all so formal.
This is my own company's board meeting.
What's there to be afraid of?
Ningxue, don't get it wrong.
That's not what he meant.
Everyone was getting a bit anxious.
And,
you know the company situation.
As for Mr. Gu...
So you're already calling him Mr. Gu?
You're all eager to hand the Lin Group
over to Gu Yuanbing, right?
Lin Ningxue,
mind your manners.
Ever since Mr. Lin handed
the company to you,
how much has the stock dropped?
How much business has been lost?
Only cooperation with the Gu Group
is the best option now.
Your so-called "best option"
is just ignoring Gu's ambition
to swallow the Lin Group whole.
What exactly did Gu Yuanbing give you
that made you betray the company?
That's not how you put it.
In business, there are
no permanent enemies,
but permanent interests.
We're thinking about
the company's interests,
not the feud between
the Lin and Gu families.
Exactly.
Feud?
What Gu wants is
our family's secret formula.
He wants to ruin the whole Lin family.
Are you all really unaware of this,
or just pretending?
What does your feud with the Gu family
have to do with us?
The company isn't yours alone.
Exactly.
Ningxue,
business is a battlefield.
The situation overrides personal gain.
Gu Yuanbing
plays dirty.
We've already lost too much.
If we keep resisting,
we...
can't afford to lose.
That's about you, not me.
The Lin family still has backbone.
My dad founded the Lin Group
and never once thought
of yielding to the Gu family.
If we say yes to the Gu family,
tomorrow every single person here
will be at their mercy!
Enough!
Stop fearmongering.
Board votes are the rule.
Those in favor of cooperation with
the Gu Group... raise your hands.
Lin Ningxue,
a wise man knows when to bend.
Take my advice.
Before my dad fell seriously ill,
he made it very clear:
when he can no longer serve as chairman,
all shares and decision-making power
are to be fully entrusted to me.
I
have the right of veto.
Still being stubborn!
The group will be ruined by you!
Wait and see.
This Heavenly Yin Cold Marrow
really can open
a mortal body's meridians
and connect spiritual power.
How is the company doing?
The company... everything is fine.
You've been strong-willed
since childhood.
Your worries always show on your face.
Did the Gu family try something else?
All our previous partners are afraid
of the Gu family.
They're cancelling contracts one by one.
At this rate,
in less than three months,
the whole market's gonna be Gu family's.
And the board...
they...
The Gu family is going
to wipe us out completely.
Dad,
as long as I'm here,
I will never let Gu Yuanbing
get his way.
At this point,
only one person can save our family.
You mean...?
Su Wubing?
I can tell...
he's here for you.
Mr. Lin,
Miss,
something's wrong!
People from the Gu Group...
What happened?
Gu Yuanbing has forced his way in!
Let's go!
Rong.
Mr. Gu is here in person today.
We're not receiving guests today.
Please leave.
Mr. Lin,
you've been unconscious for so long.
Are you sure you understand
what's going on?
My engagement with Lin Ningxue
was something you begged for.
And now you want to back out?
You're embarassing Gu family?
Mr. Gu,
you're here to settle
the engagement, right?
Now that Rong has recovered,
let's just hold another wedding.
Then it's settled.
That's best.
Otherwise it'll hurt
the Lin family's reputation.
Gu Yuanbing,
you used my dad's illness
to threaten me,
so I had to agree to marry you.
I came here today
to show you some respect.
You will marry me
whether you want to or not!
In Fan City,
(Jiang Yao, Gu Group)
Mr. Gu's words
are basically law.
Who would dare disobey?
See them out.
Rong,
we should put the family first.
Lin Rong,
I call you "sir" out of respect.
Otherwise,
you mean nothing to me.
You...
Dad!
Dad...
Gu Yuanbing, you're not welcome here.
Ningxue,
don't tell me you really think
that Su guy can save you again.
Come back with me obediently.
Otherwise...
Mr. Gu.
You're pushing your luck.
Stop it!
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪