♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 6=
Who are you?
Immortal King.
Once I come out of seclusion,
I'll settle the score with you.
I'll take your soul and complete
the Demon Clan's grand plan.
Too noisy.
Wubing, did he hurt you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Su Wubing,
why were you pretending
to be weak before?
Now you're this strong.
Are you getting close to Ningxue
to protect her,
or do you have other motives?
Don't tell her what just happened.
Why keep me in the dark?
What are you hiding from me?
(The demons have already shown up.)
(If they can find me,)
(they can find Ningxue too.)
Ningxue...
He's not just trying to win you over;
he's also got a good "little sister".
I'm not feeling well. I want to go home.
Yingying, he treats Tian
like a real sister.
You know her?
Ningxue.
Tian just got scared.
Take her home first.
I'll explain everything to Yingying
and come find you.
Why didn't you let me
tell Ningxue just now?
And...
why were you acting weak
at the martial hall?
And now you're staying at the Lin family
under the excuse of protecting her.
What's your real goal?
I just don't want her living in fear.
That's why I didn't tell her.
As for the rest...
I'll explain another day.
No. Tell me now.
What's wrong with you?
I barely even used force.
Ye Tianmiao's Herb Order...
How do you have this?
Take me to the Herbal Hall.
Now.
So you're Su Wubing's sister?
We are...
Childhood sweethearts?
Ningxue, do you... like Wubing?
You're overthinking it.
He saved my father.
I'm just repaying a debt.
That's all.
So the house we're living in is yours?
I gave it to him.
I'm not taking it back.
(She clearly likes him
and she's so generous...)
(How am I supposed to compete?)
(Childhood sweethearts...)
(Looks like he really cares about her.)
Stop!
Who are you?
I'm from Shan family. Move aside!
Another one here to
curry favor for pills?
Get lost!
You...
This...
Please come in.
What's going on?
Without Master's order,
no entry for outsiders.
You.
Look at him.
He was unstoppable just now,
and now he's this weak?
And he even has the Herb Token...
Just how many secrets is he hiding?
And Ningxue and him...
Tianmiao.
My Lord.
Your mortal body can't
withstand Heavenly God Realm power.
Every time you use immortal energy,
it damages your meridians.
This body still
hasn't adapted.
Someone.
Help my Lord change.
Yes.
(This medicinal pool is)
(filled with rare treasures
collected by me.)
(It will greatly help restore
your cultivation.)
(Herbal Hall)
(Su Wubing...?)
(How is he here?)
(I didn't expect his physique
to be this good.)
Dr. Ye...
Su Wubing...
(She actually has a pure Yin body.)
(It forms at the peak of extreme Yin,)
(absorbing innate Yin energy.)
(The poison seeps into bones.)
(When it flares up,
it's agony beyond words.)
Sorry for this.
Dr. Ye.
I know you can hear me.
Your condition is special.
If I don't treat you in time,
I'm afraid you...
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪