♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 2=
(Ten Thousand Years Ago)
(Lin Ningxue, Holy Maiden)
After 300 years of seclusion,
I finally reached
the Heavenly God Realm.
I'm finally back.
(Su Wubing, Immortal King)
♪Snow falls upon your sleeves♪
♪Yet it cannot conceal
a fate-bound curse♪
♪A thousand years of cultivation
were distilled into a single lamp♪
♪Foolishly trying to light
the long night♪
Ningxue.
I did it.
I've reached the Heavenly God Realm.
From now on,
I'll break your curse.
No matter what it takes.
Break!
Ningxue.
Ningxue!
You, a lowly immortal, dare defy me.
Defy the Heavenly Dao?
Your soul shall return to the void.
The Heavenly Dao?
So the Heavenly Dao
actually curses people from birth
and kills them at such a young age?
Stubborn fool.
Ningxue!
No!
It wasn't easy for you
to reach the Heavenly God Realm.
Don't ruin it.
All my cultivation
is for her.
How is that ruining anything?
Sword, come!
Whether you're the Heavenly Dao
or a demon,
eat this!
If you want Ningxue,
step over my dead body first.
Even if my soul shatters,
I'll defy you to the end.
Even with Heavenly God Realm power
overwhelming,
Immortal King just ended seclusion.
Ningxue!
The Heavenly God Sword
isn't fully refined yet.
It may not be able
to stand against the Heavenly Dao.
Even if the Heavenly Dao won't allow it,
I swear to follow you forever.
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
The Holy Maiden's curse can actually
activate the Time-Space Array.
From the heavens above
to the underworld below,
I will never fail you.
Just you?
This is spiritual power?
A low-level martial artist
like you can't cure
my father's illness.
Get out.
Get out!
- Welcome back, Miss.
How is my father?
Master, he...
It's still the same.
In this life,
her family is fairly well-off.
Tonight, without my permission,
no one is allowed to disturb my father.
Yes.
(Yingying)
Hello.
Hello, Ningxue.
The person with you...
I knew.
He wasn't arranged by you.
He wasn't,
but he's from our martial hall.
You know him?
Of course.
His name is Su Wubing.
His mother has been
seriously ill for years,
and they're very poor,
so I let him stay and do odd jobs.
And he can't even beat kids.
Basically useless...
Just an ordinary nobody.
How is that possible?
Alright, I got it, Yingying.
(A martial hall apprentice?)
(I wanna give it a try anyway.)
(I didn't expect)
(the curse is still clinging to you.)
What are you doing?
Stop spacing out.
Keep up.
(Only three months left.)
(In this life,)
(she's just a mortal.)
(She can't bear the curse anymore.)
Can you really cure my father?
Yes.
The Lin family's fate is in your hands.
(I'll save the Lin family,)
(and you, too.)
Come with me.
Dad,
I've found someone who can cure you.
(Lin Rong, Head of Lin family)
Xue,
my time has come.
Dad...
No. It won't happen.
The burden of our family
is all on you now.
After I'm gone,
the Gu family will
definitely move against us.
Take care of yourself.
Dad...
Dad, no.
You'll get better, you will.
(This is Abyss Poison.)
Stop!
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪