♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 3=
Stop!
Uncle Hai?
(Lin Hai, Little Brother of Lin Rong)
Who is this guy?
He's the one I brought
to treat my dad.
Treat him?
We don't need outsiders meddling.
What I decide is final.
No need for you to worry.
Uncle Hai, please leave.
Alright.
I won't waste words with you.
I invited Ye Tianmiao,
the Medical Saint of Fan City,
to treat him.
(Ye Tianmiao, Medical Saint)
Can't say no now, huh?
Mr. Ye?
(These two...)
I just came out of seclusion
and heard that Rong is seriously ill.
so I came right away.
Since someone's already treating him,
I'll observe for now.
That won't do!
How's my dad really doing?
Lin Ningxue!
Are you really gonna
put your dad's life
in the hands of this unknown guy?
I've made up my mind.
If Su Wubing can't cure my dad,
I'll take responsibility.
Take responsibility?
What makes you so confident?
You ran from the wedding?
The Gu family will never let us off!
Everyone here knows
the Gu family is ruthless.
If it weren't for my dad,
I wouldn't have agreed to the marriage.
Nonsense!
Dad!
Uncle Hai, please leave.
Alright.
I'm done arguing.
If anything happens to Rong,
You'll pay for this.
This poison has reached his bones.
The Abyss Illusion is the only cure.
Break!
(It's the power of the Immortal King...)
(My Lord, I finally found you.)
How's my dad?
Dad.
Dad!
What did you do to my dad?
Don't panic.
Once the black blood is expelled,
the poison is gone.
(The Abyss Poison is lifted.)
Don't worry.
A little rest and he'll recover.
Really?
After ten thousand years,
I finally see you.
Mr. Ye, what are you doing?
Do you... remember me?
Mr. Ye is the Medical Saint of Fan City.
How could he kneel before him?
Tianmiao?
It's me.
You remember!
It's been ten thousand years
since we parted.
(To directly call Mr. Ye by name...)
(Who exactly is Su Wubing?)
Mr. Ye.
Please stand up.
Stand up.
We can talk privately.
Yes.
The Herbal Order represents
the Ye family's legacy.
This legacy is meant
to help you come back.
This Order can mobilize
all Ye family's resources.
The Herbal Hall is also open to you.
You can use all the treasures inside.
Mr. Ye.
This token is so precious.
You can't do this.
Who exactly is Su Wubing...?
Rong still needs rest.
I won't bother you further.
We'll invite you to our house
another day.
Dad.
Ningxue.
What's...?
What happened?
Dad.
You're alright.
Rest a bit more.
Don't move yet.
Follow me.
Who exactly are you?
(She doesn't remember anything now.)
(Telling her would just cause trouble.)
You ruined Gu Yuanbing's wedding.
And now the Medical Saint treats you
with such respect.
What's your goal in approaching me?
Ten thousand years...
all just to protect you.
What?
Why do you talk like
someone from a novel?
(I just cured the Abyss Poison.)
(It must've used up
too much spiritual power.)
You... what's wrong?
Su Wubing!
Su Wubing, wake up!
What secret are you hiding?
You're awake.
I...
I haven't thanked you for yesterday.
You cured my dad.
A token of thanks.
There's five million
in the card and a villa.
All yours.
Take it.
I don't like owing anyone.
Another question.
You must answer honestly.
What caused
my dad's illness?
(Someone must've poisoned)
(Lin Rong maliciously using Abyss Poison.)
(And each dose was tiny)
(and hard to detect.)
What are you thinking?
Someone...
poisoned your dad.
Come in.
Got it.
(Dad's illness is cured,)
(but the Lin family's crisis isn't over.)
(Gu Yuanbing won't stop easily.)
(I still need to stabilize
the group first.)
Where did that idiot come from?
How dare he ruin my plan?
Mr. Gu.
You.
Get down!
Down!
Open your mouth.
Hole in one.
Alright, stand up.
Spit it out.
Mr. Gu,
that Su guy just does chores
in the martial hall.
Not even an apprentice.
Go check
his connection to the Lin family.
Also, tell Lin Hai,
within a month,
get the Lin family secret formula,
or forget being the head
of the Lin family.
Yes.
And what's that guy called… Su...?
Su Wubing.
Mr. Gu.
Should we teach him a lesson?
I heard he has a sick mother.
A sick mother?
Alright.
This matter is yours.
Do it well.
Got it.
The ball?
Lin Ningxue...
You.
The Lins' secret formula.
And the Lin group.
They will all be mine soon enough.
Go, get lost!
Boss, it's this room.
You!
(Ye Xiaonuan, Doctor)
What are you doing?
You alright?
Yeah.
Go to the clinic for treatment.
This is the ward.
We're here to find Su Wubing's mother.
Mind your own business.
Leave.
This is a hospital.
You can't cause trouble here.
Trouble?
Listen, miss.
You probably haven't seen
how we guys make trouble.
You go first.
Get lost.
I don't care about your relationship
with Su Wubing.
This is a hospital.
Su Wubing's family are my patients.
I'll say it once more.
Leave.
Leave?
I can't touch him.
I can still handle you.
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪