♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 8=
Come back with me obediently.
Otherwise...
Mr. Gu.
You're pushing your luck.
Stop it.
Su Wubing! How dare you
be rude to Mr. Gu!
Su...
Su Wubing!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Did you kneel down
and beg the master for mercy?
So he spared your life.
The guy in the teahouse
was someone you hired?
How shameless.
So what?
No one can stand in the way
of our family.
If you refuse this marriage,
your family will be
wiped out in Fan City.
See them out.
Again?
You old fool.
For Ningxue's sake.
I was going to let you
live out your days in peace.
You're digging your own grave.
As for you,
Su Wubing, once I deal
with the Lin family,
I'll make sure you watch
with your own eyes
how I break her down.
Mr. Gu!
Let's call it a day.
I'll spare your life.
Now get lost.
Looks like he didn't survive by luck.
Maybe his cultivation is already
above Xue Wuhen.
Our score isn't settled yet.
We'll see.
Mr. Gu.
Hey...
Please.
Thanks for your help.
If you had arrived a step later,
who knows what that Gu brat
would've done.
You're welcome. Uncle Lin.
I promised you
I'd protect Ningxue properly.
Wubing has saved us more than once.
This is a great favor to us.
When you restrained Gu Yuanbing,
have you considered the consequences?
Dad.
He didn't do anything wrong.
When did I say he did?
I'm saying, to outsiders,
you're already tied to the Lin family.
From now on, you must be extra careful.
Uncle Lin,
I suspect your illness
didn't come out of nowhere.
(Personal Information: Su Wubing)
Xue Wuhen is trash.
And so are you!
You can't even figure out Su Wubing.
You still dare to stand?
The villa where Su's mother lives
seems to be a restriction set up.
Our men can't get close.
Tell Lin Hai to make his move.
Get the Lin family's secret formula
within three days.
Yes.
And that Xue Wuhen...
Turn the place upside down and find him.
He's making money off me? Not that easy.
Understood.
Get out.
Ningxue,
I don't feel safe recovering at home.
My chest still hurts a bit.
Let's stay in the hospital
for a few days.
I'll recover better there.
Alright, I'll arrange the admission
right away.
I'll stay with you.
Look,
I'll go notify the hospital first.
I can guarantee you won't
be disturbed there.
Rong.
Isn't it better to recover at home?
Hospital is such a hassle.
No.
The hospital is safer.
You should
keep an eye on things here.
Don't let anything go wrong.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Alright.
Careful.
Rong, take it slow.
No barrier.
Uncle Hai.
Dad.
You... you didn't go to the hospital?
I suspected you all along.
We said that just to lure you out.
I came here just to help you
pick something up
in case you needed it at the hospital.
Stop pretending.
We've already found out
you poisoned Uncle Lin's medicine.
Uncle Hai... why would you do this?
What do you know?!
What can a little girl like you do?
Business is a battlefield.
Only joining forces with the Gu family
is our only way out.
You!
Someone!
Don't come closer!
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪