♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 1=
Help!
Don't run!
- Stop!
- Don't run!
Help!
- Stop!
- Don't you run!
Stop there!
Help!
Trying to run?
Run, huh?
(Jia Zhengdao, Gu Group)
Thought you could run, huh?
Well...
If you can get away under our noses,
what happens to Gu Group's reputation?
B-Boss, I...
If I'd known this was so risky,
I'd never have come, I swear!
Look,
jump from here right now.
If you can still get back up,
I'll let you go.
No guts?
Boss, please...
You guys, help him a bit, okay?
Wait!
Boss, please!
Spare me!
I was wrong, boss!
Go down.
This mortal body...
can rival the gods.
Divine power.
You ants,
how dare you act up!
(Su Wubing,
Reincarnation of Immortal King)
This is...?
Ten thousand years later...
The Heavenly Dao
still carries such might?
Ningxue, I'm coming to save you!
Today is a big day in Fan City.
The Gus and Lins are joining together.
(Lin Ningxue, Holy Maiden; Gu Yuanbing)
What's more,
that Young Master Gu and Miss Lin
are truly a perfect match.
Mr. Gu Yuanbing,
do you take Miss Lin Ningxue
as your wife,
for better or worse,
for richer or poorer,
faithful for life?
I do.
Miss Lin Ningxue,
do you take Mr. Gu Yuanbing
as your husband,
through thick and thin,
standing by his side,
till death do you part?
Why isn't Miss Lin
saying anything?
Could it be a forced marriage?
Ningxue.
Your father's waiting for us.
(For my father...)
(this is the only way.)
I...
I do.
Ningxue.
I promised you
that no matter how far,
I'd find you.
(Who exactly are you?)
Who are you?
How dare you crash my wedding?
Where'd this punk come from?
How dare you cause trouble
for Young Master Gu!
Who is that guy?
Where did he pop out from?
Who cares?
This is about to get interesting.
(Shan Yingying,
Apprentice in the Martial Hall)
(Shan Yingying, Martial Hall Apprentice)
Why is it him?
Didn't I send my senior?
(Two Hours Earlier)
Ningxue, you can't marry him.
You know what kind of man
Gu Yuanbing is.
Yingying...
You know I have no choice.
Two years ago,
my dad suddenly fell ill.
Even our family's Longevity Pill
can barely keep him hanging on.
Now...
only the miracle cure in
Gu Yuanbing's hands
can save him.
But what if that medicine's a scam?
What if he's lying to you?
For my dad's life,
I'll take that risk.
If that's the case...
then
after you get the medicine,
I'll ask senior to take you away.
Will that really work?
Where did this idiot come from?
Daring to stir trouble
at Mr. Gu's wedding!
Throw him out!
Yes!
(Since when did this city
have someone like that?)
Ningxue.
Come with me.
I'll explain everything.
Wait.
Ningxue.
The miracle cure...
is still with me.
Your father's illness...
Let's go.
What?
They're just leaving?
What the...?
♪Snow falls upon your sleeves♪
♪Yet it cannot conceal
a fate-bound curse♪
♪A thousand years of cultivation
were distilled into a single lamp♪
Lin Ningxue,
you chose this yourself.
Don't blame me then.
Get in the car.
Looks like
she doesn't recognize me at all.
This is to thank you.
Hand over the medicine
and you're free to go.
Ningxue...
You may have lost your memories,
don't worry...
I will help you get them back.
What are you talking about?
It's just the two of us here.
Drop the act.
Acting?
You're not sent by Yingying?
Of course not.
You get the money, I get the medicine.
Medicine?
That's not medicine at all.
It won't cure your father.
But I can.
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪