I wanted a job where I could make things.
Like my dad.
The pain the victim felt,
and the pain the perpetrator feels…
Now, they're equal.
They're even.
Nice and even.
MINORU - CALL ME
TSUDA'S NOTEBOOK IS MISSING
Excuse me, please don't look.
Hello, sir.
Mr. Tagusari, where did you go?
Who is the body?
Takamichi Uno.
Uno recently submitted
his resignation letter.
So he did this to be with his wife.
It's too early to jump to conclusions.
Uno was caught on a surveillance camera
near Ayaka Nishiura's apartment.
There is no doubt that Uno killed her.
-What?
-Really?
After finishing his revenge, Uno…
Hello.
-Hello.
-Hey.
A fatal fall?
Yes.
Takamichi Uno, 50 years old, male.
We got a report of him
falling around 6:00 p.m.
We secured the scene and…
It's a suicide.
This one has no foul play.
-I'm taking a look at the roof.
-Okay.
Oh, Dr. Kiritani.
Please handle the autopsy procedures.
Yes.
Don't add extra work for us.
However you look at it, it’s suicide.
I'm just doing my job.
Uno's revenge is over. That's why he…
I told you before.
I'm only interested in the truth.
-Uno jumped from the building!
-You want it to be suicide that badly?
-That is the truth.
-It's not.
Minoru.
This isn't suicide.
It's murder.
All of this began three years ago.
Ms. Ayaka Nishiura was driving a car,
when she struck Yoko Uno,
who had jumped out into the road,
and killed her.
And the other day,
Ms. Nishiura
was murdered inside a moving car
by carbon monoxide poisoning.
The suspect is Yoko's husband,
Takamichi Uno.
CCTV footage confirmed that the man
who tampered with Ms. Nishiura's car
was Uno.
We believe he held a grudge over losing
his wife, and did it for revenge.
However, yesterday around 6:00 p.m.,
Takamichi Uno fell from a building.
He was found dead.
Examiner Tagusari!
Normally, in the case of a jump,
the body lands
directly beneath the building.
On the other hand, if a person is pushed,
they fall in a parabolic arc,
so the landing point tends to be
a certain distance away from the building.
The body was found
directly beneath the building, right?
Takamichi Uno
struck something before landing.
He struck something?
There were abrasions on his head,
which matched the bloodstains found
on the wall of the adjacent building.
It is likely that Uno hit
the neighboring building,
then landed directly underneath this one.
Based on the above,
it is highly likely
that this fatal fall was a homicide.
We have to find witnesses,
trace his steps after quitting his job,
and recover the data
from his damaged smartphone. Hurry!
Yes, sir!
What is it?
May I check the alibi of Takumi Agatsuma?
Ayaka Nishiura's fiancé?
Agatsuma has more than enough motive.
It's pointless.
It hasn't been made public
that Uno killed Nishiura.
But, if we consider people
who may have a grudge against Uno,
I think he is the most likely candidate.
True, we can't ignore Agatsuma.
However, drop your preconceptions.
If you label someone a suspect,
that's all you'll see.
Understood.
Anyone checked the cameras?
Yes!
But we haven't found a suspect yet.
Mr. Agatsuma,
where were you yesterday around 6:00 p.m.?
Yesterday, I went with…
my parents to the real estate agency
to cancel the lease on my place,
then went home.
After that, were you alone?
Yes.
That's enough.
Excuse me.
Mr. Tagusari.
WELFARE OFFICE CONSULTATIONS
COME TALK TO ME ANYTIME!
KANAGAWA POLICE
RECOVERED DATA FROM APPS
TELESEEK
Mr. Tagusari!
Ms. Kudo is here to see you.
It's about Detective Tagusari.
Don't you think
he has been acting weird lately?
Lately?
He is often unreachable
and abruptly cuts investigations short.
I know he thinks of things as a hassle,
but this feels different.
When did it start bothering you?
After he went to the city hall, I think.
The city hall?
The welfare consultant there
doesn't sit right with me.
Now, three of her consultees
have become murder suspects.
Takumi Agatsuma,
Takamichi Uno, and Atsuko Narita.
Narita?
The mother from the case
of the AI grading error.
The one I'm stuck on is the mother.
I saw a TeleSeek notification
on her phone.
That app that doesn't store
message history?
Could it be that the consultant urged
the three of them to commit murder?
What is her name?
It's Sayoko Hatano.
WELFARE CONSULTANT
Only the bereaved
who have lost their loved ones…
Why?
Why must they be the ones
to continue suffering?
KANAGAWA POLICE
MAKOTO TAGUSARI
-Ms. Hatano.
-Yes?
A Mr. Tagusari is here for you.
Okay.
So you are Minoru, his younger brother?
I heard from Makoto
that you work as a forensics examiner.
You're so talented for your age.
What did you talk to him about?
Are you curious?
Yes, I am.
You majored in criminal psychology.
What could he be talking about with you?
I'm sorry,
I inquired with your university.
Could you tell me?
I can't disclose my consultation--
This is also a consultation.
I am consulting about my brother.
I listened to what was at his core.
I'm sure those are things
he could never tell anyone, not even you.
What's at his core.
But…
you have them too, don't you?
Things you can't tell your older brother?
I don't. Not really.
If you want my counsel, you must not lie.
COME TALK TO ME ANYTIME!
Hatano might have been
inciting the murders.
Even if she led them to commit crimes,
it would be difficult
to build a legal case.
I'll probe into her background
with First Division.
Please do.
Oh, where is Tagusari?
He's not feeling well.
Since that day,
Makoto has always protected you, right?
You were still so young.
It's no wonder
you shut yourself away, Minoru.
But, you knew…
didn't you?
What your brother, who was only seven,
had been carrying since that day.
Aside from the incident,
Makoto had to fill the void
left by your deceased parents.
His daily life,
his studies and future.
He prioritized you
over himself, didn't he, Minoru?
And you began to feel guilty about that.
Thinking that you couldn't
do anything for your brother.
It's almost like
you saw my whole life story.
But…
there is something you can do.
There are things that only you can do.
However, I'll be the one to do it.
I will carry him at the end.
This time,
won't you tell me
what's at your core, Minoru?
You should take it.
All right. Excuse me.
Oh, they hung up.
It's an unknown number.
A spam call?
-I see.
-Right.
There are a lot of scams lately,
so be careful.
Oh, sorry.
I'll go get a cloth.
ONE MISSED CALL
TELESEEK
Makoto?
What are you doing here?
What about you?
We need to talk.
I found the TeleSeek app
on Sayoko Hatano's phone too.
They must be sending messages
that could be evidence.
Which means, no matter how much we dig,
we won't find anything.
She's a troublesome opponent.
Makoto!
Who are the real troublesome ones?
The perpetrators
who don't get judged, right?
Hold on! The Igarashi-gumi
disposed of the notebook.
I am very sorry!
Sakuraba.
Did anything come up besides the drugs?
Are you kidding me?
What?
You gave me false info.
This.
HARUKO ASHIKAGA
THE IGARASHI-GUMI'S CLEANERS
Their cleaners?
We might find Tsuda's notebook there.
We're closed for the day.
Come back tomorrow.
I'm sorry, but I'm busy tomorrow.
I'm glad.
Do you remember me?
What do you want?
Don't be so on guard.
You're not here to see the wares, right?
Why did you come back here?
Just by chance, that's all.
Back then,
was it "by chance," too?
What?
The day of the murders.
Why were you in front
of the Tagusaris's home?
When are you talking about?
1995.
April 26.
Around 10:54 p.m.
Why were you there?
I told you already.
I was passing by on my way home
from my part-time job.
It has been 30 years.
Stop interrogating me.
Then stop helping those brothers.
You know what those guys
are doing, don't you?
The statute has expired.
That case is over now.
Stop selling fakes.
Is Mr. Sasaoka…
doing well?
I heard your partner back then
was forced to quit being a detective.
INSPECTOR DISCHARGED
So this is where you were.
Ex-Detective Sasaoka from First Division.
I heard you used to be quite close
with the Igarashi-gumi.
INSPECTOR DISCHARGED FOR LEAKING
CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION
Hey, you guys.
I heard you guys
can dispose of anything here.
Do you really accept everything?
Let's say we have something
we don't want anyone to see.
We only work with companies
we have a contract with.
Do you mean the Igarashi-gumi?
This place is the Igarashi-gumi's
dumping ground, right?
Show me the things
you've received recently.
What are you talking about?
No way we have anything like that.
This.
You want me to show it
to the Igarashi-gumi?
You only pretend to dispose of them,
but you've actually been reselling them.
If the Igarashi-gumi finds out about this…
Can you really restore
something like that?
We have no choice but to try.
Because Tsuda's notebook is inside this.
You used to like puzzles.
It's not like I did puzzles
because I liked them.
After the incident,
I just didn't want to go outside.
Back then, everywhere I went,
people stared at me,
they all looked like enemies to me.
Friends, adults,
people I met for the first time…
Well, that hasn't changed even now, but…
At this point,
I'm even afraid of making allies.
I know.
Sayoko Hatano is the enemy, you know.
She's just pretending to be our ally.
Put the white paper in a separate pile.
Go steal the evidence from those brothers.
Why the sudden visit?
-Oh…
-Do you want…
Do you want something to drink?
I can't betray those boys after all.
I've known them since they were kids.
I can't…
What about us?
We've known you
since before they were even born, right?
That's true, but…
Do you not care what happens to us?
No…
Mogi!
Oh, right!
The other day,
I took some test shots with my new camera!
Karu, had such
a wonderful expression on her face.
Take it home with you.
Mogi.
It's for the sake of everyone.
So we can all be happy.
Minoru!
Don't talk about cases
in a place like this.
You're fine, Mogi.
The consultant, Sayoko Hatano,
was in charge of three suspects.
The first was Atsuko Narita.
Her son, Kenshin, came forward
to take the blame for her.
Atsuko herself has not confessed.
Her presumed method
was a lethal combination of medications.
We found a newspaper article
about the method.
PRESCRIPTION ERROR LED
TO 63-YEAR-OLD WOMAN'S DEATH
The second person was Takamichi Uno.
It is believed he murdered
Ms. Ayaka Nishiura while she was driving,
using carbon monoxide poisoning.
This is a mystery novel
that utilizes a similar trick.
And the third person is Takumi Agatsuma.
It's possible she led him
to pushing Uno to his death.
According to
a Welfare Department colleague,
Hatano would recommend books
and materials to her consultees.
It's highly probable she used those
to suggest methods of murder,
prompting them to seek revenge.
However, because Uno used
an app with high encryption,
no evidence could be recovered
from his smartphone.
The TeleSeek app was also present
on Hatano's phone,
but that isn't enough to build a case.
We must find definitive evidence
of the murder
and force a link to Hatano's involvement.
Why go that far?
Well, they're a bit similar
to my own family.
My dad was always busy,
so we barely spent any time together.
It was mostly just my mother and me.
I caused her
quite a lot of trouble back then,
so now I want to put her mind at ease.
That's why I think
Narita's son will understand too.
That it's his turn now
to save his mother, who made a wrong turn.
Reporting to Ayaka?
Since it's all over,
won't you talk to me now?
What are you talking about?
Don't you think it's strange?
Why doesn't everyone take revenge?
"If anything ever happened to my child,
I would never forgive them."
You hear people say that all the time,
but barely anyone acts on it.
They use their remaining family
as an excuse
to force a lid on their own feelings.
And Sayoko Hatano pried open that lid
which you had fought
so hard to keep closed.
Though she never experienced
any pain herself.
Is Sayoko Hatano…
truly on your side?
Excuse me.
Mr. Agatsuma.
Blue.
Transparent.
Purple.
White.
The roof?
There they are.
What are you doing?
Help us search for the power stones!
Can you explain more clearly?
Agatsuma wore a matching
bracelet with his girlfriend.
After the murder, the arrangement
of the stones changed.
Arrangement?
After the murder,
a single white stone was missing.
How did you even notice that?
If the bracelet snapped
when he pushed Uno off the building here…
The stones he missed might still be here.
So, what if we find those stones?
It means Agatsuma was definitely here.
Come to think of it,
Fumi comes to the restaurant often these…
This is…
the back side.
There.
Oh, right.
Amazing.
Since I was a kid, I often
got absorbed in things like this.
Same with cooking, right?
Well, once I get started,
I just can't stop.
Shall we eat soon?
What about Makoto?
I don't know when he'll be back.
I'll make something.
Really?
We have nothing here,
I'll run to the supermarket.
What?
Keep working on that.
Go steal the evidence from those brothers.
I wonder if he picked up all the stones…
Or maybe it snapped
somewhere else entirely,
completely unrelated to the murder.
Shall we call it a day soon?
We've hit a complete dead end.
-Kudo.
-Yes?
I need a handsaw.
What?
What for?
Ishizaka, go up to the rooftop
run water down the pipe.
-What?
-Hurry up.
-Move it!
Okay.
That day,
I went to the rooftop,
like the counselor told me to.
How did you get Uno
to go up to the rooftop?
She called him out for me.
And after that?
Are we bringing Hatano in?
No, it's impossible.
We have no evidence
she ordered the murder,
nor do we have proof
that she called Uno out.
If only we had that, we could arrest her.
But Hatano has been meticulous
about erasing all traces.
Mrs. Narita.
What is the matter?
I spoke with my son.
I will tell you the truth.
In Mr. Ichijo's murder,
there were a few unclear points.
How did you find out about
the cover-up of the grading errors?
Through a tablet.
-Once in the morning.
-Mr. Ichijo…
He frequented the pharmacy where I worked.
Here you go.
One day, when he went
to get his prescription,
he forgot his tablet.
I immediately tried to run after him, but…
MASAOMI OKAMURA
ABOUT THE GRADING ERROR
What?
It's just a prank email.
But the email clearly mentions an error.
I won't tell a soul,
so could you please let my son pass?
How much do you want?
What?
I bet your goal is money, right?
Darling.
You have a guest?
-I'll be done soon.
-He didn't even take me seriously.
But to go as far as murder…
Surely there were other ways
to make it public?
I went to the city hall,
and Ms. Hatano told me…
"The university would never admit to it,
and it would probably just be covered up.
If things stayed like this, Kenshin
would be the only one left to suffer."
I just couldn't
bring myself to forgive them.
Why couldn't you stop yourself?
Now that you, his mother, have done this,
it only makes it harder for him.
ADVICE FROM MOM
DON'T PUSH YOURSELF TOO HARD!
TO KENSHIN
There's no doubt that Hatano also incited
Narita to commit murder.
What about the evidence?
Hatano merely laid out
facts and possibilities.
And she only showed a newspaper article
for the murder method.
That doesn't warrant an arrest.
Then, Hatano…
We might have
to take the loss on this one.
Where are you going?
Causing trouble for your partner again?
-What did you come here for?
-For work.
And also…
Hatano incited others to kill,
without leaving traces of herself.
However, while she used
an article for Narita
and a mystery novel for Uno,
we couldn't find any clear motif
regarding Agatsuma's homicide.
True, Uno's death
was handled as a fatal fall.
Maybe their plan went off the rails?
Since Uno had submitted
a resignation letter,
there was a possibility
he was attempting to flee.
That's why Agatsuma needed to hurry.
Which means Sayoko Hatano also…
As for the rest, you'll understand
once you check this data.
I'll go check it.
Did you plan to become bait?
Not really.
Hatano is going to manipulate you again.
Shut up. Like hell she will.
If that's the case,
make sure you bring her down.
I can't stand her.
Wait here.
What?
I met your younger brother the other day.
Please bring him with you next time.
We won't meet again.
I'm here today to arrest you.
Arrest?
You have consulted
with various people in this office.
Your consultees
trusted you so deeply,
they spoke your name with respect.
But, in those sessions,
you were carefully examining them.
The depth of their wounds.
Atsuko Narita,
Takamichi Uno,
and Takumi Agatsuma.
You found clients who had someone
they wanted revenge on,
and goaded them into committing murder.
I was simply doing my job.
Your job?
I merely listened to their worries,
and occasionally recommended books
or other material, for a change of pace.
How is any of that a crime?
True,
if that's all, you wouldn't be
judged by the law.
But,
the final one, Takumi Agatsuma,
was different, wasn't he?
Uno, the target of his revenge,
attempted to flee.
He probably got cold feet
because the police were closing in.
However,
if Uno escaped,
Agatsuma's revenge would fail.
You called Uno to that building,
pretending to give him runaway funds.
Then you led Agatsuma there,
setting things up
so that he would kill him.
To trigger a cycle of revenge.
You seem remarkably composed.
If I look that way to you,
perhaps I am.
It's true that
because you used TeleSeek,
there is no physical evidence.
Even if Agatsuma testifies,
if you deny it,
the truth remains out of reach.
So, how are you arresting me?
Don't misunderstand.
The lack of evidence
is only on your consultee's side.
Uno's sudden escape was unexpected.
That's why you had to rush
Agatsuma into the crime.
You had no choice but to give
instructions from right here.
This is
security footage from the city hall,
one hour before Uno was murdered.
I see nothing.
It starts from here.
The audio from this section.
I had the forensics lab analyze it.
…from the rooftop…
…Uno…
Push him off the rooftop.
Kill Uno and make it look like a suicide.
Well, see you again.
I already told you.
We won't be meeting again.
Is that so?
I am quite certain
you will come to see me, though.
I'll take over.
This way.
You here for a consultation too?
I'm sorry.
That won't be possible today.
Kenshin…
You should stay out of this.
Narita's son has turned himself in.
Is he actually talking this time?
He's incredibly cooperative.
How is Makoto?
He's completely back to his usual self.
Well, that is troublesome too.
You said something before.
What?
That you and Mr. Tagusari go way back.
We're from the same hometown.
Are you connected by those murders?
What?
April 26, 1995.
The Yomogida-cho family murder case.
The culprit still hasn't been caught.
The statute has expired, you know.
What about the evidence?
Did you find it?
I made sure to search thoroughly.
I'll run to the supermarket.
Keep working on that.
But there was nothing there.
Really?
Yes.
So, you don't need to worry all that much.
You really want…
to protect those brothers, huh?
Now we have Tsuda's notebook…
We should be able to find out
what happened 30 years ago.
"However, the darkness surrounding
the illicit manufacturing runs deep.
The involved parties
include the Karashima Metal Factory,
the Igarashi-gumi,
and beyond that…"
Who could it be at a time like this?
Why?
You don't think…
Mr. Koike was involved too?
Everyone will continue to be happy.
Do you trust Tsuda more?!
Do you want to know the truth that badly?
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.