[One year ago]
And the final member joining Wakers is...
Trainee Kim Hyun Jae, congratulations.
The idol survival show, Next Stage.
The last of Wakers...
Hyun Jae, congrats.
Even before the show kicked off...
I'll debut too, no matter what.
Make sure we see each other again.
Yeah.
We'll meet again for sure.
- Call me...
- Stay in touch...
With outstanding skill and stage presence...
Mind if I keep in touch?
The sixth member of Wakers...
- Yeah, of course.
- Trainee Kim Hyun Jae...
One more round of applause, please.
Congrats.
You did well.
Now let's hear a few words
from trainee Kim Hyun Jae.
Hyun Jae!
What are you doing here?
Ditched practice.
Is that okay?
Things kick off tomorrow and it'll get crazy,
so I wanted to see your face before that.
Well, you saw it, so you're good.
Anything else?
Nope.
That's it.
Then head back before I call your agency.
Hyun Jae!
Knock it out of the park.
You got this!
This one's a hit.
Almost fell for you.
Whatever.
They really won't give me a break.
Looks like they're squeezing every penny
out of us this year.
They're ruthless.
You feeling okay?
I'm fine. How about you, holding up?
I've got fans now,
the agency's backing me up...
Debut might be around the corner.
We'll share a stage soon, so brace yourself.
Will do. I'll be waiting for it.
[What's up?]
Finally wrapped.
You done?
Yeah.
Did I wake you up this late?
No, just...
Practicing, also waiting for your reply.
You were practicing?
That's rough.
No way, you've got it way harder.
Pretty exhausting, right?
You must be wiped. Go to bed.
You too.
Sleep tight.
[Did you eat?]
Hey, should I try out for a girl group too?
Who am I even talking to?
Why wait around? Just send it yourself!
On second thought, I'll do it!
Give it to me!
[Miss you, Hyun Jae. Don't you miss me?]
Hey, Soo An, are you practicing?
Sorry to say this, but...
the debut lineup timing we discussed
is getting pushed back.
Things are tight at the company.
The CEO is out chasing new investors right now.
So just hang in there.
Okay.
Got it.
And as for practice...
you should take a break starting tomorrow.
Sorry?
We couldn't renew the studio lease.
I'll let you know once we find a new place.
Okay.
- Waker! Hi, we're Wakers.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[Miss you, Hyun Jae. Don't you miss me?]
[You're busy... I'm bu...]
Hyun Jae, congrats.
I'll debut too, no matter what.
Make sure we see each other again.
Things are tight at the company.
[Caller Blocked]
We couldn't renew the studio lease.
[Contact Blocked]
It seems like...
[Mom]
I shook off all those pipe dreams, as you said.
I'm working hard. Don't worry.
Yeah.
Yeah, I will.
Okay, bye.
Gone cold already.
You a zombie?
Done with practice?
[Kim Hyun Jae]
Ugh, it's cold.
Drink it anyway.
You said you can't wake up lately.
Coffee tastes best when it's hot.
Want me to warm it up?
Hey!
Someone might walk in!
Nobody's coming. We're fine.
No, I smell like sweat.
You don't.
Just hold on like this.
Just a moment.
Warm now, right?
This isn't right...
[Hotel LUXE]
You can pay me back...
with your body.
What is going through his head?
This is awkward. Let's head in.
What? You're the one who wanted this.
It looks rough out here,
but inside should be fine.
People are giving us weird looks,
hurry up.
What?
You booked it ahead?
You don't look the type,
but you're really thirsty.
Is this really happening?
Hey!
Wait up!
What was I even thinking?
What brings you here all of a sudden?
If you've got nothing to say, I'm out.
This.
Didn't you leave it for me to see?
Why'd you cut off contact?
Cut off?
Forget it.
We're not the kind to keep in touch anyway.
Then what are we to each other?
Business.
We used each other to get noticed.
You debuted, so isn't that enough?
What?
The whole thing was staged.
What more could there be?
You really feel nothing for me?
In Korea,
there's a tradition when you move in.
- Cheers.
What?
Nothing, you just chug it down.
First glass is one shot in Korea, right?
Some wonderful person taught me that.
Tastes good.
Why are you drinking so fast?
Are you a heavy drinker?
I don't know.
You don't usually drink much,
because it's a Buddhist country?
Buddhism?
No.
I drink like hell.
You learned all the wrong words.
Pretty damn good, right?
Yeah. Damn good.
But that's a bad word in Korea.
You're speaking casually, too.
You're Korean, aren't you?
Pouring your own is bad luck.
I can't leave any drops...
You really feel nothing for me?
I was worried something might still linger.
Good thing there's nothing.
[Episode 4 Preview]
This is crazy!
Why can't I remember anything?
Sleep well?
You...
Did I say anything weird?
I don't know.
I can't speak Korean.
Haven't you milked me enough for business?
Got more uses for me lined up?
Right.
Want me to sleep with you too?
Don't ever show your face again.
Fine.
If that's what you want.