[I miss you, Hyun Jae. Don't you miss me?]
[Delete this message]
Personal phones are prohibited from now on.
If you need a phone,
ask your manager for permission.
You will then use the communal phone.
What, really?
Yes. We've already arranged with your agencies.
But this is too sudden.
I know you've been through a lot.
But...
we can't allow personal mistakes
to interfere with others' hard work.
Not only that,
but the agency,
which is putting all their trust in you,
family, and your fans.
You wouldn't want to trouble them, would you?
We'd appreciate your cooperation.
Are we clear?
Do you really have no feelings for me?
What?
Dangerous...
You!
You're dangerous.
Pay you back with my body?
Usually, I'd just swear you out.
Bam!
That's what I'd do.
Or else, people would...
get the wrong idea.
I can't believe myself!
Darn it!
This can't be!
It was just a few shots of soju!
Why can't I remember anything?
[Exploring Relationships]
[Make teams of two to get to know each other]
In this class, you will pair in twos,
and present on the partnership.
We finished teaming up last week.
The course adjustment period ends today, right?
Who's our newest addition?
Oh, I'm Shin Jae Min.
We already made teams during orientation.
What now?
Is there anyone who would like
to operate as a team of three?
Shin Jae Min? Isn't he from that show?
Didn't he have some sort of controversy?
He's that stalker, right?
Stalker? Where?
I'll do it.
I'll team up with him.
Oh, Mr. Khun.
You signed up from the language center, right?
Perfect, the two of you can team up.
[Sorry, my legs are too long]
Excuse me.
- Is that Kim Hyun Jae?
- Kim Hyun Jae?
I think so.
Go home. Right now.
Can we talk?
There's nothing to talk about.
Will you be here tomorrow?
Why are you doing this?
Why do you keep showing up?
- I'm here to study.
- Nonsense.
I missed you.
Missed me?
You have it easy, don't you?
You just act on your whims.
Who do you think you are?
- Do I look like some pushover?
- Can you not be difficult for once?
What?
Can't you smile for me?
Say hi, stuff like that.
- Why would I do that?
- Why are you so cruel to me?
Kim Hyun Jae!
The show's over.
We're nothing. Nothing at all.
Wasn't it enough, using each other for fame?
What more is there? Oh, I see.
Want me to sleep with you?
If not, leave me alone.
I don't want to see you ever again.
Okay.
If you want it that badly.
Let's never cross paths again.
Did you sleep well?
You...
Now, are you seated in teams?
Let's move on to the lesson.
Yesterday, I...
I didn't say anything weird,
or make any mistakes...
did I?
Mistake.
Did I, like, say weird stuff?
I don't know.
I can't speak Korean.
Wow, playing that card, huh?
Nowadays, personal choices and beliefs...
Are we a...
couple?
Couple?
Now, you will pretend to be married...
to your partner in class.
Then, shall we learn about couples, lovers,
and their relationship to marriage?
[Starting point of marriage: Couple]
A couple is when two people
maintain a close relationship
- Oh.
- emotionally, sexually,
and economically.
Now, let's get to know each other better.
Keep a close eye on your partner.
Find out what they like, and don't like.
So, what do you like, Khun?
Favorite.
You know, Jae Min.
What?
Yesterday, we already showed each other.
Didn't we?
What you're good at...
and what you like.
What?
Jae Min.
Do you have any questions?
No, ma'am.
When did he even stop by?
Acting like he owns the place.
Ah, what the hell!
- Hi.
- What are you doing at my place?
Never mind.
Hey, you're drunk.
Is everything okay?
Anyway.
What got into you? You spent the night out.
Huh?
You're in yesterday's clothes.
What's it to you?
Do you have it going with someone?
I can't tell if it's going well...
or badly.
Well, you slept over. I'd say that's good.
Good for you.
Meanwhile, I'm doomed.
What do you mean?
Hey, did you bump into Soo An or what?
Hey, are you crying?
Hey, talk to me!
Hey!
[Manager]
Hey, it's from work. Take it.
[Unicorn Yung Jun]
A merger?
With Unicorn?
That's right.
You'd know, too.
It's Soo An's agency.
Who would've guessed?
Aren't Soo An and Hyun Jae
supposed to be really close?
No, stop being rude.
Hello.
But that's too far!
What a soulless jerk.
Good, you're here.
Why did you bring me back as a trainee?
I just don't get it.
The company needs you.
What's he doing here?