Bro.
Bro, what are you...
Golden Guard Pan.
Pan Yucheng.
Looks like there's no escaping today.
Bring on whatever tricks you've got.
If I so much as flinch today,
I'm not your daddy.
But you listen to me carefully.
Man acts, and Heaven watches.
Every torture you use on me today,
sooner or later,
will come back on you.
You're tough, huh?
Five taels.
I get a share too.
Why would I give it to you?
Because I bet too.
When did you ever bet?
You weren't even part of our chat.
I said it in my head.
If you disagree, I'll beat the piss out of him,
and you still lose.
Th-this...
I heard your inner voice.
Five taels.
Are you guys even human?
In the middle of the night,
playing "Lights Out" with me here?
Wait, are YOU even human?
The boys have been at it all day,
finally got those corrupt officials sorted out,
and you say we're not human?
Exactly.
We played deaf and dumb for you.
You think it's easy on us?
These men here,
their crimes are countless.
Too many to even write down.
Especially the Imperial Uncle.
The crimes he committed,
warrant a hundred deaths.
Based on all this,
I figure
you've got a shot at surviving.
As for what we can do,
that's all of it.
Someone will come soon,
to take you to face the Emperor.
Once you're at the palace,
you must fight for yourself,
for the best chance to survive.
Seems I misjudged old Pan.
He's actually a decent man.
You...
What "you"?
Alright, stop standing around.
Take him out.
Careful.
Not bad, Chen.
You kidding?
I'm a soldier.
Some soldier.
Who has the absolute nerve,
daring to break into our Inspectorate?
Investigate.
No matter who's behind this,
drag them out for me.
Yes, sir.
Golden Guard Pan.
Are you sure you want to investigate?
Investigate.
The Empress and the Third Prince
both want vengeance for the Imperial Uncle.
Next is the Left Chancellor.
And I killed the Imperial Uncle,
a crime punishable by clan extermination.
The Ning family is wed to the Chancellor.
This may drag in the Chancellor's household.
This is the Imperial City.
At the Emperor's very feet.
If I die at the Inspectorate today,
His Majesty will surely fly into a rage.
Then he'll pour all his focus
into hunting down the killer.
That way,
they'll have a chance to escape blame.
Am I wrong about this?
Ning.
Haven't you noticed
you have a real talent for stirring up trouble?
Brother,
even though you're extraordinarily gifted,
just look around.
Every single person who wants you dead
is some kind of major figure.
Doesn't matter.
If I'm willing to face death,
I'd dare to drag Emperor Xuan off his throne.
Just shut up already.
If you don't want to live,
don't drag your brothers down with you.
Exactly.
Dawn is almost here.
Hurry to the palace for the audience.
Let's go.
Who knew the one who dared behead the
Imperial Uncle was such a young lad.
So Uncle Tianxuan really is Emperor Xuan.
How dare you, Ning Chen!
In the presence of His Majesty,
why haven't you bowed yet?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I have a matter to report.
The Inspectorate was attacked last night.
The intruders had a clear target.
It was Ning Chen.
How audacious!
They dared strike at the Inspectorate?
Do they have any regard for Us at all?
Please quell your anger, Your Majesty.
We have failed in our duties.
Is that all you ever say?
Geng Jing.
Investigate this.
Get to the bottom of it.
We do not care who they are.
We shall execute their entire clan.
I obey Your decree.
Your Majesty.
Ning Chen has not yet been tried.
Very well.
Let the court speak, then.
How should Ning Chen be punished?
Punished?
Will Your Majesty not execute Ning Chen?
Sire, Ning Chen defied the law,
slaughtered the innocent,
and scorned imperial authority.
Any of these warrants clan execution.
I humbly petition:
drag Ning Chen out and behead him at once,
to make an example of him.
Since the court all deems Ning Chen worthy of death,
fine, drag him out and behead him.
Your Majesty is wise.
Uncle Tianxuan.
You're not even going to try me?
That's awfully hasty, isn't it?
Your Majesty.
Ning Chen has indeed committed grave crimes,
but when he set out for Chongzhou,
You bestowed upon him the imperial sword,
granting him the right to execute before reporting.
When did His Majesty give me an imperial sword?
Your Majesty.
The imperial uncle, as royalty,
should have loved the people as his own children,
and cared for them.
Yet he treated lives as worthless,
abducted innocent women,
and made life unbearable in Chongzhou.
Ning Chen had no choice but to slay him.
Had Ning Chen turned a blind eye,
he would have failed Heaven's grace above,
and the common folk below.
He is young and lacked foresight.
Driven by hot blood,
he made the rash move to slay the Uncle.
This old servant believes
there were grounds for his deed,
and the crime does not warrant death.
What's going on?
What kind of act are you two putting on?
We did grant him the imperial sword,
but not to slay royal kin at will.
Your Majesty.
Though the uncle was royal kin,
he was also a corrupt official.
Ning Chen's slaying of him
hardly amounts to scorning imperial might.
Something's off here.
Your Majesty,
Ning Chen is but a lowly Silver Guard.
Why grant him the imperial sword?
Because We deemed him quite talented.
We greatly admired him,
and so bestowed the sword upon him.
But who would have thought
he would disappoint Us so.
Minister Yu,
does Our answer
satisfy you?
I dare not.
What the court does not know
is that days ago,
the strategies against the Tuoluo Kingdom,
along with those brilliant verses,
all came from Ning Chen's hand.
So it was him.
So that's it.
So that's it. Now it makes sense.
I should have realized.
Why else would His Majesty so dote on him?
I'm the real fool here.
However,
the entire court right now
is demanding that We put you to death.
Ning Chen,
have you anything left to say?
This makes things easier.
Your Majesty.
I...
I truly had no choice at the time.
The Imperial Uncle, right before my eyes,
brutalized innocent civilians.
With the imperial sword in hand,
and bearing Your Majesty's grace,
how could I remain unmoved
and stand idly by?
Besides, just consider this:
the people of Zhenyuan County
are all subjects of our Great Xuan.
If left with no way to live, what would they do?
They'd rebel!
Utter nonsense and scaremongering!
In these prosperous times,
how could the people be suffering?
I oversee the nation's lands,
its fields,
its census,
its taxes,
salaries, and all related affairs.
In recent years, the taxes
have always been paid first by Chongzhou.
There's no way the people are suffering there.
You're clearly trying to escape blame,
fabricating facts,
exaggerating claims,
slandering the Imperial Uncle,
and deceiving His Majesty!
Old man,
are you reciting a tongue twister?
Have you ever been to Chongzhou?
Though I haven't been there,
the annual taxes alone make it clear:
Chongzhou's people live and work in peace,
happy and content.
That's bullshit!
You think high taxes alone
prove the people are doing well?
What kind of twisted logic is that?
Did you come to court today
and leave your brain at home?
You...
You, you, you...
Stop pointing that filthy finger at me!
Hearing is doubtful; seeing is believing.
You've never even been to Chongzhou,
so how can you claim
the people there live in peace and joy?
I...
I, I, I...
Go get some sunshine in your spare time.
Get a bit of a tan,
so no one calls you a pale idiot anymore.
Pale idiot?
You... I...
I'm your grandpa!
Can't even speak straight,
how did you even become an official?
And you dare pose as upright
and selfless?
A corrupt dog like you in our Great Xuan
is a sorrow to the people
and a disgrace to the court!
Let me tell you,
people like you meet only one end:
And that is,
"Your name and body shall both be ruined,
while rivers flow on forever."
That's you!