Sis, where are you?
Big brother is here with Master Ning.
We've come to save you.
Imperial Inspectorate, official business!
Tell Hu Qiang to get out here!
Who dares cause such a racket?
This is outrageous!
Master Ning.
He's Hu Qiang.
Who dares call me by name?
By the look of it, we're still in time.
Who are you?
How dare you barge into the Hu residence?
Where is Xiao Mei?
What Mei?
Help!
I don't know.
I don't know where Xiao Mei is.
I don't know!
Still not talking, huh?
Stop!
You...
Who are you?
I am Hu Maode.
Greetings, my lord.
What crime has my son committed?
Take my advice.
Have another son.
As for his life,
I'm taking it.
My lord,
I am a scholar from the seventh year of Rende.
Though with the Imperial Inspectorate,
you cannot use unauthorized punishment.
You broke into my house without cause,
brutalizing my son. This is...
You dare call yourself a scholar?
As an educated man,
is this how you raised your son?
What on earth happened here?
My lord,
the person you're looking for,
two hours ago,
said there was an emergency at home,
and has already left the residence.
You're lying!
My sister never came home at all.
Dare to deceive the Imperial Inspectorate?
If you don't believe me, my lord,
feel free to search the Hu residence.
Trying to stall for time, are you?
Stop!
You madman!
Father, save me!
Save me!
Not afraid I'll appeal to the Emperor?
No one's stopping you.
But are you even worthy?
I'll ask one more time.
Where is Xiao Mei?
She's, she's, she's...
in the well, in the well!
In the well, in the well!
Take me there, now!
Hurry, take him there!
Sis!
Sis, you can't die on me, sis!
This...
This isn't my fault.
She was too headstrong.
She brought it on herself.
My son!
Master, Master, Master!
The Master has fainted!
Are you all right, Master?
Sis!
She can still be saved.
Xiao Mei!
Wake up!
Master.
Is it really you?
It's me.
Thank goodness.
I thought
I'd never see you again.
Sis!
What happened?
She's fine.
She just passed out.
Take this.
Take good care of Xiao Mei for now.
Master Ning.
This is too precious. I can't accept it.
Just take it when I tell you to.
Xiao Mei.
I have to go on a long journey.
I might not be back for a long time.
You must take good care of yourself.
Imperial Inspectorate, official business!
Seal off the Hu residence.
My lord!
Ning, are you all right?
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
You've got the nerve to ask.
We were living it up at the Music Bureau.
Yudie told me you were in trouble.
Good lord.
Didn't even have time to put my pants on.
Ran to the Imperial Inspectorate for help.
Ning Chen, what's the matter with you?
First you killed the royal brother-in-law,
and now you storm a scholar's residence.
Do you have any idea?
He holds an official scholarly rank.
Even if he were guilty,
he must be sentenced before punishment.
Using private punishment like this,
if those treacherous officials find out,
they'll surely impeach you to the Emperor.
Ning, can you stop being so reckless?
Follow some rules, would you?
Rules?
Reckless?
If the one lying here today
were your own family,
would you still stand here
lecturing me about principles?
Xiao Mei may be a humble nobody,
but she treats me best in this world.
When I used to get bullied,
she always stood in front to protect me.
When I was starving,
she always shared the food
from her own bowl with me.
When I was sick,
she stayed up all night by my side,
taking care of me.
So...
Sister,
if the law won't protect you,
I will.
If this world
is destined to be shrouded in darkness,
then I'll be the blade
that cuts through the darkness.
Hu Qiang
got what he deserved.
Silver-Robed Ning upheld the law fairly.
Hu Maode failed to raise his son properly.
Demoted to commoner.
His Majesty is wise indeed.
Next time I see the old man,
I've got to kowtow to him.
Ning,
what's your relationship with His Majesty?
Yeah.
Let's just say it's quite extraordinary.
Practically like father and son.
Could it be...
an illegitimate son?
Don't talk nonsense.
What rubbish.
Ning Chen killing Hu Qiang
was justified.
But now we need a way out
to silence the wagging tongues.
The front lines are dangerous,
but if Ning Chen can return alive,
then he'll have earned military merit.
But, Father,
once he reaches the border...
Guards!
Lord Chancellor.
Do as I told you before.
Yes.
Grandfather,
what are you trying to do?
If only you three brothers had any spine,
why would I have to
stoop to acting against a youngster?
Candied hawthorns!
Want one?
How much, sir?
Two coppers.
Here.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
This one looks pretty good.
You have it first.
Candied hawthorns!
Is it good?
Move!
Out of the way!
Move aside!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What about you?
Seize him at once!
Ning Chen is a good man!
A good man?
He's a lackey of the court.
He kills the innocent without a care.
His crimes are countless.
Ten deaths wouldn't pay for them.
That's a lie!
For the people of Chongzhou,
Ning Chen risked his own head
to slay the Emperor's brother-in-law.
Everyone praises him as a hero.
Enough talk.
Today, I'll grant your wish.
Die together as star-crossed lovers.
Retreat!
Don't move.
Ning Chen!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Take him back to the Imperial Inspectorate.
Interrogate him thoroughly.
Yes, sir.
Move!
My dear Ning, you're hurt.
Let me take you to a physician.
Yudie.
Do you know how dangerous that was?
Why didn't you run away?
Wherever you are,
that's where I'll be.