This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[IQIYI]
[Present]
♫Never met anyone who could make me understand this word♫
♫But when I met you, my heart started beating fast♫
♫You’re the only one in my heart who could make me feel this way♫
♫This long-awaitied moment is now over♫
♫From now on, my heart and soul will be yours for the rest of my life♫
♫Always have each other, never let go♫
♫Trust in me ‘cause I’ll be by your side♫
♫Hold my hand, Baby♫
[Desires in the Wind]
[Previously]
I don’t need you in my life anymore.
I hope you'll understand.
Do you believe me now that you can’t follow the protocol for this matter?
I’m going to keep my promise.
I’ll respect your decision.
Where are we going?
My older sister’s house in Hua Hin.
Don’t you have any cash on you?
Why can’t we just take the bus?
You’ve just arrived and must be exhausted.
Please go get some rest.
Thank you.
Considering Miss Blew’s situation right now, all I could do is hide her somewhere safe.
Your island. Your private island, Fai.
My father said the suspects have been arrested.
Now, we wait for Fah then we’ll go to Fai's private island.
Yes, I plan to feature it in the headlines.
But I need to confirm it with my informant first.
I’ll get it done as soon as possible.
Fah.
Yes?
That news you’ve asked me to write–about a clash between the cops and suspects in Chiang Rai.
It’s done. Do you want me to post it now?
Let me see it first.
Mhm, it’s good. Go ahead and post it.
Make sure to hype up the story, so that people would be keen to know who these suspects are.
Sure.
We’re lucky they tried to cover up the news and didn’t mention anything about the princess’s security team.
But the news is hitting every headline, what if those reporters try to dig up more…
and find out we’ve tried to kill the princess?
Don’t worry.
I already told our men to lay low and don’t make any move during this time.
Not until we can locate the princess.
Good. And make sure those arrested will keep their mouths shut forever.
That’s a punishment for failing their job.
It’s late, what is weighing on your mind still?
I’m merely thinking about Sister.
You and your sister have never been apart this long.
You must miss her so dearly.
That’s not all, Father.
Not only that I miss her, but I’m also worried.
What is it that you’re worried about?
I had a chance to speak with her on the phone, but something about her seemed off.
As if she were someone I barely knew.
She couldn’t recall anything we used to talk about
Did you get me a souvenir from Thailand, Sister?
What is it that you want?
An inhaler. Don’t you remember?
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
Can I get you something from Japan inste
What do you want?
I already told you what I want from Japan.
Don’t you remember, Sister?
I have to go now, Karel. I’ll talk to you later.
All those things we used to talk about, she couldn’t remember anything.
Your sister is probably too exhausted from her hectic schedule.
Please don’t overthink it.
I also hope that would be the case, Father.
According to Madelin’s rules, you will be able to help lighten your sister’s burden of responsibility in three years.
And once she ascends the throne, you can stay by her side as her supreme secretary.
When that day comes, I do hope you will be another great support to help bring further prosperity to our country.
I shall never disappoint her.
F**k!
Find out where that bloody princess is!
Yes, sir.
Miss Blew?
Miss Blew.
Please pardon me.
Miss Blew?
Miss Blew!
Miss Vayo!
I’m over here!
Why did you leave the house without telling me first?
What if anything bad happens?
I just needed a walk.
Please don’t worry about me that much.
I’m fine.
Just having you out of my sight already makes me worried.
I mean, I’m your bodyguard so I must keep watch over you all the time.
I appreciate that.
But please don't let your worry stress yourself out. I’m really fine.
But the weather here is quite hot indeed.
Could you do me a favour, Miss Vayo?
I saw a leaf in there, so I just removed it.
Thank you.
I’m sorry.
Did you just kiss someone?
Aww, looking so flustered.
When did you get here?
Have you fallen for the princess now?
What?
Usually, it’s you flirting and making girls falling for you.
This is the first time I’ve seen you being the victim instead.
Karma is catching up to you.
Stop being delusional.
Hey, not so fast.
You can fool anyone all you like but you can’t fool me.
I see the way you look at Miss Blew.
I can sense there’s definitely something there.
Sense what? Nonsense!
Come eat together, Miss Vayo.
I’m not hungry
But it’s time to eat.
I’m not hungry.
Then, I’m not eating either.
Wait. I’ll eat. Let’s eat.
Why are you standing so far away?
Come closer.
Is that what you call close?
Yes. This is close enough.
What’s wrong?
I think I got dust in my eye.
Please let me see.
Don’t rub it.
Can you blow it?
What?
When I was little and got dust in my eye, Father would always blow it for me.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
I have a question.
Are you still mad at me?
What do you mean?
That time when I said I didn’t need you anymore.
It made you upset.
It’s not about that.
Who would dare to get mad at you?
And that was also many days ago.
I thought so too.
So, if you’re not mad, why are you stepping away?
It’s for another reason.
What is it? Can you tell me?
Rightness.
I don’t understand.
You are a princess while I’m just a commoner.
Between us, there will always be a line that I can never cross.
I still don’t understand.
Is this the line of rightness?
Yes, and I can never cross it.
From now on, I’m afraid you and I…
I’m afraid we…
We…
I will cross that line to be with you.
Yes?
Now, you and I are standing on the same side
Please act normal and be yourself.
I hate it when you treat me like a stranger.
I will cross that line to be with you.
Does the princess’s charm still leave you on cloud nine, Sis?
Are you stalking me or what?
Of course not. I just happen to smell someone in love.
I think it probably comes from here.
Stop it.
Why are you still here?
I thought you said you’d go get things ready for the island trip.
I’m about to leave.
Just want to say bye to you and the princess first.
See you at the pier then.
Be safe.
Hold on, not so fast.
What?
I’m your sibling, Sis.
I can see right through you.
If she’s the one, then just go for it. What are you waiting for?
Aren’t you going to stop me like Din and Nam?
No. Why do we have to create conditions in life that would make ourselves unhappy?
Isn't it better to make the most of every day and be happy with it?
Besides, nobody knows if we’ll even live to see tomorrow.
You’re so lucky to finally find someone you’ve been waiting for. So, just go for it.
Go all in. So that you won’t regret it later.
Are you sure?
The princess already crossed the line, didn’t she?
Were you snooping?
No! I was just looking for you and didn’t want to interrupt.
Let’s just say, no matter what you decide, I’m always here to support you.
Thanks.
Just promise me that you and Miss Blew will stay safe.
Can you do that?
Sure. Thanks a lot for your concern.
Who’s concerned?
You, of course.
Don’t get emotional.
I really can’t deal with this version of y
- Come on, Little Sis.
- Geez, go away!
- Give it a try.
- No way!
- No way! Don’t do it. What’s got into you?
- Give it a try.
Come on, just try it.
Let’s go.
Get off me!
Thanks a lot. I’m so touched.
Nobody knows if we’ll even live to see tomorrow.
You’re lucky you’ve found that person you’ve been waiting for.
So, just go for it. Give it your all.
Today, I’ll teach you how to use a gun.
So that you can use it to protect yourself in case of emergency.
I’ll do my best so that I can protect you too.
You don’t have to protect me. It is my job to protect you, Miss Blew.
You’ve sacrificed yourself for me.
I want to do something for you too. Please let me do it.
Let’s begin, shall we?
Try holding the gun in a position that you feel most comfortable.
Keep your finger off the trigger.
Now try to aim at the target.
You’ve never used a gun before.
Let’s not do it with one hand. It’s dangerous.
Use both hands to make it steady.
So that when you fire, it would be more accurate.
Okay, got it.
Good.
Now, let’s try shooting it.
So that you’ll learn the force when the gun fires and kicks back.
Don’t be scared. I’m right here.
For the first shot, I’ll help support the gun for you just to be safe.
Please allow me.
Relax, don’t be afraid.
I’ll count to three.
After that, you can pull the trigger.
One, two, three.
Let’s call it a day.
I’m tired now.
Just shooting for the first time, why is my heart beating so fast?
Sorry, are you the Princess of Madelin?
No, I’m not the princess.
Can we take a picture with you, please?
No taking pictures. Stop!
Of course, you are!
Please, stop!
Stop! I said stop!
Wait!
- Please wait.
- Please stop! Stop!
Please.
Put that away now! It’s illegal. I could sue you.
Oh, okay. Sorry.
Please delete all the photos.
Oh Okay.
- I deleted them already.
- Sorry about it.
- Sorry.
- Have a nice day.
Let's go.
I’m sorry.
Don’t worry about it.
Will the photos get out?
I don’t think so.
Hey, Lom.
Fah! You’re early.
This is Fah, the reporter cousin I told you about.
Hello.
My informant in Madelin said King Arthur is still safe.
There’s no sign of rebellion there.
And no one knows about the fake princess either.
If Sir Antione still hasn’t made any move by now, I’m afraid this is only Grace and Henri’s doing.
Then, should we find a way to inform King Arthur?
I’ve asked you to come because I have a way to do that.
But I might need your help.
How?
I’d like you to deliver my letter to Prince Karel.
But how can she do that without drawing anyone’s attention?
Usually, Karel will pay his friend in France a private visit every month.
We can secretly contact him during that time.
Please give my letter to Karel there.
Once Karel reads it, he will surely find a way to send help.
I’ll prepare everything for you.
Okay, I’ll go to France…
and hand your letter to the Prince myself.
Thank you.
It’s my pleasure.
Is that Madelin language?
Wouldn’t it be dangerous if those criminals get the letter?
This is the royal family’s secret language.
Only those in the family would understand.
Which means only Father and Karel can understand it.
Do you want to learn it, Miss Vayo?
I can teach you.
Maybe not. I’m not part of the royal family.
But you saved my life. You’re someone the royal family remains grateful for.
Come and sit here.
Please pardon me.
You can just teach me some words,
so that we can use them to contact each other in case of emergency.
What should I teach you then?
‘I’ is like this.
This is ‘You’.
What about ‘Princess is safe’?
‘Princess is safe’ is like this.
Like this.
[Princess, run away.]
If I write you this word, you must run.
Okay.
What does this word mean?
It means ‘Love’
You’re so lucky to have found someone you’ve been waiting for. So, go for it.
Just go all in.
What does this mean then?
[Love Princess]
Lom.
I’m here to take the letter.
I’ve just finished writing it.
This is Sebastian’s address, the Prince’s friend.
If Sebastian doesn’t believe you, please show him the clip I recorded for you.
Yes.
I’m counting on you.
Please don’t worry. I’ll get everything done as fast as I can.
Thanks a lot.
It’s nothing, Sis. No need to thank me.
Are you going to Fai’s island tomorrow? Have a safe trip then.
Are you leaving today?
Yes, I think so.
But you’ve just arrived.
Didn’t you want me to help?
Have a safe journey, Miss Fah.
Thank you.
Are you done packing everything, Miss Blew?
I don’t have much to pack.
Then, should I take you to buy more things before we get on a boat?
It’s all right. What you’ve given me is quite enough.
I’m afraid not. We’ll be going somewhere quite deserted.
No shops or restaurants there.
If you don’t buy it beforehand, you might have a hard time there.
Aren’t we going to Miss Fai’s house?
Not her house but her private island that Uncle Ak, Fai’s father, bought for her.
What business is he doing? Why did he need to buy an island?
Well, there’s mining, palm plantation, and also rubber plantation.
Pretty much everything a businessman can do in Surat.
But if I go there, will it cause people on that island any trouble?
Please don’t worry.
It’s a private island–only a few fisherman families live there.
You can only get there by boat.
If those goons try to come to the island, we’ll know right away.
I really can’t picture what it’d be like.
Are you sure they’re here?
Yes, from those photos I saw on social media, it’s definitely here.
They’re staying further back in a VIP zone.
Be discreet and don’t draw any attention this time.
Yes, sir.
Hold on.
Miss Nam told me to bring you some snacks, Miss.
I see. Thank you.
Excuse me, what is my older sister, Fai, doing?
She’s already in bed, Miss.
Thank you.
Miss Blew, wake up. Miss Blew.
What happened?
They’ve found us.
The pills should have their effect by now.
Let’s go.
You go downstairs. And you, upstairs.
Wait.
They know we’re here, but probably haven’t gone that far.
Search the whole place.
That’s it. Come and get more tomorrow.
Sure.
Thank you.
Yeah. Is that all? Make sure to recheck it.
It’s all right. You’re safe now.
Hey! The towels are already here.
Why don’t you unload them?
Lom!
Lom! It’s really you!
I miss you so much!
It’s really you in the flesh! I miss you so much!
Hi, Buahima.
Oh my gosh, you remember me?
Do you know that after you left,
I couldn’t eat or sleep for months?
I’m sorry.
I forgive you but…
Really?
Yes.
You’re naughty!
Oh, by the way, why are you here?
I’m here to catch the criminals.
I’m on a secret mission.
It’d be safer for you if you don’t know about it.
Hold on, are you hurt anywhere?
Tell me if you’re hurt anywhere.
Oh, are you hurt anywhere?
My precious Lom. My sweet baby, you’re safe now.
I’m so worried about you.
Yes.
So, who’s this girl that looks less pretty than me?
She’s my colleague.
We’re working on a mission together.
Your colleague?
Buahima, can you possibly find someone to drop me off in Surat Thani?
If that’s what you want, I can always make it happen.
It’s a top secret though.
Got it, top secret.
Aww, you’re as lovely as ever.
Please wait here. I’ll get it done for you in a jiff.
Thank you.
Kiddo! I need to use one of the cars.
Give me one.
You’re so popular, Miss Vayo.
It seems you have an admirer in every province.
Oh, not that much.
So, almost then?
Let’s go.
Fai!
Lom!
Go get the boat ready.
Yes, Young Boss.
What’s the situation at the resort?
Nam said she found traces of intruders there.
There were probably 3-4 of them.
But Nam already told the police to collect whatever evidence there is.
They’ve found us much faster than I thought.
The boat is ready, Young Boss.
Do we have to get on this boat?
Yes, are you okay with it, Miss Blew?
I’m fine. I’m just surprised. I’ve never travelled on a boat like this before.
Lom, this is Yod.
Hello.
Yod will take you to the island.
Once there, Uncle Boonsong will come to pick you up.
One more thing, there’s no phone signal on the island.
If there’s any update, I’ll let you know through Uncle Boonsong.
Or tell him if you need anything.
He’s coming ashore every weekend.
Okay.
Take care of them for me, Yod.
And don’t you ever tell my dad about this.
Sure, Young Boss.
I’ll never let the Master know about this.
Come, let’s get you on a boat.
Take care, Lom.
See you later.
Let’s go.
This way, Miss.
Are you okay, Miss Blew?
I’m good.
But you don’t look so well though.
Smell this. It might help.
Miss Blew! Miss Blew!
Are you all right?
Miss Blew, are you okay?
Please hang in there. We’re almost at the safehouse.
Oh, you’re here?
Paka!
Yes?
Hi, Uncle.
Hello there.
Come in.
Please come in.
Hello.
Hello, girls. Come on in. Come and sit down.
This is Uncle Boonsong, a village chief on this island.
And this is Phaka, my wife.
Hello.
And my daughter–hey, kiddo!
Yes, Dad?
Come here, quick!
Geez, Dad. I’m working.
This kid and her endless whining.
My daughter.
Hi, I’m Bua.
Another Bua?
May I know your names?
I’m–
Phatpha.
Her name is Phatpha. But you can call her Phat.
What about you, Pretty girl
I’m–
Wind.
Wind–that’s a beautiful name, don’t you think so, Mum?
Young Boss already told me everything, so please don’t worry.
We’ll take really good care of you.
If you need anything, you can always tell us.
Or if you need an errand, Bua can also do it for you.
That’s right. I’m at your beck and call for 24-7.
Any time at all.
It’s very nice to meet all of you.
Yes.
We’ve arranged a place for you to stay but it’s quite far–at the end of the beach.
But it’s very private.
Quiet and not so many people there.
Too bad there's no phone signal there.
If you want to contact someone onshore, just come to my house.
You’ll get a full signal there.
Thank you so much for taking the trouble to arrange everything for us.
Oh, it’s my pleasure.
All of us here are so grateful to Young Boss and the Master.
We’re more than happy to help.
Yes.
Hey, Darling.
What?
Take Miss Wind and Miss Phatpha to their house.
It’s okay, Mum. Just stay here and rest.
Let me take care of it.
Okay. Bua will take you there then.
Please follow me. Be careful too. Please watch your step.
Why is she so hardworking?
I don't know either.
She hardly tells us to be careful.
The weather is really nice today.
Maybe because you’re here, Wind.
We’re almost there.
Please watch your step.
There you go, this is your house.
Miss Fai told us to have everything arranged for you.
Thank you.
If you need anything, just let me know. I’m happy to help.
Thank you so much, Miss Bua. We’ll take it from here.
We’d rather not bother you any further.
Oh, it’s not a bother at all. I want to help.
Well then, I should get going. Remember, I’m at your beck and call for 24-7.
Please go ahead.
I’m off then.
Call me if you need anything.
I can come anytime.
You certainly are very charming, Miss Vayo.
So, this is how people on an island live.
Do you think you can make do with it?
Of course, it’s much better than the fruit and vegetable trucks I used to sleep on.
You’re quicker to adjust than I thought.
We might need to stay here for a while so let’s agree on some rules.
What rules?
While we’re here, we must address each other with our new names so that we’ll get used to it.
Sure. So, I’ll call you Wind and you can call me Phatpha–
the name you’ve given me.
Yes.
Then, you have to drop the ‘Miss’ and just call me by my name.
And talk to me normally. Don’t think of me as a princess.
If not as a princess, then what should I think of you?
Well, as a…close friend!
Fine. Close friend.
Sure.
Any other rules?
While we’re here,
we have to blend in with the people here as much as we can.
So that no one will suspect us.
Okay, I’ll try to blend in as best as I can.
Then, let’s start with…
Can you eat Southern food, Phatpha?
I’ve never eaten it. But I’ll give it a try.
Great! This one is Fermented Fish Entrails Soup.
Sour Soup.
Stir-fried Stink Bean with Prawn.
Stir-fried Malindjo Leaves with Egg.
This one is Sun-dried Squid with Spicy and Sour Seafood Sauce.
Wanna try it?
Why is it so spicy?
That one is probably too spicy for you. Let’s try this one.
I like this one the most.
Then, have the whole dish.
This one too. It’s not spicy.
Aren’t you eating, Wind?
I’ll eat the rest.
They actually look delicious. But I don’t like spicy food.
Tomorrow, I’ll tell Aunt Paka to make an egg menu which is not spicy for you.
Sorry to trouble you and everyone. I’ll try harder to adjust to it.
You’ve done a great job so far.
Eat as much as you like so that we can fight the traitors.
You too, so that you’ll have enough strength to protect me.
I'll return the dishes after we finish eating.
If you want to take a shower, please go ahead.
Okay.
Do I really have to shower here?
It’s cold.
Phatpha!
What’s going on? What’s wrong, Phatpha?
I’m fine.
Why did you scream then?
The water is cold.
Okay, water is cold.
I’m done setting up the mosquito net. Let’s sleep.
I’ve never slept in a place like this.
The vibe is actually quite nice.
Aren’t you going to sleep, Wind?
I’ll sleep downstairs.
Come sleep here together.
Together?
How could I let you sleep downstairs when I’m the one who has put you into all these troubles?
But it’s not appropriate.
But here, I’m Phatpha–not a gracious princess from somewhere.
You’re the one who told me that, remember?
I remember.
While we’re here, I’ll think of you as my close friend.
Just a close friend?
Pardon?
Nothing.
I want to get some rest now.
Why are you still outside?
Can I just sit and nap here?
No, it’s time to sleep.
Sweet dream.
Goodnight.
You seem to like it here.
I love being here.
Being Phatpha makes me experience freedom for the first time in my life.
I can throw away the royal title I was born with, even for a short while.
And live like a commoner.
I want to learn about this.
So that in the future, I can rule with empathy and understanding.
Then, feel free to be yourself while you’re here.
Be Phatpha that nobody knows who she is or where she is from.
I’ll be Phatpha the way I want her to be.
And I’ll be Wind the way I want.
Your kind of Wind, what is she like?
I’ll just…do whatever my heart says.
I will…
I’ll…
[Next Episode]
Why didn’t you invite Bua to eat with us too?
I prefer to be with someone I like.
Pretty Miss Phatpha, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Does Win have a girlfriend or someone she likes yet?
If so, I’ll back off. But if not, I’m going to pursue her.
You traitors! I’ll have all of you executed!
What are you doing?
Hey! Don’t touch me!
Last night, I just got drunk and fell asleep, and didn’t do anything weird to you, did I?
You passed out the moment your head hit the pillow.
Was I dreaming?
Was it a good dream or a bad dream?
Good dream, I guess.
♫ I wonder which star it is that guided me to meet you ♫
♫Or is it destiny that has brought us together♫
♫You’re like the wind, carrying me to the sky♫
♫No matter how high, I won’t be afraid♫
♫ Only you is enough, I don’t need anything else ♫
♫ust us together is enough, you’re the meaning in my life♫
♫Every day from now, please stay by my side♫
[Desires in the Wind]
♫and we’ll always have each other♫
[North Star Entertainment]