[Chu Tae Jeong]
Tae Jeong is a cop.
You can never escape him.
You spared Chu Tae Jeong
just because he's a cop?
Luckily, I found out right before
the execution and stopped immediately.
Things are getting annoyingly complicated.
Are you sure he really thinks
you're Heo Dong Hwa's brother?
Yes, I'm sure.
It's been so long since he saw him
that he doesn't remember his face.
Then keep pretending to be Heo Dong Jin
and let him go without him noticing.
You need to get this job done flawlessly
if you want to be heard, don't you think?
Are you really going down to Dongcheon?
That case closed ten years ago.
The evidence was solid.
Your father's car was found in the reservoir.
[Reservoir]
How did I fall into such a deep sleep?
You're awake?
Are you going to have breakfast?
Want some too?
Sure, I'll go wash up quickly.
By the way, Dong Jin.
Did Dong Hwa call you?
It's like he's dead, you know?
Did you sleep well?
You look tired.
It must've been chilly last night
without a blanket.
Right, the blanket.
Thanks.
You must've felt inconvenienced yesterday
because of me, right?
No, not really.
I'll just leave if we don't hear
from Dong Hwa by this evening.
What's that sound?
It sounds like it's coming
from outside, right?
Outside?
Doesn't it sound like it's coming from below?
Is there a basement in this house?
The ventilation fan is acting up.
It keeps making weird noise as it spins.
Where is the ventilation fan?
Sounds like it needs fixing?
I'll help you.
It's fine.
I can take care of it myself.
Dong Jin, let me return the favor
at least for letting me stay.
Can you see inside the fan?
They say usually something gets stuck between
the filter and the motor, causing the noise.
Oh, is that right?
I heard they're building
a resort in Dongcheon.
They're leveling the mountain over there
to build a golf course.
The population here will grow, right?
Is that why you got assigned
to Dongcheon Police Station?
No, I volunteered.
- But how did you know I'm a cop?
- Well...
I saw the uniform in your closet.
Why did you volunteer?
My father was a detective
in Dongcheon's violent crimes unit.
I want to follow in his footsteps.
Is he retired now?
He passed away ten years ago.
He committed suicide.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Actually, I don't believe it.
My father wasn't the type to
make such a choice, leaving me behind.
That's why I came.
I want to know what happened
before Dongcheon changes.
How can you be so sure?
The day after my father passed
was my birthday.
He had even reserved a restaurant
for us to have dinner together.
He wouldn't have made that kind of choice.
Didn't you tell this to the police
investigating the case back then?
I did.
No matter how much I said
it was strange, no one would listen.
They said the evidence was clear.
I brought up
such a heavy topic out of nowhere.
I must've felt very comfortable with you.
Investigate it thoroughly.
Huh?
You said it's important to you.
Why do you smile like that?
Actually, you're the first person
who's ever said that to me.
Thank you.
Go wash up now.
I'll clean up and head back in.
Okay.
"Final past due notice"?
[Final Past Due Notice from Jungjin Bank]
Where on earth is Dong Hwa?
This isn't why I gave you that.
I guess you're not hungry enough.
Is Tae Jeong still alive?
I told you to answer my questions, didn't I?
So he's still alive, isn't he?
How come? You should've locked him up too.
You can't harm him because he's too cute?
That's none of your business.
Do you really think Chu Tae Jeong
isn't suspicious of you at all?
You're a stranger
staying at his friend's house.
Hey, stop talking nonsense.
Tell me where the cell phone is.
If I tell you, then what?
Try me.
Let me have a smoke too.
A smoke?
You're dangling it in front of me.
It's driving me crazy that I can't have one.
If I let you, then what?
If I tell you,
you'll spare my life at least, right?
Make up your mind by today.
Where did you go?
I had some quick errands to run.
Dong Jin, you don't like loud noises, right?
It's okay.
Play it.
What are you making?
Let's have dinner together.
I actually brought it for Dong Hwa.
Dong Jin, do you like shrimp?
Huh?
Not sure. I've never tried it.
What?
But Dong Hwa loves shrimp, you know?
That's so odd. How is that possible?
How is it?
It's good.
Isn't it?
I've made pasta like a thousand times.
How come?
Because I spend a lot of time alone.
When you're alone, instant noodles or pasta
is the easiest to make.
You wouldn't know the loneliness
of eating alone, would you?
I do.
How do you know?
When I was young,
I spent a lot of time alone too.
What did you usually do when you were alone?
I exercised.
Repeating the same routine every day.
Did you draw those around that time too?
What?
Actually, I looked through your sketchbook.
You're really good at drawing.
Have you ever taken lessons?
It's just a hobby I do on my own.
Then why not take proper art lessons?
Your skills are too good
to waste as just a hobby.
That sort of thing doesn't suit me.
I've been told that a lot too.
"Can someone like you really be a detective?"
"Aren't you just going to
get caught by criminals?"
Things like that.
But I think you really have talent.
Even though I don't know much about art,
I sensed that as soon as I saw your drawings.
It's not that good.
I especially like your ocean drawings.
Where is it?
Faroe Islands.
Have you been there?
They are islands in Northern Europe.
I just drew them from a photo.
Then why don't you go see them
for yourself sometime?
Why would I go there?
Just to draw?
What do you mean, "just to draw"?
I'll buy that drawing from you.
Before its value goes up.
You're exaggerating.
I talked too much, didn't I?
At least you know.
It was nice to see you again, Dong Jin.
Dong Jin!
I'm going now.
Are you already asleep?
Dong Jin, say hi to Dong Hwa for me.
Dong Jin?
Are you asleep?
Dong Jin.
Are you not feeling well?
You have a fever.
Are you allergic to shrimp?
So you really hadn't tried it before.
This isn't good.
Let me get you to the hospital.
No, not the hospital.
What do you mean? Look at your condition.
I said no.
I'll be fine after a little rest.
I'm calling 911.
Jeez, good grief.
Dong Jin.
Dong Jin, I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were allergic.
But... it was delicious.
You were sleeping so deeply
so I didn't want to wake you up.
I think me being here
was inconveniencing you,
so I'm leaving without saying goodbye.
It was fun even though it was a short time.
How could he leave without saying goodbye?
It does look amazing indeed.
So it is you, Chu Tae Jeong.
Chul Jin? Are you on duty?
Yeah. Hey, if you're here,
you should've called me, man.
I'm your senior at work now.
Sorry, I've been out of it.
I was kidding, you punk.
Jeez, you're still so uptight.
How will you survive at work?
Where are you staying now?
At a motel in town.
Rough times.
The dorm will be fixed soon,
so hang in there for a few more days.
The Seoul office didn't make a fuss
about you coming here?
Not really.
Even if they did, it is what it is.
You're right.
I put in a good word for you with our chief.
I told him you were my buddy from home
who's super smart.
Thanks.
Anyway, I was already planning to bring it up
when we met.
You can't just stir things up here
like you did in Seoul.
Don't mess around, got it?
What did I stir up?
I was just investigating a case
that needed to be looked into.
Tae Jeong.
Don't you know
what kind of place my hometown is?
It's quiet, isn't it?
People are living peacefully here.
Don't go poking around for no reason
and drive down the land prices.
Just do what you're told.
I can take care of myself.
Your business becomes my business.
That's why I'm telling you this, you punk.
By the way, since you got here,
you've been staying at the motel?
No, I was at Dong Hwa's place.
But where on earth
did that punk disappear to?
I haven't heard from him.
You're right. He hasn't answered
my calls either, you know?
So you were alone at Dong Hwa's place?
No.
I was with Dong Jin.
Who?
Dong Hwa's brother.
Heo Dong Jin.
Darn you, why are you
playing such a sick joke?
What are you talking about?
Jeez, you're a lunatic.
Dong Jin died last year.
You've gone too far
with your jokes, you punk.
Don't you know
Dong Hwa's still messed up over that?
Did you see a ghost or something?
Who were you staying with?