Who is it?
Can I... help you?
Mr. Heo Dong Hwa?
Yes, that's me.
Can I help you?
Yes, I'm about to handle it now.
Stop. Abort the operation.
Huh?
Heo Dong Hwa has a phone containing evidence.
The mayor ordered us to retrieve that phone.
Then...
They say he hid the phone
somewhere in his house.
Should I wait?
Find the item first.
Until then, don't kill Heo Dong Hwa.
There should be a secret passage
leading to the basement of the house.
Lock up Heo Dong Hwa there.
It's a secluded place,
so no one should be coming.
But be careful not to be seen by anyone.
But have you given some thought
to what I mentioned last time?
This doesn't seem like the right time
to bring that up.
Don't you know how important this task is?
Then when can I get an answer?
Take care of this task flawlessly first.
Then we'll meet in person and talk.
Okay, I'll see you soon.
Dong Hwa, I'm home.
Are you in there?
I'm coming in.
Heo Dong Hwa.
Who are you?
Don't tell me...
Are you Dong Jin?
No?
You're Dong Jin, right?
- Who...
- I'm Tae Jeong, Dong Hwa's friend.
Don't you remember me?
Tae Jeong?
Dong Jin, it's been so long, you know?
Has it been 10 years
since you went to the States?
No, it must be more like 15 years, right?
It was really hard getting here.
Did you come here alone?
Walked all the way without a car?
Yes, I took the bus and got off,
and then walked from there.
By the way, when is Dong Hwa coming back?
Didn't Dong Hwa tell you I was coming?
No, he didn't tell me anything.
I got a job in Dongcheon.
There's a problem with the company dorm,
so I can't move in for about a week.
I talked to Dong Hwa,
and he said I could stay here.
That's an arrangement
between you and Heo Dong Hwa, isn't it?
It doesn't seem to have
anything to do with me.
I'll just wait quietly here.
Since we agreed to meet here,
I should just wait for him.
By the way, Dong Jin,
you really don't remember me?
We were quite close.
Is it because we were too little?
Actually, if I saw you on the street,
I probably wouldn't recognize you either.
Is it okay if I sleep on the sofa?
Dong Hwa said it's okay
for me to stay in the living room.
No.
As I said, the arrangement between you
and Heo Dong Hwa has nothing to do with me--
It will get dark soon, won't it?
What if I go out and meet someone strange?
I even talked to him this morning,
so he should reply soon.
But where did he go?
An unexpected situation has arisen.
A person named Chu Tae Jeong
showed up at the house out of nowhere.
He seems to be an old friend of Heo Dong Hwa.
He mistakenly thinks I'm Heo Dong Jin,
Heo Dong Hwa's old brother.
It's going to be difficult to proceed
according to the plan.
Since my face has been exposed,
I'll temporarily suspend the operation.
I'll get rid of him first thing tomorrow.
Dong Jin.
Don't you know how to knock?
Oh, right. I should've knocked.
May I come in?
- For what?
- Well...
Dong Hwa said
he'd leave a blanket for me to use.
I was wondering if you knew where it is.
- I don't know.
- Then, may I look for it?
It wasn't in the living room.
Wait.
I'll look for it.
What?
Is this your room, Dong Jin?
Where does Dong Hwa sleep?
What?
It seems like this house
only has one bedroom.
Oh, Dong Hwa sleeps in the living room.
You don't think
anything happened to him, right?
I still haven't heard from him.
Maybe something urgent come up.
It's not in here either.
Just... use this to sleep.
What about you?
It's okay. I'm fine.
Do you want to play catch?
I'm having trouble sleeping.
What does that have to do with playing catch?
Moving around and sweating
might help me fall asleep.
This is the signed ball I gave you as a gift.
Back in elementary school in Jamsil.
Don't you remember?
It's the home run ball.
I gave it to you before you left as a gift.
I know.
The ball signed by Lee Dae Ho.
Of course, I remember.
But it's not Lee Dae Ho.
It's Lee Dae Hyung.
Don't you know how rare
a Lee Dae Hyung's home run ball is?
I'm disappointed.
Are you really Dong Jin?
Okay, fine.
By the way, Dong Jin,
you seem to have become really quiet.
Is that so?
But I like quiet people.
Since I'm more the talkative type.
Yeah, I'm more comfortable listening too.
But Dong Jin, did you
come back from the US for good?
Yes.
That's good.
I was really upset
when you suddenly left like that.
Actually, I gave you that signed ball
because I wanted to be friends with you.
Let's hang out more.
Okay.
By the way, when did you come back to Korea?
Dong Hwa didn't say anything.
Well... It was not long ago.
Why did you come back?
I wanted to start fresh.
Welcome back.
Dong Jin, it seems like
you're getting your old skills back.
I'll throw it properly too.
You call that a proper throw?
Are you okay?
I think I broke my bone.
I'll get some ice.
Dong Jin!
You're still so gullible.
I'll go wash up first.
Sorry.
Got your message.
Someone came by?
Yes.
As I said earlier,
I'll send him away tomorrow...
Kill him tonight.
Pardon me?
Who told you to stop the operation?
You don't have that authority.
Just do what you're told.
Oh, Dong Jin!
Can't you keep it down a little?
Sorry.
But can't I just listen to this one song?
Shut it.
Okay.
Go inside.
Sleep in the bed.
Huh?
The sofa is uncomfortable.
No, the owner should sleep in the bed.
I can sleep anywhere
as long as I lay my head down.
But in the living room,
it will be hard to fall into a deep sleep.
I'm really fine.
But if that's what you prefer,
I'll do as you say.
Dong Jin!
Good night.
Why aren't you replying?
I'm with Dong Jin.
But Dong Jin...
As I said, the arrangement between you
and Heo Dong Hwa has nothing to do with me--
It will get dark soon, won't it?
What if I go out and meet someone strange?
Use this to sleep.
What about you?
It's okay. I'm fine.
You're still so gullible.
Why is he so cute?
It makes me want to tease him.
I almost felt a little flutter...
[I almost felt a little flutter...]
What's this?
Is this Dong Jin's?
Hey, Heo Dong Hwa.
You know Chu Tae Jeong, don't you?
Chu Tae Jeong?
Tae Jeong is here?
Answer the question.
He's my oldest friend.
What does he do?
[Chu Tae Jeong]
Tae Jeong is a cop.
You can never escape him.