Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Did We tell you to rise?
Kneeling again? What's going on?
Ning Chen.
We have a question for you.
Is this Music Bureau really that fun?
Your Majesty, didn't you say you wouldn't interfere
with the Imperial Inspectorate going to the Music Bureau?
Why are you giving me a hard time?
It's fun, of course.
Then tell Us about it.
How exactly is it fun?
Just how much fun is it?
Your Majesty,
at the Music Bureau,
I met a girl named Yudie.
Her beauty could topple kingdoms,
truly a peerless beauty.
Her temperament is so gentle,
and her voice is so lovely.
And the best part is,
she's the real deal.
But Your Majesty, you...
We what?
Well...
What's with that look?
I feel sorry for Your Majesty.
I think Your Majesty is rather pitiful.
Ridiculous.
We rule all under heaven.
What's there to pity?
With a brush, Your Majesty pacifies the realm,
and on horseback, you settle the world.
Unmatched in both governance and warfare,
your achievements will last forever.
Truly an emperor for the ages,
a peerless wise ruler.
The only pity is,
you've never seen a real beauty.
Ning Chen!
Don't talk nonsense.
He's truly talking nonsense.
We have three thousand beauties in Our harem.
Which one isn't a beauty?
Your Majesty,
what I'm about to say will offend many,
but I simply must speak my mind.
When daughters of nobles are sent to the palace,
they have money and connections.
With a few bribes here and there,
when Your Majesty picks a tablet each night,
their tablets
just happen to be in the most visible spot.
But those girls from poor families,
some of them are truly beautiful.
Just because they have no money,
their tablets
will never reach Your Majesty's eyes.
Even if they grow old and die in the palace,
they'll never see Your Majesty their whole lives.
They're done for.
That's how palace dramas always go.
Is what Ning Chen said true?
Your Majesty,
this is an unwritten rule of the palace.
Then how come We didn't know?
Did you take bribes?
I beg Your Majesty's discernment.
This servant would never dare.
As expected, I'm so clever.
Guards!
Here!
Please calm your anger, Your Majesty.
I think
over such a trivial matter,
if Your Majesty harms your royal health out of anger,
it wouldn't be worth it.
Why don't I take Your Majesty to the Music Bureau?
The twelve houses of the Music Bureau,
every single girl is as beautiful as a flower.
Except for Nanzhi and Yudie, of course.
Your Majesty, take your pick, choose freely.
It's on me.
This kid has lost his mind.
You...
What kind of person do you take Us for?
A real man.
Although Your Majesty is the Son of Heaven,
you're also a healthy man.
All of Great Xuan belongs to Your Majesty.
A visit to the Music Bureau isn't too much, is it?
By the way,
Your Majesty wouldn't even need to pay, right?
Of course not.
You know, what you're saying makes some sense.
No time like the present.
Let's prepare to depart for the Music Bureau now.
I... I...
Such vulgar words.
No sense of romance.
Your Majesty.
This is a new weapon invented by Ning Chen.
It's tremendously powerful.
I came specially to present it to Your Majesty.
What is this thing?
A musket.
It fires iron pellets at incredible speed.
I consider my martial skills decent,
yet I couldn't even track its movement.
We are well aware of your skills.
How does it compare to a crossbow?
Stronger.
Faster.
Excellent.
Then demonstrate it for Us.
Your Majesty, please step outside the hall.
No need. Demonstrate it right here.
How filthy.
Then I must trouble Eunuch Quan.
Thank you.
Eunuch Quan, stay your hand!
We are unharmed.
Let go.
Let go of me!
You wretched eunuch!
Your skills are so impressive.
You've been hiding them well.
Ning Chen wielded a strange object.
He nearly harmed His Majesty!
You made this thing?
Yes.
Come. Let Us take a look.
Not that.
Lift your head up.
We want to see your neck.
Come here.
Such a vicious blow.
You scoundrel!
It happened so suddenly, a momentary slip.
Ning Chen.
Eunuch Quan acted out of loyalty to protect Us,
and in his haste he wounded you.
Do not hold it against him.
We know
you've long wished to leave the Ning estate.
How about this:
When you return from the border,
We shall grant you a manor,
a hundred acres of land, and ten thousand taels of gold.
How does that sound?
And what if I die at the border?
Who curses themselves like that?
Blades show no mercy,
Your Majesty.
If by chance
something truly happens to me
and I cannot return,
I beg Your Majesty to permit
Lady Yudie of the Music Bureau
to be restored to freedom.
The manor Your Majesty promised me,
along with the land,
please bestow upon Lady Yudie.
As for the gold,
please grant it to my brothers,
and let them divide it.
You truly are a man of loyalty and affection.
You've arranged it all quite nicely.
But We will not agree to it.
On the contrary,
if you fail to crawl back alive to see Us,
then We shall take that
beloved Lady Yudie of yours
and have her killed to join you below.
A sovereign does not jest.
I...
I... well...
Is this gun easy to make?
It's easy.
But only easy for me.
For others, well,
without knowing the principles,
even if they make the parts,
if they can't assemble them,
it's useless.
What if We demand you hand over
the methods for its production and assembly?
This thing here
was always meant as a gift to Your Majesty.
Your Majesty may select a portion of the troops,
arm them with muskets, and form a firearms corps.
Muskets are devastating against cavalry.
With a single bullet fired,
I guarantee twice the result for half the effort.
It seems you've already planned
to use this against the Tuoluo cavalry.
Yes indeed.
Good.
Then We approve it.
But have you considered,
if this weapon is leaked,
the consequences would be unthinkable.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
By then,
I'll have built even more powerful firearms.
It seems
this isn't the only one you've mastered.
At such a young age,
brimming with talent,
full of wit and resourcefulness.
We were just thinking,
if you'd been born in an enemy state,
you would be
Great Xuan's most terrifying enemy.
A gentleman dies for the one who appreciates him,
and a woman adorns herself for the one who loves her.
Your Majesty's discerning eye discovered me,
and gave me such a grand
stage to showcase my abilities.
I am deeply grateful,
and shall keep it engraved in my heart.
For Your Majesty, I am willing
to climb mountains of blades and seas of fire,
to brave any peril,
and would not hesitate even if it meant ten thousand deaths.
Good.
Well said.
You may withdraw.
I take my leave.
Shipeng.
Do you realize
that this firearm
is a lifesaver for Great Xuan's mighty army?
A boon for the present,
and a legacy for the ages.
That silly lad,
he didn't even think to ask Us for a reward.
Hasn't he just joined the Imperial Inspectorate?
He probably hasn't received his stipend yet.
Then bestow upon him a hundred bolts of fine silk
and a thousand taels of gold.
How does that sound?
Ning Chen has a youthful temperament.
Might he grow arrogant from such favor?
Arrogant? Let him be arrogant.
For a once-in-a-century talent like Ning Chen,
even We feel proud on his behalf.
Now go, quickly.
As you command.
A mere youngster like Ning Chen,
yet he's turned the capital upside down.
It seems
I truly underestimated him.