My lord.
My lord! My lord!
Are you all right?
Your bodies and names will perish,
but the river flows on for eternity.
Well said!
Ning Chen.
Everything you have spoken of
is merely your one-sided account.
How are We to place trust in you?
Your Majesty, I beg to report.
The Chongzhou officials have confessed.
Please review them, Your Majesty.
Are these still officials of Da Xuan?
They're nothing but a pack of beasts!
Inventing pretexts, disregarding lives,
forcing decent women into prostitution.
Their crimes are too numerous to list.
How dare they act so recklessly!
Your Majesty, they deserve death!
Your Majesty,
for such acts,
only their deaths can appease the people.
We beg Your Majesty to issue the decree
and give the people of the realm justice.
We second the motion.
Minister Qian,
you just said
the people of Chongzhou lived in peace.
Your Majesty,
I was momentarily confused.
I beg Your Majesty for mercy!
Confused?
Just how much did you take from them?
Guards!
Throw Qian Xingguo into prison.
Imperial Inspectorate, investigate the Ministry of Revenue at once,
and prosecute all involved in the Chongzhou case.
I obey the decree.
Your Majesty, spare me!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
I believe
the Imperial Uncle enraged heaven and men.
Ning Chen's offense doesn't warrant death.
I beg Your Majesty to show mercy.
Your Majesty,
Ning Chen acted to defend royal honor.
I also feel he does not deserve death.
Your Majesty,
Ning Chen excels in both letters and arms,
brimming with talent.
He may truly be the Poet Immortal reborn.
He will surely become a pillar of Da Xuan.
If we execute him today,
it would be a great loss to our literature.
I implore Your Majesty for leniency.
I second the motion.
What a fine performance indeed.
Truly worthy of Your Majesty.
This round,
I've lost.
Left Chancellor,
you are head of all officials.
What is your view on this matter?
I beg to report, Your Majesty,
I believe
the other ministers are absolutely right.
Though Ning Chen slew the Imperial Uncle,
there was due cause.
He deserves a lenient sentence.
The Left Chancellor makes a fair point.
It seems justice lives in people's hearts.
Ning Chen.
I have a few words
I'd like to share with all the ministers.
The salary you receive,
is the people's flesh and blood.
The common folk may be easy to oppress,
but heaven cannot be deceived.
We are all subjects,
living on the sovereign's salary.
We must fulfill our duties faithfully
and ease His Majesty's burdens.
That flattery he just dished out,
is on a whole other level than mine.
Well said!
Ministers, bear Ning Chen's words in mind,
and do not disappoint Us again.
We shall engrave them in our hearts,
and not fail Your Majesty's grace.
Ning Chen,
although the ministers all plead for you,
you struck down the Imperial Uncle,
slighting the royal family's dignity.
The death penalty may be spared,
but your crime cannot go unpunished.
What's he up to now?
When we discussed saving him in the study,
this wasn't part of the plan.
The Tuluo Kingdom often raids our borders.
This matter is like a stubborn disease.
Your previous strategy was effective,
but it is not a permanent cure.
If you can devise a way
to keep our border safe this winter,
We will not only pardon all your crimes,
but also reward you.
Ning Chen,
are you willing to redeem through merit?
A newborn calf fears no tiger.
The entire court has no solution.
What can a mere youth possibly do?
The cavalry of the Tuluo Kingdom
has long been a grave threat to Us.
If you are unwilling to go,
We shall not force you.
When that time comes,
We shall have no choice
but to lead a Personal Campaign.
Your Majesty, this must not be!
Your Majesty.
The battlefield changes in an instant.
Your priceless body
must not be put in harm's way.
Please rescind this decree, Your Majesty.
Ning Chen.
His Majesty is someone who,
With the pen, he brings peace to the realm;
on horseback, he secures the empire.
What the hell is the Tuluo Kingdom?
Are they worth a Personal Campaign?
That would be flattering them too much.
Your Majesty.
This subject
is willing to go to the frontier.
If I fail to handle the Tuluo Kingdom,
I vow never to return to the capital.
Excellent.
Then We shall await good news here.
Court is dismissed.
Long live Your Majesty!
Ning Chen.
Drop by my residence sometime.
I'll be sure to visit when I'm free.
Old General Chen.
Thank you for helping me today,
otherwise I'd be done for.
Thanking me with mere words won't do.
I want fine wine from Zhuangyuan Tower.
As much as you can drink.
Lord Ning.
Congratulations.
You've raised your son well.
I must seek your advice someday.
My useless son
can't do anything right,
and only knows how to eat.
Truly, like father, like son.
Lord Ning has brilliant literary talent,
and your son is even more gifted.
How enviable.
You flatter me.
I thought he was as good as dead,
who knew he'd be the Poet Immortal reborn.
Skilled in both letters and arms.
He's finally brought me honor.
Chen'er.
Come here, come here.
Are we that close?
A scumbag who abandons wife and children,
yet you have the nerve to cozy up to me.
My lords,
I have some matters to attend to,
so I'll be taking my leave.
Goodbye.
I'm getting on in years,
I really shouldn't be walking backwards.
Well...
Lord Ning's lawful wife
is the Left Chancellor's daughter.
Why talk of 'abandon wife and children'?
I heard Lord Ning has three sons.
Which one of them is Ning Chen?
I've met all three of Lord Ning's sons.
There's no Silver Guard Ning among them.
Lord Ning,
who is Silver Guard Ning's mother?
I never heard you took a concubine either.
Indeed.
Farewell.
Farewell, farewell.
Damned bastard.
Utterly disgraceful.
If rivals know I abandon wife and children,
and impeach me,
with His Majesty's favor toward Ning Chen,
my days as Minister of Rites are numbered.
The old ginger really is the spiciest.
Old General Chen,
I have plenty of ginger and chili at home.
And undiluted wine too,
as much as you'd like.
I must visit and taste them someday.
Absolutely.
Greetings, Old General Chen.
Greetings, Crown Prince.
You two chat.
Crown Prince, do you need something?
Congratulations, Ning Chen.
Do you know that your acquittal this time,
besides Father's mercy
and the ministers' pleas,
also owes thanks to Princess Huai'an?
Princess Huai'an?
She actually pleaded for me?
I asked her to.
After you slew the Imperial Uncle,
Father was in a foul mood for days.
I didn't dare approach him,
so I had Princess Huai'an plead for you.
You didn't dare go,
so you pushed your own sister out there?
Let's go.
A debt for saving your life
is best repaid in person.
I'll take you to her.
I'm coming to catch you!
Princess!
I caught you!
You stink so bad!
This girl's doing it on purpose.
I just haven't bathed for a few days.
You reek!
What's wrong with you?
Did you fall into a latrine or something?
So young,
yet your tongue's so sharp.
Say that again, I dare you.
He was in the Imperial Inspectorate prison.
He was only pardoned and released today.
He hasn't had time to bathe or change.
A bit of an odor is unavoidable.
Brother Crown Prince,
what brings you here today?
You pleaded for Ning Chen earlier.
He came today especially to thank you.
Thank you for speaking up, Princess.
Well, tell me,
how do you plan to thank me?
I have no power or influence,
and truly nothing worthy to offer.
If the Princess doesn't mind,
let me treat you to a meal.
As if I need a meal from you.
But I'm so poor,
what could I possibly offer the Princess?
You're not as handsome as my royal father,
nor as tall as my royal brother,
and as for personality,
compared to mine,
yours falls far short.
But they say you're brilliantly talented.
How about this?
Write a poem for me.
What?
Am I not worthy of one?
You're worthy, absolutely.
You!
The Princess is worthy.
I was just deep in thought.
You really want a poem on the spot?
Let me warn you,
if you dare to slack off,
I'll have you caned.
That's right, Ning Chen.
You're known as the Poet Immortal reborn.
If the poem you give Princess Huai'an
fails to please her,
your Poet Immortal title
will be ruined.
That won't happen.
Princess, please listen well.
Clouds long for her raiment, flowers for her face;
Spring breeze caresses the rail, dew-drenched with grace.
And the next two lines?
If not seen atop the jade mountains' crest,
Then 'neath the moon on Jasper Terrace she'd rest.
What a magnificent poem!
The Poet Immortal reborn, indeed.
So beautiful, Ning Chen.
How does that little head of yours work?
How can you write such beautiful poetry?
Besides,
am I really as beautiful as you describe?
You're making me blush.
I don't see
a hint of a blush on you.
As long as the Princess is pleased.
Ning Chen,
can you write a poem for me too?
Come on, come on.
Have you no shame?
The Princess is a young lady,
so a poem to please her is fitting.
A grown man like you wants a freebie?
Your Highness,
my inspiration is exhausted today.
How about another day?
Fine then.
I'll keep this in mind.
You owe me one poem.
Attendants!
Quickly write down Ning Chen's poem.
I want to show it to Father.
Yes.
Greetings, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
What brings you here?
By order of the Empress,
I'm to summon Silver Guard Ning.
Me?
What if I don't go?
You must.
When the Empress summons,
you must go.
Don't worry.
I'll accompany you there.
Your Highness,
the Empress instructed
that she will see Ning Chen alone.