Your Majesty.
Ning Chen defied the law and executed him.
By law, he must be beheaded.
Your Majesty.
I impeach Minister of Rites Ning Ziming.
He failed to discipline his son,
who committed a heinous crime.
He should face the same punishment.
Your Majesty.
I impeach Geng Jing of the Imperial Inspectorate.
Ning Chen serves under him.
He allowed his subordinate to commit murder,
slaughtering royal kin. By law, he must be beheaded.
I second the motion.
I second it as well.
This is big trouble.
How did I father such a wretch?
Silence!
A pack of fools chasing their own fame.
Can they not see
that His Majesty is losing his patience?
Ning Chen is already being escorted back to the capital.
Let us wait until he returns to discuss this.
For today,
that will be all.
Your Majesty.
This old minister has a memorial.
Ning Chen killed the Imperial Uncle.
This is an undeniable fact.
By law, it warrants Extermination of the Nine Clans.
Fool.
My dear Minister Yu,
your service over the years has been great,
but now you are advanced in years.
Are your ears failing you?
that you cannot even hear
Our words clearly?
If you are unwell,
We can let you retire to your hometown.
To think Imperial Father favors Ning Chen
to such an extent.
Old General Chen, Geng Jing,
follow Us to the Imperial Study
to discuss this matter.
We obey, Your Majesty.
Last night,
the Empress fainted crying here many times.
Speak, both of you.
What shall We do about Ning Chen?
Your Majesty, a report.
What bastards!
To be imperial kin, yet so brutal.
Worse than pigs and dogs.
Those are all Our people!
The bark on nearby trees was stripped clean.
The people were driven to cannibalism.
How dare they be so brazen!
Is Da Xuan still Our Da Xuan?
Ning Chen,
even a youth of twenty understands
that water can carry a boat, but it can also sink it.
Yet they, well-read in the classics,
and feeding on the sovereign's salary,
have the audacity to treat Us this way.
They deserve death.
Every last one of them deserves death.
Judging by His Majesty's words,
he intends to protect Ning Chen.
Your Majesty.
Though Ning Chen killed the Imperial Uncle,
he had his reasons.
His crime does not warrant death.
This old minister agrees.
As royal kin by marriage, the Imperial Uncle
should have obeyed the law
and set an example.
Instead, he preyed upon the people,
slaughtered the innocent,
and treated lives like dirt.
If the people are left with no way to survive,
we all know the consequences.
He was driving the people to rebellion.
That is treason, Your Majesty.
But the Imperial Uncle
is, after all, the Empress's elder brother.
If We do not execute Ning Chen,
how are We to answer to her?
Unless there is some way
to smooth this matter over.
We cannot think of one.
There's no rush.
We have plenty of time.
You may stay here and take your time to think.
Pour the tea.
Enough.
Pour.
Father.
What's happened?
My lord.
What on earth is going on?
Father.
What has upset you so?
That unfilial son!
Ning Chen...
has killed the Imperial Uncle!
My lord.
Is that true?
Ning Chen killed the Imperial Uncle in Zhenyuan County.
He is now being escorted to the capital.
But that is the Empress's elder brother!
This is disastrous.
This warrants Extermination of the Nine Clans!
We are all finished.
Ex... Extermination of the Nine Clans?
Then...
we are included in the nine clans!
That damned Ning Chen!
I should have killed him back then!
My lord.
Come with me to find Father.
Let's go.
Go. Yes, yes.
I already looked for him.
When court was dismissed,
I went to see my father-in-law.
He told us to wait for news at home.
But this matter is far too grave.
It involves the Empress herself.
No one can save us now.
I fear even your father cannot.
We are all going to die!
Not one of us will escape.
Mother!
Father!
Father, please think of something!
Call the physician, quickly!
Aren't you the Minister of Rites?
You must be able to find a way!
Father!
I'm still young!
I don't want to die, Father!
I don't want to die either, Father!
Father!
Ninth Princess,
Why don't you sit down
and we'll push you instead?
Yes, Ninth Princess.
Let's go back to your room.
It's fine. Come push me, quickly.
Hold the rope tight. Slow down!
Brother Crown Prince!
Greetings, Your Highness.
You're here just in time.
Come push me!
Brother Crown Prince,
why do you look so unhappy?
Did Imperial Father scold you again?
It's all right.
You're always being scolded by him anyway.
Ning Chen stood up for the people of Zhenyuan County
and beheaded the Imperial Uncle.
What?
Then Imperial Father should reward Ning Chen.
Let me tell you,
I saw that Imperial Uncle in Mother's palace.
A brainless, fat, and sleazy pig.
And a lecher, too.
He harassed one of my maids,
so I gave him a piece of my mind.
It's not as simple as you make it sound.
However bad he was, he was still imperial kin.
Imperial Father should decide his fate.
Ning Chen beheading the Imperial Uncle
is a crime warranting Extermination of the Nine Clans.
That serious?
Huai'an,
Imperial Father is in a terrible mood right now.
Usually,
Imperial Father dotes on you the most.
Seeing you
might improve his mood a lot.
That's true.
Brother Crown Prince, aren't you coming?
I...
I have important matters to attend to.
I will take my leave now.
Oh, and...
if possible,
put in a good word for Ning Chen.
I don't want to bother with that annoying guy.
That previous cell
was small and gloomy,
damp, and full of rats.
We two brothers
specially moved you to a bigger one.
The bedding is all new.
See that wooden bucket?
We bought it for you to soak your feet.
Ningzi, if you need anything else,
just tell us brothers directly.
I'm just afraid we won't get another chance later.
Do you even know how to talk?
What? What chance?
Chenzi,
just stay here for now.
Golden Guard Pan has gone to gather information.
There's still a chance.
A chance.
What chance is left?
Actually, Old Feng is right.
The only pity is,
I promised to take you both to the Music Bureau.
You'll just have to go by yourselves.
My lord, the cell is ready.
Go, go, go.
The Old General has arrived.
Greetings, Old General.
Old General.
I told you, time and again,
to show the imperial family
the proper respect.
It seems
you only paid lip service,
and didn't take it to heart at all.
Every word you said, Old General,
I have kept in my heart.
But if you, Old General,
had seen the suffering of the people of Chongzhou,
I believe you would have done the same as I did.
Do you regret it?
I have no regrets.
You've got guts, kid.
This is wine and roast chicken from Zhuangyuan Tower.
It's the only thing I can do for you now.
You may leave.
Yes, sir.
Old General, I beg you,
save the people of Zhenyuan County.
To root out Chongzhou's corruption,
killing one Imperial Uncle is not enough.
The truth is, I've already gathered
evidence against every official in Chongzhou.
But now that I'm trapped in prison,
my hands are tied.
I can only beg you, Old General,
to restore justice for Chongzhou's people.
You have evidence?
Then why didn't you bring it out sooner?
I don't trust anyone in the Imperial Inspectorate.
But I trust you, Old General.
This evidence
concerns the very lives of Chongzhou's people,
and it implicates officials in the capital,
as well as the current Empress.
Old General,
do you dare to take it on?
I've spent my whole life on the battlefield.
What storms haven't I weathered?
What I lack is a leg,
not courage.
I knew I hadn't misjudged you.
You little brat!
Is that how you speak to your elders?
Come, have some chicken.
Come, Old General.
Here.
Cheers!
You little brat!
This time the wine really isn't watered down.