That reckless boy.
We tried every way to clear his name,
and what does he do?
He had evidence and didn't show it sooner!
What?
Doesn't he trust Us?
Laugh, laugh, laugh.
He trusts you most, alright?
Shipeng.
Your Majesty.
Send men to Zhenyuan County
to find the evidence Ning Chen mentioned.
Verify whether it's authentic.
If confirmed,
arrest every official in Chongzhou,
and bring them to the capital for trial.
If anyone resists or obstructs,
execute them on the spot.
Yes.
Old General Chen.
The poem that boy wrote in the prison cart,
have you heard of it?
A poem?
Listen carefully.
We shall recite it for you.
A thousand strikes carved it from the mountain deep,
Through raging fires it stands unflinching.
Though crushed to dust, it bears no fear at all,
To leave its purity upon this world.
Listen to that! Look at this!
If he weren't an immortal reborn,
how could he, at his age,
possess such brilliant talent?
Send people to spread these poems,
but don't reveal who wrote them yet.
Yes.
Oh, by the way,
did the Crown Prince plead for Ning Chen?
The Crown Prince said not a word.
Such a fool.
This was the perfect moment to win hearts.
Truly,
he really worries Us to death.
Look,
even Huai'an knew to plead for Ning Chen.
Why did Huai'an suddenly plead for Ning Chen?
Could it be the Ninth Princess didn't want
a young talent like Lord Ning to be executed?
It would truly be a loss for our Daxuan.
No way.
I know that silly girl too well.
She couldn't possibly think that deeply.
Counting the years,
Princess Huai'an must be nearly 18 now.
Could it be...
Your Highness, we've reached the capital.
Your Highness.
Finally back in the capital.
Stuck in the Weilong Army camp every day,
it was so dreadfully dull.
Once we return to the manor,
you two
must help relieve my fatigue properly.
Your Highness, rest assured.
We shall serve you well.
Good.
Your Highness, something big has happened!
Imperial Inspectorate Silver Robe Ning Chen
beheaded the Imperial Uncle in Zhenyuan County.
The Empress has fainted from weeping several times.
What?
Where is that what's-his-name Chen?
In the Imperial Inspectorate's dungeon.
To the Imperial Inspectorate!
Remember to wake me up tomorrow morning!
So you're Ning Chen.
He's not here on friendly terms.
I'm talking to you. Are you mute?
No, I'm not.
My name is Ning Gan.
Ning Gan, huh?
Your Highness.
He is Ning Chen.
How dare you!
You dare deceive me at death's door!
Striking down the Imperial Uncle,
defying the dignity of the royal house.
Today, you shall pay in blood.
Your Highness.
This guy's a prince?
Open the door.
Yes.
Your Highness,
I must remind you,
this is the Imperial Inspectorate.
Are you sure you want to do this here?
What of the Imperial Inspectorate?
If I kill a lowly Silver Robe like you,
would Father really execute me?
You killed my uncle,
leaving my mother in tears every day.
If I don't kill you today,
I'd be unworthy as a son.
Today, I'll use your head
to honor my uncle's spirit in heaven.
Who's there?
Geng Jing.
How dare you!
Daring to defy your superior,
and raise a hand against me!
It is my duty.
You'd protect him?
Ning Chen has yet to be tried.
If he dies here,
I cannot answer for it.
And what if I insist on killing him?
As long as I stand here,
he will not die.
Your Highness,
Geng Jing is highly skilled.
We are no match for him.
This is the Imperial Inspectorate's prison.
Trespassing here is already a grave offense.
If matters escalate further,
the Empress could be implicated.
Geng Jing,
are you certain you'd offend me
for his sake?
Imperial Inspectorate serves His Majesty.
Fine.
We shall see about this.
Are you all right?
Lord Geng, you're impressive.
Upright and unafraid of power.
I truly admire you.
However,
that prince is quite the fool.
Storming the Imperial Inspectorate to kill?
Isn't that
twisting the tiger's tail?
The Third Prince is the Empress's only son,
and the Crown Prince's greatest threat.
What a powerful background.
So the Crown Prince isn't the Empress's son?
As long as the position remains open,
anyone has a chance.
It doesn't matter.
Lord Geng, when will you sentence me?
So eager to die?
Stuck in this sunless place every day,
keeping company with Xiaoqiang,
I'd rather you just end it quickly.
Who is Xiaoqiang?
Xiaoqiang isn't a person.
And you won't be one much longer either.
His Majesty will have you torn apart by six horses.
Six horses?
Aren't you supposed to be exceptionally gifted?
The Third Prince trespassed in the Imperial Inspectorate.
His Majesty is furious.
To protect the Third Prince, the Empress
agreed not to pursue Ning Chen.
But the order from above is clear,
Ning Chen must die.
Don't worry.
I have my own plans.
There's nothing left to squeeze out of Chongzhou.
Cut ties when we must.
But those above still need plenty of silver
to maintain connections.
For this matter,
I trust the Left Minister will see to it.
Understood.
I take my leave.
Chongzhou, built up over many years,
gone just like that.
Ning Chen!
Even grinding your bones to dust
won't quench my hatred for you!
I'll love you even in death!
Torn by six horses is for the best!
I crossed over to this place,
The Imperial Uncle was a total disgrace,
Only I have the most handsome face!
Not a bad life, eh?
Wine and meat,
and a little tune too.
You big beasts, one and all,
greetings!
It's been quite a while.
Enjoy the Imperial Inspectorate's dungeon?
Back when you were brutalizing the people,
did you ever imagine this day?
Take it back.
Come on.
Throw them in.
Open up.
Pretty spacious.
Pan Yucheng, what's the meaning of this?
We're out of cells.
Don't give me that nonsense.
The cell next to mine is empty.
So is the one across.
If I say there's none, there's none.
What's this Pan up to?
Locking them in with me, does he want—
Pingzi, Ah Zheng,
keep a close watch on these prisoners.
Don't let them
brawl among themselves.
Understood.
I'll love you even in death!
Sir!
You can't lock me up with him!
He'll kill me!
That's right, sir!
Please move us to another cell.
I beg you, sir!
"Brawling"
means a private brawl.
My esteemed lords,
we meet again.
Surprised?
Shocked?
Oh, by the way,
my dear lords,
don't you all love a good tune?
Today I'll sing one for you.
Only thing is,
this dump has no pretty girls.
You'll all just have to make do.
N-Ning Chen!
You... you...
I haven't been tried yet.
I haven't been convicted.
I'm still an official.
Lay a hand on me and I'll report you!
Lord Ai, what a comedian.
I'm already condemned to death.
What good would reporting me do?
Hack at my grave one more time?
This—
These two lords—
Aren't you going to stop him?
Yes, sir!
How did I go blind?
I can't see a thing.
Why is it so pitch dark in here?
Sir!
Old Feng!
Old Gao, what did you say?
Old Gao! Old Feng! Old Feng!
Sir!
I can't see, Old Feng!
Old Gao! Old Gao!
Sir!
Don't go, sir!
You can't just abandon us!
Sir, come back!
I'll love you even in death!
Torn by six horses is for the best!
Let us out, sir!
We're in here!
He's really going to beat us to death!
Let us out!
You can't abandon us, sir!
Aren't you going to do something, sir?
Help us!
Take this!
Spare me! Spare me!
You all know how to sing it now?
Yes, yes, yes!
I'll love you even in death!
Torn by six horses is for the best!
I crossed over to this place,
The Imperial Uncle was a total disgrace,
Only you have the most handsome face!
Not bad.
Old Feng.
Take Ning Chen away.
Yes, sir.
Move.
Hey, wait.
What's that supposed to mean, Old Feng?
The prisoner has been brought in.
Brothers!
Hard at work, huh?
Look how late it is.
And you're still here pulling overtime.
Look at my poor brother here, so tired
he can barely keep his eyes open.
Yet still standing so straight and proper.
Still as cold and aloof as ever.
Why's your rope still this long?
Been hitting the bottle hard again lately?
Your beer belly's back, huh?
Why work at this hour anyway?
There's no overtime pay.
Why hang around this godforsaken place?
Go get a late-night snack,
have some drinks,
hit up the entertainment quarters.
Smooth-talking little punk.
Watch your attitude.
Take a good look at where you are.
Where is this?
Isn't this just the Imperial Inspectorate?
What kind of attitude do I need?
My attitude
is to look out for my brothers' 9-to-5.
Still running your mouth?
Guards!
Take him down.
Pan Yucheng, you're serious about this?
What did you expect?
Chenzi.
This is bad.
Apply the torture.