I'm exhausted from being with you, Takahito.
Please forget about me.
I enjoyed our time together.
Feeling better now?
Sorry. I'll move out
as soon as I find a place to stay.
I told you, you don't have to rush.
Okay, here it is.
Enjoy.
Thanks.
Shiori, you're forcing that smile,
aren't you?
Huh?
You don't have to act tough in front of me.
Yeah.
But make sure you eat something at least.
You have a baby inside you.
Thank you.
Thanks for the meal.
As long as you find happiness, Shiori,
nothing else matters to me.
I feel the same way...
if it means Takahito can be happy.
Good morning.
Morning.
Shiori, where were you yesterday?
At Yuna's place.
Sorry for worrying you.
Hey.
Tonight...
- Can we talk...
- My things.
I'll come get them when you're not around.
[Episode 8]
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Oh, Shiori. Did the CEO
say anything about the orders?
No, nothing.
I see.
I guess the project's
really getting canceled.
Even though we've come this far.
I'm sure it'll be okay.
The CEO is doing his best too.
Let's focus on what we can do.
You're right.
Okay, let's get to work!
What? Takahito came to you too?
He noticed I was steering him
into marrying you.
Is that so...
But I never thought
that boy would be so foolish.
When I started the Seko Group,
they said it'd be impossible,
and that I had no backing.
I struggled and fought back.
But it's different for him.
The fortune I built...
The position I earned...
He gets it all without any effort.
He has no idea how blessed he is,
or how fortunate
this marriage arrangement with you is.
He understands nothing.
Not even what kind of outcome
marrying that girl will bring.
It'll be fine, Chairman.
Takahito knows it all in his head.
It's just that
his heart hasn't caught up yet.
Eventually, his heart will follow.
- Let's go drinking.
- No, let's work.
Let's go, I really need it.
Are we really going?
I wonder if the CEO is okay.
They still haven't found a factory
for that project.
They're out of time.
I heard he hasn't been coming
to the office at all lately.
I guess rich heirs don't handle crises well.
Yeah.
Your muscles are so stiff.
I see.
It's Asakaze again...
Got it.
Thank you.
Don't get hung up on trivial things,
whether it's work or people.
It ruins the quality.
Damn it!
The clothes made by Seko's team
have cute designs,
and they're particular about their materials.
I think that kind of success
requires true commitment to his work.
Hey, you're enjoying the night view with me,
so lighten up, will you?
Rena.
Could you back off already?
Back then, when our parents
decided we were engaged,
you didn't care.
So why are you getting in the way
of my marriage now?
Are you satisfied
with just doing what our parents say?
No.
My family's not why I'm marrying you.
This is what I want.
You know...
Ever since I was born,
I've been expected to act like an heiress.
And before I knew it, that became normal.
Then, at some point,
I stopped knowing who I really was.
The truth is...
I was always scared.
Like I was being swallowed up
by the Asakaze family.
But...
you were the only one who noticed how I felt.
That's because you went through
the same thing, right?
Born into the Seko family,
you suffered just like me.
Whenever I see you,
it's painful for me.
Like I'm looking at myself,
forcing my way through.
You're the only one...
in the whole world who would say that to me.
Hey, Takahito.
I can understand your feelings.
I can be there for you,
better than she ever can.
Takahito.
I...
fell in love with you.
From the moment we met.
I don't want to imagine a life
where you belong to someone else.
Please.
Marry me.
This looks good.
So this little one's finally mine, huh?
I can't leave it
at Takahito's place forever, you know.
It fits the shop's atmosphere too.
But...
it looks a little down.
[From Takahito Seko: Meeting notice.]
[Sorry for the short notice.
Please gather in the planning room at 10.]
Everyone, I apologize
for making you worry for so long.
At long last,
we're ready to continue the project.
Really?
That's great!
Um, what happened with the orders?
Another team is handling
the production orders.
What I want all of you to do
is to put all your energy
into developing new products.
Thank you again for your hard work.
Thank you.
This is what I wanted.
I thought this is what I wanted.
Why am I...
[Two months later]
Your motto: "comfort that makes
everyone love themselves."
It's not limited to women, is it?
That's right.
Ultimately, our project aims to reach
people of any age and gender
to bring them joy from wearing our clothing
and changing how they see the world
just by wearing our clothes.
My project team and I share that vision.
Look. It's the CEO again.
[An inside look at the future of Style Web]
You're right.
With this many interviews,
it's no wonder he hardly shows up here.
True. We haven't seen him in months.
Well, it's a little lonely,
but our products are selling like crazy,
so we can't complain.
Oh, Haruka. Slacking off again?
Oh, sorry.
Here's the revised proposal
for the slimming jacket.
Could you check it?
Got it.
And where's the maternity wear material list?
- Oh, I'll bring it now.
- Thanks.
Phew.
Let's pick out some fabric.
Ever since that day,
I've thrown myself into the project.
Hey, what do you think of this fabric?
[I've been wanting a design like this!
Best cost-performance. Perfect balance!]
[It made my figure look better!
I love my side profile.]
So many people love our clothes now.
That's what keeps me going.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Rena? Why?
I'm the one asking questions.
I'm asking why you haven't married Takahito.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Isn't the CEO marrying you?
Huh?
I mean, the reason the project started again
was because he accepted your offer.
Wait, he didn't tell you anything?
No way...
Takahito. He turned me down.
What?
Please.
Marry me.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Do you like her that much?
Rena,
you said that I was the only one
who understood you, right?
For me, that person is Shiori.
Shiori is the only one
who sees me as Takahito Seko,
not as an heir.
I can't imagine being with anyone but her.
I'm sorry.
Then what's going to happen to the project?
At this rate, you'll drag everyone down.
As for the project,
I'll make sure it succeeds.
Takahito said that?
I think Takahito
desperately looked for factories
just so he could reassure you.
To prove his love to you.
All for me?
Don't make that face.
Takahito turned down
an amazing woman like me
and chose you, so remember that.
Give me this.
Here.
I have a meeting with Takahito here later.
Go in my place.
Huh?
I don't mind
if you don't like him back anymore.
But if you don't talk to him properly,
I'll never forgive you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Just go. Hurry.
Hey, Shiori, listen to this...
Huh?
Oh, welcome.
Oh, hello.
Um...
I'll have a cup of coffee then.
Oh, we don't serve coffee here.
Takahito...
for my sake...
You have no worth?
That can't be true.
I want you to recognize
your own charm more.
No matter what happens,
I promise I'll protect you.
From the very beginning,
Takahito only ever thought of me.
And yet I...
CEO!
Shiori?
Long time no see.
CEO, we need to talk.
Are you prepared to go through hell
for Takahito's sake?
Just as my wife once did.
Please lend me your strength.
Please marry me.
I love you too.
Let's be happy together.