You two, stop fooling around.
So many people have shown up.
Let me tell you,
with this many Imperial Guards here,
this is no small matter.
Ning Chen.
Well, if it isn't handsome Quan.
Not attending His Majesty in the palace?
Out for a stroll, are we?
Silver Guard Ning,
you've been quite hard to find.
Eunuch Quan, let me explain.
Too much explaining is a dead giveaway.
Don't use your smile
to mask the fear you feel toward me.
Tell me,
where are you hurt?
Hurt?
Silver Guard Ning.
I meant, are your injuries all right?
Me?
My injuries?
You could say I'm hurt,
or you could say I'm only slightly hurt.
It's all my fault,
I was too reckless.
You call that reckless?
That was a blatant assault on me.
Well...
Look,
this... this blatant wound,
is it any better?
I have quite the temper, you know.
Don't think giving me a few things
will calm me down.
You... you...
Feel any better?
Better now?
How about this?
Has your anger faded?
A misunderstanding! It's a misunderstanding.
You were acting for His Majesty after all.
I completely understand.
Long live understanding!
Actually,
there's one more matter
I'd like to trouble you with, Eunuch Quan.
Speak freely.
Speak, speak.
Please help me deliver these
to the Ning Manor.
I'll see to it at once.
Rest assured.
Good.
Guards!
Old Pan.
What is it?
What's all this about?
What's going on?
What do you mean?
You're treating me like a dog too?
What? I'm no lapdog.
Let me tell you,
Ning Chen.
You...
You've been at the Inspectorate a while now.
This month's wages haven't been paid yet.
I don't need it.
You...
Keep it for yourself.
We're brothers, don't stand on ceremony.
The gold's for you,
and the silk's for Lady Nan Zhi.
Old Pan,
I'll be honest,
at first I really disliked you.
But after spending time together,
I realized you're actually
a pretty decent guy.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Tonight, the Music Bureau,
my treat.
Why do you never learn?
I'm a Golden Guard of the Inspectorate.
If I go to the Music Bureau with you daily,
how would that look?
Fine, don't come.
I'll go with them.
Ning Chen!
I didn't say I wouldn't go.
We've got to knock off work first, right?
Right?
Nan Zhi.
Nan Zhi likes green.
Knock off, knock off, let's knock off.
Mother, look.
Truly,
all this fine silk and satin,
we really are a family.
We could never spend all this.
Chen'er,
keeping all this money on you
surely isn't safe.
Let your father look after it for you.
Right, Fourth Brother.
All this silk, satin, and gold,
let's put it in the storeroom.
It'll be safer.
It's not safe.
These are imperial gifts.
Who'd dare steal them?
This money,
I'm going to use it to take a wife.
Whoever dares lay a hand on it,
I'll chop their hand off.
Wait a minute, Chen'er.
Don't you have a sweetheart
at the Music Bureau?
Lord Ning's quite well-informed.
So it's true.
I'm warning you,
I will absolutely not let some courtesan
step through our gates
and disgrace the Ning family name.
Yu Die may be a courtesan,
but she's pure and untainted.
Compared to you, who does nothing but sneer
and scheme with petty malice, Madam,
she's far better.
You scoundrel, you!
Ning Chen!
How dare you speak to your mother like that?
Ning Chen,
your mother fed and clothed you all these years,
and in the end,
this is how you repay her?
My lord, just look at him.
Does he even see me as his mother?
You're defying your elders,
this is utterly unfilial!
Fine. If Yudie can't enter the Ning Manor,
then I'll follow Guo Qiling's example.
I'll let her marry me instead.
I'll move into her household.
Who the hell does Guo Qiling think he is?
I'm laying it down right here, right now,
these things belong to the Ning Manor.
That whore
will never set foot in the Ning Manor.
After all that talk,
you just want these things, don't you?
You should've said so sooner.
I would have just given them to you.
Take it all.
Really?
Let me grab one more.
Seriously.
Imperial Inspectorate, on official duty.
Everyone stay where you are.
Anyone who disobeys
will be executed.
You're really letting a little power
go to your head, aren't you?
Stealing items bestowed by the Emperor,
showing contempt for imperial authority.
The crime is unforgivable.
Everyone,
come with me to the Inspectorate for trial.
Listen to me.
Don't go pinning false charges on us.
My father is the Left Chancellor.
I dare you to lay a finger on us.
Madam,
the law shows no mercy.
As a Silver Guard of the Inspectorate,
deeply trusted by His Majesty,
I must lead by example
and uphold the law fairly.
So,
today I'm raiding the Ning Manor.
If any of you dare to interfere,
I'll deal with you.
If the Left Chancellor dares interfere,
I'll deal with him too.
Mother.
What do we do, Mother?
He's not really taking us to the Inspectorate, is he?
That place is a living hell.
No one ever comes back from there.
Mother, I don't want to go to the Inspectorate.
Calm down, calm down.
Say something!
Chen'er.
Just tell your father,
what exactly do you want?
Honestly, what's with His Majesty?
Couldn't he just give us a banknote?
So many gold bricks,
we can't even carry them.
Lord Ning,
today was just a warning.
If you want your three sons
to stay alive,
let me bring Yudie home as my wife.
This color looks lovely.
The fabric's nice too. So festive.
What's wrong, Yudie?
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Just thinking of you going to war
makes me want to cry.
It's all right.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of myself.
Blades have no mercy.
It's so dangerous.
Don't worry.
Oh, right.
His Majesty has promised me
that if I make it back alive,
he'll release you from servitude
and restore your freedom.
Even so, I don't want you fighting on the battlefield.
It's far too dangerous.
For your sake,
I'm willing.
Madam, what brings you here?
I've got something good to show you.
A few years ago,
a wandering warrior visited our Music Bureau.
He didn't leave the bed for ten days,
went through more than a dozen girls.
The bastard ran out of money afterward,
so he handed over this prescription
to settle the bill.
Is that so?
According to him,
this prescription is priceless.
Whether brewed or used in a medicinal bath,
it does wonders for the body.
It strengthens the body,
keeps your vital energy flowing,
and makes a man full of vigor.
I had someone test it later,
and it really does work.
Ancient Wei.
I don't need it.
Silver Guard Ning, drop the act.
You've got such a frail little frame.
Compared to the other Silver Guards at the Inspectorate,
you're really nothing special.
I just think you're a decent fellow,
so this prescription,
it's yours, free of charge.
I'm nothing special?
I'd say you're just okay.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, I...
Yudie, you see,
hasn't been with any other man.
But compared to your colleagues in the Inspectorate,
you're really quite ordinary.
Well, thanks.
You're welcome.
I'm only
thinking of Yudie's
future happiness, you know.
It's so hot in here.
Why's it so hot all of a sudden?
Actually,
it's not that hot, is it?
Thank you, Lord Ning.
I won't disturb you any further.
Carry on, you two.
Now then,
allow me to attend to your bath, my lord.
A medicinal bath.
Sounds good.
Who is it?
Lord Ning.
Brother Mei, please, save my sister!
What happened to Xiaomei?
You may not know this, my lord.
A few days ago, Xiaomei was out shopping,
and Hu Qiang of the Hu family took a fancy to her.
Today the Hu family came and dragged her away.
I tried to reason with them,
and they beat me up for it.
Xiaomei still hasn't come back.
Why didn't you come to me sooner?
I...
Die'er,
something urgent has come up.
Wait for me to return.
Lead the way.