Take care, young master.
Safe travels.
No need to see me out. Please stay.
Hey, Lao Gao.
Stop shoving me.
Ning Zi!
Get over here.
Tell me.
What did you do to my Yudie?
Exactly what you're thinking.
He's a complete animal.
Don't!
Don't stop me.
I'm settling this with him once and for all.
Him and me...
Lao Gao.
You want to measure up against him?
You think you stand a chance?
All right, all right, all right.
You're out.
Didn't sleep all night.
That impressive, huh?
Not bad.
How'd it go with Miss Nanzhi?
Sanniang already told me everything.
Our boss here
sat upright the entire night,
till Miss Nanzhi dozed off waiting.
Lao Pan.
Is there something
seriously wrong with you?
You're the sick one.
You're sick.
You're the one with issues.
Until I'm sure Miss Nanzhi
actually has feelings for me,
I won't lay a finger on her.
Aren't you worried Miss Nanzhi
might doubt her own charm?
might suspect there's something
physically wrong with you?
Would she?
Really?
She would.
This is the Music Bureau.
What do men come here for?
The girls know perfectly well.
Playing innocent at a time like this
would be too hypocritical.
I'll go explain.
Brothers, let's go!
Fourth Young Master!
Fourth Young Master! Fourth Young Master!
Fourth Young Master, we meet again!
Fourth Young Master!
You two fellow beggars,
the kindness of a piece of cloth back then,
I shall never forget.
For you.
So much money! So much money!
I knew it!
Come to the capital and beg,
and a meteoric rise awaits.
Thank you, Fourth Young Master!
Fourth Young Master,
we have two other brothers
who'd like to meet you.
Yes, yes!
Brother.
I've seen many heroes of the world,
but your carefree grace stands above all.
A man of fire and valor true,
a model hero for us all.
I'm Xing He.
I'm Wu Xian.
Pleased to meet you, Fourth Young Master.
Xing He, Wu Xian.
Fine names.
Fine names indeed.
Meeting is fate.
What troubles you two?
Well, Fourth Young Master,
we came all this way
just to
talk about our dreams.
Dreams?
Speak freely.
You see, I'm the kind of guy
who just wants to make it big.
I want to be rich.
You're too blunt!
Isn't that what we mean?
To succeed and get rich,
the best way
is to become a boss.
No, no, no!
That's not what I meant.
That's exactly what you meant.
You're a good man.
Let me play you a tune.
No, no, no!
Get to the point.
Achieve your dreams with your own hands.
Good luck!
Wait, no...
Why am I so sleepy?
My three lords,
this is evidence from the Jingxi Mine Murder Case.
Witnesses and evidence are all here.
If there's no issue, I'll file it away.
Go ahead.
Wait.
What's he doing?
Flint.
It's just a stone.
Why's he treating it like a treasure?
What do you know?
This is called flint.
Flint.
This thing
comes from the Xishan Mine.
The stone used in the capital
all comes from the Xishan Mine.
Right.
Good, good, good.
It's time to show some real skill.
Greetings, Silver Guards.
Can this thing be forged?
It doesn't seem difficult.
I can have it made for you within a day.
Much obliged.
I'll come pick it up tomorrow.
What's this mysterious thing you're forging?
A spear.
Who do you think you're fooling?
Like I've never seen a spear before?
Not the kind of spear you're thinking of.
Forget it, you wouldn't understand anyway.
Oh right, A Zheng.
After you head back tonight,
get me some sulfur,
saltpeter, and charcoal.
Don't let anyone find out.
What are you doing?
Who said you could—
Greetings, Commander Geng.
Where's Ning Chen?
Re-re-reporting...
Reporting to Commander Geng, Ning Chen has arrived.
He arrived and went straight in.
Acting all secretive, who knows what he's up to.
Sounds like he's practicing something...
Practicing with a spear.
A spear?
A spear.
Ning Chen!
Come out, I need you.
Get lost!
Don't bother me!
Has he gone rabid?
How dare he talk to me like that?
Does he know who I am?
Get out here!
I don't care who you are!
Whatever it is, it can wait!
I finally did it!
This...
Demons, ghosts, and black bull spirits!
By Lord Lao's command, obey at once!
Command, my foot!
Ning Chen!
What are you doing?
You—
Congratulations, everyone.
You're about to witness our Da Xuan
enter the age of firearms.
Have you gone rabid?
What on earth is a "firearm"?
He's gotten dangerously obsessed with his training.
You can't just practice with any random spear.
You call this a spear?
Where's the spearhead?
Who says without a spearhead
it can't kill?
Gentlemen.
Cover your ears.
Lord Geng,
how tough of you.
Lao Gao,
help me cover my ears.
Thanks a bunch, kind soul.
What'd you say? I can't hear you!
He said,
"Thank you."
"Eat rice."
Aren't we having buns for lunch? He said—
What on earth is this?
First a spark,
then a roar like a dragon.
This,
is the musket.
Why are you just mouthing words?
He said,
"This is a musket."
A musket?
Ning Zi,
where did this iron pellet come from?
I'm asking,
Get it now?
On the battlefield,
arrows leave a visible trail,
giving enemies time to react.
A musket fires
without a trace.
At close range,
it pierces armor.
Commander Geng truly has insight.