Kneel here and wait.
Kneeling again?
If I kneel down here,
and the Empress doesn't show up,
won't I be kneeling till I die?
But if I break the rules,
they could find any excuse
to charge me with lèse-majesté.
Brilliant.
Empress,
where are you?
Which way should your subject kneel?
Ning Chen!
No shouting in the Furong Palace.
But I should at least know
which way to kneel toward Her Majesty.
It'd be awkward to kneel the wrong way.
Besides,
that would be lèse-majesté.
Just kneel when told.
Enough with the nonsense.
Listen here, sister,
it's not that I don't want to kneel.
I just...
I was tortured at the Inspection Bureau.
Both my kneecaps are shattered.
And my backside is a bloody mess.
It still hurts.
I dare say
the Empress won't strip me to check.
So this is the Mother of the Nation?
She looks like a gas tank.
How could His Majesty even bear it?
I'm truly impressed.
So you're Ning Chen.
What audacity.
You dare not kneel before Us?
Your subject is wounded.
I cannot bow properly.
Ning Chen,
you rose by trampling the Imperial Uncle.
Feeling rather smug, aren't you?
The Empress misunderstands.
Your subject killed the Imperial Uncle
out of sheer necessity.
I, your subject,
deeply regret it.
The Imperial Uncle was Our brother.
You killed him and walked away unscathed.
In all of Daxuan,
no one else compares to you.
You should feel smug.
Since His Majesty has pardoned you,
We have nothing more to say.
The days ahead are long.
We will remember you well,
Ning Chen.
Thank you for your concern, Empress.
Guards!
Ning Chen is unkempt and defies the rules.
This is true lèse-majesté.
Thirty strokes of the cane.
Wait.
We act by protocol. You dare resist?
His Majesty ordered me to the border.
Your subject is already wounded.
If punished further,
I won't be able to move for a while,
which may delay the war effort.
You dare threaten Us?
If the Empress insists on punishing me,
your subject dares not resist.
Your subject
willingly accepts the punishment.
Delaying war is a state matter.
If His Majesty grows enraged,
even We could not bear the blame.
Since His Majesty has pardoned you,
today, We shall
spare you for your lèse-majesté.
But you remember this well.
No matter how an ant jumps about,
it remains nothing but an ant.
We are the Mother of the Nation.
Crushing an ant
takes no effort at all.
Thank you for your mercy, Empress.
Your subject
will keep this in mind.
Get out!
He's infuriating!
Your Majesty,
don't be angry, don't be angry.
He's infuriating!
Chen, Chen.
Chen.
What happened?
What's going on?
How did it go?
Say something!
His Majesty showed mercy.
He let me see you guys one last time.
I'll be executed in three days.
I'll go see His Majesty.
I'll have Geng Ziyi...
His Majesty sent me to the front lines.
To atone for my crimes through merit.
So, you see...
I was just messing with you.
What's wrong with you, huh?
Seriously, you little brat.
You scared me half to death!
He's crying! He's crying!
I am not.
Still denying it, you little punk?
You almost cried too, Pan Jinyi.
I have no feelings.
What feelings could I have?
No feelings, my foot.
Suddenly you have no feelings again?
Alright!
You saved your neck, you little brat.
We've got to celebrate!
Tonight we go to the Jiaofang Si.
My treat.
Sounds great, alright!
But...
Let me go home and wash up first.
I've been wearing this for days.
I stink.
Fine.
Old Gao.
Anyone who heard it is invited.
I'm coming along too.
Hold on.
If they both come, I'm short on cash.
Lend me some first.
Why play the big shot when you're broke?
Well...
I'll treat then.
Count me in.
I'll tag along too.
Let's all go together.
The Jiaofang Si!
Don't yawn.
You're making me yawn too.
Imperial Father.
Greetings, Imperial Father.
Why aren't you in bed at this hour?
Did you come to see me about something?
Imperial Father.
I want to show you something.
What's this?
A poem.
Clouds long for her gown, blooms her face.
Spring breeze brushes the rail, rich dew.
If not seen atop Mount Qunyu,
Then met by moonlight on the Jade Terrace.
Beautifully written.
Huai'an.
This poem...
Did you write it?
Imperial Father!
I'm not that shameless.
That rascal Ning Chen gave it to me.
So what do you think of Ning Chen?
He's a bit annoying,
but his literary talent is undeniable.
Aside from his talent,
what about his looks?
His looks?
Nowhere near as good as yours, Father.
Oh, you.
You really know how to flatter me.
If you admire something about Ning Chen,
that's a good thing.
He gave you a poem.
But what will you give him?
What I'll give him...
I can't think of anything either.
Imperial Father, help me think of a gift.
Give him a shield.
Next time you hit him with a duster,
he can block, block, block.
Then you won't scare him away.
Imperial Father!
I'm a proper lady, you know.
I know.
You're my most well-behaved daughter.
Does His Majesty want him as a son-in-law?
Goodness me.
The 9th Princess is his favorite daughter.
A bunch of country bumpkins
coming to the Jiaofang Si?
Who do they think they are?
The people who can come here
are mostly rich or noble.
None of them have weak backgrounds.
His Majesty lets us indulge ourselves,
but if we cause trouble here,
he won't go easy on us.
Boss.
Where is Miss Nanzhi?
Who's Nanzhi?
No wonder they call you a greenhorn,
you really don't know a thing.
The Jiaofang Si has twelve chambers,
and each one is filled with beauties.
Talented and gorgeous,
they sell their art, not their bodies.
Among them,
Miss Nanzhi is the most outstanding.
The flute she plays
is the finest in the capital.
No wonder fatty obsesses over this place.
Our boss
has a soft spot for Miss Nanzhi.
He only comes here for her.
The mighty Pan Jinyi of the Bureau
can't even win over a courtesan?
In this capital city,
the men wanting to take Miss Nanzhi
are too many to count.
Our boss earns plenty,
but compared to those
truly wealthy and powerful men,
he falls short.
And our boss,
he's just not good with words.
Every time, he can only watch from afar.
Young Master Gao.
Madam San.
Come, come.
Find a fine seat for us young masters.
Right away, Young Master Gao.
Your private booth
has been ready for a while.
Let's go.
Young Master Ning, after you.
Ladies, come quickly!
Still so lively in here.
Young Master Ning, take the head seat.
Where are our girls?
Don't be impatient.
Come.
Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter.
Do you like them?
Serve the young masters well.
We greet you, young masters.
Don't be shy.
Come on, Chen.
You pick first.
Hold on.
I...
You four ladies
should go attend to your own matters.
What?
Winter, Autumn.
What are you doing, sending them away?
Think about it.
With Ning Chen's current status,
are these ordinary girls really worthy?
He deserves a girl from the 12 Chambers.
That makes sense.
Ning Chen,
your taste has gotten higher.
How about a different selection?
No, no, no need.
You all enjoy yourselves.
I'll just watch.
Don't hold back here.
A first-timer.
So bashful.
But what he said makes sense.
The girl who serves you tonight
should pay you instead.
This is your first time.
The highest bidder wins.
Let me arrange it.
Everyone!
Hear me out for a moment.
Especially the girls of the 12 Chambers.
We have here one...
Get the hell out of here.
My buddy here had too much to drink.
It's fine.
You shut your mouth.
Quietly wait for your Twelve Chambers.
Still being shy.
Young masters,
Lady Nanzhi and Lady Yudie will perform.
Each table gets a pot of wine
and two side dishes.
Great, great, great.
Dim the lights.
Ning, you really lucked out today.
Lady Nanzhi's flute
and Lady Yudie's pipa
are the two finest in the capital.
Relax.