Wonderful!
Bravo, bravo, bravo!
Excellent!
Simply brilliant!
Wonderful!
Young Masters, please enjoy yourselves.
I shall take my leave now.
Don't be in such a hurry.
Wait, wait...
Lady Nanzhi.
This is a poem I wrote for you.
I hope you won't find it lacking.
Lady Nanzhi.
A Night-Luminous Pearl from foreign lands.
This one's nice.
I'll take it.
Lady Yudie.
I spent a fortune
to get this Dangling hairpin made for you.
I hope you like it.
This one's nice too.
How thoughtful of you.
Make way, make way, make way.
Step aside.
Isn't this the Eldest Young Master Ning?
What's this guy doing here?
Eldest Young Master Ning.
Lady Nanzhi.
I had someone specially
seek out this Jade flute for you.
I hope you like it.
Thank you, Young Master Ning.
You're welcome.
As long as you like it.
That's all that matters.
Means I've got a chance tonight.
Old Pan,
just sit back and watch.
I'm
just an uncultured warrior.
I'm not worthy of Lady Nanzhi.
Just watching makes me
happy.
What are you chickening out for?
We brothers have got your back.
For literary talent, you've got me.
For martial prowess,
you've got us.
No need.
In the Imperial Uncle case,
you saved my life.
Today I'm returning the favor.
Really, there's no need.
No need, no need.
Come on.
Lady Nanzhi.
This here is our leader,
Pan Yucheng, the Golden Guard Pan.
You could say he's dashing and elegant,
a fine figure of a man.
Strong as an ox, healthy appetite.
Skilled in letters and arms, and upright.
And he's long admired you.
Lady Nanzhi, pay them no mind.
I know these people.
Crude and vulgar,
with filthy minds.
You, get out of the way.
Lady Nanzhi,
our Old Pan here
has composed a poem for you.
A Country bumpkin writing poetry?
That's a first.
He probably doesn't know Tonal patterns.
Hold on.
This Tonal patterns guy here,
could you shut your mouth?
If you can't listen to reason,
I happen to know how to use my fists.
What do you think you're doing?
Do you know who I am?
Then do you know who he is?
A Country bumpkin,
some unworthy nobody.
This nobody you speak of
is the man who killed the Imperial Uncle,
Ning Chen.
Don't say such things again.
If word reaches His Majesty,
it'll bring trouble to Chen.
Then we can mention
Ning Chen's other identity.
That's right.
Let me tell you all something.
The Great Scholar of the Hanlin Academy
once told my brother Ning Chen
that he's the Poet Immortal reborn.
Poet Immortal reborn?
What audacity!
If you have the skill, write a poem now.
Damn it.
A chance to shine like this
should be mine, Eldest Young Master Ning.
Why should a bastard like you show off?
Exactly.
Li Hanru, Chancellor of the Academy,
is famous for empty flattery.
He casually praised you,
and now you're getting smug about it?
Showing off, are we?
Oh, come on.
I...
Chen,
let's compose one and show him.
Alright then,
here's one.
Go on.
The warm southern branch blooms early,
letting her reign as queen of all flowers.
Unrivaled by time, holding spring within,
moved by your longing...
seeking...
a smile.
There.
Bravo, bravo, bravo!
Wonderful, wonderful!
This poem,
Not quite 'To leave purity in the world',
is still a rare masterpiece.
Especially the first line,
which contains Lady Nanzhi's name!
With this poem out,
Lady Nanzhi's worth
will multiply many times over.
Indeed, indeed.
Old Pan is upright and honest,
steady and hardworking.
Choosing him is definitely the right call.
Now look at this one.
Pale face,
sunken eyes,
the very picture of Excessive debauchery.
Who knows,
he might even carry some filthy disease.
I...
No, you...
What "you"?
Bringing some shabby flute,
thinking you can win over Lady Nanzhi?
What flute hasn't Lady Nanzhi seen?
Would she ever fancy the likes of you?
Ning Chen!
What?
Eldest Young Master Ning wants to play?
You, you, you...
You're standing up for him, are you?
Ning Chen is our brother.
What's wrong with standing up for him?
What are you bulging your eyes at us for?
Mind if we gouge those eyeballs out
and stomp on them like firecrackers?
Ning Chen,
are you alright?
The Eldest Young Master Ning is hurt!
Look at my leg!
Today's humiliation,
I'll repay it someday.
Quick, go report it!
This poem,
did he write it,
or did you give it to him?
Ning Chen wrote it.
Just as I thought.
After all this time,
he hasn't improved one bit.
Golden Guard Pan,
if you don't mind,
won't you come to my chamber
for a cup of tea?
Gladly.
Lady Nanzhi has chosen a Favored guest!
To enter one of The Twelve Houses
is an immense honor indeed.
Go on.
Go!
A perfect shot!
An unforgettable night!
Unstoppable!
Go for it!
Lady Yudie, Lady Yudie!
Lady Yudie!
Brother, we're brothers, right?
No, we're not.
We are brothers.
Listen,
write me a poem too.
I've liked Yudie
for a long time.
Come on, just help me out.
Then I'll...
You what?
You're already married!
I'm still single!
What's wrong with asking Chen for a poem?
Tell you what,
if it works out,
I'll call you my godfather.
Godfather? This is my real dad!
You what?
You're about to be a father yourself,
and you're still stirring up trouble?
There's more than one girl here.
Why are you fighting over her?
Look at that greasy head of yours.
Young Master Ning.
I wonder if I might have the honor
of inviting you to share a cup of wine.
Are you talking to me?
Not you.
Of course.
What do you mean, "of course"?
Hold on.
Why is she inviting him for a drink?
All he can do is write a few cheesy poems.
Besides,
I'm better looking than he is.
Why isn't she asking me for a drink?
When did you go blind?
Get lost, go play somewhere else.
Ning.
Lady Yudie has already asked.
Why not compose a poem for her too?
Compose, my ass!
Really?
Would Yudie have such an honor?
Yes.
Of course.
Sanniang.
I've got it.
After countless calls, she finally appears,
her face half-hidden behind her pipa.
A few twists, a pluck of the strings,
Emotion flows before the melody begins.
Wonderful!
A brilliant poem!
Truly eye-opening!
What a poem!
Move aside.
Is Lady Yudie pleased?
Yudie is most pleased.
To receive a poem from you, Young Master,
I shall have no regrets in this life.
Young Master,
what is the title of this poem?
"For Yudie."
Thank you, Young Master.
If you don't mind, Young Master,
would you join me in my room for a drink?
This...
One poem and he's taking Lady Yudie away?
That easy?
This...
I should have done the same!
Exactly.
Lady Yudie,
go easy on our Ning.
He's never been with a woman.
You alright, Young Master Gao?
Yudie.
Sanniang.
Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter.
Alright.
Sanniang.
And Plum, Orchid, Bamboo, Chrysanthemum.
That's eight of them!
Yudie.
Young Master.
This is the finest Apricot Blossom Rain.
Please, have a taste.
I wonder if I might have the honor
of seeing your true face, my lady.
Through ages, no peerless beauty endures,
Yet a fair maiden delights the eye.
A face that topples kingdoms and cities,
Astonishing all under heaven.
Young Master,
do you truly admire me?
this is my very first time.
Just now, my feelings rose unbidden,
and ran ever so deep.
If I have given any offense,
please forgive me, my lady.
Young Master, you misunderstand.
Yudie may hold one of The Twelve Houses,
as long as I remain in the Music Bureau,
my purity will be surrendered eventually.
Young Master, you are so talented,
and Yudie
truly admires you with all her heart.
Allow me to attend to you, Young Master.
I beg you, Young Master,
please be gentle with Yudie.
Flower path was never swept for guests,
today, my humble gate opens for you alone.