=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 27=
(Six years later)
Is everything ready
for taking over the house?
Everything's ready.
Go ahead.
Uncle, this is my ball.
Here.
Thank you, uncle.
Why are you playing here
alone at the hospital?
I'm used to it.
I've been in the hospital
since I was little.
Everyone here knows me.
(If we had a child,)
(they'd probably be about this age too.)
That's impressive.
How old are you?
I was born in the Year of Bingchen.
The Year of Bingchen?
So you're five years old?
That's right.
Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao!
Mom!
Where did you run off to?
Mom,
there was a really
handsome uncle just now.
We were chatting.
Uncle?
Mm.
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
♪Falling into your smile before my eyes♪
♪Stirring my dreams
and awakening my heart♪
♪Past and future both fade away♪
♪Love is so strange,
the way it entangles me♪
Shaoyuan.
♪Still gently holding onto the♪
♪Happy game that began within a dream♪
♪Joy and pleasure♪
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Just scraped my skin a little.
Let's go.
Mm.
♪Forcing me to trade pain for the past♪
♪In this world♪
♪Love is a beautiful exchange♪
♪Hearts connecting in that very moment♪
(Seeing you're still alive)
(is enough for me.)
(Of the two of us,)
(at least one should live happily.)
♪Love is so strange,
the way it entangles me♪
Where did you hide Xiaoxiao?
We've never registered a marriage,
and we've never
been husband and wife in truth.
What right do you have to take her away?
Darling, I heard
you met an old friend today.
Did you think that now he's back,
you and Xiaoxiao would finally be safe?
What do you mean by that?
Haven't I suffered enough all these years,
being threatened and tormented by you?
You deliberately
gave Xiaoxiao a false birth year.
What exactly are you trying to do?
What am I trying to do?
For the past six years,
I've given you
and that child a comfortable life.
Yet you wouldn't even let me touch you.
Every single time,
you threatened me with death.
Haven't I treated you well enough?
And yet you're still thinking
about Lu Shaoyuan.
Don't forget,
six years ago, you killed him
with your own hands.
Do you think he could ever forgive you?
You've stayed faithful
to him all these years,
but does he even know that?
What he sees
is six years of you sharing my bed.
Oh, right.
Let me remind you of something.
If he ever finds out that this child
is his biological daughter,
then that child's life
will be in danger too.
Gu Shaoyan, you're insane!
What, still want to kill me?
Too bad you can't.
If I die,
Xiaoxiao will be buried with me too.
Lu Shaoyuan!
Guards.
Take him away.
What are you doing?
Lu Shaoyuan,
even if you're the Commander in Chief,
you can't just arrest
a city commander on a whim.
Cheng Yi, Commander of Yancheng,
for smuggling opium
(Arrest Warrant)
and violating the opium ban,
you're hereby placed under arrest.
Your house,
your woman,
I'll take them all.
Madam,
he's trying
to destroy this family
and tear us apart.
You can't arrest him.
He endangered Yancheng
and harmed the people.
Why shouldn't he be arrested?
No matter how many wrongs he's done,
you still can't take the law
into your own hands.
You can't ignore the law.
Darling,
don't beg him.
I've failed you and the child.
I've failed both of you.
Wasn't Miss Zhuang
talking to me about the law?
Then let me tell you this.
In Yancheng, I am the law.
Take him away!
Lu Shaoyuan!
I'm begging you.
You can't arrest him.
Please let him go.
I'm begging you.
I'm begging you!
Please listen to me.
I'm begging you.
If someone has to be locked up,
then lock me up instead.
Please let him go.
I'm begging you!
If you're going to beg,
then beg properly.
The way Miss Zhuang is acting now
sounds more like a threat.
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
I'm begging you.
♪Falling into your smile before my eyes♪
So anyone who breaks the law
can just kneel before me
and have everything forgiven?
Then I'll kneel here
until you're satisfied. Is that enough?
Fine.
Then kneel properly, Miss Zhuang.
Right now, I don't see
any sincerity at all.
♪Still gently holding onto the♪
Good.
Stay like that.
♪Joy and pleasure♪
(Every moment that passes)
(will puts Xiaoxiao in greater danger.)
♪Forcing me to trade pain for the past♪
♪In this world♪
Commander-in-Chief,
I really don't have much time left.
I'm begging you, let him go first.
Just let him go.
I'll do whatever you ask.
Alright?
I'm begging you,
please let him go first.
Your clothes are dirty.
Miss Zhuang is dirty too.
Let me help clean you up.
Guards.
Have the Commander personally
prepare bathwater for Madam and me.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪