=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 30=
Once I die,
you'll never find Xiaoxiao.
Everything I've become today
is because of you.
Lu Shaoyuan.
I'll never give you
the chance to defeat me.
I don't need your gift.
I only want you to be like your brother,
obedient and not causing trouble.
There's only one of these.
I only wanted you to have it.
You stole something
and still won't admit it?
I'll beat you to death.
Do you admit you were wrong?
(From childhood until now,)
(I never once managed to beat you.)
Nianchi.
I came here specially
to appoint you Commander of Yancheng.
Shaoyan.
Where's Godmother's medicine?
This is...
He's just some thug. Let's go, Dad.
Alright.
Yes.
Shaoyan.
Godmother's medicine.
Don't go!
(From the moment I took your place)
(and became Commander,)
(there was no turning back.)
(Investigation into)
Gu Nianchi.
(Yancheng Opium Addiction Groups)
Wasn't the reason
you came to me in the first place
to make me take the fall for you?
(In the end,)
(perhaps)
(this was fate all along.)
(Lu Shaoyuan)
(always carried light within him.)
(And you)
(were just a rat hiding in the dark.)
(Your life was never
meant to see the light.)
We were once brothers.
How did we end up like this?
He's dead.
Then where's Xiaoxiao?
Where did he hide her?
- Did you ask him?
- Yunqiu.
Yunqiu, listen to me.
Xiaoxiao was already gone
when I arrived.
He never told me where she was.
Then what do we do?
What about Xiaoxiao?
Yunqiu...
We'll find her together.
We will find her.
We will.
Trust me.
I pray the Lord
reunites my daughter and me soon.
Don't worry.
We'll find Xiaoxiao.
Yunqiu.
Let's go check the shelter again today.
I prepared some stationery
for the children.
Alright.
Miss.
Please help us.
Could you spare us something to eat?
Mister, we haven't eaten in days.
Where do you live?
How about
letting them come home with me?
No.
We still have a younger sister.
We can't leave without her.
That's right.
My brother and I
still have a little sister.
We'll never be separated.
Mm.
Then how about
all three of you come home with us?
But can you even afford to raise us?
There are three of us.
We eat three meals a day.
That's impressive.
Three meals a day, huh?
Sis.
I've got good news for you.
We won't go hungry anymore.
Really?
That's wonderful.
Look.
Those kind people
said we can live with them.
Mom!
♪Fates intertwined,
right and wrong no longer clear♪
Mom!
♪The world becomes a prison♪
Xiaoxiao.
I'm sorry.
Let me see.
Mom, I finally found you.
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
Xiaoxiao, this is your father.
This is your father.
Dad.
Hey.
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
♪How can love remain so calm?♪
♪So called blame,
nothing more than an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
Careful, sis.
Come here.
Darling.
Not only did we find Xiaoxiao,
we gained two more sons too.
How am I this lucky?
There's more.
Let me tell you a secret.
Soon,
you're going to have a fourth child.
Come here.
Got you.
No.
Again.
Don't run.
Really?
Look over here.
Sis, he's over there.
Then give me a kiss.
The kids are watching.
Turn around.
Hurry up.
Mom and Dad are so embarrassing.
Stop it.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪