=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 29=
You've never forgotten her.
And you've never truly loved me.
Not even for a moment.
I'm sorry, Xue Wan.
I'm very grateful you saved my life.
But you know it too.
When it comes to you...
I've always understood it clearly.
You never truly loved me.
And actually, I didn't
love you that much either.
So I came today to tell you something.
With the war lately,
my brother has decided
to move the whole family abroad.
The Xue family
did so much for me before,
yet I did nothing in return.
I've decided to go abroad
with my brother and help him.
You're leaving?
Mm.
So today I want
to say something honestly.
You don't need to feel guilty toward me.
Actually, I realized long ago
that what I felt for you
was more admiration than love.
I helped you return to Yancheng
and become Commander-in-Chief
only because when you
were Commander of Yancheng,
it was a blessing
for all the people of Yancheng.
And that had nothing to do with love.
I respect your decision.
You're a good woman
who cares about the world.
You deserve someone better.
Thank you.
Today, even though
I knew your intentions,
I still went along with this act.
Because only this way
could I see your gentleness toward me.
Sometimes I wonder
if without her,
I wouldn't have become who I am today.
But when I saw today
what you did to her,
I felt terrible inside.
I thought I hated her.
Hated her for taking my identity
and marrying you.
But when I tortured her,
I realized I wasn't happy at all.
I believe you're the same.
You're speaking for her?
I'm just saying what's truly on my mind.
Actually, Zhuang Yunqiu
never truly hurt you.
Everything between you
was only a misunderstanding.
But it's different for me.
She personally
said those hurtful words to me
and personally shot me.
But you survived, didn't you?
Maybe there's
another side to this matter.
Anyway, we've known
each other for some time.
I hope everything
goes well for both of you.
And I hope everything
goes well for you too.
Then I'm leaving.
Someone.
Prepare the car to the hospital!
The Commander's wife
really has a hard life.
What do you mean?
Not only does
the Commander treat Madam badly,
he treats the child badly too.
The Commander often hits the child.
One time when they were arguing,
I overheard it.
This child isn't the Commander's.
And for some reason,
the Commander kept telling Xiaoxiao
that this child wasn't
born in the Bingchen year.
Not born in the Bingchen year?
Then when was she born?
Get me her medical records.
This...
What?
Fine.
Commander.
Here.
(The First Army Hospital of Yancheng)
(Zhuang Xiaoxiao.
Date of Birth: May 29th, Yimao Year)
May 29th, Yimao Year?
Xiaoxiao wasn't born
in the Bingchen year.
(Reason for hospitalization: Malnutrition,
frequent dizziness, bruises found on the body...)
She's my child.
(It was to protect our child)
(that you suffered so much.)
(And I...)
(I misunderstood you all this time.)
(Don't worry.)
(I'll save her.)
Eat.
Follow him.
Don't alert him.
Gu Shaoyan.
(Only this way can I find Xiaoxiao.)
Xiaoxiao.
(This...)
(Could he already know?)
- Madam.
- Where's the Commander-in-Chief?
Where is he?
Commander.
Where's Xiaoxiao?
She's my last bargaining chip now.
Bring her to me.
Commander.
Xiaoxiao is gone.
What?
Commander.
Let me help you escape. I've arranged a car.
I can get you out of here.
Com...
Commander.
You can't even handle
something this simple.
Lu Shaoyuan.
Gu Shaoyan.
Stop struggling like a trapped beast.
I checked the hospital records.
Xiaoxiao is my daughter.
Lu Shaoyuan!
Zhuang Yunqiu and I
were together for six years.
Six whole years,
and I still couldn't have her.
And now,
she's going to be with you too.
I will never let
your family get what you want.
Never!
Hand over Xiaoxiao,
and I'll spare you.
Lu Shaoyuan.
Then kill me.
I've spent my whole life
living in your shadow.
I'm never going
to let you have your way.
It was me
who made you look so high and mighty.
As long as I die,
you'll never find Xiaoxiao.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪