=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 28=
What are you trying to do?
Isn't the Commander
very important to you?
He prepared all this for us himself.
Do you like it?
He prepared this?
Where is he now?
Does your husband
know how beautiful you are?
What?
Can't take it anymore?
Wasn't it you who said
that as long as I let him go,
you'd do anything?
Then what exactly do you want?
Simple.
Show me
your most beautiful side
until I'm satisfied.
There are people outside.
Doesn't that make it even more exciting?
And one of those people
is your husband.
You don't mind him watching, do you?
I'm begging you,
please stop provoking him, alright?
Do you even realize
what kind of consequences
this will bring?
Consequences?
I rule Yancheng.
What consequences would I fear?
Zhuang Yunqiu, weren't you the one
who begged me to let him go?
Now I've granted your wish.
Isn't it perfect to let him stand
outside and guard the door for us?
Make him speak!
Lu Shaoyuan!
Let her go!
She's my wife!
She can only belong to me!
You can't touch her!
Lu Shaoyuan, let go!
Lu Shaoyuan!
I'm begging you, Lu Shaoyuan.
Please...
Stop provoking him,
alright?
Please.
Miss Zhuang,
are you begging for your husband again?
Fine.
Zhuang Yunqiu, think about your child!
Think about our child!
What?
Now you don't care
whether your husband lives or dies?
Isn't this enough already?
Not even close.
Zhuang Yunqiu,
I'm really curious.
During these six years,
every time you shared his bed,
was there ever even a moment
when you thought of me?
Even for a moment?
Was there?
Lu Shaoyuan, let her go!
Stay away from her!
Lu Shaoyuan!
That voice sounds wonderful.
Louder.
A little louder!
Lu Shaoyuan, what are you doing?
Let her go!
She's your sister in law!
Sister in law?
Lu Shaoyuan!
Let go of your sister in law!
Get him out of here.
Lu Shaoyuan!
Let go!
That's enough for today.
We'll continue tomorrow.
What should I do?
Xiaoxiao...
I'm so sorry.
What am I supposed to do about Xiaoxiao?
Commander-in-Chief,
our wedding is coming up soon.
Why don't we go pick out
a wedding dress?
Alright.
We'll go after lunch.
Eat some food.
Mm.
Commander-in-Chief, Miss,
please enjoy.
Who told you to make this?
I thought you liked it.
I don't.
Make it again.
Commander-in-Chief,
I like fish.
Why don't we have fish instead?
Alright.
Go make it.
Yes.
Commander-in-Chief, have some fruit.
Please enjoy.
Stop right there.
Pick the bones out
of the fish for Miss Xue.
Commander-in-Chief,
how did you know I don't like
picking fish bones myself?
You're so good to me.
These past years,
you've treated me even better.
I know.
What are you standing there for?
Pick the bones out.
Eat.
Done.
Did you even taste the fish
before serving it?
What if it tastes bad?
Exactly.
What if you poisoned it?
Fine.
I'll eat it.
Why did you stop?
Isn't fish your favorite?
Keep eating.
You cooked it yourself,
yet even you look miserable eating it.
Now you've ruined everyone's appetite.
Take it away.
Commander-in-Chief,
come take a walk with me.
Alright.
We should go pick out
the wedding dress too.
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
Yunqiu...
Yunqiu!
♪Past and future both fade away♪
♪Love is so strange,
the way it entangles me♪
♪I still haven't awakened,
though I know I shouldn't♪
♪Still gently holding onto the♪
♪Happy game that began within a dream♪
♪Joy and pleasure♪
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪