You are the one who has it.
Are we coming with them later?
It's okay.
FEMALE HEROES
Wait for me outside.
I'll just go to the restroom.
Okay.
Wait for me outside.
- Okay.
- All right?
- Rene!
- Hey, Tonette!
- They're calling for a faculty meeting.
- What about?
I don't know.
Maybe about the student's grades…
For you, sir and ma'am!
Sir, do my parents really need to come?
- Thanks for the coffee.
- All right.
Your student is nice.
But why do you need her parents?
Why did you give them our coffee?
Don't fuss about it.
I'll just buy you another.
- Let's cross the street!
- I'm scared, brother!
They won't run us over, I promise!
- You want to cross?
- Yes.
All right, wait.
I'll guide you, but let's hurry.
Go!
Where are you headed?
- Where are you boys headed?
- Just over there.
- Where are you going?
- There.
- That way?
- Yes.
Light's green. We can cross now.
Pedestrians may now cross…
- We can cross now.
- Okay.
or if we have a Scotch,
that'll keep him there longer.
Oh my God. Who put
all this peanut butter here?
Why do we have so many jars here?
Nobody eats this!
Bianca, you've been working
for me a long time.
- Tomorrow? I have a trip to Cebu.
- But then, it was kind of long--
- Cebu? What time are you leaving?
- Yes. Tell your Mom.
- Tonight.
- Just for them.
So, you're not coming.
- Mom, you're needed in school tomorrow.
- Gloria! She needs something.
- Can't your dad go?
- He's going to Cebu.
Okay, I'm hurrying already.
All right.
Just give him whatever he wants.
I'm leaving.
Babe, please put the groceries
in the fridge, all right?
- Please, take care of it.
- What?
Put this stuff in the fridge.
Yes, I've got it.
Mom?
Oh!
There's a lot of food
in the cabinet, okay?
Concha!
Angel's here!
Hey, Angel!
Grandma!
What is it?
Oh, don't! My hands are dirty!
- What brings you here?
- You should've worn gloves.
This is Roger, my friend.
Grandma, come with me to school.
What?
I need you there.
Why?
The teacher wants to talk.
Why me? What about your parents?
Daddy's going to Cebu.
Your mommy?
I'm not sure she heard me.
Come on, Grandma.
Angel, I've been gardening.
You see how dirty I am.
Why didn't you wear gloves?
The plants won't feel my care
if I don't touch them.
Ma'am, I invited you here
to inform you…
MR. RENE B. SANCHEZ
PROFESSOR
…that Angel's grades are failing.
She can take remedial classes,
but maybe that's not enough.
She needs to take summer classes
in math and in chemistry.
Angel.
You have to pass the summer classes
so you won't have to repeat Grade 12.
All right.
Actually, if you pass this summer,
That's what's nice about it.
You just need to pass these two subjects.
All right.
Thank you.
Angel.
Let's go.
When is your flight?
Tonight.
So?
What do we do about Angel?
Obviously, you take charge of her.
You know we have to deal
with Angel's issues.
She'll have more years of schooling.
You're the mother. You take care of her.
What do I know about that?
Just because I am the mother?
What about you? Aren't you her father?
You have a responsibility to her.
Do I need to carry everything?
We both made her.
Why would you push that problem on me?
You're the mother.
I should focus on my job.
You should manage the home, not me.
I work too!
Just because we're both working,
you won't attend to your child?
So when it comes to caring for her,
I should do it solo?
That's your duty. Don't force it on me.
Don't forget our roles.
I forget--
My God, Raymund!
From the start,
you didn't participate in rearing Angel.
It's always me, the mother.
Why is that?
Do your part now.
Give me--
Am I asking for too much?
Oh, my God. Can I do the asking now?
What are you saying?
I've stayed here for so long.
All that time, I was here for you.
What am I to you?
Was I useless?
Yes, you were here.
You go in and out of the house…
without even asking how we're doing,
how we're getting by on our days!
How you talk! Who stayed home, huh?
- Who was there?
- Exactly.
- I'm the one who's always here.
- Even on weekends, you weren't home!
I'm working. Come on!
You were the one who's not here!
- You take care of Angel now!
- That's no excuse!
You know what? That will do her good.
Bring her to Cebu with you.
Give her a fresh start.
She can make new friends.
She doesn't need to be here.
I have nothing left for her.
I have given her so much.
I've had enough.
I'm done with Angel. I'm done with you.
I'm done with this kind of life.
Your turn. Do your part.
For God's sake!
I'm done.
The subscriber cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Where are you? Why weren't you picking up?
I was with my mom.
We went shopping. We ate out.
Why didn't you text me?
Ran out of battery.
Ran out? How come you can text me now?
Nonsense.
Of course, I tried to turn on
the phone to reply to you.
Now you're annoyed,
when this is the only time we can talk.
I wanted to tell you something!
Never mind!
- What did you get?
- Why do I have a tank top?
- I can't open mine.
- I got a tank top.
Open it. Hurry!
- Open it. Help me!
- Let's see.
You're so excited for it.
Wait, what's this?
This should be mine! Take mine!
Concha?
Angel will be staying
here with us for now.
Oh?
What happened?
Let me stay here, Grandma.
All right.
Same room as always.
Bring your luggage there.
Sorry?
I said bring your things to your room.
All right.
Anyway, what happened to your school?
It's all settled.
All right, take your things upstairs.
This is my grandma's house.
I'll give you a tour.
Here, look!
Check this out. So cute!
Does this still work?
Here's a painting of my darling grandma.
Hi, Grandma.
And then here, we have… the family photos!
We look alike, right? Beautiful.
Isn't she perfect?
My grandma is so beautiful.
See where I inherited my looks from?
What's this?
Is this thing working?
How do you use this?
Never mind. I might break it.
This way leads back to the living room.
See how huge Grandma's house is? My gosh!
So, that's it! That's Grandma's house.
No bashing, okay?
Help me catch one.
We'll have chicken soup later.
- Okay.
- Go on.
Pick a fat one.
Wait.
The tail.
Wait, I'll let it relax a bit. Wait.
It might poop on me!
Wait.
Doggie?
Be a good boy! Wait!
- Wait.
- Give it to me.
- Finally! I got it!
- See?
We got it.
Now you know how to do it!
Grandma, why do you care for them
if you're just going to eat them?
Their purpose is to nourish us.
It's not selfishness.
It's the circle of life.
Grandma Ninay, how long
have you been here?
A very long time.
Imagine, I took care of your grandmother.
And your mother, too.
When you were born,
I also took care of you.
Do you know that?
But only for three years,
because your family moved.
When did Grandpa die?
- Come again, child?
- When did Grandpa die?
You were…
You were about five when he passed.
What did he die of?
He liked eating
unhealthy food.
He loved eating stewed pork
and grilled pork.
So he had a heart attack.
So stop eating junk food.
It's not good for you.
That's why I always cook vegetables
for your grandma.
This is good for our health.
We don't have that at home
because my mom doesn't cook that.
I'll open it.
Why did you leave the gate open?
Hey, Angel.
You didn't even tell me you're here.
If I hadn't seen your post,
I wouldn't have known
that you're with your Grandma.
I just visited Grandma.
You could've told me that.
I'd have permitted you.
I couldn't attend to my clients
because I was worried about you.
- You want rice?
- Yes, just a bit.
- One more.
- I don't eat rice that much now.
Here, Angel.
Hey, here.
- Ninay!
- Here!
Have some of this chicken soup.
- That looks wonderful.
- Eat while it's hot. Here.
That's delicious and nutritious.
Hey, Gloria.
Angel said you don't cook vegetables.
That's wrong.
But she's the one who won't eat veggies!
Angel, eat vegetables. You heard Ninay.
- Make her eat vegetables.
- Ninay.
Ninay, sit down.
- Join us for lunch.
- Later. I need to clean the kitchen.
Go ahead.
Give me some soup.
Angel…
That's yummy for sure.
Do you cook chicken soup, Gloria?
I don't cook often
because I'm always at work.
So this one mostly eats take-out.
You should learn to cook.
Ask Ninay to teach you while you're here.
Ninay, thank you for cooking.
It's delicious.
It's perfect.
Gloria, have you sold
the in Solar Ventures, Inc properties?
I sold one.
- One?
- But that was a big account.
Just one?
Those offered in Tagaytay
are hot properties.
Well, I have other prospects
under negotiation already.
Those properties are great,
but they're also expensive, Ma,
so people have to consider it,
but I'm pretty sure…
they'll decide to buy it.
- I'll close those deals soon.
- You've been selling those for a while.
How can you become the top broker
if you don't sell more?
How's Raymund? How's his work?
He's concentrating on Cebu.
He might stay there,
since he opened a business.
That's good.
Mom--
Grandma? What's the matter?
- Ma?
- What's happening?
Ma?
What's happening to her?
- Ninay!
- It hurts!
Ninay!
Ninay, bring Mama's medicine here.
Ma?
Let's go to your room.
It hurts!
- Ninay!
- Ninay, the medicine!
- The medicine, please!
- It hurts!
Come, you should lie down.
Ma?
Is the medicine working?
Are you still in pain?
Mom?
What's Grandma's illness?
She has cancer.
Pancreatic cancer.
Will she get better?
She's given a few months to live.
I need to go.
Mom, I'll stay here for bit.
Up to you.
You look after her, all right?
I have to go.
Mom…
I won't take the summer class for now.
I'll stay here to take care of Grandma.
All right, you look after her.
Paul and I are going to Baguio.
Okay. Bye.
Grandma, who are you speaking to?
No one.
Why are you still up? It's late.
Let's go to sleep.
Come.
Grandma, what are you doing?
Oh! Nothing.
Just looking at my prom dress.
Here's the other one.
This one.
This is my prom dress before.
Let me see it on you.
Wow.
- Looks like it'll fit you.
- Grandma.
Turn around! I'm sure it suits you.
Looks beautiful.
Looks like it'll fit you.
Angel, try it on.
- What?
- I want to see you in it.
All right, I'll put in on in my room.
Okay, thank you! Good night.
YOUR GRANDMA IS SO ADORABLE!
MISS MINE NOW
Somehow there is assurance
that our people are being taken care of…
The President likewise guaranteed
the support of our government
to all affected families,
especially those who lost their homes
to this devastating flood.
Ten-year-old girl rescues
drowning cat during flood.
In the middle of waist-deep
flood waters in Barangay San Isidro,
a ten-year-old girl named Anna
became a hero when she risked her life
to save a drowning cat.
‪LOW PRESSURE SETS COURSE FOR REGION
Holding on to a rope--
Grandma?
CATHERINE DE LEON
TO CONCHA
TONIGHT, I CAN WRITE THE SADDEST LINES…
TO CATHERINE
DEAREST CATHERINE
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'LL EVER READ THIS
Grandma…
Who's Catherine?
Grandma, do you need help?
Yes, sure.
Grandma, how did you meet Catherine?
Catherine was my high school teacher.
But we became close
because of a planting activity.
She is fond of plants too.
My life revolved around school
and home then.
Maybe I was the only student
who got excited to attend class every day
because I got to see her.
Catherine.
She was alone.
An adopted child,
though treated like family.
She was like a sister to me.
More than a sister.
With her, I could show my true self.
She guided my life.
That was the happiest time in my life…
The days when we were together.
What happened afterwards?
My father had me transferred
to another school.
Before I graduated.
He didn't want me to be close to her.
He said she was a distraction
to my studies.
Grandma, do you want me to find Catherine?
Hey, let's go!
- Hurry up, bud.
- Wait, I'll just finish this game.
No need for that.
Why did you have to play here?
Our home WiFi got cut off.
Roger, about what I told you…
Can you drive me somewhere?
That's a tough request.
I need to borrow the car from Mommy.
And I only have a student's license.
Come on.
I'm almost done.
I'll drive, as long
as we go back immediately.
You worrywart!
Why, am I not your girlfriend?
This is the only time I asked you a favor.
Me, I always treated you.
True, but we need to go back immediately
because my mom might get mad.
She uses this van
for her delivery business.
Even if I lose my way
I'll find the road leading to you
You're my destination
It might get dim
But you'll still be my light
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Why do I thirst for your dance?
Why is it always you?
I won't let go, I'm yours, always yours
I'm cold, come here, stay with me
DR. LYDIA M. PROFETA
BUILDING
Sir, where's the faculty?
Where do they keep the records
of retired teachers?
Just go that way,
then you'll see it, ma'am.
All right, thank you.
All right, ma'am.
I'm looking for Catherine de Leon, sir.
Catherine de Leon.
What year was she here?
1974 or thereabouts.
1974…
- Fatima?
- Yes, sir.
Look for the records of Teacher Catherine…
- Okay.
- de Leon.
Year 1974.
You know, there's only a few
old-timer teachers like me here.
Many teachers transfer to private schools.
There are more
opportunities there, I guess.
So, you won't find
a lot of old-timers here now.
- You found Catherine's?
- Yes, these are her records.
Catherine de Leon.
Oh, I remember now.
Cathy! Yes, she was a teacher here.
Wait. It says here her address is 827…
- 827 B…
- B…
Peñafrancia Street…
Peñafrancia Street. Okay.
- Barangay Pio del Pilar…
- Barangay Pio?
- Yes.
- Del Pilar. All right.
- Paco, Manila.
Oh, okay.
Ma'am Cathy…
I remember she used to teach
English literature here.
As far as I recollect,
she used to sit in that area.
That's her favorite spot
when she's doing research.
This is Catherine's classroom.
This is where she teaches.
‪…but I had lost her.
Why do you need to find her?
They're just friends.
They are more than friends.
More than friends?
What do you mean?
They're lovers or something?
Yes?
They've had a deep bond
since they were young.
Not like you. You're shallow.
Huh?
You fuck!
Moron!
Hey!
- Are you an idiot?
- Hey, hey!
Can't you see where you're going?
- Roger, enough! Stop that!
- Use your eyes, shitbrain! Fuck you!
What if this had gotten a scratch?
If he'd hit us.
- My mother will kill me.
- You blockhead, if we had gotten caught,
you don't have a license!
Exactly, I have no license,
so I'm being careful,
but he has to bump me!
Street moron.
That was close.
We couldn't take care
of Catherine anymore,
so we brought her
to a retirement home five years ago.
We can't give her the proper care.
I have health issues.
These stairs? It's too steep for me.
That's why I often sleep downstairs,
on that sofa.
It's just the two of us here.
Our kids have gone abroad, too.
Eat some more.
Take this with you, too.
Which home did you bring
Ma'am Catherine to?
She's in Asilo, in Sta. Ana.
All right.
Eat.
- Thank you.
- Eat more.
These are all for you.
- Wrap it and take it home.
- Come on, enough of that…
So you'll have snacks on your way.
- We need to go now.
- Are you sure?
Yes, sir, we already found the place.
- Thank you!
- Take care, then.
‪Bye-bye.
ASILO DE SAN VICENTE DE PAVL
Sister Fely.
Please come in.
This is Angel Torres,
the one I told you about.
You can leave them here. Have a seat.
How are you related to Catherine de Leon?
She's my grandmother's friend.
They haven't seen each other
for a long time.
Why are you looking for her?
I'm not sure, but they haven't
seen each other for years.
Do you have an ID, my child?
How did you find Catherine?
We searched the internet.
It's easy nowadays.
- Have you heard of AI?
- No.
You type the name of the person
you're looking for,
and the information will appear.
- Really? That's wonderful.
- Yes.
That's how I found my father.
Now I can easily stalk him online.
- Good morning, Sister Fely!
- Good morning.
This is Grandma Concha.
- Grandma, this is Sister Fely.
- Good morning.
Good morning to you.
Thank you for allowing us to visit.
You're welcome.
The relatives and friends
of our patients can visit anytime.
Sister, what is going on?
Sorry, we have many people here now
because we have lots of activities.
We have an event today.
- Can we enter now?
- Of course, you can go inside.
- Can my grandma join that?
- If she wants to, why not?
‪All right, then.
- Do we need to sign--
- Looks fun!
Yes, it's fun!
No need for that.
You don't need to show an ID.
- Up to what hour can we stay?
- Thank you.
As long as you like. It's fine.
You can park over there.
All right.
- Thank you, Sister.
- No problem, child.
Catherine?
Is that old telephone still working?
Before she lost her memory,
she said we shouldn't take it away
because she's waiting for a call.
We see no problem
with your request, Ms. Concha,
and you're on good terms with Mr. Durian.
You only need to sign a waiver
that states that we are no longer
responsible for Ms. Catherine's care.
I will.
Thank you, Sister.
- Thank you, Concha.
- You're welcome.
You know, we're old and retired.
We'd like to spend time
with our families in Canada,
so we can't always look after Catherine.
All our lives, we've been teaching.
Now we want to be with our families.
If Catherine hadn't gotten sick,
she'd still be teaching now.
I remember you.
You're the one who tried on
prom dresses in their house, right?
But she wasn't able to go
because Auntie Cielo died the next day.
Yes.
Angel, did you fart?
No, silly.
It stinks. I might throw up!
Catherine…
Did you poop?
My goodness!
- Angel, you have tissues?
- What the hell, Angel!
- I just borrowed the van from Mommy!
- Tissue, please.
I'm sorry.
You could've told me to drive
to the gas station.
You know she's sick.
Can you park on the side?
- Be careful!
- It's going to be wet.
It stinks!
You whine too much! I'm so sorry, Roger!
Don't touch me!
- Where are you going?
- I can't stand the stink!
- We can stop somewhere to use a restroom.
- Angel!
- What do we do about this?
- She pooped already.
What could I have done?
- I can't take it!
- I'll pay for the cleaning service.
- You should have said something!
- Get in. You might get run over!
- I really can't take it!
- Drive us home!
- I need to wash Catherine!
- Don't touch me!
- Let's go home!
- Hey! Let's go.
- No!
How can I drive when I can't breathe?
- Clean her up!
- Roger!
- Help your grandma wipe that shit!
- I need to bathe Catherine!
- Catherine needs to wash!
- Can we clean that if we're stuck here?
Get in! I'll pay for your carwash.
- I'm done!
- Get in the car!
Calm down. Don't cry.
Hey! Get in!
More soap, so you'll feel fresh.
It hurts!
Ninay!
Grandma, why isn't Mom
the one caring for you?
Oh, your mother is very busy.
I'm content to have Ninay.
And you're here.
Yes, but Mom can give you better care,
since she's your daughter, right?
Your mother and I,
we didn't develop a close relationship.
Even as a child…
she's been independent.
It's as if she didn't need us.
She grew up with me
and your grandpa bickering constantly.
We couldn't give her enough love.
Is that why she acts that way with Dad?
Maybe.
She wants to be alone.
She prefers to survive on her own.
Is that wrong?
Not exactly.
But our hearts should remain connected
to the people we love.
Even if there's distance between us,
our ties should stay.
It's not about the physical presence.
True love lives in the heart
of the one you love,
even if she's far away from you.
Ninay.
Ni--
Has Catherine eaten?
Yes, I've fed her.
Where is she?
She's there.
Again!
Hey!
That's challenging.
Again?
Look at us!
You're a better dancer than I am, Grandma!
You need to eat.
Swallow it.
Say ah!
Open up.
That's it! Very good!
More? Look at you.
No more!
‪I don't like.
Are you full?
You don't want to eat more?
You've eaten enough?
- We'll just dye
- What is that?
- those white hairs of yours.
- Who are you?
Ouch, it hurts!
This will be quick. This won't hurt you.
It hurts!
Why do this?
Who are you?
Why?
I said it hurts! Hurts so much!
- It hurts! Stop it!
- Okay. No more.
Stop it!
Now there's a stain on the floor.
I'll wipe it.
Who are you? Why are you doing this to me?
- Wait a second.
- Who are you?
No more!
- Stop, I said.
- It hurts!
- I'll stop, Catherine.
Stop it!
Okay, I'll stop.
Yes, it hurts.
It hurts…
Does it still hurt?
Okay.
Let's wash up.
Catherine…
You might not remember this,
but I want to thank you.
The evening you came to my house
so I could try on the prom dress
you gave me,
and we spent the whole night together…
That's the happiest day of my life.
I felt how much you loved me,
what we meant to each other.
I wanted to feel each second.
I wished for time to stop.
So we could remain
in that embrace forever.
But that's the same hour
our world crumbled.
After that night,
- my whole life changed.
- I knew it!
- My father became cold towards me.
- Animal!
- I'm sorry, Dad!
- You brought shame to this house!
You condoned this!
My mother fell ill,
and it led to her death.
- My father blamed me for everything.
- This is all your fault.
Even though they took me away from you,
- not once did I forget you.
- Your child is stubborn!
Let's go!
Catherine!
Your child is stubborn!
Do you want us to lock you up?
Do you want us to send you to Mindoro?
We'll send you to your relatives,
so that woman can't reach you!
He married me off to Armando.
It produced a child.
Still, it's you who owned my heart.
I never thought there'd come a time
when we'd meet again.
But even if you don't remember,
I know that…
in your heart, you felt like I did.
How much we loved each other.
LOVE POEMS
PABLO NERUDA
Concha…
Concha.
Concha?
Why does the sun go on shining?
Why does the sea rush to shore?
Don't they know it's the end of the world?
'Cause you don't love me anymore
Why do the birds go on singing?
Why do the stars glow above?
Don't they know it's the end of the world?
It ended when I lost your love
I wake up in the morning and I wonder
Why everything's the same as it was
I can't understand, no, I can't understand
How life goes on the way it does
Why does my heart go on beating?
Why do these eyes of mine cry?
Don't they know it's the end of the world?
It ended when you said goodbye
Catherine?
Concha?
Hey!
You're up so early.
- You're working already!
- Look.
- What happened?
- Poor bird.
It fell.
- What happened? Is it dead?
- It's injured.
Poor thing.
Come inside. You're probably tired.
Come with me.
Who are you?
You're right, Grandma, it's beautiful.
It fits me perfectly.
What should I do now?
You're already gone.
What happens to me now?
Where do I go?
Nobody wants me.
What happens to me and Grandma Catherine?
I don't know what to do, Grandma.
Grandma…
Just don't forsake me.
I can't do this alone.
Please continue guiding me, all right?
Even if it's hard,
I will try to wake up every day for you.
I will choose
to be a good person because of you.
Embarrassing. Our guests had to wait!
Are you going to be fine?
Uncle! You're here.
Traffic's crazy.
Hi.
You've been waiting a while? I'm sorry.
Traffic's crazy.
Have some snacks, please.
Please serve them drinks. It's so hot.
Angel.
Tell Ninay to serve the food, okay?
The guests are arriving from the funeral.
Are you guys comfortable?
I'll send some food for you.
Attend to them too, please.
Hey, Raymund!
because our flight got delayed.
Raymund's here.
Take a seat.
Who else is here?
There's Uncle William…
Grandma Ninay…
Catherine!
Stop this madness!
You! You've condoned them!
Catherine!
Your child is stubborn,
won't accept discipline!
Do you want us to lock you up?
Do you want us to send you to Mindoro?
We'll take you to your relatives,
where that woman can't reach you!
Catherine!
Don't worry, Grandma Catherine.
I'll be here for you.
I'll take care of you.
I am sure that is what my grandmother
would have wanted.
I will never abandon you.
This is not a sacrifice,
but a service,
and a way to thank you,
because the two of you showed me
what true love is.
Who are you?
My name is Angel.
- Angel wants you to eat.
- Who are you?
Please?
- Enough.
- Angel wants you to eat.
No more, no!
No more!
That's enough!
Who are you?
Let's take this off.
I'm Angel.
Who are you?
Angel.
Oh!
Grandma Catherine…
Grandma…
Let's eat.
Grandma Catherine…
Grandma…
Granny, do you need help crossing?
We'll walk with you.
The signal says "go" now.
Let's cross.
Thank you.
Don't be afraid. We can walk now.
Let's cross now, Granny.
Let's go.
- Dad, you promised me.
- All right, anytime.
Just make sure you focus on your studies.
- That's right.
- I will.
Cebu will always be there
if you want to visit.
All right.
- When you're ready, we will go there.
- Mom's here.
Okay. Okay.
- Hi.
- Hi, Uncle.
I heard your vacation was great.
Thank you for taking care of Angel.
Of course.
When can we have dinner together?
Whenever you're available.
We're free anytime.
We'll message you.
I'm sure we'll find a common schedule.
All right.
Go on, Dad! I might be late for class.
- I love you.
- Take care.
- Study hard, okay?
- Yes, I will!
- How are you, Mom?
- Had fun?
- Yes, super fun!
- That's good, baby!
Here's your money.
Let me know if you need anything else.
That should be enough. Don't lose it.
Hey, don't miss our dinner.
- All right!
- I'll pick you up.
Really? Sure.
- I'll see you again?
- Of course.
- Bye, Uncle.
- Study well!
- I will.
- Bye!