(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Scenes with child actors
followed production guidelines.)
I'm saying this loud and clear.
I, Im Ju Hyeong, chose him.
This man is a resident of Yeonri-ri
from now on.
You got that?
Yes.
Seong Tae Hun.
I won't hold back today...
and eat as much as I want.
In that case, I'd better go ahead...
and prepare a feast for everyone.
Big sis.
Thank you...
so much.
If it weren't for that fund,
I don't know what would've happened to me.
- Honey...
- It's fine.
I'm just glad everything's settled now.
Thanks to you, I paid everything back.
Goodness.
But I don't know
how to repay this kindness.
Honestly, I was in agony by myself
without being able to tell my husband.
You saved my whole family.
In that case,
let's just say, as an older sister,
I looked after my younger sister.
Big sis.
Little sis.
Honey.
Goodness.
What are you talking about?
What money did you pay back?
Honey, it's not what you think.
What did you help her with?
You see...
Did you get into some kind of trouble?
Explain it to me.
Debt? What is this about?
The moms I borrowed money from...
came here, looking for me.
Why...
didn't you tell me?
You didn't say it was a demotion,
but honestly, that's what it looked like.
How could I tell someone
who already sacrificed for the family...
that I lost our kids' tuition too?
Even so, you should've told me!
A village fund?
Do you even know what kind of money
that is? How can you accept it?
That...
Ms. Nam gave it to me out of generosity.
She made an excuse to do so.
Why does she need $20,000?
It's my wife's insurance money.
Even so, how could you accept that money?
Ms. Nam put in her own money too.
Is everything solved now
because you paid it back with that money?
Is that so?
Isn't this debt too?
It's an even heavier one.
Now you own them emotionally too.
Yes, I know I was foolish.
But what was I supposed to do?
I had to educate our kids,
but we were always short on money.
How was I supposed to know it was a scam?
(MAT STORY)
Mr. Seong.
Your internal loan application
has been approved.
Since it's an internal loan,
the interest rate is relatively low,
but the repayment period
will be quite tight.
What do you mean?
As you can see here,
the full amount must be paid back
before you leave the company.
(Internal Loan Agreement)
(EP 11 At the Edge of a Cliff
To Be Or Not To Be)
(That Is The Question)
(Executive Office)
Come in.
Hey.
Did you call for me, sir?
You're here, Mr. Seong.
Have a seat.
I think it's time you knew.
We're planning...
to build Mat Story's third factory
on the Yeonri-ri site.
A factory?
It'll be a smart factory, so it won't
even need much manpower.
That land in Yeonri-ri...
is the perfect location.
You should produce a harvest
more valuable than cabbage...
with your own hands, Mr. Seong.
The company will help you do your part,
in its own way.
Mr. Seong.
No, sir. We can't build a factory
on that land.
What do you mean, we can't?
The people there...
have lived for generations
trusting that land and farming it.
To them, it's not just land.
It's their livelihood, their life.
I've been there and seen it. I know.
If you build a factory there, they will...
Mr. Seong.
I know you care,
but business isn't run on feelings.
More importantly,
the villagers have already
given their consent.
(Mat Story Third Factory
Establishment Consent Form)
Wait.
This is the list
for the free fertilizer distribution.
I personally...
(Mat Story Third Factory
Establishment Consent Form)
This can't be.
The title should be...
(Mat Story Third Factory
Establishment Consent Form)
Yeonri-ri residents.
Mat Story is giving away...
premium fertilizer for free.
Please sign. Right here.
You know, people's hearts...
It's hard to get past the threshold.
But once you're in, they stop questioning.
And be sure to organize
and submit the residents' list.
(Mat Story Third Factory
Establishment Consent Form)
You did great work.
It isn't easy to go to each villager...
and collect their signatures.
Thanks to you, construction will go
very smoothly.
Just stay on my side...
and enjoy the result of this list.
I know how country people are.
They talk about being family
and being one,
but the real family you want to protect...
isn't them, right?
There's no issue with the schedule,
so don't worry.
Let's just push it through.
Okay.
Why did you report falsified information
to Mr. Bae?
Let's talk later.
What I submitted...
was a list of recipients
for the free fertilizer program.
How did that turn into
a factory consent document...
and get approved?
You were so busy,
so I did it for you.
Business is all about timing.
This is clearly document falsification.
I'm going to correct this.
So what? Are you going to become
a whistleblower?
Well...
There's a long line of people...
who want to take your position.
If you don't like it,
you can always leave.
Why are you getting so worked up?
Is that a threat?
No.
I'm just helping you understand
your place.
I heard you took out
an internal loan today.
You're digging into my personal life now?
Digging? Not at all.
I just happened to find out.
The burden of being
the head of the family.
Watching you struggle like this
just to protect your family...
It almost brings me to tears sometimes.
Let me ask you just one thing.
Why Yeonri-ri?
What?
There are factory sites
all over the country.
So why Simwoo-myeon Yeonri-ri
of all places?
That's...
something the company decides.
Stop asking pointless questions.
The Yeonri-ri seedling
unsuitability report.
Go and sign that.
You're dragging out something
that should've been finished already.
(CEO Kong of Hyeongam Construction)
Go.
Go and do your work.
(Yeonri-ri)
Don't just sit there.
Come on.
Come on. Cheers.
He put effort into making this.
Just one sip, Dad.
Mom. Dad. Guess what this is made of.
I don't know.
Black raspberry?
Omija berries.
Ta da.
This is omija?
You couldn't tell, right?
Ji Cheon made it using a special recipe.
It's called omija because it has
five different flavors.
Sweet, bitter, sour, spicy, and salty.
I tasted omija for the first time
in Yeonri-ri.
It might sound presumptuous,
but the taste is just like life.
Goodness.
Joy, anger, sorrow, and happiness
are all over the place, just like life.
From those flavors,
I focused on the sweet, bitter,
and sour taste...
to make this omija mojito.
Omija mojito.
Wow.
Yes.
It's the taste of life.
It's medicine.
This is amazing.
Cheers.
- Okay.
- Everybody, cheers.
Cheers.
Ji Cheon.
You...
That omija mojito was really good.
In the future,
even if someone comes and tries...
to sweet-talk you
into giving them the recipe,
don't give it to them.
Let's go.
Definitely don't give it to people
like that.
It's Seong Tae Hun.
Look. It's our hero, Seong Tae Hun.
Thanks to you,
the people of Yeonri-ri
can finally sleep peacefully.
So we prepared an appreciation plaque.
But that foolish Wang Dong Sik
didn't bring it.
So I'll get it myself tomorrow...
and give it to you.
I don't need a plaque.
What do you mean?
You should accept it, of course.
The father helps out with work,
and the son helps out with his drink.
Mr. Seong and Seong Ji Cheon.
May you become rich.
That omija thing.
What was it called again?
- Mojito.
- Maldives?
Have you tried that omija mojito?
It's incredible. You should make him one.
It's sweet and delicious.
You should take your father home.
Are you treating me like I'm drunk?
I'm not drunk.
You're trying to send me home.
Let's see. Where's my house again?
Look. I'm going home.
Omija...
I'm saying this loud and clear.
This man is a resident of Yeonri-ri
from now on.
You got that?
Yes.
Seong Tae Hun.
We're planning...
to build Mat Story's third factory
on the Yeonri-ri site.
(Wang Dong Hardware)
It's dazzling.
Look at that shine. It's great.
Look at that edge. It could cut me.
That's sharp!
You're here.
- Are you finished?
- Yes.
- Is it done? Let me see.
- Take a look.
The appreciation plaque. Seong Tae Hun.
It's awesome.
It's great.
I, the village chief, should present it.
Yes, of course.
But I saw him on the way to work.
It looked like Mr. Seong
was headed somewhere.
You know the livestock shed
past the field over there?
The livestock shed?
I'm doing what I was told.
What are you doing here?
Was it from the time you were assigned
to the Yeonri-ri branch?
That you got on the same boat as Mr. Choi.
You told me...
that I'm just like you.
I finally understand what you meant.
A situation where you bite the bait
thrown by someone like Mr. Choi...
and end up making others
cry tears of blood.
That's what you were trying to say, right?
Tell me! Why Yeonri-ri?
Mr. Choi didn't see...
this land as farmland from the beginning.
He probably had another use
for it in mind.
Another use?
What's this?
I didn't know there was a place like this.
It's a nice setup.
Are you in there, Tae Hun?
What is this place?
There you are.
Your plaque is ready.
Hello. Let me...
Let me say hello.
I don't think we've properly met.
What are you doing here?
How dare you!
Calm down.
Calm down and let's talk.
Let go.
Do you even know what he did to Yeonri-ri?
Hey.
Wait.
So...
what do you mean
you won't pay for the cabbage?
(Ten years ago)
How dare you bring us
cabbage contaminated with chemicals?
They found an excessive amount
of pesticide.
How dare you.
That can't be true.
Our cabbage was grown
only with eco-friendly pesticides!
Let's go.
No, please. You can't leave like this.
Please help us.
Everyone in our village depends
on this land to survive.
Please help us. Please save us.
Please?
Don't touch me with those filthy hands.
Come on.
This is a breach of contract, okay?
Just be glad we're not charging penalties.
How dare you.
You...
Are you even human?
Didn't you tell us to trust you?
When I was the youth leader,
they came with a business proposal.
They said they'd turn Yeonri-ri
into a cabbage specialty region,
talking about mutual growth.
Do you know what Mat Story did...
with the cabbage our people worked
so hard to grow?
Our Yeonri-ri cabbage is clean.
We raised each cabbage...
like we were raising our own children.
Do you know how much care went into
growing each and every cabbage?
Please hear us out.
Our Yeonri-ri cabbage...
Please let it be inspected again.
Please inspect it once more.
You shouldn't do this to other people.
(Mat Story deceived
the farmers of Yeonri-ri)
Do you know how many people
left the village after that?
My family ended up buried in debt too.
Now do you understand
why I hate Mat Story so much?
I just want to die
when I think about that time.
I had no idea about that.
But Tae Hun...
I trust you.
Goodness.
(Appreciation Plaque, Seong Tae Hun)
([Deposit] $30,000 Mat Story)
Honey.
What's wrong?
Did something happen today?
You...
felt quite frustrated that I stayed...
in the same position for years, right?
I'd be lying...
if I said I never did.
You only focused on research,
and you were never good
at pleasing your superiors.
But that's who you are. What can I do?
If I...
had been like them,
doing whatever it takes to climb up,
would our lives be different now?
Why would you think about that...
out of the blue?
I've just...
had a lot...
on my mind lately.
Mom.
Yes?
Goodness.
This is my friend. Her name is Han Wu Ju.
Hello.
I see.
Hi.
I was told never to visit
a friend's house empty-handed.
My dad told me to bring this.
This Yakdol pork is really good.
I've heard...
this is really good.
It's also good for your health.
He said it'll taste even better
if everyone eats it together.
Give me a little time.
I'll grill it for you right away.
Okay.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Do you want to see my pea plant?
It's grown more since last time.
That? Yes.
Ji Sang, you read some pretty hard books.
I read them in Canada.
Really?
Ji Sang, those are all my...
You got something in your mouth.
If there's any book you want to read,
you can take it.
Your little brother is so cute.
Your name is Ji Gu, right?
Yes.
Is Ji Sang your first boyfriend?
I...
When Ji Sang was in Canada, Carol...
Mom.
Mom, that Dol pork...
It's Yakdol pork.
There's plenty,
so eat up.
Enjoy your time here, Wu Ju.
Look after Ji Gu, okay?
I'm going out for a bit.
Okay, Mother.
I'll look after my brother.
Don't worry and be safe.
Okay.
It's good.
Try some kimbap too.
My goodness.
I told you to take your time
paying it back.
Why did you pay it back so quickly?
My husband was able to get a loan
from his company.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad it all worked out.
But Mr. Seong is going to have to work
even harder now.
I know.
My husband ended up
carrying an even heavier burden.
A married couple is one body.
When things get tough for him later,
you can do the same for him.
I'm home, honey.
What are you doing in the kitchen
at this hour?
And what happened to your hands?
I was practicing using a knife.
A knife?
You told me yourself.
Choices come with responsibility.
I...
want to properly learn how to cook.
Cook?
A knife used to cut a human body...
was always so terrifying to me.
But...
when it's used for cooking,
a knife is kind.
You've...
found your path.
Thanks, Dad.
Even when I decided to drop out on my own,
even when Mom left because of me,
you trusted me and waited.
I will do my best in life as your son.
Hi, Mr. Jeong.
Mr. Seong. I'm going to Yeonri-ri
tomorrow on a business trip.
This soon?
Mr. Choi said there's no time to delay
and told me to hurry.
He said that if you're busy,
I should get it started myself.
I'll see you tomorrow.
There's a long line of people...
who want to take your position.
I heard you took out
an internal loan today.
The full amount must be paid back
before you leave the company.
(Deposit $30,000 Mat Story)
I know how country people are.
That's how it is in Yeonri-ri.
They live with their lives laid bare
like this,
so how could I possibly turn
my back on them?
Here.
The same goes for you now.
Now that you've eaten this food,
you've taken a piece of everyone
in Yeonri-ri.
You got that?
I'm saying this loud and clear.
This man is a resident of Yeonri-ri
from now on.
You got that?
Seong Tae Hun.
They talk about being family
and being one,
but the real family you want to protect...
isn't them, right?
I don't care what I go through.
I can endure anything.
But not my family.
It's okay.
I will get through this no matter what
and go back.
Back to my position at Mat Story in Seoul.
In my life, there is no such word
as giving up.
You three and my cabbages.
Come out and eat breakfast, kids.
Cheon, Sang, and Gu.
Come and eat.
What's going on, honey?
You just came back from headquarters.
Are you going somewhere again today?
Mr. Jeong is coming here today.
I'll be back later.
Okay.
Honey. Eat breakfast before you go.
You're leaving without eating?
(Cafe Sunny)
Where's the powder?
Kids, where are you off to?
A workshop for menu development.
A date?
No. It really is a workshop.
Anyway, we'll be back later.
Goodbye, boss.
All right. Have a good time.
They are dating each other, right?
Are you going to let them?
They said it's a workshop.
Sure. You're so naive.
She's smiling with joy.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
There are so many pretty things.
This is so pretty.
This would totally suit you, Bo Mi.
It sparkles,
like you.
Let's try it on.
It's my gift to you.
What? For real?
Wow. It's so pretty.
Try one on too, Ji Cheon.
Me? Why would I?
If it suits you, we can wear them
as matching bracelets.
It looks better on you.
I know. But...
if it looks good on you,
we can both wear it as a couple.
Matching bracelets.
I can't wear things like this.
Why not? Just try it.
- Just once.
- No.
Why not? Just once.
Just once.
- Something smells fishy.
- Fishy?
- Your cutie is here, Hye Sun.
- Hello.
Where's the light bulb?
You didn't bring it?
Dong Sik will bring it.
Are they playing hooky already?
Bo Mi took him away.
What? Just the two of them?
Maybe you should be looking
for a wedding hall already.
No, they're just kids.
- No, I can't let her get married.
- Goodness.
You were calling out his name
with love the other day.
Your eyes were smitten with love.
Emergency! This is a huge problem!
- Emergency!
- What's wrong with him?
What is it?
Where's the light bulb?
That's not the issue right now.
- Didn't you see the news?
- The news?
What? Some idol's dating scandal
or something?
No.
They're building...
a Mat Story factory in Yeonri-ri.
In Yeonri-ri?
- A factory?
- Yes.
Take a look at this.
What?
Simwoo-myeon Yeonri-ri...
is selected as the site
for Mat Story's third factory?
My goodness.
Then what happens to all the farmland?
How can they build a factory here?
- Hey.
- Chief.
Where are you going?
Wait.
I've put together
a full list of landowners.
But Mr. Seong...
I heard you've grown quite attached
to the residents here.
It won't be easy convincing them
to sell, right?
(List of Landowners
in Mat Story Third Factory Site)
(Kang Sang Jin)
This is livestock land.
But he's the only one
who's not from this village.
That land?
The ownership changed about ten years ago.
Did you set up a separate meeting
with him?
Not yet.
I was planning to contact
the current residents of Yeonri-ri first.
I'll do it.
What are you talking about
out of the blue?
Are you telling me to sell this land?
The company has already set...
compensation guidelines.
Cooperating will be in your best interest.
He's right, sir.
Up to this point will be part of
the factory site development.
You see this here?
If you look here, from here...
There he is. Goodness.
Mr. Seong.
Seong Tae Hun.
Why aren't you answering your phone?
Goodness.
I saw a weird article.
It says Mat Story is building
a factory here.
How ridiculous.
If you've seen the article,
then it'll be easier to explain.
That's what's going to happen.
You think this is some kind of a joke?
What in the world are you talking about?
We'll begin the land acquisition process
starting today.
Please cooperate in persuading
the villagers.
Is something wrong?
Is the company forcing you to do this?
It was Noh Hyeon Gap, wasn't it?
You've been like this ever since
you met that jerk.
Does he have something on you?
I'll go talk to him. Wait here.
Stay right here.
If the village chief's reacting like that,
cooperation might be difficult
moving forward.
Let's go.
You're not going to wait for the chief?
Please cooperate with us.
Noh Hyeon Gap.
You jerk. You're here, aren't you?
You.
What did you say to Seong Tae Hun?
What did you say to turn that bear
into a snake?
What did you say to him?
Tell me.
Should we end this once and for all?
You got something, don't you?
Unbelievable.
This is that document from ten years ago.
What are you up to?
They found an excessive amount
of pesticide.
How dare you.
(Analysis Report)
(Written by Seong Tae Hun)
We were completely fooled.
That report from ten years ago...
The one that ruined our cabbage
saying it was contaminated...
The one who wrote that piece of paper...
was Seong Tae Hun.
Are you serious?
There's no way.
I checked it myself.
He came to us pretending not to know,
gained our trust, and waited
for the right moment to betray us.
Unbelievable.
Everyone.
They can never build a factory here, okay?
- Okay.
- Of course not.
All right.
They must buy the land to build a factory.
Hey.
Please say something.
Is what the chief said true?
Since you're all here,
it'll be easier to tell you.
It has been finalized...
that Mat Story's third factory
will be built in Yeonri-ri.
What?
What are you talking about?
For smooth progress,
we need your cooperation.
Please...
sell your land.
Mr. Seong.
How can you say such a thing?
We thought of you as family.
How could you do this to us?
Tell us.
Are all these things true?
Selling the land...
isn't a bad thing for you either.
The compensation has been fairly set,
and I'll explain everything one by one...
Shut your mouth.
You scumbag.
How dare you.
Why are you doing this?
Even if you respond emotionally,
the outcome won't change.
Unbelievable.
You animal.
How dare you!
I'll come back another time.
Traitor! Don't ever come back.
Get out of our village.
Mom, Dad. You're back.
We'll make you something nutritious.
Dad.
Mom.
Why is Dad like that?
You should go home.
What?
Mother. Did I do something wrong?
This is an adult matter.
He's burning with anger today,
and it won't cool down easily.
Mom. Dad.
Honey, you're home.
Honey.
What happened?
What is all this?
There was an incident.
I think something happened
to village chief's family.
What?
Goodness.
This isn't your wrongdoing, is it?
Right?
Please take one and read it.
Please pass it back.
Those who received free fertilizer...
have already been listed as
having agreed to the factory construction.
What?
When?
Those...
who sell their land
during the first acquisition period...
will receive an additional compensation
of $30,000.
$30,000?
Then it's better to sell.
These are the most considerate terms
the company can offer.
Don't miss this opportunity...
and please make a quick decision.
You said it was free fertilizer,
and now you're saying it was
a consent for the factory? How ridiculous.
I only took the fertilizer
because I trusted the village chief.
How could this happen?
Let's be honest here.
Isn't it actually better for us to sell?
What?
Are you saying
you're going to sell your land?
If Mat Story offers a fair price,
I'll sell too.
Exactly.
I should help with my kids' rent.
That's right.
You're going to destroy
the whole village...
over a bit of money?
- Don't be ridiculous!
- We can't sell the land.
Come here.
Stop fighting. This is crazy.
Enough!
This is all my fault.
We've known each other our whole lives.
What are we doing right now?
What?
Ten years ago, because of my incompetence,
I broke your hearts.
This time too...
Even if it costs me everything,
I'll take full responsibility.
Please trust me just this once.
Please trust me...
Ju Hyeong.
Chief.
Seong Tae Hun.
Are you really a monster?
There's some misunderstanding...
This isn't something
to handle emotionally.
It's company business.
Company business?
Turning people who've been like brothers
for 30 years against each other...
over a bit of money.
That's company business?
Doing this to them...
Does it put you at ease?
This is the only way.
You should think carefully too.
The company won't stop.
Good work today.
Mr. Jeong.
What was this compensation plan based on?
That was directly instructed by Mr. Choi.
Directly?
So the compensation
will definitely be paid as is?
I'm not sure.
I also thought the amount was excessive.
But maybe it's just because they need
to secure the land first.
So it's bait?
I don't know.
I just do what I'm told.
I'll go meet the other residents.
Go ahead.
(Yeonri-ri Land Acquisition
and Farm Support Notice)
How's the land purchasing going?
I was actually just about to call you.
About the first compensation plan.
The amount seems to be set quite high.
Is it okay to proceed like this?
That's...
something to discuss after we get them
to sign the contract.
Don't be so naive.
Are you presenting false conditions
to the residents?
Leave that to Mr. Jeong.
The seedling unsuitability report
we sent earlier.
I called you to see when you will sign it.
One report from you,
former top researcher of Mat Story,
declaring the crops
grown in Yeonri-ri unsuitable...
would finish everything.
You know that better than anyone.
We need to finish
acquiring the land first...
to avoid complications with the paperwork.
I'll complete the land acquisition first,
then handle it.
Goodbye.
What's he doing here?
Unbelievable.
You're late, Ji Cheon.
I wasn't sure if I should come.
Is it okay?
Of course.
Adult matters should be handled by adults.
It's him.
- Let's go.
He's the son of Mat Story, right?
Let's go.
Where are you going?
At least finish eating first.
I guess they were done eating.
Bo Mi.
I ran into your mother on the way here.
She asked you to stop by the salon.
My mom?
Why didn't she just call?
I'll be right back, Ji Cheon.
Okay.
Would you like an Americano?
It feels uneasy...
to see everyone including Bo Mi trying
not to make you feel uncomfortable, right?
You weren't exactly welcomed
from the beginning.
What exactly are you trying to say?
Honestly,
the way you are right now looks pathetic.
I know.
Even if I can't do anything right now,
I'll find a way to change things soon.
Until then, I'll keep coming here.
And from now on,
I'll protect Bo Mi.
That mindset is enough.
When you feel like you can't do anything,
just focus on one thing.
See if the person you love...
is crying or smiling.
Good luck.
What was that? My mom said
she never asked for me.
Did Officer Park leave?
Yes.
Just one thing.
Didn't you hear what I said?
Just sell your land, Chief.
Then I won't approach anyone else.
Your land connects to the factory site.
If we secure that,
the company won't...
try to expand any further.
If word gets out that I sold my land,
everyone else will start lining up
to sell too. That's what you're saying?
Wow.
Thinking about exploiting others...
hasn't changed at all, has it?
I guess I should pay the price
for trusting you, right?
Go ahead and buy my land.
In return,
don't you dare go to anyone else
and ask for their land.
You know what?
Every corner of this village
is owned by someone.
You won't be able to do anything
without their permission.
I'll be watching closely...
to see what you do with that land.
You!
Have you lost your mind?
You're selling your land?
What are you, Jesus?
Buddha?
Why do you always carry the cross
all by yourself?
Ten years ago too.
You ran around alone
as the village chief...
and ended up completely heartbroken.
And you're doing it again?
You think becoming a fool alone...
will fix everything?
How do you even bear
to show your face around here?
Leave.
Don't even set foot in our yard.
Just go.
Leave!
Go.
Why you...
- Go!
- What's this?
What's wrong with her?
What's this?
It's salty. It must be sea salt.
Ju Hyeong.
I'm getting too tired now.
Look at our youngest, Mak Rae.
How long can I keep living like this,
working the soil?
It's nice and salty.
All the land is under Mak Rae's name.
We'll sell the land,
get a small apartment downtown,
and the three of us will live together.
We can't farm anymore.
Here's the contract.
Please stamp here.
I'll do it.
I don't have my seal.
Ju Hyeong.
Where's my seal?
What did you do with it?
I'll go bring it.
Just wait here. I'll go find it.
I'm going crazy here.
Dong Sik.
The chief isn't selling his land, is he?
Imagine why he's doing this.
He just couldn't stand...
watching the villagers fight like that.
Tell me.
Why are you so desperate to ruin us?
I'll see you at Mat Story.
Hey!
Seong Tae Hun.
Unbelievable.
I guess he's bent on seeing this through.
I never thought Mr. Seong could do this.
Goodness.
Is the chief all right?
Tell me, you jerk.
Is that all Yeonri-ri means to you?
Is that all I mean to you?
Tell me, you jerk. Tell me what happened.
Yes, Mr. Choi.
The land acquisition is still in progress.
Mr. Seong?
It seems like he's still persuading
the village chief.
You've made a good choice.
Set up the meeting then.
I think he's been persuaded.
The chief is going to sell his land.
All right.
(Yeonri-ri residents strongly oppose
factory construction)
(We are against building a factory
that threatens our livelihood)
(Shameless Mat Story, leave our home)
(Mat Story)
You'll be building a factory on my land.
So I figured I should come
see your faces myself.
So here I am.
You've made a wise decision, Chief.
In the end, all that remains
is trust, right?
You'll only hurt yourself if you resist.
You're sitting here in your nice office,
scheming how to suck the life
out of other people.
I just need to sign my name here, right?
Please sign here.
Once you make the move,
persuading the villagers
will only be a matter of time.
We'll make sure you're well taken care of.
We've set aside $300,000...
as an incentive for you,
including the land.
This is well above the market value.
Cash, of course.
We can't leave a trace.
It'll be clean and simple for both sides.
And you know, right?
There's a fee.
Thirty percent.
It's done.
Okay.
It's over.
Mr. Seong.
What are you two up to?
Sell the land of Yeonri-ri to you?
We wouldn't sell you
even a worthless scrap.
(You think it'll work)
You think it'll work?
Unbelievable.
When they're standing...
at the edge of a cliff,
where they can neither live or die,
people usually think about falling.
But...
a true farmer...
plants roots in the cracks of that cliff,
breaks through the wall,
and finds...
a third path.
(Cabbage Your Life)
(Epilogue)
If my dad finds out
we're meeting like this,
he'll rip all your hair out, Ji Cheon.
- He'll rip my hair out?
- Yes.
That's not good.
Bye.
I guess I won't lose my hair.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)