=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 6=
Thank you all
for coming today
to the final exhibition
curated by my father.
Even though he's gone,
the art he loved
will live on.
Let's all move over this way.
Everyone, please stay a moment.
I know
you were all my father's
closest friends.
So before we begin,
we've prepared something special.
Let's honor his memory through art.
We hope everyone will
leave a few brushstrokes
in his memory.
Xiaomi,
are you happy
with my arrangement?
In that case,
let's invite the new owner
of Comic gallery
to give us the first painting.
Come on.
Paint something for us.
I...
She used to be an award-winning artist.
Really.
Please, Miss Qiao.
Go ahead.
Our genius artist.
I wonder what she'll paint.
Xiaomi.
Let's see what you've got.
What, too shy to show off?
Don't tell me amnesia
made her forget how to paint too.
Xiaomi,
Dad's watching over you.
Is she nervous?
Just paint something.
(Dad.)
(I really can't paint anymore.)
(But why?)
(Why did losing my memory)
(make me forget how to paint too?)
It's okay.
Trust me.
I'm sorry. I'm late.
I've come back to marry you.
(Qin Yu... my fiancé?)
I'm your fiancé.
Go ahead.
Tell me first.
Why did you suddenly
want me to paint you?
What's wrong with wanting
to preserve my beauty?
Miss Qiao,
I believe I told you before.
I don't come cheap.
Name your price.
I can afford it.
One
voluntary kiss.
Deal?
Scared?
Just kidding.
I love painting.
And my favorite thing to paint
has always been you.
Enough talk.
Let's get started.
Would you mind taking off your jacket?
I'd rather not.
Miss Qiao,
time to pay up.
I...
Put it on my tab for now.
I'm going to change first.
Xiaomi,
just like you asked,
all the paintings we kept off display
and the ones gathering
dust in storage are here.
What are you up to?
Catching a thief.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Just go home.
(Qin Yu)
(It really was him.)
(He really painted my portrait.)
(Qiao Zhiwei was lying after all.)
How did you get in here?
Do you remember the day
I painted this portrait of you?
It was your 19th birthday.
You said
if it snowed in September,
you'd believe in miracles.
Don't you want to know
what else happened that day?
Not interested.
Stop pretending.
You're sweating.
Seeing me
has you all flustered, hasn't it?
The AC's broken.
Idiot.
Do you really have
no interest in our past at all?
Get out of my company.
Or I'll call the cops.
It's getting late.
You should head home.
If you still want
to believe in miracles,
come with me.
Qin Yu!
Do you know how annoying you are?
Don't try that on me.
Look up.
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
I know what you're afraid of.
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
But you have me.
From now on,
♪Let me go, set me free♪
you'll have nothing to be afraid of.
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪
Move the story along.
Cut the cheesy romance act.
Or you know the consequences.
I'm the main character.
How the story unfolds,
I call the shots.
Even if the fire was an accident,
what about Ye Xiaoduo's miserable life?
You caused all of it.
Could I be the killer?
How do you know you're not?
Liar.
Sc*mbag!
Qin Yu,
what the hell are you doing?
You've actually
fallen for Xiaomi,
haven't you?
So you think
I'm the one who should die.
Right?
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪