=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 10=
This place
is the old cultural center in Aiye Town.
Recently,
haven't you been worried
about the exhibition?
I brought you here to
pick out some paintings
that could be displayed
at the exhibition.
It'll help you relax a little too.
I feel like...
I've been here before.
Xiaomi.
This is where you used to study art.
(Morning Light)
I have absolutely no inspiration.
Xiaomi.
If you're tired, let's just go home.
You can paint tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
The Orange Light Cup is
the day after tomorrow.
This time, I have to take first place.
So, what are you
planning to paint?
Can you go easy on me?
Maybe don't paint so well?
How am I
supposed to do that?
Xiaomi, if you want to win,
you have to rely on your own skills.
Dummy.
You really don't get it.
If I don't win first place, my dad...
So what are you planning to paint?
I...
I haven't decided yet.
No way.
Really.
Come on, tell me.
Did you hide it from me?
Tell me.
I really haven't.
Please tell me.
I'm begging you.
What's going on?
I'm scared.
What's happening?
Don't be scared.
It's probably just a power outage.
Then turn it back on!
Hurry up, you dummy!
Well...
Look.
Got any inspiration now?
Just tell me!
See that beam of light on the canvas?
Doesn't it look like
hope in the darkness?
A sunrise.
Morning Light.
You're incredible, Qin Yu.
(Title: Morning Light;
Artist: Qiao Xiaomi)
Are you okay?
But...
did I really paint this?
Of course you did.
But...
you didn't paint it alone.
Otherwise, how do you think
you got that gold award?
You mean...
this painting...
was painted by both of us?
Right?
Then hurry up and tell me.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Maybe fate saw how
hard you worked before.
So it erased that memory on purpose.
Just to let you take it easy for once.
I guess you're right.
Out with the old, in with the new.
At worst,
I'll just switch careers.
Switch careers?
What are you going to do?
Bread.
From now on, I'll set up a stand here.
I've even thought of the name.
It'll be called...
Sweet Memories Lost.
Anyone who tells me a story
gets free bread.
I want to live in the present.
From now on, I'll open
a stall right here.
And help people get better.
If the elderly can't afford it,
I won't charge them a penny.
(Why is it that they look
completely different,)
(yet feel so alike?)
Why do I feel
like I've been here before too?
It feels like someone held my hand
and walked here with me.
Like this?
(How does she know that too?)
Thank you for bringing me here.
Compared to that cold,
busy city of Mancheng,
I like this place much more.
What do you like about it?
Its atmosphere. The
feeling of real life.
It's peaceful.
It's comfortable.
It makes you feel at ease.
After we graduate from college,
will you come back here?
Of course.
I like it here.
I like its atmosphere.
What atmosphere?
The feeling of real life.
Besides painting at the
old cultural center,
do we have
any other special memories here?
Back then,
that used to be a
traditional herbal clinic.
Now it's a convenience store.
The accident...
happened there that year.
Don't you remember?
Is anyone there?
Hello? Anyone?
Thank you for today.
I had a great time.
(I brought her to Aiye Town.)
(She was really happy today.)
(It's as if she's forgotten)
(what happened here.)
(She seems different.)
(Different from the Qiao Xiaomi
I used to know.)
(But for some reason,)
(sometimes I feel)
(that this difference)
(is strangely familiar.)
(I'm even starting to be drawn to her.)
(I really don't think)
(I can hate the Qiao Xiaomi
standing before me.)
(Should I keep doing this?)
You're drinking alone
without inviting me?
I didn't want to disturb your rest.
Qin Yu.
No.
Ji Ran.
Forget it.
A name isn't important.
It's just a name.
Qin Yu.
I've made a decision.
About what?
I've decided to stop dwelling on
getting my memories back.
I want to live in the present.
That's how people
should live, in the present.
♪We say good morning, we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is, the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪