=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 2=
I wish I could paint too.
Then I'd get to see Qiao Xiaomi
all the time in class.
You can pretend to be me
and go to class.
Relax.
No one's going to figure it out.
There are so many students
in the Art Department.
Just get to know her first.
You'll have plenty of chances later.
Trust me.
Take it easy.
Hold this for me.
Qin Yu!
Ji Ran, hold that for me.
I'm going after Xiaoduo!
(Qin Yu)
Qin Yu?
You're Qin Yu, the guy who always wins
first place in the city's
youth painting competition?
I...
I've seen every one of your paintings.
I love them all.
I've always wanted to meet you.
I never expected
that not only are you a great artist,
you're handsome too.
My name is Qin Yu.
A fire three years ago
changed the fate of all four of us.
Where's Xiaoduo?
Ye Xiaoduo, the girl
you're looking for, is dead.
My face was disfigured.
My best friend, Ji Ran, died.
I know I saved
the girl I loved, Ye Xiaoduo.
So why was it
her half-sister, Qiao Xiaomi
who survived?
To find out the truth,
I had surgery to look like Ji Ran.
The first person who fell for it
was her brother, Qiao Zhiwei.
Unbelievable.
You look exactly like him.
But
I do have my strengths.
I'm loyal.
It's been three years.
I've missed you every single day.
I've come back to marry you.
I'm your fiancé.
(Background Investigation Report)
Qin Yu.
Who are you, really?
Miss Qiao,
Dr. Chen has been waiting
for you for a while.
He's here again?
Let's do it another day.
I'm still exhausted.
But I looked him up.
He does have quite a reputation
in the field of psychology.
Beneath those bold red strokes
lies a sense of unease.
Yet beneath the blue tones,
there's a search for balance.
What a fascinating contradiction.
You must be Miss Qiao,
the owner of this gallery.
Hello.
What can I do for you?
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Chen Yue.
I'm a psychologist.
My specialty is research in art therapy.
Therapy?
That's right.
My team studies
and develops artworks
that help people process emotions
and better understand their inner world.
I've noticed
that many pieces in your gallery
align closely
with my research interests.
So I was wondering
whether you'd be interested
in collaborating with us
on art therapy programs
or related research projects
for specific groups.
That does sound interesting.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot to mention,
all of my projects are nonprofit.
There's no compensation involved.
If you're not interested and say no,
I won't be offended.
Miss Qiao, Mr. Qin is here again.
This is already the third day in a row.
Miss Qiao, where are you going?
I can't stop him, so I'm leaving.
But this is your company.
If anyone should leave,
it should be him.
Good point.
Then make him leave.
Yeah.
Why should I leave?
Take me away.
Take me far into the future.
I've told you several times already.
Miss Qiao really isn't here.
Take me away!
Cut the act.
Take me far into the future.
Stop acting!
Let him perform.
Xiaomi.
Come with me.
These are from three years ago.
After that incident,
I forgot everything.
I even forgot who I was.
My fiancé,
who keeps saying he loves me,
where were you
when I cried in front of a blank canvas
until sunrise?
Where were you
when I was in so much pain
that I couldn't sleep all night?
When I looked in the mirror
and saw my scars,
when even I couldn't stand
the sight of myself,
where were you?
Even if you're not lying,
then tell me this.
Why did you abandon me halfway through?
I know I owe you so much.
More than I could ever repay.
Xiaomi.
Give me two months.
Within two months,
I'll help you get your memories back,
pick up your paintbrush again,
and finish every painting here.
If I do it,
can you give me one more chance?
Let me spend the rest of my life,
everything I have,
making it up to you
and staying by your side.
Alright.
I promise.
Two months.
If you fail,
then get out of my life.
Zhiwei,
why the long face?
What's bothering you?
Tell me. Maybe I can help.
You help me?
Want another designer bag?
So that's what you think of me?
Stop beating around the bush.
Just say what you want.
Zhiwei,
I heard the gallery's
curatorial department is hiring.
That's exactly what I studied overseas.
As long as you say the word,
Xiaomi won't refuse.
Why don't you just ask Xiaomi yourself?
You know perfectly well
she doesn't remember anything.
Zhiwei,
if you're willing to help me,
I can help you
take back everything
that belongs to you.
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪