=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 8=
(Ji Ran,)
(Logic tells me you're gone.)
(But why does this so-called Qin Yu)
(have the exact same face as you?)
Xiaomi, you're back!
Zhiwei and I were just
talking about you.
I came to apologize.
That day,
I shouldn't have brought up
those painful memories.
Zhiwei's right.
We should all move on.
But some people
just can't let go of the past.
You said we're friends, right?
Of course.
You remembered?
That's great!
Then do you know Qin Yu?
Qin Yu?
Of course I do.
You two were head over heels.
But honestly,
he really is handsome.
Half the girls at school liked him.
As for the other half,
they were into Zhiwei.
Do you even know what handsome means?
Look at these brushstrokes.
It's copying the style
of early abstract expressionism.
But the colors are far too commercial.
And while the composition
looks bold,
it's actually quite conservative.
Now look at this one.
Technically flawless.
The ultimate academic style.
But where's the soul?
Where's the emotion?
There's nothing there.
A piece like this
has commercial value,
but no artistic value.
Are you even listening?
I didn't come here
for an art appreciation class.
For this exhibition,
as long as the paintings sell,
that's all that matters.
Qiao Xiaomi.
So you're running this gallery
just to sell paintings?
A commercial gallery
is a business after all.
Is that what you were after
when you first picked up a brush?
If you want to paint again,
you need passion.
You need to truly love it
from the bottom of your heart.
Just like loving someone.
Just knowing who they are isn't enough.
You have to feel it again.
Fall in love again
with that first heartbeat.
Right now,
I just want to cut loose for once.
After that,
we can talk about
love and all that.
Keep up, fiancé.
So this is what you meant
by "cutting loose"?
What else
did you think it meant?
Fine.
Then this time,
I'll cut loose with you.
But after that,
once we're done,
you'll follow my training plan.
Get back to painting.
Otherwise, I'll have reason to think
you're just dragging this out
until the two months are over.
You think I'm a sore loser?
A bet's a bet.
I just let my guard down earlier.
But from now on,
I'm getting serious.
You'd better do the same.
Give it everything you've got.
Hey.
Easy there.
You're a grown man.
Is this really necessary?
Don't touch it.
Xiaomi,
I admit that since I came back,
sometimes you feel like a stranger.
So much so that
it's like I don't know you at all.
But other times,
you feel so familiar.
So familiar that
it's like you've never changed.
Then in your memory,
what was I like?
Very pretty.
How shallow.
So how did you
end up falling for me?
Love
doesn't exactly follow logic.
You always say
we were deeply in love.
But you've never told me
how we got together.
That year,
at the city youth art competition,
you won second place.
Who got first?
Alright, stop.
Don't tell me.
Then what happened?
Then we ran into each other
on the street.
You picked up my sketchbook.
Then you asked me
to an art exhibition.
And then?
Then we got together.
You're lying.
What am I lying about?
I asked you out
to the exhibition?
That's right.
I...
I asked you out
to the exhibition.
Now that sounds believable.
Exactly.
She confessed to me.
And then?
How far did it go?
We kissed.
Who made the first move?
She did.
But honestly,
I still can't shake this feeling.
I'm afraid
that if she finds out I lied,
she'll hate me.
She likes you.
Whether you can paint or not,
she likes you.
Be a little more confident.
Girls like confident guys.
My dad bought me some new clothes.
I'll bring them to you tomorrow.
Really?
Like this.
Take this
and twist it into a loop.
Qin Yu, can you focus?
This hairstyle...
My arm...
Alright.
Hurry up.
Wait.
You dragged me out this late
just to do this?
How about
we do something more meaningful?
Less talking.
Just do it.
We're running out of time.
Running out of time for what?
Hurry up.
♪The bud is tinted into wisdom♪
♪Raising butterflies♪
♪Strong and radiant♪
♪Adorning the lilies♪
♪Weaving together clouds and poetry♪
♪Circling at the edge of sunset♪
♪Tears are distilled into piles of sand♪
♪The clouds gather fresh water♪
♪For another spring♪
♪My rose blooms high and far away♪
♪Yet it weeps beside my ear♪
Happy Birthday to You.
My birthday?
Surprised?
♪Tempering my cold eyes,
scorching my back♪
♪Cast into the ashes,
evolving into islands♪
♪In the end, I become
the one who can weave♪
♪Rivers that wind around♪
♪Watering these vines
to the ends of the earth♪
Don't tell me you're crying.
♪I am so heavy, yet so rich♪
♪Great disasters, ordinary joys♪
You're really crying?
No.
It's the candle smoke.
♪In exchange for♪
♪The richness of my soil♪
It's just...
it's been so long
since anyone celebrated my birthday.
Didn't I ever celebrate
your birthday before?
♪Yet it weeps beside my ear♪
♪Come walk along my secret path,
my diamond-like heart♪
♪From the ruins rise dazzling thorns♪
Thank you.
♪The footprints of angels and beasts♪
♪They are all a part of me♪
You're welcome.
♪Watering these vines
to the ends of the earth♪
♪I am so heavy, yet so rich♪
♪Great disasters, ordinary joys♪
♪Let them drift away with the wind♪
♪In exchange for
the richness of my soil♪
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪