=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 3=
Xiaomi,
listen to me.
If you've forgotten, just let it be.
Xiaomi,
I just heard from Zhiwei
that you've lost your memory.
Is that true?
Who are you?
Back in high school,
I bought breakfast for you every day.
You really don't remember me?
I'm Xu Yifei.
Xu Yifei?
That's right, Xiaomi.
I honestly never thought
I'd see you again.
If it weren't for Ye Xiaoduo,
you wouldn't have ended up
like this after that fire.
That scheming little witch
got exactly what she deserved.
I remember back in high school,
she was already manipulative.
Just thinking about her makes me mad.
Give me back my bag!
Or I'll...
Your bag?
You thief!
Give Xiaomi's phone back, right now!
Ye Xiaoduo,
are you asking for trouble?
Give it back!
Teacher!
Ye Xiaoduo!
You don't even remember her?
Ye Xiaoduo was your father's
illegitimate daughter.
Everyone knew she was jealous of you
and wanted to take everything you had.
I also heard
that she started the fire.
Xiaomi,
are you okay?
Xiaomi?
Didn't Dad say the fire was an accident?
Why did he never mention Ye Xiaoduo?
You're distracted.
It's not safe to drive like this.
I'll take you.
Don't ask me why I'm here.
And don't ask what I'm trying to do.
I'm your fiancé.
Of course I'm going
to keep an eye on you,
and protect you.
Do you know Ye Xiaoduo?
Of course.
She's your half-sister.
Did something come back to you?
You don't look well at all.
You need to relax.
How did I fall asleep?
You're asking me?
Where am I?
An herbal clinic.
Why am I at an herbal clinic?
I brought you here to help you relax.
As for why you fell asleep
the moment you walked in,
I have no idea.
It's been two hours already.
The scent here
feels so familiar to me.
It makes me feel safe.
The smell of mugwort.
Don't be afraid.
Take my hand.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
Who are you?
Who exactly are you?
Why did you bring me here?
What are you really after?
To help you relax.
And see if it helps you
remember anything.
What do you want me to remember?
Me.
What are you looking for?
Let me help.
If you dare gamble again,
I swear I'll kick you out.
What are you talking about,
my dear sister?
Father left you so much money.
Can you even spend it all?
Was Ye Xiaoduo really
Dad's illegitimate daughter?
If everything they said is true,
then why isn't there
a single trace of her
anywhere in this house?
Don't be afraid.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
Could it be
she's the girl from my dreams?
But why
didn't I feel
even the slightest bit
of hostility from her?
Xiaomi.
Xiaomi!
What a lunatic!
Morning, Xiaomi.
Look.
I picked these shoes just for you.
Perfect for a morning workout.
Do you even know what time it is?
Did you forget our agreement?
If you want to start painting again,
you need a healthy body first.
As long as you stop bothering me,
I'm perfectly healthy.
Fine.
But if you stay this weak,
everything in the Qiao family
will end up in Qiao Zhiwei's hands.
You could've waited until I woke up.
I'm going to change.
Let's start with a two-kilometer jog.
I'll teach you how to pace yourself
and breathe properly.
Do you know that waking up early
ruins the whole day?
You agreed to let me help you
recover your memories within two months.
For these two months,
you do as I say.
Unless
you can beat me.
See that streetlight over there?
Whoever gets there
first...
Relax your shoulders.
Lean your weight forward.
Swing your arms.
Let them drive your movement.
In through your nose,
out through your mouth.
That's it.
Just like that.
That voice...
What is it?
How can you run so fast?
Convinced now?
From now on, if you want to run,
do it yourself.
You got a head start, okay?
One more round.
Dr. Chen.
Qiao Xiaomi?
Why is it you?
I...
I've lost some of my memories.
I'd like to ask for your help.
Have you seen a psychologist before?
The doctor said
my chances of recovery were near zero.
From a psychological perspective,
memories can be rebuilt.
But you need a trigger.
It could be a place,
an object,
or perhaps...
a person.
A person?
Could that person
be Qin Yu?
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪