=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 9=
(She celebrated my birthday today.)
(But if she finds out
it's actually your birthday,)
(and realizes I'm not you,)
(will she be heartbroken?)
(No.)
(Right now, I am you.)
(I have to find out the
truth for all of you.)
(I have to find out)
(what exactly happened back then.)
(Ji Ran.)
(Happy birthday.)
What's wrong?
I don't want to lie to her anymore.
Tomorrow, I'm going
to tell her the truth.
No matter how it ends.
Every time she calls me Qin Yu,
I feel like I'm deceiving her feelings.
What worries me most right now
is that she doesn't
really like me at all,
but she likes the paintings you created.
What matters most is the heart.
When you love someone,
it's about the true feelings,
not anything else.
Your feelings for her are real,
and her feelings for
you are genuine too.
That's enough.
As for everything else,
it's really not that important.
How did you get in here?
I paid for the room.
I can come in whenever I want.
Come on, man. I told you to deceive her,
not fall in love with her.
Mr. Qiao.
That's easy for you to say.
If I didn't romance her,
how would I get her
to sign the agreement?
I'm running out of patience, sweetheart.
I'll speed things up.
Focus on the art exhibition.
You don't seriously want
to be my brother-in-law, do you?
(Rizhao Sun Park Travel Guide)
♪Everything was so beautiful
in my memories♪
♪In every photo,
you were always smiling♪
♪And that little cat by the window♪
♪Always stretching lazily♪
♪Sometimes I dream
about it without realizing♪
♪About us frozen in that embrace♪
♪And somehow, tears always come♪
♪As that old song
echoes in my ears again♪
Hey!
Liar!
Sc*mbag!
J*rk!
Either talk, or get out of the car.
And stay out of my life for good.
You're right.
I am a liar.
And the lies I've told you
are far more than you
could ever imagine.
I'm not Qin Yu.
My real name is Ji Ran.
Qin Yu was my best friend in college.
He loved painting.
I loved sports.
The first time we met,
somehow, you mistook me for Qin Yu.
And you said you liked my paintings.
The truth is, I used to
be a very honest person.
But at that moment,
I decided to tell the
first lie of my life.
Later, we got together.
I was very happy.
But I was also terrified.
I was terrified that one day,
it would all come out.
And sure enough,
you eventually learned the truth.
You were furious.
And we broke up.
After we broke up,
I went abroad.
I worked hard to become a better artist.
Hoping that one day,
I could become someone you'd love.
Then later,
I heard about your accident.
I was so worried about you.
You lost your memory.
But...
part of me felt relieved.
What gave me hope
was that it gave us a
chance to start over.
But what broke my heart
was that all those
beautiful memories we shared
were remembered by me alone.
It's been three years.
I thought I'd become a better person.
But I never expected
that I'd still be this cowardly.
I know you hate me.
And I hate who I am now, too.
So.
we really did have
a lot of happy times together,
didn't we?
♪We say good morning, we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is, the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪