=Episode 1=
(I once thought)
(I was going to lose her.)
(So...)
(I left behind everything I owned,)
(including)
(my properties,)
(the Comic gallery,)
(and)
(its entire collection,)
(every bit of it,)
(to my daughter,)
(Qiao Xiaomi,)
(as her sole heir.)
We will always love you
and always miss you.
Thank you all for coming
to my dad's memorial service.
Let's take a look back
at the work he loved most in his life.
Mr. Qiao,
after that fire,
Miss Qiao may develop
post-traumatic stress disorder.
From now on, she should avoid
anything related to fire if possible.
Understood.
Thank you, Dr. Lin.
You old fool.
You left your entire fortune
to this useless idiot
who can't remember a thing.
Aren't you worried she won't
be able to handle it?
So,
my dear sister,
do you like the gift I got you?
Qiao Xiaomi!
Get away from me!
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Who are you?
=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
You're awake.
You just fainted.
Have some warm water.
Xiaomi.
Do you really not remember me?
I'm Qin Yu.
I've come back to marry you.
I'm your fiancé.
They all said you had amnesia.
I didn't believe them.
You're taking advantage of me.
Isn't the one taking advantage of you
your beloved brother,
Qiao Zhiwei?
For you,
I'd be your fire in the cold.
In this house,
no one is allowed to mention
anything related to fire.
I don't know you.
Leave now.
Stop right there.
A fiancé who suddenly showed up
out of nowhere.
The grand gift I carefully prepared
was completely ruined by you.
Qiao Zhiwei,
to hurt Xiaomi,
you'd even sabotage
your own father's funeral.
It's been three years.
How are you still such a loser?
You dare call me a loser?
I hate it when people call me that.
Then let me show you
what I'm capable of!
You've got some nerve.
Today, I'll teach you a lesson.
If you're going to fight,
take it outside.
Get out, both of you!
Qiao Xiaomi,
is that any way to talk to your brother?
Show some respect.
No need to thank me.
Qiao Zhiwei,
listen carefully.
Starting today,
I'm the one in charge
of this family.
So you'd better learn
how a dog wags its tail.
Otherwise,
I don't mind leaving you with nothing.
Do you understand?
Let...
Let go of me first.
Fine.
As your brother,
I won't stoop to your level.
Enjoyed the show?
Three years apart,
and now you've learned
to train dogs too.
Then why are you still here? Get lost.
The thing is, this dog
doesn't train easily.
But
I do have my good points.
I'm loyal.
Don't you want to know
what you've forgotten?
Drink this tea,
and leave.
The day your father forced us apart,
we were both heartbroken.
But I promised you
that I'd come back for you.
It's been three years.
I've missed you every single day.
How touching.
But I don't believe you.
Why not?
Because my father wasn't
the man you claim he was.
He was barely laid to rest.
If you say one more thing
against him,
I really won't go easy on you.
That's okay!
I'll help you recover
your memories, little by little!
What a performance.
Keep it up.
Don't worry about me.
There's a role I'd like you to play.
Not sure if you're interested.
(July 7, 2022) (Every time
I dream of that fire, there's a girl...)
(March 26, 2024)
(Memories have an easel.)
What exactly
happened three years ago?
I'm Qin Yu.
I've come back to marry you.
I'm your fiancé.
It's been three years.
I've missed you every single day.
That's okay!
I'll help you recover
your memories, little by little!
Is Qin Yu really my fiancé?
(Qin Yu... My fiancé?)
Why did he choose to come back now?
Dad,
for the past three years,
you never allowed me
to bring up anything
related to the fire.
But I've never stopped
trying to recover my memories.
Don't worry.
I'll protect this family,
and find my true self.
I've waited three years.
This show is finally about to begin.
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪