=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 4=
What bad luck.
Qiao Zhiwei,
was Ye Xiaoduo really our sister?
I'm curious.
Do you want her to be,
or not?
I know she was Dad's
illegitimate daughter.
But why did no one ever talk about her?
Not you, and not Dad either.
Didn't you just say
she was illegitimate?
Keeping her hidden
isn't exactly surprising.
Were we ever mean to her?
Listen to yourself.
An older brother and sister
playing with their younger sister.
How is that being mean?
Especially you. As her big sister,
you loved playing with her the most
your special game.
What are you talking about?
You don't remember?
Your favorite special game.
What are you doing?
When you come home, could you
just stay in your little corner?
Stop wandering around here
and being an eyesore.
Give it back!
Cheap stuff is cheap.
What kind of junk is this?
It's not junk.
My mom made it for me by hand.
Didn't your mom make things for you too?
So you're jealous?
Jealous?
I'm jealous of you?
My silly little sister,
can't you tell what she's really saying?
She's mocking you for being motherless.
You can't let
this illegitimate girl beat you.
Otherwise, Dad will like her even more.
Say that again.
Say that again!
What are you staring at?
You got a problem?
I honestly don't get it.
Why do girls like you,
illegitimate daughters,
always so defiant?
Give it back.
Qiao Zhiwei!
Apologize.
How dare you raise
a hand to your sister?
Where are your manners?
Is that how your mother raised you?
Don't push me.
Or none of us will have a good time.
Just wait.
Did you remember something?
Back then,
I was the only one
who truly looked out for you.
Ye Xiaoduo had already lost her mother.
Why did you still bully her?
She's already dead.
Who are you saying all this for?
I'm all the family you have left.
Try being a little nicer to me.
And don't forget
my allowance from the old man.
First tell me how Ye Xiaoduo died.
Her?
She died because she was stupid.
Tell me, and I'll send
the money right away.
Sometimes fate really isn't fair.
One fire,
and some people die in the flames.
While others
inherit a fortune worth billions.
So...
that fire...
Ye Xiaoduo really started it?
What else would it be?
But Dad said it was an accident.
You're funny.
You were there.
And you're asking me?
Then why
wouldn't Dad let me be with Qin Yu?
Because he's a liar.
He said he could paint.
He said
you were the only one he'd ever love.
Too bad.
They were all lies.
Losing your memory
is a blessing, Xiaomi.
If
you really remembered your old self,
you might end up hating who you are now.
Enjoy the good life you have now.
And don't forget my allowance.
(Feb 15, 2023) (A faceless man appears.)
Because he's a liar.
He said
you were the only one he'd ever love.
(Jul 7, 2022) (A girl was in my dream.)
The fire you survived
is the same fire that killed her.
(Mar 26, 2024)
(Mar 26, 2024) (An easel in my memory.)
Xiaomi.
I've come back to marry you.
I'm your fiancé.
It's been three years.
I've missed you every single day.
Too bad.
They were all lies.
(Qin Yu, a liar?)
Ye Xiaoduo.
The fire.
Qin Yu.
Ye Xiaoduo is dead.
I've lost my memory.
Qin Yu vanished, then came back.
None of this can be a coincidence.
Qin Yu...
Why exactly did he come back?
Miss Qiao,
it took me a lot of effort
to acquire this painting
from a collector.
As for the style,
it perfectly matches
the style Mr. Qiao loved most.
Just look at the texture.
It fits perfectly
with your gallery's style.
Qin Yu, are you insane?
Who are you?
Are you crazy?
This painting...
It's worth millions!
Worth millions?
Do you really think
there's no one in this family
who knows art?
Or do you think
my fiancée is an easy target?
Caravaggio-style chiaroscuro,
yet it uses cadmium red,
a pigment made in the 19th century.
This isn't a forgery.
It's an insult to art history.
Y-You're talking nonsense!
This painting comes
with authentication papers!
With genuine old paintings,
the pigments seep
into the canvas itself.
But in this one,
the paint sits on the surface.
Would you like me
to call the authorities right now
and have them take a look
at your so-called
million-yuan masterpiece?
Before the force arrives,
the intent leads.
Go with the flow.
Borrow the force.
Redirect the force.
What's that?
Who's talking?
Are you okay?
You're a grown man.
Is it really that serious?
How about I take you to the hospital?
What's wrong with me isn't physical.
A hospital can't fix it.
I sent you the medical bill.
Go by yourself.
What do you take me for?
You went to all that trouble
to show up at my father's funeral.
And time after time,
you've come to my rescue.
Isn't it all for our family's money?
Even if
I wanted your family's money,
do you really think
a 200-yuan cash gift
would be enough to get rid of me?
Then how much do you want?
Name your price.
The only thing I've ever wanted
is for you to remember me.
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪