=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 5=
All I ever wanted
was for you to remember me.
Feeling sorry for me already?
At least you've got a conscience.
I'm just worried you'll
die at my company.
Quit pretending.
I know you care about me.
So, are you dying or not?
Die.
Just kiss me,
and I'll drop dead right now.
Since you know so much about art,
why not stay and help me?
Miss Qiao,
are you serious?
I don't come cheap.
How about I buy you dinner?
Let's go.
Why do you keep staring at me?
Just thinking.
You're a rich heiress,
and this
is your idea of a big meal?
Then what do you want to eat?
I want...
Tell me.
Are you working with Qiao Zhiwei?
I'm on your side.
Then where have you been
for the past three years?
What else would I be doing?
Missing you.
Why did you get close to me?
What are you really after?
I have three objectives.
You.
And you.
Was what I said really that gross?
You think I'm disgusting?
You actually look kinda
cute when you throw up.
Hold it in.
I'm warning you.
If you throw up on me,
I'll dump you on the side of the road.
Were you always this mean to me?
Of course.
Back then,
if you didn't listen,
I'd beat the crap out of you.
No wonder my dad didn't
want us together.
Because I'm his favorite daughter.
He'd never let anyone...
You brought me to a hotel?
This is my place.
I couldn't find an apartment,
so I'm staying here for now.
Just you wait.
I'm going to fight you till...
till...
daybreak.
Get some sleep.
We'll settle this tomorrow.
Come on, fight me.
Don't you want to?
I...
What are you hiding from?
Well.
Aren't you my fiancé?
What haven't I seen?
The hell you have.
Stay right there.
Don't move.
What?
Don't tell me we've never...
Nice body.
You...
Don't start acting crazy
just because you're drunk.
I'm warning you.
What do you want?
What do I want?
You really don't know?
Why are you pretending?
So who's pretending here, you or me?
Weren't you drunk?
Pop quiz.
What's my favorite flower?
Roses.
What's my favorite color?
Black.
Do I prefer cats or dogs?
Both.
Hot pot or barbecue?
Hot pot in summer, barbecue in winter.
Not one answer was right.
I don't like roses
because they have thorns.
I don't like black
because it's too depressing.
I've never had a cat or a dog,
so I wouldn't know.
As for hot pot and barbecue,
I don't like either.
Because I don't like
fire.
You're lying.
Aren't you?
No, you're the one
who's lying.
Because I like roses.
I like black.
I like cats and dogs.
I like hot pot in the summer
and barbecue in the winter.
You told me all that back then.
Because I liked them,
you liked them too.
So...
are you lying now,
or was it your past self who lied?
Why argue with someone who has amnesia?
Game over.
No matter who you are,
let's never see each other again.
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪