=Visage and Soul=
(The "Different Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 7=
Weren't you saying on the phone
the debt collectors broke your leg?
What a load of crap.
Xiaomi, Xiaomi.
I had no other choice.
You can't just leave me hanging, right?
Zhiwei,
is the money ready?
They're all waiting.
Mr. Luo.
Who are you? Do I know you?
Get out!
Xi... Xiaomi.
You've got to help me.
Please, help me.
Gotcha, didn't you?
Fine.
Got it.
Xiaomi.
What a coincidence.
Talk to you later.
I'm buying today.
A bunch of our classmates are inside.
Come join us.
Let's go.
They'll be thrilled to see you.
And you're still gorgeous.
You sure know what to say.
Come on.
Everyone, look who's here.
Qiao Xiaomi!
Xiaomi's still as pretty as ever.
Come on, have a seat.
She's here to celebrate
me getting hired at Comic gallery.
You all better drink with her.
You got a job at the gallery?
Yeah.
I was going to wait until I started
to surprise you.
I made it through every
round of interviews.
You'll be my boss from now on.
You're not mad I didn't
tell you sooner, are you?
Of course not. Congrats.
Oh, right.
This is our classmate, Li Xiaowen.
Remember her?
She used to let you copy her homework.
Xiaomi,
I heard you lost your memory.
Is that true?
I also heard Ye Xiaoduo did it.
Ye Xiaoduo was ruthless.
Back then, even if we all teamed up,
we still couldn't beat her.
Really?
I remember she bit me once.
This illegitimate daughter
of the Qiao family.
She always carried around
that ragged cloth bag.
Who knows what she kept inside.
Maybe she stole something from Xiaomi
and hid it in there.
Don't touch my stuff!
You parasite living off the Qiaos!
Why are you acting so tough?
Give it here!
She was terrifying back then.
Like a rabid dog.
That's why
you should stay away
from unstable people.
Otherwise, you might not
even know what hit you.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm gonna head out.
You guys have fun.
Xiaomi.
It's like that fire
turned her into a
completely different person.
She's not nearly as
spoiled as she used to be.
Her dad just passed away.
She's probably taking it hard.
Probably.
Come on.
Come on, drink up.
Are you okay,
Miss Qiao?
There are a lot of people here.
You should be careful.
How'd you get here so fast?
I turned around after a
call, and you were gone.
What are you doing here?
Don't touch me.
Thank you.
Sorry.
My fiancée hasn't been
feeling well lately.
It's okay.
You know each other?
No, we don't.
Really?
Miss Qiao,
if you're not feeling well,
you should head home and rest.
Then I'll get going.
Thank you, Dr. Chen.
(Ji Ran,)
(how can there be someone)
(who looks so much like you?)
(Or...)
(could it be that you never died?)
(Maybe, just like Miss Qiao,)
(you lost your memory.)
Zhiwei,
I tested her just now.
She really doesn't remember.
Who does she think she is?
Everything she has now
was given to her by you.
Zhiwei,
you're the true heir to the Qiao family.
Listen up.
I want her first-ever art show
to crash and burn.
Completely.
Pull it off, and I'll
pay whatever you want.
Got it, Zhiwei.
I'll do whatever you say.
But Qin Yu's always with her.
He's not easy to handle.
There's no one I can't handle.
Just do your job.
Especially you. As her big sister,
you loved playing with her the most
your special game.
Everyone knew she was jealous of you
and wanted to take everything you had.
I also heard that she started the fire.
(But Dad said it was an accident.)
(You're funny.)
You were there.
And you're asking me?
Why are you still here?
Stop trying to tough it out.
If you catch a cold and get sick,
who's going to honor that two-month bet?
Was I...
really that awful before?
Why would you think that?
Let me tell you something.
You're the kindest,
sweetest girl
I've ever met.
Past or present.
What exactly happened
between me and Ye Xiaoduo?
Don't you remember?
Your favorite special game.
Do you know Ye Xiaoduo?
She's your half-sister.
Don't be afraid.
Take my hand.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
Ye Xiaoduo had already lost her mother.
Why did we still bully her?
She's already dead.
Who are you saying all this for?
(Sometimes fate really isn't fair.)
(Some people)
(die in the flames.)
(While others)
(inherit a fortune worth billions.)
Let go of me!
What are you doing?
Move.
Xiaomi.
So in that dream,
you were the one hurting yourself.
When I woke up this morning,
I actually started
to hate myself a little.
I'll prescribe something
to help you sleep better.
By the way,
how do you feel lately
about that person?
My feelings toward him
are strange too.
Sometimes he feels familiar.
Sometimes he feels like a stranger.
I'd suggest
looking through old belongings.
Or maybe
go somewhere you two used to visit.
Dr. Chen,
if what I remember
is bound to make me miserable,
wouldn't it be better to stop now?
Take your medicine on time.
As for the answer,
I think deep down,
you already want to find it.
Hello.
It's you.
You look a lot like my younger brother.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Dr. Chen,
has Qiao Xiaomi come to see you?
Miss Qiao
did come to see me.
Why do you ask?
Why did she come to see you?
You're her fiancé.
Shouldn't you
be asking her that yourself?
Here's the thing, Dr. Chen.
Because of an accident,
she lost her memory.
But I'm not sure
whether she'll get it back.
I'm sorry, Mr. Qin.
Patient confidentiality
prevents me from saying more.
Sorry for the trouble.
So...
do you really want
Miss Qiao to regain her memory?
Of course I do.
She's my fiancée.
Alright.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
(She has to remember.)
(Otherwise, how will I know
who you really are?)
♪We say good morning,
we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is,
the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪