=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 9=
Shiqi!
Open the door!
It's Ouyang Qing.
I can see the light flickering.
Stop hiding.
I already saw you!
I'll tell my dad
that you're ignoring me.
Ouyang Shiqi!
Stop yelling in the dead of night.
We're trying to sleep.
I got dumped.
Do you have any sympathy?
I'll call the police!
Just you wait!
Ouyang Shiqi,
he said I was not good-looking.
He dumped me.
But I spent a whole year in England
eating nothing but fish and chips
just to be with him.
Ouyang Shiqi!
Officer,
I got my heart broken.
Man the decks.
Isn't it loud?
Should I take you home first?
You want a drink?
Who's the lightweight here?
Get drunk?
Why turn off the light
every time I knock?
This door
has a glass window.
I can see right in.
What's wrong?
Not feeling well?
Since you're free, let's talk.
Your mom told me
you drew monsters on those red socks
and gave them to your classmates.
Who's this supposed to be?
Wu Xiaoxuan's dad.
You captured his look perfectly.
Looks like a troll.
Who is this?
It's you.
Is that really
how I look in your eyes?
Ever since they said
you won the lottery,
you've changed.
Your eyes were never big,
but they used to have me in them.
And mom.
and my two grandmas.
And light.
But now,
you're just stuffed
with junk.
Is there light in my eyes now?
Do you know why
I gave my classmates socks?
Sharing. You're rich now.
There's no light.
Once
in my dream,
someone handed me a note
with a string of numbers on it.
They told me
it was Chen Liyang's number.
But two of the digits were smudged.
I couldn't make them out.
So I tried every combination.
I made 12 calls.
34 calls.
None was right.
No one answered.
Just as I was about
to make another call,
I woke up
and someone came in.
Who?
The police.
The police came.
Almost.
I almost succeeded.
What a shame.
(2018)
Happy birthday!
It's good.
No.
That's not the taste.
Not this.
Why is it wrong?
Why can't I make
the flavor right?
You eat longevity noodles
and you're supposed to live long.
Give the money back to them.
That money killed my father.
I don't want to see it again.
You shouldn't let her drink.
Who are you?
When she drinks,
it brings back a lot
of bad memories.
She'd be upset.
Take good care of her.
Don't cross the line.
I can't do it anymore.
Let me sit for a while.
I need a minute.
We built the houses above us
with our own hands.
Every angle is beautiful.
We built that house,
but we can't afford it.
A house that nice...
we can only look at it.
What can you do?
We don't have the money.
Money
is a wonderful thing.
We work so hard.
Why doesn't it ever come to us?
Isn't it right there?
Break through and we'll have it.
I can't dig anymore.
I'm starving.
Didn't you have dinner?
Just steamed buns with some pickles.
That's not very filling.
How about
we get something nice to eat?
What you left
has been found.
I know what to do.
As long as it belongs to Zinuo,
no one can take it from her.
(2011)
Zinuo feels insecure.
She's like a snail.
She needs
a shell to protect herself.
She has to carry it everywhere she goes.
It's exhausting for her.
Ms. Li is too strict with her.
She feels awful.
I'm the buffer
between her and her mom.
You're the same.
One day, if her mom
takes away her shell,
you should be her shell.
Don't worry.
I'll do
what I should do well.
Damei.
(Du Lei)
Hello.
The best way to honor someone who's gone
is to do what they
wanted you to do.
He left thirty million.
You take thirty million.
If he thought it was yours,
then it's yours.
Hello.
I've told you so many times.
Don't drink straight from the bottle.
It's unsanitary.
Pour it into a cup.
You don't even care
about how I'm feeling.
No, you just worry about the hygiene.
So heartless.
How could
others drink from it?
Sorry about that, sis.
Don't call her that.
She's my cousin, Ouyang Qing.
Yeah.
We're cousins.
Hello, Qing.
We were born into the same basin.
He's only three hours older than me,
but he's always bossing me around.
you help me keep him down from now on.
We're on the same side.
Take him down.
All wild
and flashy.
How can I go out wearing this?
It's so ugly.
And the color is red.
Like a red lantern.
6,999 yuan?
Oh, my god!
It's from my daughter.
Good-looking.
After tailing her for a few days,
I found
Wen Yitong's mom is very frugal.
She won't spend a penny
on anything unnecessary.
Now she
is in charge
of the family's groceries.
Every two days,
she will go to the wet market.
So going by this pattern,
tomorrow
(Grandma, don't forget fried chicken!)
is her market day.
She's a pretty girl,
but her handwriting is a mess.
Every time she goes to the wet market,
(Wet Market)
she'll first go to this place
to buy some vegetables first.
Then she takes a detour to here
and buy some meat.
There's a discount today,
Cut a piece from here.
Right about here.
Finally,
she'll go to the seafood section.
Got it.
So we strike
at the seafood section, right?
It's slippery there.
That won't work.
It's slippery, sure,
but it's also crowded.
Other people may disrupt our plan.
So what do we do?
One portion of popcorn chicken.
Large. Make it large.
Look.
When she comes out of the market,
we set up a roadblock
right here.
Always fixing the roads.
Roadwork during the day
is a huge hassle.
They weren't doing it just now.
She
must take
those stairs in that lane.
We'll pour the oil right there,
on those steps.
Those stairs have no handrails.
A slip.
She'll fall straight down.
Which scoundrel
has poured oil on the road?
After that,
I'd wait for her nearby.
What's the matter?
Why are you on the ground?
I fell.
Please help me up.
Okay.
Sorry about it,
but can you try to get up by yourself?
I can't move.
Who poured oil on the road?
Be careful, it's very slippery.
I'm currently in the alley
on Simingquan Road.
I just passed by this lane
when I saw this lady fall.
Now it's
1:32 p.m.
Madam,
can you try
to turn your head
to one side?
My head?
I can't move.
No good.
She's so painful
that she can't turn her head.
I'm calling an ambulance now.
I...
Madam,
I'm a migrant worker
from the countryside.
I'm poor.
Everything I earn
goes back to support my family.
Don't try to scam me.
No, I fell myself.
I'm not going to scam you.
Okay, these are the words I want.
I've recorded it as evidence.
Call my daughter.
Okay.
Don't panic.
Ouyang finally agreed
to return the money to us.
I really want
to burn my phone.
No house buying, no loans.
No travel, no retirement plans.
Is this Wen Yitong?
Is Fan Meijuan your mother?
What about my mom?
Well, it's like this.
I'm beside your mom.
As for her,
she tripped and fell.
She is in so much pain
that she can't move.
I called an ambulance for her.
We're heading to the People's Hospital.
The People's Hospital.
Hurry up.
Mom!
Hurry up!
Are you a relative?
No.
Not this one.
This one.
We're here, Madam.
We're here.
Is this Fan Meijuan?
Mom.
Yitong.
Be careful.
Mom,
it's fine.
- I fell.
- You're her family?
I know.
That's her bag.
It's fine.
Be careful.
Go check in and pay first.
I fell myself.
I didn't call ambulance immediately
because I was afraid
someone would
accuse me
and take all my money.
Please don't blame me.
To be honest,
I need to raise my daughter.
It's a heavy burden.
I can't afford the risk.
When the paramedics lifted her,
she said, "Be careful."
Do you know why?
She said the dress was new.
You bought it for her.
It was her first time wearing it.
The dress was very expensive.
She'd feel really bad if it gets dirty.
Madam, let me add you.
Sorry to take up your time.
I'll transfer you 5,000 yuan.
I didn't help her for the money.
Old people shouldn't fall.
A hit to the head and they're gone.
I'll transfer you 10,000.
You're living a hard life.
I told you
I didn't help her for the money.
I helped
for my own peace of mind.
I'll earn my own money.
My mother fell once too.
She fell into the bathtub.
Thank you.
We're from the same hometown.
Helping you was fate.
Just for peace of mind.
Alright.
I brought over a bowl of noodles.
I asked, "Hot or not?"
He at once got mad and said,
"I came to eat here.
Why are you kicking me out?"
I dared not say that again.
I'd just ask whether it's too hot.
That's hilarious.
I'm done.
It's good.
Did you make it?
My husband is a cook.
My mom is a dish washer.
As for me,
I cook and wash dishes.
I worked as a housekeeper
and a caregiver for ten years.
I used the money I made
to open a restaurant.
Those who came for noodles
were all regulars.
The landlord saw I was making money
and wanted to
raise the rent.
Then I found it no longer a good deal.
So I shut it down
and went back to work.
Either way, it's still making a living.
Yeah.
You're here.
Ms. Jiang
You're already eating?
I've eaten.
I don't know who made it for me,
but it's really good.
No chili, right?
No.
I used to be a caregiver.
I know what can be eaten
and what not.
Jiang
has a professional
nursing license.
Back at the hospital,
she had the best reputation.
The hem was torn.
I mended it.
You're so good at this.
I can't even tell where it was torn.
It looks brand new.
And you even washed it.
I bought two meals.
Have you eaten? Join me.
I already ate.
One for each of us.
I've eaten.
Time for your medicine.
Eat with us first.
Apply this
morning, noon, and night.
Since she was wearing a dress,
here and here are both swollen.
She is shy,
so you apply it for her.
I'll clear the table.
Okay.
Done eating?
Done.
I'll take these then.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's up?
She is diligent,
and she cooks well.
Quick and good at cooking.
Got it.
It's done, mom.
The doctor said it was not serious.
We can go home after observation.
Okay.
That's good.
Jiang,
my mom keeps praising you.
She said you were nice and diligent
and you cooked well.
Look.
If you're free in the days to come,
could you
take care of my mom for a few days?
Recently, we've
been very busy.
We're a bit tied up.
It would be great if you could come.
I am actually not very busy.
But I won't be at home...
Please, just come.
If you're free,
you can just come.
Just say yes.
Excuse me.
(Zhan)
I'll take a call.
Yu Ming.
You like her?
No.
Why did you stare at her like that?
Is it okay, Mom?
Alright.
Done eating?
Don't move.
Let him do it.
I'll do it.
You
and Shiqi...
I'm just staying here for a few days.
I'll move out once I find a place.
No worries.
Stay as long as you want.
Shiqi likes having people around.
The liveliness.
Right?
Is it usually
lively around here?
No.
Not lively.
Yeah.
It's really quiet.
You only miss
what you don't have.
Shiqi
seems to be outgoing.
In fact, he is an introvert.
And he is very reserved.
When I was in high school,
a lot of guys chased me.
So he went to my school
and beat them all up.
He even returned all the gifts
they'd given me.
Seriously.
He really cares about you.
He cares about you even more.
When I come alone,
he never cooks.
What do you want to drink?
I'll get it.
Anything is fine.
This girl is not bad.
Lock it down.
Don't talk nonsense.
She was driven out by her landlord.
I wanted to help her.
She is just sharing the place.
Mr. Ouyang,
do you really believe that yourself?
Why wouldn't I?
Keep lying.
Go ahead.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Don't miss out.
The way her hair is done,
that curvy style.
It's a 100% match.
No.
There are just a few
types of hair buns.
There are 700 million women in China.
200 million wear it like that.
That's way too broad.
I thought about that too.
But her body type matches too.
Anyway, I just felt she was so familiar
when I saw her.
I felt like
I was returning to that night.
Fine.
Let me change the perspective.
She came from nowhere
and saved your mom.
Even if it was coincidental,
fine. She helped, end of story.
But then she stuck around
for follow-up care.
That feel calculated.
Is there a possibility
that she's just
warm-hearted,
like you?
I'll come later.
I found someone called Jiang Juan.
Take a look and see if it's her.
That's her.
Yes, it's her.
She has worked here
for seven or eight years.
She's our top caregiver.
You need an appointment.
Everyone wants her.
Let me tell you,
not only does she
cook amazing Sichuan food,
but she's also
very creative.
She came up with
games for the elderly
to help prevent dementia.
You're really lucky
to have her.
My mother-in-law has a sharp eye.
Looks like I really misjudged her.
Look at Ouyang.
Isn't this the first time?
In the past, whenever
you were in trouble,
he'd lend his help.
Why is he
ignoring you this time?
You were exhausting yourself,
yet he just stood by and watched.
What's this called?
That's "hope your buddy does well,
but not better than you."
Isn't Jiajia
jealous of you?
Jiajia isn't.
You know our relationship.
We've been through thick and thin
for over a decade.
Ouyang and I have saved
each other's lives.
♪Work hard and make money♪
(Qian Weijie)
Who is it?
It's him.
This guy gets jealous.
It's Qian Weijie?
Reject it.
Okay, reject it.
I'm getting one too.
Who is this?
Ouyang is a good guy.
He is very kind.
He just doesn't know
how to express himself.
He doesn't want us
to touch this money.
Here you go again.
Aren't they tired?
Turn off the phone.
Here it comes again.
I'll turn it off.
Turn it off.
Hello.
The number you dialed
cannot be reached now.
Don't waste food.
Look how stingy you are.
Like it's costing you a fortune.
In this lifetime,
you'll never amount to much.
Hello.
The number you dialed
cannot be reached now.
Look how pathetic you are.
You heartless,
ungrateful wretch!
Now that you have money,
you're a ruthless fat cat.
Sooner or later,
a big truck
will run over your head.
Crush you to death!
Mr. Yu,
you must be busy.
You didn't answer my calls.
Here's the thing.
About what I told you before,
now everything is in place.
Just waiting on you.
When
you have time,
just come through for us.
Hit me back
when you're free.
Boss,
have they moved the money
to somewhere else?
Yu Ming.
Our noodle shop was doing fine.
It was making money.
Why sell it?
The noodle shop, or 30 million.
Which one do you pick?
I want 30 million.
See? You want the money too.
Now I'm watching them
and running the shop.
I'm too swamped now.
Are you out of your mind?
What if we can't find the money?
We'll cross
that bridge later.
We took such a huge risk
to come to Luzhou
just to open a restaurant?
Of course not.
You keep your eyes on Unit 505.
I'll keep an eye on their place.
We will definitely
get the money.
Yes.
Definitely.
This one and the noodles I cook,
which one's better?
Of course yours is better.
There's no comparison.
I don't eat it.
After the restaurant is closed,
it won't be so easy to eat my noodles.
Then
I'll have some more these days.
Make more for me.
I'll only eat noodles these days.
Just go for it.
You fool.
Zhu,
come and look.
What's up?
Let me look.
Did we dig through?
We did.
Step back.
Zhu,
did we dig into someone's grave?
This doesn't look like a basement.
If you want to hide
that much money,
you have to dig
really deep.
Why don't we just
hire a professional team
to do the digging?
When it's almost done,
we take over.
No way.
We can't let that many people know.
Who would dig
a big hole in their basement?
We can't leave any trace.
If it takes a week,
I'll dig it myself.
A month,
I'll still dig it myself.
A year,
I'm digging it myself!
Zhu.
That's money!
The money is not up there.
It's here.
Zhu,
be careful!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Go!
Quick, go!
Zhu!
Hurry!
Go!
Turn off the lights.
Turn off!
No one.
No one's coming.
So much money.
The money covered two whole walls.
If someone gave me that,
I'd call them daddy on the spot.
Wait.
Something's wrong.
The money wasn't
supposed to be in the wall?
Yeah.
We built those walls.
So how is there
so much money underground?
Hu Deshuai
has hidden so much money,
but won't pay us back what he owes.
I told you,
Hu Deshuai is no good.
I said don't work for him,
but you just wouldn't listen.
See?
Well,
when did you ever say that?
Just at that time,
when we were...
Stop nagging.
Keep it down.
He already saw us.
What do we do?
I don't know.
What's that attitude?
How about we go home?
We leave tonight.
Go home?
We won't take the money?
You still want the money?
Worry about your life first.
Keep your voice down.
What if they call the cops?
The tunnel entrance is right there.
They'll find us for sure.
I'm calling the shots today.
San and I will pack up.
You go buy the tickets.
San, let's go.
Go, San.
How can you sleep at a time like this?
You've got some nerve.
San!
Zhu.
What's wrong with San?
San!
100, take it away.
(500,000)
30 million here, and 30 million there.
Well,
Lamp's Aladdin?
Well, I...
Aladdin's Lamp.
About those three who dug the tunnel,
think hard. Remember
the two who broke in the other day?
Are any of these three those two?
I don't think so.
Look now.
The one on motorcycle chasing us,
the ones who climbed the wall,
the ones digging tunnels.
All came for this money.
Look how dangerous we are now.
What do we do?
Who knows if there's more
coming?
We have to figure out the situation.
What's really going on here?
Does Chen Zinuo know this 30 million?
I mean this 30 million.
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
Maybe there wasn't enough room upstairs,
so they put more underneath.
Or like what my mom said,
you can't
put all the eggs in the same basket.
My heart's racing right now.
We really have to figure out
whether there is more money or not.
What if more turns up?
We can't handle all this now.
This is just too much.
It's already 4:30 a.m.
I'm going home to check on my mom.
She just got out of the hospital.
I'll come too.
No, you stay.
There's so much money here.
Someone has to watch it.
You're not going anywhere.
Watch this place.
Pull up
that old case
about the homeowner
and go through it.
Maybe you can find something.
Don't go.
Yu Ming,
you're just a big scammer.
An ungrateful wretch.
If I fed a stray dog,
at least it would be grateful.
I was so fool
to pay your debts.
Just begging to be used.
Pathetic, that's what I am.
Just you wait!
Don't rush me!
Yu Ming!
Yu Ming, I know you're home.
Come on, open the door.
I won't beat you.
Yu Ming,
about investing in those coins,
you said you'd invest three days ago,
then two days ago,
then yesterday.
Where's the money?
Come out. Let's sort this out.
Okay?
I sold my kidney
to pay
that loan shark off for you.
The last 20,000 yuan?
I borrowed it for you.
Whether you like it or not,
you owe me money now.
I'm your creditor, your know.
Yu Ming,
no matter what,
we're partners.
Do you understand?
You're putting
in the money.
You hear me?
Yu Ming,
I can see you.
Open the door quickly!
Yu Ming!
What's wrong?
Bro,
didn't I pay back
the money Yu Ming owed you?
Whatever he borrowed
from you after that,
that's on him.
I'm not paying that.
Tell me about the 30 million.
30 million?
What 30 million?
Bro!
Wait a moment, let me think.
Let me think.
I still can't remember.
Wait.
Bro, don't beat me.
Can I have a tissue?
Bro, my...
The money in that house.
30 million.
What did you and Yu Ming
plan to do with it?
30 million?
Bro, there's no 30 million.
He fooled you.
Yu Ming
won the lottery,
and the prize was 130 million.
(Luzhou Commercial Bank)
It is that 130 million lottery prize.
Or else how could I
secure the 100 million deposit?
Are you sure your client
is the same person
who won the 130 million prize?
How could I not be sure?
This person was my wife's
classmate in elementary school.
The day he claimed the prize,
my wife recognized him
on TV.
So, these days,
I've been working on this deal.
Only this morning
did I secure it.
What's his name?
His name?
Would I tell you his name?
It's the client's privacy.
Yu Ming.
Do you know Yu Ming?
Who?
Yu Ming.
Who is Yu Ming?
Yu Ming, you scoundrel!
You big scammer!
I skimped and saved,
pinched every penny
to pay off his debts.
That was my blood and sweat!
No wonder that brat
didn't dare spend
a single cent.
Boss, I'll follow your lead.
How about we team up?
You call the shots.
Finish him off for me!
Finish that darned wretch off!
If you want to stay alive,
just don't touch that money.
I won't.
I want to live.
I want him dead!
(Next Episode)
(Actor, Guo Jingfei)
Hi, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
Are you here?
Don't move!
Stay put!
What are you doing?
Step back!
Move!
Let's cut to the chase.
Why were you digging this tunnel?
For money.
What money?
How did you know there was money here?
Pei Wen'an?
You are the Shiyi she mentioned.
If you love someone, be brave.
Miss the right moment,
and you may lose the chance.
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪