=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 8=
(My Queen)
We found a house we like.
But we are short over a million.
I just hoped Ming could help.
After all, Ming is Weijie's cousin.
Cousin?
Has Qian Weijie ever
treated Yu Ming like one?
Whatever you say,
they are still cousins.
Related by blood.
Do not play that card with me.
You think I do not know
what you are after?
I know exactly
what you're thinking.
You saw those two
come into money,
so now you want their deposits
to hit your targets.
That is selfish,
and hypocritical.
I am selfish?
Funny.
Let me tell you.
I'm helping them
manage their money.
And I'm selfish?
You're also trying to drag them
into your tutoring business?
You fraud.
Fraud?
I am helping Yitong start a business.
What do you know?
How dare you
call that helping?
Help her?
Where were you before?
How can you even say that?
Listen.
We are family.
Blood is thicker than water.
What are you?
What am I?
We are colleagues
who help each other,
and work as one team.
Got it?
Please. Colleagues?
Weren't you
the one who gave Yitong
a hard time?
Keep your hands off me.
I know everything.
Before this, did you ever
treat Yu Ming as your family?
None of your business.
That is our family matter.
And you'll go broke
running that
tutoring business.
Watch your mouth.
No one touches that money
without my approval.
Oh, come on.
I already told you.
It is about family.
Not money.
Family!
Family, my foot.
A million?
Do you think Yitong
runs a bank?
How can you
talk like that?
So ungrateful.
I have been speaking up
for Yitong all day.
Do not talk about banks.
That money
belongs to our Wenwen.
Why should it all be Wenwen's?
They're not even divorced yet.
Then divorce!
Now!
Good heavens!
Sis,
can you stop talking
about divorce all day?
Better to save a marriage
than tear one apart.
Besides,
the two of them
are trying to have a baby now.
A baby?
I am telling you,
in this lifetime,
Wenwen is the only child
they'll ever have.
Deposits? These days?
How old-fashioned.
With your luck,
you'll go broke.
Yu Ming.
Get out of my way.
You are back.
Stay away from my bro.
Ming, let me manage your money.
Yitong has stood by you for years.
Now it is your turn to back her.
Money in hand brings peace of mind.
Ming.
The tutoring market is still
a pie waiting to be sliced.
Ming, saving money is discipline.
It is your strongest safety net.
Ming.
Save what?
Money you spend is wealth.
Money you don't spend
is just inheritance.
Move.
Let me do it.
- Let me.
Me.
Enough!
Bro.
Who is your bro?
Me?
Or money?
And you.
Have you forgotten
how you treated me?
How you
treated my wife?
How dare you
ask me to invest in you?
Don't you
have GPS?
Know your place.
Oh! Yitong is home!
Yitong.
Only now?
The ultrasound clinic is almost closed.
Enjoy your checkup.
Liar.
Are you sober yet?
Yes.
Fully sober?
Completely.
Last night,
what did you
promise me?
Do you remember?
I remember.
Then say it.
There's nothing
between me and Liu Xinlu.
I need to drink less and stay grounded.
That's key.
The singing monkey.
I'm telling you.
None of these people mean well.
They are not here for you.
They're here for the money.
You need to separate the wolves
from the sheep.
Yes.
I have my principles.
I'll delete
Liu Xinlu.
Can we call this matter
done and over with?
Then I have news for you.
There was a fire at Unit 505.
Someone deliberately set it
with gasoline.
Back to the shop.
Text Yu Ming.
Send him all the photos you took.
Commit to the act.
Think long term.
If you play your cards right,
the money is yours.
Right?
Send it.
Dear Ming.
Are you awake?
Feeling better?
Look at you.
Why did you drink so much last night?
Is Tong mad at you?
Last night,
I think she misunderstood us.
Do you need me to explain for you?
He blocked me.
Here comes the cake.
This cranberry one is sweeter
than the blueberry.
Everyone, try some.
Ouyang.
I have diabetes.
Can I eat this?
Do not worry. I prepared yours.
This is whole wheat, no sugar.
The walnuts inside are very healthy.
It's easy on the stomach.
It's okay.
Okay.
You know what?
When you eat cake,
you've got to have music with it.
You see those Westerners?
That is how they do it.
Nuo is not here today.
If she were here,
then we'd
have music, right?
Where is Nuo?
Where did she go?
Nuo.
You arrived.
What happened? You look terrible.
I am fine.
Wait a moment.
Is Nuo low on blood sugar?
You should take her out more.
Let her get some sun.
Yes.
Good for calcium.
She is a little too thin.
It is fine, madam. You eat first.
I will talk to her.
All right.
Thank you.
What exactly happened?
My landlord kicked me out.
Why?
He'll rent it out.
What will you do?
Stay here for tonight, I guess.
There's a spare room.
Where are you planning to rent next?
I'll see after I get paid next month.
I gave him all the money I had.
I have an extra room at my place.
You can rent from me.
Utilities are all included.
It is on the island.
As for rent,
no rush.
Pay me whenever you have it.
Think about it.
♪Sunlight falls through the curtains♪
♪Softly kissing your face♪
♪Like a secret♪
♪A little secret♪
♪Whenever we're together♪
Thank you.
What happened to your cello?
It was fine yesterday.
♪A little understanding♪
♪Our bond growing deeper♪
The landlord tried to keep it.
It broke when I tried to take it back.
♪I see the stars shining♪
♪Listening to your heartbeat♪
♪Such a special rhythm♪
Thank you.
♪I'm falling for you♪
♪Now baby I love you♪
Your helmet.
♪And I just need you too♪
♪Every second♪
♪Every minute, every day♪
♪I want to be by your side♪
♪The moments that steal my heart♪
♪Whenever we're together♪
♪Another perfect day♪
♪Rain or shine♪
♪As long as I'm with you♪
Yu Ming.
That motorcycle behind us...
I noticed it long ago.
He is following us.
Is he after our money too?
I don't know.
We cannot go back to the shop now.
Should I slam the brakes
and send him flying?
No.
Then should we...
Then what?
Speed up. Circle around.
Okay.
Hello?
I am on him.
He is in the restroom.
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
♪A villa by the sea♪
♪Seafood every day♪
Come on. Come on.
It is stuck.
Hurry. Hurry.
The streetlight is broken.
It might be dark
when you come back.
I'll have someone fix it tomorrow.
If you feel scared
coming back,
call me and I'll come
get you.
This is my place.
Come in.
Here, let me.
Thank you.
My stepmom and I
decorated this place.
So you may see
quirky stuff around.
My parents divorced early.
Later, they both
remarried.
So now I have
two dads and two moms.
They all get along well.
Usually though,
I barely get to see any of them.
This is my bedroom.
Let me put your cello inside.
You can stay there.
What about you?
I will sleep upstairs.
Kitchen's over there.
Guess they're afraid I'll starve.
So they keep sending food over.
But most of it
is what they like to eat.
Feel free to cook
whatever you want.
(Ride safely)
(Drink water. Eat well. Sleep early.)
Damei.
Damei, there you are.
Come here.
Damei.
You have a cat?
Yes.
She is my stepmom's cat.
When she got her,
she was tiny.
Then she got huge.
So her name means "Big Beauty."
Yes.
She's a little naughty.
She is shy around new people.
Excuse me.
Fire inspection?
You cannot reach Yu Ming?
All right.
What time tomorrow?
Okay.
Get some rest.
I may need to step out.
The showerhead is a bit tricky,
just so you know.
Let the water run for a while,
or it will be cold.
And the sheets and covers
are on the top shelf of the closet.
I'll take you
to the landlord tomorrow,
and get all your stuff back.
Don't worry.
Where's the girl living here?
Who are you?
I asked where the girl is.
She moved out.
Where did she move?
Does she owe you money too?
That shameless girl.
Always causing trouble.
Does she owe everyone money?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Let go.
I'll call the police.
You...
Go ahead.
Just wait.
You dare
hit people in broad daylight?
Stop it!
Stop. Stop.
Please stop!
Stop hitting him!
I am begging you!
Stop this!
We can talk this through.
Please stop.
Call them, go on/
I won't. I won't call.
I'm not calling.
Please.
Stop hitting him.
(Chen Zinuo)
(Du Lei)
Just to be safe,
I've already turned off my phone.
So they can't track us.
Who do you think
is following us?
Could it be Hong Jinkui?
No, no.
That person's build
was not as huge as Hong Jinkui's.
He could hire someone.
Who knows
about tbe lottery?
How many?
Quite a few.
Auntie's family.
Song Youcheng.
The lottery shop owner.
Mr. Xiang.
Right.
Here.
Write them down.
Who else? Anywhere else?
Some other lottery players.
A lot, really.
Write them. Every single one.
Someone broke into our villa before.
One with long hair,
one with short hair.
One tall,
one short.
Four people?
Two.
One man, and one woman.
Why didn't you tell me?
Was that before
or after the lottery?
Before.
That means
these people probably knew
there was money in the villa, right?
Right.
It was on the news too.
A pair of thieves, a man and a woman.
They're on the run.
A man and a woman.
Good thing we moved the money.
Now no one knows
where it is.
Safe. For now.
Write those names down first.
As long as we stay careful
cautious, we'll be fine.
Ouyang.
How bold.
Hello, Ms. Zhang.
Hi, Ms. Wen.
Can you
come to the school?
What happened?
Wenwen is acting a bit
strange.
One more for you.
Another one. Not this one.
Thank you.
Wu Xiaoxuan, give me a pair.
Wu Xiaoxuan, trade with me.
Look at these little monsters.
Aren't they cute?
Mine has them too.
Your monster's eyes are so pretty.
Those eyes...
Okay. Okay.
Sorry for the trouble.
These red socks...
Why so many red socks?
Wenwen?
I bought them.
How many did you buy her?
Fifty or sixty?
Twenty to thirty pairs?
Fifty or sixty sets.
Fifty or sixty pairs.
Why did you buy her
so many red socks?
She likes them.
What?
She caused trouble.
Did she wear all fifty or sixty pairs
on her feet at once?
Is she a centipede?
No, she handed them out.
She drew monsters
on every pair
and handed them out.
Don't know where she gets it.
I am going to the school.
Just grab a cab back.
Hurry.
She was sharing with others.
How is that "causing trouble"?
Stop wasting my time. Hurry up.
Do not drag this out.
She is being kind.
Hello.
The number you dialed is powered off.
How can you keep the money here?
The fire inspector is coming.
I'll hold it for you first.
Put it in the bank soon.
What is this?
Need a hand?
No.
Hello?
I'm off to the nursing home.
Don't wait for me.
Okay.
Want me to drive you?
No need.
I can go myself.
Xiu.
Did you see anyone go into my shop?
Ouyang came by
several times.
Lucky he came by more than once.
Your place is a mess.
Fire inspection is tomorrow.
And he couldn't reach you by phone.
Did you take it?
Where is it?
Where are you?
Right next to you.
Why would you do this?
I...
Because you are jealous.
You cannot stand seeing me
richer than you.
You want to be rich too, don't you?
Fine. Everyone likes money.
You saw all that cash.
You could have left me some.
Or talked to me first.
So why take every last bit of it?
Why?
I...
Because you are selfish
at heart.
Because you never
treated me like a brother.
If you needed money,
you could've told me.
I would have shared it with you.
But taking all of it?
That's just
too ugly.
What do you mean?
Chen Zinuo.
Hang up.
So it was her.
She put you up to it.
She told you to take
all my money, didn't she?
You are good by nature.
I didn't expect someone so vile
to be pulling
your strings.
You chose a woman over your brother.
No, it is worse than that.
You crushed brotherhood,
trampled on it,
and let it blow away in the wind.
You're seriously messed up.
After all these years,
this is how you treat me?
Let me tell you.
The money in that villa
is mine.
It has nothing to do
with Chen Zinuo.
This money came from the villa?
Yes.
You never won the lottery,
did you?
So what?
You stole Chen Zinuo's family
money.
You stole from her family.
Nonsense.
You did steal from them.
Her family's money?
Do you know
how hard she has it?
All the money in that house is mine.
I'll call the police
right now!
My treasure.
I'll call them.
Go ahead.
You have really lost your mind.
These drawings are so ugly.
All teeth and claws.
Why?
My drawings
are the worst in my class.
I draw ugly things
because the people I see are ugly.
What kind of talk is that?
Who exactly do you see that's ugly?
Am I ugly? Or your dad?
Anyone with money in their eyes.
So you are the pretty one.
Can I have a pair of those socks?
You just said they're ugly.
I am not ugly.
So what if they're ugly?
You should read fewer books.
You'll be
the neighborhood philosopher.
No idea who you take after.
Definitely not you or my dad.
I should kick you out.
Then give me back the socks.
Look at these.
One big, one small.
This is cheap garbage.
These two aren't even a pair.
Give me a matching pair.
This is clean.
Why rush to change?
He's gone.
Return home?
Oh.
If you had some money,
a lot of money,
how would you spend it?
There is no "if."
Just pretend there is.
What would you do?
You want the truth?
Yes.
I would burn it.
Someone hanged himself in Unit 505.
I know.
That was my dad.
The police said
he was strangled with a rope.
I don't think so.
What do you think?
It was money.
What's meant to be yours
will always be yours.
You are back.
Min.
Back from school.
Yitong.
Dad.
Go upstairs first.
I need to talk to your mom.
Take this up with you.
Let Grandma try on the clothes.
Why are you
sneaking around here?
What happened?
Ouyang took
our money.
Why?
There was a fire inspection.
The community office called,
but I missed it.
Then they called him.
He went over,
saw all that money,
and took it away.
I asked for it back but failed.
Then we got into it.
Wait.
He won't go crazy
for money.
Yeah, but he knows that money
didn't come from a lottery win.
It was hidden inside the wall.
So he says that money belongs to
Chen Zinuo,
and refused to give it back.
Has love gone to his head?
Come on. Let us get it back.
Anywhere else hurt?
No.
He's no match for me.
He may look worse than I do.
I have a place on the east side.
It is spacious,
south-facing.
Chaoming Park is right downstairs.
It's very convenient.
I mentioned it before.
Go stay there.
It is safe.
I am not in danger now.
Living in someone else's home
is never convenient.
And your place isn't my home either.
Zinuo.
After what happened to Mr. Chen,
a sum of money went missing.
No one knew
where it had gone.
Not even the police.
That money was meant for you.
Can you imagine
my dad hanging there?
When someone
hangs themselves,
the muscles of the tongue relax.
The jaw opens from the pressure.
The tongue falls out.
Drool drips down.
And the body loses control.
I can't understand it.
My father was such a clean man.
Don't ever
bring this up to me again.
Please.
Whatever he left behind,
it has nothing to do with me.
Ranran!
Ranran.
Who is she to you?
My little sister.
What is her name?
Ranran.
Brother.
Ranran, I am here.
Open the door, please.
I can't wash it off.
Ranran.
I can't.
I can't get clean.
(Kill)
Ranran was timid.
(Sun Leran's Grave)
Just seeing a cockroach
would make her jump into my arms.
When she jumped into the sea,
how much courage must that have taken?
It is over now.
Change your name.
From now on, you are Du Lei.
(Du Lei)
Leave the honesty
to me and Zinuo.
You must protect her.
Don't let anyone hurt her.
From this day on,
Zinuo is your sister.
You must become her way out.
Her last resort.
We're here.
I live here.
Why insist on living here?
Because of the fridge.
The fridge?
He has two dads
and two moms.
The fridge holds four people's care.
I never knew
a fridge could
hold so much.
The cushions on the sofa
look like the sun.
Holding it feels warm.
You can buy those things.
No, you can't.
I never had that.
Not once.
Damei, dinner time.
Damei.
I knew you'd be here.
Come on, let's go eat.
Here.
If you had some money,
a lot of money,
what would you do?
I can tell
you left in a hurry.
After what happened to Mr. Chen,
a sum of money went missing.
Go back to sleep.
What's meant to be yours
will always be yours.
That money was meant for you.
Ouyang.
Look, I...
I owe you an apology.
I went too far today.
But I need to tell you,
the money in that house
really belongs to me.
There is a contract.
It says
everything in the house,
even construction waste, is mine.
It is written in black and white.
Construction waste is not money.
Ming,
that money is not clean.
You don't know that?
I looked into Chen Liyang's case.
It's still not closed.
The thirty million?
No one knows
where it went.
Then those money
turns up in your villa.
It is the same amount.
Don't you find that strange?
Holding onto it now,
don't you feel dangerous?
Look, whether this money
is clean or not,
you can't just take it
and keep it for yourself, right?
Even if, for argument's sake,
the money does belong to Chen Zinuo,
shouldn't it be her
telling us that?
So why did you two end up
like this?
How could she possibly talk to you?
Ouyang.
Good. You are here.
Tell him yourself.
The things in Unit 505...
you... you...
I don't want it.
You don't have to keep
testing me.
Don't worry.
I won't take a single cent of it.
You heard Chen Zinuo.
She does not want the money.
We still have to find a way
to get it back from Ouyang.
I will talk to Ouyang again.
It really is packed.
Is this the cushion
Zinuo mentioned?
Is it warm?
(Next Episode)
(Actress, Ren Suxi)
I'm Ren Suxi.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
Fan Meijuan?
Mom,
Be careful.
You're her family?
I know.
That's her bag.
It's fine.
It's a 100% match.
She came from nowhere
and saved your mom.
Did we dig through?
This doesn't look like a basement.
Zhu.
That's money!
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪