[All characters, behaviors, locations,
organizations, professions, and events
shown in this series are entirely fictional,
created solely for entertainment purposes,
with no intention of instructing
or endorsing any kind of behaviors;
viewer discretion is advised]
A clover leaf?
I thought you said you can't remember me.
I think that perhaps love
is the memory of a time
when we were happy.
A reminder that you used to be
a crucial part of someone's life.
Have you ever felt
like that toward someone?
Because that person
hasn't realized just yet
that he is someone important to me.
And what about you?
What role do you play
on this board?
I'm tired of being compared
to a pawn by others.
I'll be the hand that moves the pieces now.
I have a job for you all.
♫But no one sees what's behind my smiles♫
♫It's the loneliness I try to hide♫
♫Will there be someone my heart's seeking?♫
♫Then today, I got you near♫
♫You made my heart drift away,♫
♫lost in your gaze♫
♫Like a stream washing over me♫
♫Wanna give this a try,
like it’s more than one night?♫
♫Let's change one night into♫
♫something more, alright♫
♫Let's follow our hearts once♫
♫Wanna give this a try, just let me get inside?♫
♫Deep inside, I'll make you feel whole♫
♫May I ask you to be my last?♫
Gale.
Is the size okay now?
Or does it need any adjustment?
Mm...
I think it looks good on the model now.
The mannequin just makes it look off.
Hm...
What's your height, Phae?
160 cm.
Why?
You're about the same height
as the model.
Can you try on the dress instead?
Sure.
Do I have to take my shirt off?
What? No.
There's no need.
I thought you wanted it to be exact.
Are you crazy?
Your shirt is so small.
It won't make a difference.
Well,
I was just asking.
Excuse me.
Looks like the shoulders
are wider by an inch.
Hey,
it's only by an inch.
So it should be alright.
Or else it would be too tight
when the model wears it.
If it's for sale,
I think you can do that.
But this is the first showcase,
so I think it needs to fit the model perfectly
to achieve the best look.
Oh...
So that's why
famous designers are very serious
when they're casting models.
Yeah.
I'll be measuring your bust size next.
I didn't mean it like that.
I'm just saying that...
It's fine.
Why are you always correcting yourself?
Well, I worded it badly.
I didn't want to cause any misunderstanding.
Can you lift your hair up?
- It's in the way.
- Oh.
Gale.
Gale?
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
This is my first time seeing you
wearing this bracelet.
Oh.
You mean this?
Mm...
Someone gave it to me
back when I was still in Paris.
Yesterday I cleaned up...
and found it.
It's pretty, right?
I think it suits me.
The person who gave me this
probably has a fashion sense.
Yeah.
It suits you.
If you got it back when you were in Paris,
why are you only wearing it now?
Well...
I just wanted to prove something.
And it looks like I got the answer.
I got your measurements.
And...
there's no need for any adjustment.
Maybe I have to trim the shoulders a bit.
I'll handle the rest.
Okay.
Gale,
I have to go to the city with my mom.
And about the accessories,
I already drafted a few ideas.
After you see them,
tell me how you feel,
and I'll take care of it, okay?
Okay.
Then I'll see you later.
See you later.
Auntie,
the fact that Boss called a sudden meeting,
does it mean there's
something bad going on?
Right?
Boss seems a bit tense, too.
I think most of you already know
that we're focusing
on improving our crop yields
in order to enter into a contract with K Group,
our partner in South Korea.
Is it not going
according to plan?
Are they not going to cooperate with us?
Well,
we are...
We're about to seal the deal!
That scared me.
Oh, Boss.
You made me so nervous there, Boss.
I thought something
terrible had happened again.
If I just said it normally,
it would be boring.
I was scared for a second.
The reason I called everyone here
is that I wanted to
tell you the good news.
And since we're about to be able
to seal the deal,
I'd like to treat you all to a meal
for your hard work at Phusangdao Farm.
I'll tell the caterer to prepare a lot of food
and drinks for all of you.
Let's finish work early today
to celebrate!
Our boss is the best!
I pray that in the next life,
I get to work as your subordinate again,
forevermore.
Come on, Paula.
Have you asked Boss
if he wanted to
meet you in his next life?
What about it, huh?
You!
Everyone,
let's get back to work, shall we?
I'll see you tonight.
And have fun,
alright?
- Okay.
- Then go back to work.
Go, let's go!
Go, go, let's go.
Party, party.
We're going to party.
I'm a heavyweight drinker, you know?
I don't believe you!
See you.
You're not going to bring your hat?
It's Auntie Nong's.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to help you.
What?!
Hey!
You brats!
Mok!
Come pick these up, Saeng.
Mok! Saeng!
These damn brats.
And I'm the one who has to
clean up their mess.
They're blending in with the grass,
so they're even harder to find.
Wait,
did you change
your eyebrow pencil today, Paula?
You can just say that I'm pretty.
It looks ridiculous.
Hey, you!
Yes, you're the prettiest of them all.
Ugh.
Your hair is this short,
so don't you judge a lady like me.
Well, if people with long hair are pretty,
then hermits are pretty too, yeah?!
- Hey.
- Ouch.
Am I not beautiful?
Jeez!
Kind of.
That doesn't mean
you're pretty, though.
Like Paula here?
Even if she's pretty,
no one would want her.
Hey, Auntie,
how can you say that?
I will definitely find my lover.
Mark my words.
You all soon will have to
attend my wedding ceremony.
Right, guys?
You think I'll definitely find a lover, right?
Really?
Hey, aren't you my friends?
Alright, alright.
To be honest,
you're very beautiful, Paula.
But...
if you shave your eyebrows
a bit sharper,
put on a little more blush,
and apply some lipstick,
you can be even more alluring.
Right?
Isn't this enough?
Come, come, right here.
What?
- Sit, sit.
- Ow, ow.
Come here.
What?
Hey! What are you doing?
Are you trying to
remove my makeup?
Don't do that.
Sit still.
Come closer.
Here, let me... Oh, hey!
How about this...
Here.
Well...
The eyebrow tail kinda looks better.
Yeah.
Then,
are you free this evening?
I'll go visit your place.
I'm available.
I can't.
- I really can't stand it.
- What?
Let me do the other one too.
I have worn my makeup like this
for years now.
Quit blabbering.
Let me do the other eyebrow for you.
[Phusangdao Group]
It will be settled tonight.
Everything will go according to our plan.
What are you doing, Mr. Chakkrit?
Ms. Wipa.
Please stay and celebrate with us tonight.
I'm throwing a big party
for the farm workers.
You are celebrating
before the deal is even closed?
We can certainly close it.
Everyone has been working
really hard lately,
so it'd be nice to unwind a little.
- But...
- Hey.
Don't worry about it.
Just come and have fun tonight.
I... I have a friend's wedding to attend.
I'm really sorry.
Boss.
I have something important to tell you.
Whoa. These fermented soybeans look so good.
Can I have a piece of this, Auntie?
- Hey, no!
- Oh?!
You can't eat that!
What? Why not?
It's not cooked yet.
How long do I have to wait? I'm hungry.
Can I have this one, then?
- Can I have it now?
- Let me help you.
Let's get the spoons first.
Ow!
Hey, you want to break your back or what?
You're not mad at me anymore?
Hey, make it quick. It's heavy!
Ow!
Saeng, I need your help.
Right, right.
Here. Let me help you.
Oh?
What about Paula?
Where is she?
Why isn't she coming to help?
Alright. Let's do a makeover!
Going all out.
Guys, look at her.
Pawn is here.
Not with that tone of voice.
Sheesh.
Stunned?
Who did the makeup for you?
Ta-daa!
No doubt it was you, Saitharn, my brother.
Thanks, Saitharn.
Without your help,
I wouldn't dare come back here.
By the way, what do you call
that thing you do?
Is it a 'maker'?
Make...
'Makeover'.
- Yeah!
- Yes.
"Makeover."
A makeover,
one to remember.
Ever heard of it?
No, I haven't.
Come, Saitharn.
Come and enjoy dinner with us here.
Are you not going to invite me?
Why should I?
Fine then.
- I'll go show off my look to Bua and Auntie.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Here, here.
- Would you like to join me?
- Sure thing.
- Good evening, Boss.
- Good evening.
So refreshing.
Our local moonshine is the real deal!
Now, hand over your cup!
Boss, would you like to have some?
A full shot for everyone, alright?
No problem.
Alright!
Cheers!
Don't hold back tonight!
Our lovely Boss
literally bought out all the liquor for us!
Tonight...
Can you please treat us to some drinks?
Good grief, I thought
it was something serious!
This is serious, Boss.
The party won't be as fun without drinks.
It must be the local moonshine, too!
Please.
Boss.
I'll take that as a yes.
- One more, Boss.
- More!
Another shot?
- Whoa, I'm getting hammered.
- Come on. Cheers.
I'm sobering up.
Come here, yeah, cheers!
Hey.
Are you drunk already?
Drunk? This is my first one.
And...
You don't call me Daddy anymore?
Huh?
Since when did I call you that?
Well...
You did when the two of us...
Hold it right there.
If you keep talking like a dirty old man,
I'll leave.
Oh, okay.
I won't.
I'll stop now.
Is that your first shot?
This is unexpected.
I thought you would've already
chugged liters of the stuff.
Oh, not so fast there.
I wish I could do that,
but the distilled liquor here
is really strong.
I need to hold back,
or else I won't be able to work tomorrow.
But look at you.
I didn't expect
that you could actually drink
this kind of stuff.
I thought you only drink fancy aged wine.
Hey, you and your words.
I'm a heavyweight drinker.
Any liquor is fine by me.
When I was your age,
I'd been through it all.
The audacity.
Who said they're a heavy drinker?
All I see is
people getting drunk and blacking out.
Hey, now.
So messy.
You're this old already, you know?
No.
Listen.
If my memory serves,
you got drunk
and fell asleep on my chest.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
Me?
It was you who was totally hammered.
- No way.
- You fell asleep before I did.
No, it was you.
It was you.
- It was you.
- No, you.
You.
- You.
- Saitharn.
- Cheers.
Right.
- Okay, cheers!
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Yay... yay.
Boss.
- Huh?
- Can we do a toast with you?
Let's do it, Boss.
Okay. Let's toast.
- Cheers.
You seem to get along with everyone.
Have you gotten used to being here?
Mm...
I have.
At first, I thought
it wouldn't be all that great.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Give me back my basket!
But now that I've gotten
used to everyone here,
it's far better than just...
sitting around
and doing nothing in Bangkok.
I'm planning to expand
my business by mid-next year.
It might not be as fun by then.
There'll be more work,
and you will have to work a lot harder.
I probably won't be around by then.
Do you plan to leave
after paying me all your debt?
What other reasons
do I have to stay here?
Me.
Can I be the reason for you to stay?
♫Not so ready to open up my heart♫
♫Not so ready to feel anything yet♫
♫No matter who came into my world♫
♫'Cause heart's been hurting for so long♫
♫It was never easy to start over♫
♫Scared to feel that pain again ever♫
♫I almost gave up on love♫
♫I thought I would never find the right one♫
♫But destiny led you to me♫
Ahh!
What are you doing sitting here?
Come drink with us. Let's go!
Come on, let's go have some drinks.
What are you hanging
around Boss for? Come on.
Let's go.
We're off to have drinks now.
Drinks, drinks, drinks!
- Quickly.
- Right.
- Yay!
- Yeah!
- Drink up!
- Drink.
If you have it, so do I.
Auntie, don't stop now.
We're having fun.
- Get up, get up.
- Ow... I can't...
- Just go.
- Come on, just get up.
Oh, oh.
I guess I have to call you
Grandma Nong now, don't I?
Deary me, Wan!
Watch your mouth,
or I'll knock you on the head.
I'm sorry.
Let her take a break for a bit.
What if she starts babbling nonsense?
Gosh, this is no fun.
Let's go dance together, guys.
Gosh.
Look at Pawn.
She was looking all pretty back there.
Now, she's totally wasted.
Would you like to head back and rest?
I'll walk you there.
- Alright.
- One, two...
Let's go.
Oh?
Auntie Nong!
Ughh!!
- Huh?
- I was waiting for you.
Ugh, wait for me too.
I was waiting for a long, long time.
Are you alright, Paula?
I'll take you home.
Is this Saitharn?
It really is you.
My best friend.
How was my accent?
Is it good, yeah?
Yeah, it's good.
Right.
You've been here for...
a few weeks now, yeah?
Do you like it here?
Well,
it's actually quite nice
now that I've settled in.
But when I first got here,
I had Saeng, Mok,
and everyone to help
make things easier for me.
I see.
Eh...
The "everyone" you mentioned
includes me too, right?
Hey,
if you're not bored with this place,
then stay with us as long as you can,
alright?
Well,
I don't even know
how long I'm going to stay here.
Oh, come on!
What are you saying?
Let me tell you something.
You don't have to find an answer
for everything.
If you're happy here, then just stay.
It doesn't matter if
you grew up here like me
or just came here a few days ago.
Auntie Nong once said,
"If we share the same pot of rice,
then we're pretty much family."
Alright, brother?
- Hey, don't move!
- Hey!
Let's go.
- Come here!
- Arghh!!
Paula, run!
Run. Run!
Help me! Please help!
Help me!
Shut your mouth!
Be quiet!!
Don't move!
Ahh!!
Ow!
Hey!
Paula...
Ugh, let me go!
Saitharn...
Help me...
I can go by myself,
just go back to Wan.
I don't want you to
pass out and not come back.
Hey!
Of all places,
why are you peeing right next to me?!
Go away.
Hey...
Let me pee!
Go away.
Fine. Or do you want some of this?
Yeah, yeah...
Hey!
What?
What are you doing?
- Hey, Pawn!
- Pawn!
- Wake up, Pawn.
Pawn, are you alright?
Help...
Go help Saitharn.
Saitharn...
Go get help as fast as you can.
Pawn is injured.
I'll go that way.
Hey, wait!
You can't go alone.
I can.
Didn't you hear that?
Pawn mentioned Saitharn.
Alright, just be careful.
Yeah.
Pawn, I'll call someone to help.
Hey, quickly, quickly.
You aren't getting away with this.
We'll see
who gets away with this, you or me.
Hey, stop right there!
Mok!
Leave him.
Come here.
Feisty, huh?
Saeng.
Saeng!
Saeng!!
Can you hear me, Saeng?!
Saeng! Saeng! Saeng!
Did you bring my parcel?
Parcel?
What parcel?
The one I texted you about this afternoon.
Didn't you read it?
I'm exhausted today.
I've barely touched my phone.
You can go get it tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
The security guard will just hand it
over to the management office.
I'm not going there.
It's too far.
Why are you so upset?
It's just a parcel.
Where are you going?
This isn't just about the parcel.
It's also about you not listening to me.
Where are you going?
I want to shower.
Let's talk.
I don't want to argue. I'm tired.
Tired?
You? Tired?
Tired from what?
You don't even go to your classes.
You're just wh*ring around
with your friends, aren't you?
You sure like showing your skin online.
Just a bit more, and
you might as well be naked.
If people didn't know...
they'd think you are an escort.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Why are you stirring things up
as soon as I got back?
Are you really losing your mind
over just a stupid parcel?
I'm f*cking sick of this.
Are you sick of me?
Phayu...
Well...
I...
Why do you think I'm like this?!
It's because of you!
I cared.
I was jealous.
Don't I have the right to feel that way?
I can't stop you from
doing whatever the f*ck you want, yeah?
To be honest,
I don't think you love me anymore.
You used me.
You only say you love me
when we're having sex.
You didn't think I'd notice, huh?
How am I using you?
What the f*ck are you talking about?
We've been together since freshman year.
But it's like you don't even
know me anymore.
It's because I know you
that I know exactly who you are.
What? Me?
I think it's you!
You don't respect me,
talk sh*t about me,
hit me,
even hurt yourself,
and blame me for everything.
Oh, and did you know?
My friends have told me to
break up with you hundreds of times.
I never listened.
Because I believed
that someone like you
could change for the better.
So?
Do you still think
I'm the bad guy here?
You should listen to your friends.
Go on.
Leave me
and go back to your friends.
Every one of you
is a wh*re anyway.
It's unbelievable
how I even loved you back then.
Now
I can't love someone like you anymore.
Let's break up.
Fine.
Go!
[Missed Call: Phayu]
[Come get your stuff]
[So you won't have to come back here again]
[This place is a f*cking mess]
Phayu.
Open the door!
Can you hear me?
Phayu.
Phayu!
Open the door, Phayu!
Can you hear me?!
Phayu!
Phayu!!
Saeng-La!
Saeng! Saeng!
Saeng, wake up!
Saeng!
Stay with me!
Come on!
Saeng!
Saeng.
Saitharn!
Saitharn, can you hear me?
Saitharn.
Mok.
Saitharn!
Did you find him?
Over there.
Saitharn!!
Saitharn!
Saitharn, can you hear me?
Any signs of him?
No, Boss.
Sh*t!
Saitharn.
Saitharn!
Saitharn, can you hear me?
Hey, you!
Who sent you?
Let me go!
Who sent you?!
Let him go!
Let go!
Ow!
Go!
Quick!
Saitharn.
Hey, Nhan.
Coming.
Yes.
Go that way.
Spread out and search.
Uncle,
what happened?
I heard all the commotion.
Someone broke in and
attacked our workers.
What?!
And...
did anyone get hurt?
Pawn was injured.
She hit her head
and lost consciousness.
She was already taken to the hospital.
Right now,
we are searching for Saitharn.
I don't know where he went.
Help. Please help.
Help him.
Please help him.
Uncle!
Saeng got shot!
I don't know what to do.
Uncle, please help!
Okay, okay.
I'll take him to the hospital.
Uncle, please help
the others look for Saitharn.
The car is parked at
the farm entrance.
Wait there.
I'll go get the keys.
Okay, please be quick.
Alright.
Saitharn!
Saitharn!! Can you hear me?
Saitharn!!
Saitharn.
Saitharn!
Saitharn, where are you?
Ugh!
Saitharn!
Saitharn!!
F*ck...
Saitharn.
Saitharn!
Saitharn!!
Phayu,
I'm sorry.
Phayu...
You used me.
You only say you love me
when we're having sex.
You didn't think I'd notice, huh?
Can you hear me?
I'm sorry.
You hit me,
even hurt yourself,
and blame me for everything.
Leave me.
Phayu!
Phayu!!
Saitharn!!
This isn't a mistake,
but your failure.
And you still have
the nerve to come back to me?
Saeng went into
the operating room yesterday.
The doctor said the bullet
struck his left shoulder,
hitting a major artery.
It's my fault
that all of this happened.
It's my fault.
It's my fault...
♫I wanna thank you for making me feel♫
♫Just how beautiful love can be♫
♫Every chamber of my heart♫
♫Will be yours from now on♫
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫
♫I wanna thank you for making me feel♫
♫Just how beautiful love can be♫
♫Every chamber of my heart♫
♫Will be yours from now on♫
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫